[
	{
		"unique_id": "010101", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEh/i1e/wLWLdAnYU42uGX7NxYnD3QbXHLuL4iYN5Ihy6mFU84TbVtrf29lAK0OriLncawNUStxt2NNuK78Dk", 
		"answer": "2+P0OMGjATqomiC8rN8eiaL8PKTislD95A==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHgxAvs9oYlEgr3yO36J2rEFnAU43CFErd8dTHQQamOLuzy2pgxLFKGmlU782WGt631t0MHgLxU+p6XdTAGMstm25CIx/Tly2lIPsdQn4xrpMxTLKQQHB7tPIWLbKY+nr6mbgXEbzCuRHln1CXejzxaqZq+52e0UpojyBBypZJ2rc4uM9rfzqCa60X4ig+F1G/RSbNgUVyctNro6lGZ4Ic1vNmZtDabwPz82uzW/c4OcAlGqpR6I1KylLoM+Tk9QoigZ1JG5OfYIVzkJyCmNU4L+Mf202cpx5FpRGYhtBJJlIYWds9k14rg/CY4Oo1pGiG/7wRC0oA8WRiENKmw1Sj39Uc5dHkuKco78H1l8d+/aF1t2n+USWxQl4Nu7sQckUR1fGNVmTQ6jUO4GdLu3vHIGx8Xr472", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "6,000°C", 
		"option_b": "10,800°F", 
		"option_c": "20 million°C", 
		"option_d": "36 million°F", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010102", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQnm9oslRl771r3wM3/VDSIDpnmGQLFxdDH3W+fDfa3Ci7JwNUiBykg75mHPrZmyt1caiuhP5s6WZDFDbYJiwdyIxe3j3TFIPYZXk5p3qNoSfedTgH2setCbJPtg3WeUPhqymRP7aycKHpTn4oyXWWPniA==", 
		"answer": "24O9ZoTgk0fuqbmwlq++Obw0wZNMKOo=", 
		"explanation": "24O9ZoTgkRD5t4omRhv8he/6M27CEWcV42uMEqJnMFTiRrPKKf6+3YB4KRyLiFh652XD46r2t1obnOhI4IOWfCMRd592iNmHl/f+3nQNc8tFiZM+pJsReLREyTO+fcDCYMJg8mC2IkvldHm0FzBgnDSWmXlVp42/tTe3VdQy1FU0hIh1rdw0OZeszKbT6UO8xhKK2TuZR6lwFEeN9d6k6k2ZtMIxu42CpCCb5/v1m+qT48cYdg1f/69rI1Kv16kL9z8sEdy8bVJY8OnVIUfkOi3jJh1d3MrxwnwlhoMnWSk89QwGg8NFa8162pn2/DE/Mt1lBjquqktOh7xzSBKAca/0kHzs5RU+YXckdppluT8w4QCaaGJ7lH6PDCVC1JZu7MlZkQ1le2pSmXj0wjmZj2jPWZLx/4i7lqjZtPlq4eMqKEWFdUnIFoATdqfMPid9zKmYDLRePJEnEyvpJdwq+XW5IZiQnzAekNgiIGLztHPJ0tn8NGCp84bxh9d9Ea1AItnE54uSsU7TaWTyYXyHa8TnSQD1XXm45wZspFgoySoV+yLMAIw/5jgfmH+zTARrlGfWaXK0hf5K75CXP4Y+x7Xt0zZQkfpwkIjn3Qk9RQi+zWtM8oiWSVkNa+iv7lq6Au3a6G8zFuEnEQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Mercury", 
		"option_b": "Venus", 
		"option_c": "Mars", 
		"option_d": "Jupiter", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010103", 
		"question": "2523f9H/3hftt4EvVw2yzOm/IWrbBiIXrG3DU+NmcWijW6GCYuT5wYMxIU6GgBtv+nOGkLD+t0cAz7pe6I2XMDYLe8tKycKd37u1M78+MBXf/f6gEJ8g+g+Z7A==", 
		"answer": "2+34ZZj9xA3v5MUhXBqyl62/Jm7TDGwVsD2g+Fs6FP25yzOvUvdtZTAh", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHyxxz49oIlEhr71un+O2jVQ2AUt2iGV600ZHnmFILDfPn2iZZ/IxydhV47wWPI46zjt1INgL1PqdfMMC8Kcodmx97J2u37wWIBe5cRysB/7ZYTdftOjDakeNvWJepr3H3JZ2n5YDGpRGRmlSfThm8WqZf79GeoRN8yxFU9kMd5/dguM8+W1KmH7UGhxlTbhTfGEe8kGl2VusOt/0aOs8IosN/NojfY+/r92rCCqIhHMFAA/4t2b16v17gM6morVMu7ZhYCse3eIVWtNimgMhsQuf7w33puhpYhVHp05w9Dh4cWY853lozsuXIxKch4FDS/40BJ1IB9URSTOP2xxCjw4V46ZjoqZ4V4qG1t4QKVJkFqn3jcTSJV1NI7vsMclgtteXwAmnnywjOCh22bPJXx5I28keD14Ip2/OMzJgGSMF3bXs05ZKHULyWQGEu/XTAVBIn/PNp66vxI", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "1 minute", 
		"option_b": "8 minutes and 20 seconds", 
		"option_c": "15 minutes", 
		"option_d": "30 minutes", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010104", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQnm9oslRl771r30O2THDSIXrG3DWqJieX/kFKPDfOa+2ZZlJFSMnht0/DbPt7aw5EYdialY7M6efiZDd5gvytWF3uHhwXUBJ8kEkoFk4doLdPEA3DK+Z93ZKfJn2nfAKEOwdDawATBkmDDYnjxaoYW+qmVYhIFnLdzaUAwuUsnB09dj", 
		"answer": "25i5eoKxdvUbehkTznztjyK2P9lruw==", 
		"explanation": "25i5eoKz2Aqq440lEg7+xPP6ISvEC2MF43eCQeNwcWPoFLfDeu72zIQxKFLJhE9osmXTsaPx9FZPjqZfqYeMMCAGcoJq3tWNl+buhHxOINIEipJ94p8Mb/1PwjyhNNXINOxhwGGNIlfjJy2yRHJx1CXejzxYrZuvtTe3VdQy1FUzkJN9/4gZPcWL0eiH5w2whxCHnG+ZTf10HkeKvMyh50qIucI3s42evj/etOT1m/bHsNICZA0Si452cBuxlqMM62oVUNqnKBML9+vTdEetJiexZwsF6cfsxHV9z40nHXsx8x5UhopYZYBn3p2kuSokOsN5HDy040tGh5xpUhaYNLS21mTx5Vs8cDgy53GTrt84hb58IHtLOOgs", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Venus", 
		"option_b": "Mars", 
		"option_c": "Jupiter", 
		"option_d": "Neptune", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010105", 
		"question": "2523f9H+0Bfzt4shRgvgxPG/JmrEBm4dqmuGQeM8fX7sWrSLLunxzIQxFF2dmEl1sn7HtaCvtTAI4bW7YsiaI9taqqkYS4I=", 
		"answer": "2+3qKJz83hf5td6Ef/O68WYRQE9mZwzH68k=", 
		"explanation": "25SrKJ71kTTr7sVyAkyhib3MNH/FEWxRq36QEvsmMHLsWqHLfOD7zdd8KFOHnhtP+n/V46jx/FYcz6FPqZqXdWITcophzcTJwO3jzDFVO8MEl49h8NoSc/tO332kepTPKPsu3WGMJlewdCCuEHV5qD/qhEhercO39DW8UckjgBg9mYk44s58D9aLzLqdqESrxjKLyHqfBP1zGV2avY6h+AOQoZA/sN/NpTra+rTtkv2T4NIKbA1G/6t6cViphbFJzCMsUMb0YQEL8KTXYEetJyGiKRpd7sL33jRohpYhVGo/tB5Sj4xFcsh2xJ2klSZwNt4qATu/40tOy408UhiZev2x3ijw6FB/ZnUnZJgtrzQmtQqRaEN3jmPcTWxVkY54+5AYgQlsbn9ImWTlvjG3jkqbdJbxq47zkenyrLwj/6woJ1LAOlqYZYwIcKHOZ258yeWOCaMcAZdiFm6mFNQ++S3sM9rU+zAC3txsb3bp8Gq8nM7wNWS+poG5vNxzFf8JJZHR4c73o1nEbi3lbHGSdMzxShywQnP33U5qsVgWyTUF+myUSIhx8W0Eij65WgRwmij1a3S11qpTqoCLP4Mw1/CsyCJQl/I4kpTkwBElBxO6mXpR8o2cShxmzETTCtgUhAA9TLVBB4LD82ORkDbdRHMDP9n/FaDHwmxM2/H6znJ0u5VOVIKKbBibiMwvzx+lQe5wUWKtjI/2M/lVA3ds+/J8xeKv992yYfvkLSU5dgmjXOIZ/JMRegt1FhidICpMZbSvUogNAelcknSKmghHST9eDE7Eu6lIWgGzucHaI2bXaLRcHhL3brZFB8b5WgfGJrG9wD/cAbeI1VOxH0YgDimVLr8Z7An3OpvzMBah035l6c73clBVQMMePyKzZGqrsaqABwMpPyUrPIUHaVfUSBUYmgLNFPhzmLUONwttTKeoF0NWlwNK3yraAU1CuFheS6rtSFIxL+lDL0kcyDP1F7IQUVzejj9KilOe0Cv/afZON11jdHKWnQzmiZ1r3+vhh86HBcbvLKkS3YNDJ7AbUJLTX0sQm/3h+6HUGWl5C2J4IOuIX/DU8Ez5DNvgo83OyUULzKgHOkkyKz7HyZ7X9Hp5J6BWL3FYuDMbqcPcZUar345c1kRtVBXu7AHwSWJhsQNyeJr/a8nVJZWk/BBPAyjLF7ZF2M95yTn2O5/Qah5/Dncm0QiEftfYhzmMMqLoggmBgjzmN796GXKv9Fa2f1w=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "67 moons", 
		"option_b": "82 moons", 
		"option_c": "79 moons", 
		"option_d": "53 moons", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010106", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEh39yPDwOyvWAmEFrG3DR7BxdDH3W+fGZ/79xoF0NRydhV47/WPSprf9+EAbz7hX6ICaZDFPPqVq2MSc2eG3xX9Fc/ZIj5R9u9g4buabkTKk2b/2TtqhKHIT", 
		"answer": "25i5fJn23Bj+/oYhXl7RxPH8IGfRF2serWzBu2kVNfR6azweOPytaEKlHg==", 
		"explanation": "25e3fJmz/xz645AuV17zy/m/BWfFF21RtHqRV+NweWLgW7HHfOj6iZZiZ13Jn15o53rS46r2t14Om6Be5I+LeSECcstsydyKwuj20HhOPdUElY4y8JIadeYAxS+/cdPOLP98jmmSJlP5czipDX96lT2Wj3pQrYCv5me0Wpo5xRw1noV3/8EyO5eP1amd7Vm5lB/C3nSVQbh3UWCRvN3o6EyRsJcstNmEvjza+LT4iujB/98IakheuoI/YkiohacH9yc9Q9v0fB0L5ezVIUf9JSuqIQceudnm0X1myJFpUm904BdDwpBde4Bk3p32uXIkN8h5EHOqr0VOwoBvHwCTZrj43Gnw5Ud/eng4YJh7uSl3GrLh1QGwRcF0YvJ8WCf/4Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Telescopic Observations", 
		"option_b": "Infrared Imaging", 
		"option_c": "Mathematical Calculations", 
		"option_d": "Radio Wave Detection", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010107", 
		"question": "25SqepD91hyq440lEhj9yfHwImLeBCIBq3qNXa5xfnCjXamCbeXsxpl+K1OOhFh6/jbJsaH15R9PnLxa+5qWfiVDaYJ7wJCd3+G3wXBTP89BiZQy4YwWePFOzzjhNMDUYO173n6PNVGwczG4RH57gDjZhDxZrsOe9DWvXJ0kgAYinoJq5Ms1KM7F5aav5mzxxiWLzniERfBqEEKQss+84kyS4I0+9dmFtHLe9ebtkrjR6Z4mYw9Xs4p+bRu9maxJ8CMrEcumbQV3/8aZIXvvMy2xMQ8J8MTtxTR9zoM9HXk49RFDloJEe4Bx2ZztuSFwPt9vVSCqq0FSzpd9UyuYV/T4/H3q4Ud/cHknbJp+uW0mqQCLIVp52k6dXjhZ05Mr/dkLlhFvfH0Aj37hhjCcwGqBPIfr7sDxiuf+nLdHu+MUIUiQck+YQIQPbLHJK25m06mUG6NOc4tvEmLuMscn5jb3HJixlnkpwtA2JnngtDqWnsjmeWq08578mNF6VLgSOcTL7Yu1qRzCbyToL3iWdNi2vLsqM4zVCP/MTTX3EY1NQQ==", 
		"answer": "25T0KLW/kTqmt6dsEjuwsz4w/YBDnHYqxfIkqM/lfg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw2Avp4ohtXB/kzPr+IWLfDSIepT+XWqY0dXDxQK+CbPS+5JZ2IlCFjFU783jC46355BMMna1MqYiNfy9DL94+kZCd2KSmkSMTc89X2oN96okWePFSyTnte9reYPFojnqIIgX1ZiuxDXVngHHSj3pfpoqv/DG+FMolzxo0hcds5ckofMOX3Oi26V+sjkaLzzuCWLVhA12atMLkq0uZroE99cSZ8THU+fHq2v7a4s0fIkBz9rpxUFO1h+8auDwxQsG2YR5C5f2QbkLoMmi3Lwtd8cTx325myMIhXHp09hpDjMNXIsx82J+ptzw/KMMqBTu/rUtNwppzUVeUYan4x2n3oFswYToqdsputD86rwCQJ1N3mWqQQDURkIVt994QgQ11eC9BjzbNgziOjGmOctTwq5bznOn3pfkr1uobJ22VO13KFogfabrQNGJhivqTArFVPZgnAyrjffAv7i3xZ4XUzDEM1NY3b3jptD6Rl434Nmq084X2m9hyVLcBINSF686yvhzIYzDkM2uSZMfxGQ7/XTz5kwJquR9l3Cgd7SLaHZ0/+yIZ3nC1SkF3gSbyZXC41qtS7oecbJo+3PGs3CFQneJxm5751xh8QQupzVpCoJCXCE8P3kTeG98OxwA6FfQUGoLY/i2bgHXYC3AMa8vkQeCkihBG9eHii3NrvoQHWoKdbA3Ti8pm2BuwD/htVHX06IT2OfUQGSQt6Lcx2f2pstiydvKobHIlehazGe1cs5heegc7Aw7eACpbLPivX5kbRaBNyzXenwIITnFfAFTY8qcGHQus6tDNYm/NYL4MCw2iK5FML8DMRkKPJfmsxj/EA7GTmwexWQQhXDOLKL4KpRf/donhZBy902Rh78TpclZJS5YZOGfxbSu8q6SKBQM/bT9lPIUHe0TWRAUqgH7FKOsnqKYSZBBqUuikDEIAlwVajTuSB0sFokkSXrGkVlYrM+lIL18U3zn5UbIaTQnDlDMEiRadxjTtJ/lONQk2dWCWnV/0mpxilvHuwoGHSsf3P6sey4QNL/ZaSp6WGlUbk/3h6vPpH2t5Fn9+IPvBTu7Uow++J4G29xNEx2D/01F6S4bJa5V7Mg==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "E,C,B,A,D", 
		"option_b": "A, D, C, B, E", 
		"option_c": "D,B,A,E,C", 
		"option_d": "C,A,D,B,E", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010108", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRoHCHV7A0cX/nFKbMffr729dwJF+Gn19y/HHKuv+wtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLQAjH3tNJSbYMJghk/JZ2TjdDyvEHl7mnHignkWqZOr9DW+Ws53zRokk4p949x8M9HfzaCWqF6tiEaLzzuVXbgkBVvZocatq1GTtIMsvMKD8T3dtODxn7jW8cwfakhusbpxK2n1pa0I6yU2Efy8bVJO8PbEaRT/LzyiMwsOucTtln191cIoRWAntBlUjY4WdcVgwtjws3I1Pt5+WXO5olFTzpp7HwOecf2rxWak9Fp/dGo7YIt//Dk64R2VO1E+m2WYDD9UgMLRDG/LUoGJk8uk1XChoZTy", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt6QzQRvg0fTwOyuYIitRonGHErd8dTHRUabRYeO+gaU4Z12biBtv4GPD7+Xx+VdPm6BeqZyacTEMcMtm25Cd3+G3x35TIcNHjsB3/IoTffpB2DSiepTUJr56xmvANFHxczywAX5g1vNftWnKLhX7KnxWXC5aJ/U=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCy1un+IW7DQ3YZomvDRqtxMHDzRKbQa+PqiZp+MVmEiFVvsnnA47H48hMcmqYb4J3fdDcGPp9giMSB0qTly2VAJ89LlMB94toLdPEAyTy/YNybFPZn3S6JNAXkdSy4RHJxlzDDmXkWvIu+tQK6Rs4/gAc9goZs6Nt8M9nf0LyAqEygjxXC2mmeRf1zFEeN9dqnq0ads5Z4gcWEonLW8fX3ibjH+N8fIhxausZsdlX8lrgZ/SsqQoigZ1JG/vLVIVXuMiewNE4J8c6jxX9whoQ7UmR08R5VlsNCbYBk04vwgDwMMfliEHOopkVTyJo8TAOXYLirkHzs4UF/YXIuJY9srjk94R2TPFVqn3jcQyIRnZR4vtEBnBcje31PkTb3hyyfwHGAPJbi+JSwxevxtapq/KRnPUmFdU/NWM0IavPBN3d3y/vbGakcIZZ0EmLnM9Fu7zztYKKc1ipN2cpgLnv0+2qNgNjweWe/sJPsndE2FaxAItnAqe62okjPITHuNXyHY9i4GQz5SXr9wQtro1g1yTME+yLXDslr/ShNu3+iXUwkkzXlLHm5hrFP74bOa4Fxx/3pnSEFlrNr34n2zQ58cwyynj9KocSIR0UP2lGWDcgChB0mCfQSAZiR4GSFkDbZRTwZd8u2BKmU12xJ1OexnWRp/5kAFZiGKVnMj80y9BmND8lxUHXoronrOLBVHmwpurNi2eizo8O0e7OlImFqexKyGf1c8oZeZkJ6Aw6dBytbaPi6RIgbDaBO3HGKgw9NB21MBEnD9egBTkSr6sfHfHjbYKVcCwbyb7ILEtrxQUmPOvfp3DjMRr6PhkKsS00qQHg4QgC7U3KdSfJs5gGXtzje", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the Assertion (A) and the Reason (R) are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the statement", 
		"option_b": "Both assertion (A) and reason (R) are true, but reason (R) is NOT the correct explanation of assertion (A)", 
		"option_c": "assertion (A) is false and reason (R) is true", 
		"option_d": "Both assertion (A) and reason (R) are false", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010109", 
		"question": "24GwbdHy3Q3j45AkV179w73rPW6QDmsVp36aErBhfjHqR+fUa//qwJRwK1CQzVRt92TOpqT0t1Ibz7xT7M6gTx08QbRQ9++2l+v5hGVJNoZAm5ky65xfaPxFjDi8Yd3VL+Ys+v84yJ5yzvmG4c1bV/IUmA==", 
		"answer": "25CpfZDn3guojz8pu1/SEpItYlP/E8Lqkw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH2wAzj+Yo4Vw2yxO/6dX/YBiIFtHDDVqJtYzHsUufWZui+0JJwNRyehV51smLOpuXj4l1PjLpU+p2aY2IXdo4vy9WF0vfjzXBNc8NVj4Fm64hfSPxJ332ldcTLJfB9jm+SKFD+Y3mQBWJ3nHGE2jxXpof7xiKrQN86whAg1tUqrecyfMOX3OiW+VixiAma2WjdCKlsFBSKoMDo4lDcpIsqsM6ZvSub++L8iPDW8dpLYxwSq456I16tgqkd9zh4ZcC9e1JG9OXechT5KCm3ZxoV/Ivww3ou1cI7XHAntB5Uh8Nea9Rn35bj/CY4Oo1PFCGuqwNTh4dpTRGXd7j40Xyk4RVmJTcvYI1/uSh1oAGbJFE+m3/cWCRU1IV669ENmhZfc1NOqH7lwj6HlGybaZfmq4/6xfz4pflw561nIFLAIVTdFowSYr/FZ2V33v6eCKgcJ5diVzHzM5I9vCv4OYXU3jcJkM0oKjfC9TiNmormeXavoZT4jdE2J7BMdt7Lqd+/tRzCcDboL3KLY9i4GRz4Sjz53xpsow0hzWEf7iLMAIw/5jgD3nejCR000iPla26kk60c65bOa4Y0k/D9yDMEl+Y69+pnw0XvbC0CEXgLjYK50A==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "E,q,u,a,tor,re,gi,on", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010110", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRoHCHV7A0cX/nFKbMffr724QxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLQAjH3tNJSbYL4uji7AZ3n+Lxj0RFFnhzTEnnVZptn7wS++FNYyzhImnsd364g4Pc6T0K+b/A2xlUaD0GyQUa4kHVuXssu6q1eUoYx4ocWI8T7e+vPtkrjc9p4Faw9aq8Zoak+0nqZJ7CI9EfymZwJC8veQXVqtYGjjZ05duYujljQphsJpHSl0tF8GwsMWIoAzltik/HJwf40qVXP64wQAh9Q8H1fWNP34kCikoBV/NTprJcot/G114U/caBQ+2ivcDGwR1MArvpBZ1UQjPS8A3Dagwn/LvGvHTtrR7oHviuaq4I1r9+MqIEWENEWYRZgSIqCAN2hhw/2SAqgcOpEnAyrjfeE88ynwI4XU1ipN3twhPXv+tDycgNn8OmS284bxnNtjE7cPI8WF/cOy8EXCYDGjmsgr+34LFijpqk/FYIQL3Q==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt6QzQRvg0fTwOyuYIitRonGHErd8dTHRUabRYeO+gaU4Z12biBtv4GPD7+Xx+VdPm6BeqZyacTEMcMtm25Cd3+G3x35TIcNHjsB3/IoTffpB2DSiepTUJr56xmvANFHxczywAX5g1vNftWnKLhX7KnxWXC5aJ/U=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCy1un+IW7DQ3YZomvDRqtxMH3mWqDWZq3xz9d1JkWFhFxz5jbPsOXx+0QOlrsb5YGRdycRPp9nyd7Jw+zyhH1EPcFQksB94toRdfNI2H26fcDTKfAu2maFZ3HiaCm0B2M0oDnfmTxfu8Ov5zK+FNgywxQnhYI4+cA5fOON1ria6174hxSHnHeeS7xwFFDZu8up+QOIqId4sNyYsCbU5ri5jfDW4ttLdgBX/5VqbRyv17oI4Tl4UNqxKBxO8PbceBT7JTq3Lg0c9Yv33mZm04UhUnwgtAtOh8NPZ8FhlqzstSFwMshrGyD6t0xB09RoVxLWZ6i2l3uk8lQmZjojbJ4tqCUw4SqdOkB23XjcXzlDkoFo+5AYgURiPWJPjnOghjaZhWabPJLt7Iz5yajxrr0j5qsiMAGBJ1mYWIIIJaDQNWJzzqmUGLIcMownGjflNZUa9DDqYISRzCwBxMpgJnmn+SWLl43mLGu2upXxmpR0EbYOMZHX7MiyuUrCZWPgNT2Hbs60bRr/X3X7wEIlthYhiC0f5mXdGsl79DQeonCMR3Bsl2fyaX2ymbAc+ZaPa4sik+Hk3CZQjPx935b+0Bk9XkSomHEEocSPQE9G2V3ZEI0Oykk6BLFBIITe4mSVhjbZWDwDes/kDbHH1Slazuryj209q5gcWpmJJBbOnp4ywBLxGPh4RyfZoI/qffUGSmUg6b0x3v+0soq5cPClOXYvLw6/XK9t4ZpBYQFoUQrPAGRDb7uvQpgaAe5K02eKgw9NB3pYEFvY9LpIaQyv6uHJfH7WJKJcDwbrcPMMAI7sR0vbMPXliDLcEv+InUL+a1YqXjOeMvAM9wKwdoPxJQe2lyhr94HxOlQbVI8WMiKze235sauGSyM7bTgtb5kHf1bASgQrhn73L/B0zaoFcRY+AbyvGERWghlK3y3HAB9W8F4fRrbtQUEiaqhJN1oI3ne7FKENUAWKkD8Yml+fwy6sKO4LJUEmO1CBgFzpmIEq3+3shY+TDtjnPq5b3YtDPL5eBInTHkgTlLHYoTfEd73UFwx1knJhlR/u", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the Assertion (A) and the Reason (R) are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the statement", 
		"option_b": "Both assertion (A) and reason (R) are true, but reason (R) is NOT the correct explanation of assertion (A)", 
		"option_c": "Assertion (A) is false but reason (R) is  true", 
		"option_d": "Both assertion (A) and reason (R) are false", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010111", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRoHCHV7A0cX/nFKbMffr724QxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPMhOhBzkVcfIJex6x2GOfQXEbzz9CHV6kyXeynNQ6Ie67Ge6Wt53zhw1npM45MZ8KN+amaac+lmwgxSMnHOURbR3AVycp8vo/UKOqYcr9dqEpTqb4Pz82vvb8dAMawZV/5V6YkizmbtJuGp4EYj0KC5FsdjeKWakEi2iNAETo4vX3nEp0oslSSk78l9SioYWZ8FhwpCjr3IxJ8R5VTC7tldF1NRqXgWPfbO/kGnq51k6ZjokY8p+qSM5qAiUPBRqknmTWStZm5V/vsQRkER6eG5S3ofnoK3BUCHwm6u0vWRewfI=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz0Ar58pc0WxH8hbXefCvRDWZRsXqCQax6MDnRHefDfOi+3YVkIhDJjFV/smTDorb/+RNHveEb4J3fZCoGPohg2sKM1PC3wWlRP8dKm5R765Rfc/IAzS6+ccbPKfFgjiahbgdu0Vq1NgDqiVpBkCuegnh2", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/NmTCEWcStz+BV6B1ZWLmFKTKb+P5wJl2Z0+MjEh0/GWGqquw41sKz6ZU+5qXdTANPoNqxdmax+zy1nQBP8NFnsBm69oJfeZZxTOqNNjeLvl6xn3AKEOwYzikRHF6kHHYg3tevMOP/SL7Rt820xo81o5rrcszLsWa2rzT+0S2hQPCyHOUCKltHUDZusjo/0uZ4Ic5p9mF9iGb9ezwibjB9c0ebhxB/49xI1+1ka4M6i82RYi1ZhVH9PeQblKtMz2tKwca8d+vln1k1oMqSWA6819SioYWbsV90Yzs/D02f8lrDD+zpExUh5VyW1eSda+z3m338xU6bWoud4Nosi4wpU+YPUZ3lGzcSCVXkoV5+94N1RBqcGpT3HnmwiuDhSWWeZLxqcN4wQ9l4yQBPI6CkOhWIj4=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both assertion (A) and reason (R) are true, and reason (R) is the correct explanation of assertion (A)", 
		"option_b": "Both assertion (A) and reason (R) are true, but reason (R) is NOT the correct explanation of assertion (A)", 
		"option_c": "Assertion (A) and reason (R) both are false", 
		"option_d": "Both assertion (A) is false and reason (R) are true, but reason (R) is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010112", 
		"question": "25y2KIb72Brit4IlXRngxO33PGjRDyIdrHyCRqp7fmKjXbSCeuX7iYd0NVWGiRt09DbUpqPi9lAbiqwb5YeYeDZDep59wd6Ol+D2038BMshA2pRl7ZYWe/xUjCmlcZTXL/Bpy32UeAelZtZg6noGjWRdUmbwH5Yp", 
		"answer": "25SsKIX71Fna+IklQVwpx3DLXZxdQdxatsKLhEEY", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHj1Avj+IFgXRiy1/j5J2rTF2cV43OKVatgMHX2Rq7Maa36yIB/Z12HiRtv5X/KqqL44xMGnOhP4YvffC0NeY583JCIw6TjzHQBI8lIn5MyzZRfaPxF3zjtZtHcKfFg3SLAM031JwqoCjBmnSLTmTxXpof75iKvR5o21FUz1pF9/9F8M9WT0LmG7Q25iAGO2TfRX7VtElzZpdyn50ySp5F4ocWI8SLe5v32nuuT/9hLZglFscZ+bV/8g78A9CM/Wdz0QRwL9+XTdRitJD2xLgAaucjmxGBoz4xpSWA58QwGjYUWdsh2loHhvSB8f9liEHOJtkoAw5t5TBnRYP2q2XvhoFotNWkuccpsqG00rQPQaEZ7iX6QWCVfk8Bi8JAJmghiby9EnW+gjS3LkGqDfYGj5Yn7jfy84K5r97EiaVWXPFDRUYUIJbDBKSd30v2eA6IcNZB1Vyf+KdAg+Dz9YIaRzTAC1MpiSft04aFlfZkXLv+d4cvr4Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "At the Equator", 
		"option_b": "At the Poles", 
		"option_c": "In the Tropics", 
		"option_d": "In Temperate Latitudes", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010113", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt5EoV17+zPP6JivUEWMGrT+MXONgeHSjU6vNbOi+3Z9wMxyBiFdrsnrJoKTk8hMfg6lY7J3ffSMXdo5iycSA1OX7yGgBMMdIloV2u9jGGT2HjShZijC52bF5dHTn", 
		"answer": "25m5fJjnxB3vt4QuVl7eyvP4PH/FB2dRj3aNV7A2kf8ciQ6Ah7VDb05RChxVrg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH/2Bfv5MU0Wh/mhfX6OXuQD20SomuGErN4cXLmR+fPb/n2zJpwM1WKjFd36zbJreXk/1ZPiKRU64vfcTAGPohuxNyM06TbxWVIJ9NAn8Bz6p5fUPtOyzS5YdDeYPJnwGuTZ2nxczCpEXRx1D3fhHlF6JGu+2erVcg2zBk3msds4ogoNNLf/LmG6Vm3lErCy3OYRLgkPVuXsse8/keZ4I4xu8ie8SDO+rT/iPfesMoDZ0h8sJRraxuMmKQMuD43Edy8bVJ4/vHEaRTdLySmZzoV/NjmlnhgyIc6HWom8R5Sh8NXIsN82YrgtTwxK8gqBiqpt0FNh4B0XgPWdbG033/3oEAsNW4kJZpksj06qAGIaFVwgyuQQy9QgIlk8JAWm0RGfH1UlDb3iyuDwGiOaJvm5oHojOvxrPli8aAyO0CDLB4jClsGydi0PVcqYefKQeK4", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Isotherms", 
		"option_b": "Contour Lines", 
		"option_c": "Latitude and Longitude Lines", 
		"option_d": "Meridian lines", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010114", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRpHqMVqZgeXKjWK7Ma/6+xpkxJhydiElp92XSsazx+xMIg6dZ7M6eYidDcZlmzd6d0uC31HBTMspIn4wy8JVfaPxFjDi8YdXPL+xnz2LAN0nxaTz9BX5w1CXEi2pTupC+tSGpW9d31B031qJ5/tw5Ltnf8a2e4V6ojgOQ2TuFR/1wGVHZgsu7/0aOrsIQsMCEoiLT8eb8xbprRcxmA+sWt2EdStAbAN8V", 
		"answer": "25i9epj32Bjk5Mdpurn6Ji+NmOBBowuhL7ET", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH/2Bfv5MU0Wh/mhfztMCvfEWsUrWuGVuNkcWPiWKvHYq3qxtdlL1nJiEpu82LJsazx+xMfg6lV7M6efiZDaplu3tWbxOG3wmNOPoZQkoUywZsMaPFSwn2FcdnSM+5my3yFZ1H/Jy21ATBDkSLCj25Y6Ku++C6oRNIy0hByl5V9rcs9MNua3eie7V+xgg+D0mitRoFqPFGLvMqh6k2P4IMqsI2EvDPc/fr4iOGT/NcFZxsSq45+dxuugqZJ/jg3XIikZx5OsfDfIUTiLC3jJgAZuc/qwH1tw8I9VWx08xNJgIYWa85n2djhvSEkf8xkEXOtpldUh5x9UwGTZ/2M2G2k0Ec2eH9rSI9/tSk8oAHcIUc+jmOZDCFUholv99EX1RBrfHsAjHfzkTqYwHGHbpz27Ii8ovr1pbd0+6AvZQGlO1vUV4MYJZLMKyd93uGeH+ZRNo1uEyvnM8Zu/Sv8YJuR3ioYwtwkb2Du4CLZgMjzPHe/vZH8zsB5VKsIM5H1+8K6tRzqZDHoJXSSaPf6ZQbER3m41wd2oxkryyRQ6mfMH4x6+20ZiXHwREF2myPpbXKy1rdPqtPOe4s2wfDpnT0W2Ph3kZz+wAg4QkSPhXpRt8SeXVkPngKGXskCwxsrCadBG5CR/mKYkn/EXngIP8f4QbyI1y1EmK0qgb7F33HM/XaeIpy7z/E=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Meridians", 
		"option_b": "Parallels of Latitude", 
		"option_c": "Great Circles", 
		"option_d": "Lines of Magnetic Declination", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010115", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRXj+YBgQBvi1/jsMGXEECJBcz+PU7d9ZGTnUfiAcJ3skIgPD8yslh9LpzxulA==", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHWwAzr44oyEJ6Fm6lw4996vDGkCTmI50c=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH2wAzr44oyEhfhhen3MCvZDmMWqnGCQLo0fHjtUefWZuzqiZN4MVWNiEg75n7D44Dx5UcHz6FV/YHfdTMWf4cvwNGFweHkiDFPPNRQksBz6p5fb/tV2DXtXcCbKe0u2maFZ0nxdT64F2Q0lzjEiXBT6Iy9tSu6QNMj1RE31oh2re09LsOX5aav5nmwg0aHzW6QXLJ2UV2K9c+k+EzctIo99cKDvSub+P33n7jc9p4HYxxbq5N7Zhuon6kduCMrEcn0bwBO8PCQYl3/IySmZy9d/tnm12ApxYs7XmUxtBZVwpdeZ4B/14rjuSEkf85jBzC2pgRUz5VoHxSXev261Sjg8lQoezoka8ps/D4lqQqOLWhwpmWoRCkRkZF+/8QWh0Rqbi9JkWbvkCuKjnHPfpbg6pXvgKj5tPlq4eMzIUTAJ1neU58Za7DFZ3d9w+ePTaBTId9qEiP1KMcn8j65LJeA1i0Y1NxgDnvrtCWNmsjneWmzvZfqzttwVLMBItjR/M+y8F3VZGPsJHyAc9nxXUj+QG7s205qpVg2xzQE4CLXDslr/ShNm2+lSFBrgBvuUHKVnrsc75Obfpo+wbXlznIRlOd335L6xBIuUwW1mT9Bt4eeWk9KjV3CXsQUhB0mCfQNHZjUsmKQ1WzVWXNNc8H4BqGT1ihNms/+gGZ0q4UKUMyHP1nWj9813QW0Bb18VHT56InrfesQGXBs9bQx3uWk9/qpfP6hbEgvfROzUO5Xv9VGYAt4GUvUFmROILSnWJheTuYP3nrEkA5cUntMRU7E+rxITQW5ucHbLn7Wcb4JCRaiRKEAFsDvR0THebGMxjfFB7GY1wR/ObCGm4RBlnpQ+c4eqvk=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Tropic of Cancer", 
		"option_b": "Arctic Circle", 
		"option_c": "The Equator", 
		"option_d": "Tropic of Capricorn", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010116", 
		"question": "2523f9H+0Bfzt5EpXxuy3/LxMHiQB20UsD+XWqY0RULQZufRfuzwiZZyNVOangQ5tJ2++1JLoIGnhgzBzw0zrg==", 
		"answer": "27C0bYf231uO+J3jwRcBUNAtrdRXaK19", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHA3g/j8pFgZxD7yvO/JnvRDWwUpz/SA+NgeXzmFL3NYOjt9ZlNKXWdzUx64TbH47Hi9l0cjKdV/YeRdSwXf4cvy9+c2fDl3TFVO8dQ2pNm9p8Lf/xFyH2rZtvWYNtv3XqFNUuwQiyvC2Bx1CXZyllXu5f71DSyVZoDyBwh1op97MYofMOX2LzT/EW9lAPCy3qCCLwkAl2eu8eu4kCdrpZ4scSLtzfJ8fr6n7ja/p4fawVX/4R6d0y5kqZJ7CI9Ed+xewZO4+qQYFrpYC2iNBoY68WjxnV70pFpUm904BdDwoBZd85nxIHYsg4+C8VvVQC1tU1F09RJUR6Zev2tw23goEE3cDoeUakm7H9v8V/cPF1znyuGQyJU1Illvt0WhhAjcmkAlWLzwhqekmqfeZLtq5T5l/r5tLZx6+9nLFmDMEzMFosTd/PrJmt7xOCVCrRdN99IFS7nLsFivC7xKZWcnywe1d1gGkPEv3rLyJ6leUy087Pqh9U6VKsIM5H25t2+tUiHVC3oLnPTc9jxXUjxD2r5wQdgowFlxydQ/GvVDcll+iMIjTLwQEpnnjLkZXKm1otoycneKdRhg7ms6AYz06QvxcunmF0Jcyfw3ScZ4tTTD11ByRTjKu5MlVl0XOQ9GqrfxmWT1UXfXXUIa47DD6GIzWxJ1vD+znRuupROUY2XIBDcgspm2xanCPN+FXPkpYO1ff4AHiQ48rcxzuy1stn7dP2gbHEjYh+kGflY4ZxUbEJ9AwTQRT1KYaruQpJeWOVOwEnEqwlpQWtMFxrY861IWQ25ucvEe37XbL9cARiid7sAU/33WE7KIbGcxjnGCP+VmwfvBh10AnqJKbVN4wjid4ngZCC8hWFh7YH3N0FORo8ePzSzdW+2tbeGD0YudyksOspIbUmVXxkpkX7ZKPdinuUJJXh2wYqzqLYjB54neaIq", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Six", 
		"option_b": "eleven", 
		"option_c": "two", 
		"option_d": "ten", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010117", 
		"question": "24KwcdH33lnm9pcnVwyyxvLqO3/CCmcC43OKWaY0ZHnmFJLxT6G+6pZ/JliIwRt6/HKGlpbDxRMOi6dL/c6SZS4Xd5tjzZCd3unyhGtOPcNXxcJzxICQb2GxxzonCfDlxIjk", 
		"answer": "25GtbdHn3ln+/4ApQF7kxO7rdWzVDGUDom+LW6B1fDHmTLPHYPm8VOWBqo+rv2ohsyBB5Qu7/w==", 
		"explanation": "25m5epb2w1np+JAuRgz7wO6/OWLbBiIFq3rDZ619ZHTnFJTWb/n72tsxBF2HjF96vjbHraGw41sKz65U+4OaYmIwcZ1mzcTJ4ur+y38BMsJLipQy6Y8TaP1QwDjtYN3WJb50wWCFNAXyYjq8EWNx1D7QymherYqptTG6R853xxA9kZV5/cA1P9aTma2L/Ei2kka21H6CTf1nHkGXodyh7lDcs5YqsNmOuXLU4vHr2vmT/N8ZZQ0Ss4lxZFKogqwA9is0Ecy9ewZK/+fVLRT6KCGgL04Q/MrtxTR9zoM9HX088Q1DwopFIsEzxZHjsjs2Ns5rGyf6p01GwZFuWhmVcf2x3ijw6FB/YXMmYMpium0xoBbcKlFqjW6ZQmxFnIUr+9EKgQFxcy9BknKglTqYlGCdctPz6pLolqj/pvl3+qZnKk6VO0jKT88V8MlkQPu2uFTcqXnk49YU", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Due to their vast geographical extent", 
		"option_b": "Due to their small size", 
		"option_c": "Due to their population density", 
		"option_d": "Due to their location", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010118", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRoHCHV7A0cX/nFKbMffr724QxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLQAjH2Repz6ab5P3X2FNVH5aDf9KHFgnSXDjnkWpIq18DT7VcgygBQ+hYg45sYzK9nf2LvT+EyqhwqO2XeCCLJiUViYoce8/keZ4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riTsJ5LIkgS/8Y/Ixv81+hJuGp4EfS6VBwDw62QU1HsMyetZyIc7cL3w3Bsho4gU2wntB5Uh8NVbc5w05bwrjszf85jBzC2plcAyJo8XleReLK61Sr8ZQ2prS3HGEO8LcVh87a/", 
		"answer": "25T4YYKzxQv/8sUiRwqy5732JiveDHZRoHCRQKZ3ZDHmTLfOb+P/3Z5+KRyGixtasJwHioDXpYP6ARJbUIaLr0w=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCy1un+IW7DQ3YZomvDXqJgeWX2UKKCYuTwzIQxJk6MzVp34XmGqKv/4F1Pjrsb+Y+NcS4Pe4d8iN+Pl+j20HhVJsJB2rR67YlfdecA2C+4cZT3Iepn2nuEIgX8bje4FzB1hjSWiXVEq4++5mevXNsjgBQgk8do7No9MNua1eiH5w2sjgPC2WqESalrAxStvcuxq0KOpcItpsiJ8SbUtPn8m+vG4ttLdgBX/4J2cE+9masMuCQ3Q9y8KB1ZsfffdEDlYCelZxoV/Ivmx2Fo0o07YWcI+itOh8NEZ8Fg2ZakryYxK8h5VSeyolAAy5VoVgODcLj43GHq5UZ/dGguJYlisi4wrxuOIVc+mWKOTyBUh8Bk8JAY1QNvcm1F3ELoiyzLiXbPepLv+IW8puf+o7xt5rEuKgGDPE7bWogPJbLSIidxw/uYAaNPc4tvFjamNdQ4+XntKJPUzDgA1ZkjKnnz8TjZvszhMHGvt5e5gt14EaxAMt6F58Sj8FTGdyahNXWWJtj1VA2wTHn2xwt39ywtzThQ6XDdSIhz+W0Om3CkTFZhlmfvYjy1nrscz4Oca4Z2wLXtxTsDpPpEka//0V0/SBapiHxX8paaTk9AwxTQEd9H0AErTLUSB5PD5mSZmzbZWDwZd8/iQaSG1yVcz+f0zm10sZUdFY2cKVnSh98hwRmwE+Q5WW7jrZW5KfQUHiQ+77wx2uyztsa3cP/kOGpqexKyGepI5pRFZxA5E5ftPux0tLJ9ahvK186JXw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "A is true but B is not correct explanation of A", 
		"option_b": "A is not true but B is true", 
		"option_c": "A is true but B is not true", 
		"option_d": "Both A and B are false", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010119", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRrn6XUatxYzHPXbTWI8SkiYB4M1TJzXdy4WKLioyqtRAK3Hr7ueBH7wEYDbm79Lg=", 
		"answer": "25C5eoX7lgqq45IpXFPcwOXrdXvcAmwUtz+UW7d8MGXrUefSYf7twJV4K1WdlBt09DbWr6T+4xMDhq5epc7fQC4WaoQi7Nmaw+35w2RIIM5BnsBw/doWaOcAyTGhfcTPKf1vwi6PNUf5c3X9KXFmh3zkj2pZpJW+5me6RtUizhFygo99re09LsOXma2F7V+hxlTVnH+QUa4oUWGLtMC9+A6zsoAxoY2ZsDne57Srw62T6dsKcBsSq4k/YFSxh6QM7C96MDFlXIGw+LEgK+5+K9gayQ==", 
		"explanation": "25T4TZDhxRGt5MU0RRf8n73JMGXFECIYsD+MVLdxfjHxUaHHfP/7zddlKByInhte82TSq+Ljt0cYhqYb64uccTcQe8tgzpCAw/e313hMOspFiIlm/doWcrRTxSeoOJTWIe19gi6BKUGwYzyzF3lgjXH+hWtTvoapuWeNUdQi01U7hcd1+Ms0fN+QzbyW+g2sjgeMnF6QWqlsUVWXsY6g6lDcocIusN+U8SbT/ffy2vnH/dEYcgBXrYNDbWeyteg59D8sXpL0WB5e5euQaEetIWinMA8P/4vz2nVnw5ZpSWE14F9PkcNYbYB/2ZbjuSBwPMJkBjq+plZFw9RoUFeUcf25kHjo4Vs6YToia8piqT91sgCQKUY+iXKPWClc1Kl/vtkK1QBqbntJknH1iyyDhWHPfoqj4pTvxe38rLBz5qokKE3AOk7aX5lQJaTILmR6iv2aBqNPc5ZzVyP1fdYi8yr8YJeHn2tUh5kBGjfz+2qNmsi1CnC085P3ipR3B/8GN8OF6Nj35AWSIQLUYXyEZ9LIVzT+bDzV0hx27VgIyTMDqGvLSJ138G0LkWuiXUwkgivhYnm11rhO5Y/Oa4Y0k8b503IRlvA4i5PylA45RAu1iTJQv4WTQ1lc2RTGEswJwR1uBbpBG4PDsn6ZmXfCC28UbNrzDOiu12xByaP+iHV4sdAcUIqLPgvejp4yx1ewEr1tXWKtlMTLOPhVOmgt9Ldl9q/htc+4dOa3KSUlaVq+TfwZ4ZBVbAtoGUbfFytYbvi9Q48YQONKkljLhRQITmwJEVLD7q8ASUS+pYTAb3zbI6UUC17ybKcAHdrxT0uPM/67iCDFB7GI1Uu3WUFpDjiINfAZ7QLif8z7N1O9nChg/MfsPFhPTZUSfCLlfW+8q6CGSxI1Pz8wOJpIaFOVXxgth37AK/hugJsOTBYJAZ21GF4DhUsPqizTAE1W8EUNH7GlRRM0L79ALk8ZjSe5EK4aSFzMlDUHzkKUx2LfPPQLMEcnO3Cbigz0k5t0m7Llg5yGD8f2ba0X04MGPPZSStrZCklcifzo7vOgAnUqEmh6btHcHurQow/3Qt7xsNqa0FJe2qsJOh8vLDWfxd/O+S5lb6xbfDBLpXoK7MXUIhSlzYlN3F9mEFTg+E73VScxswNja53vY97JJpq3sERQVi3TRPlMiv5xyS3odc/dZRQ6R1YnkAmFZZWKyCaBNLi71KwCAAvihcCeBZNo7Vpqjsi9g09Ppit5imjnSSpmk1kt/UPZr0wINmQ22I8=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Earth's twin,Next planet with the possibility of plant life", 
		"option_b": "Pluto,Distinguished by its elliptical orbit", 
		"option_c": "Mars,Revolves around the Earth every 27 days", 
		"option_d": "Uranus,Orbit takes 295 years to complete", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010120", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEgz3xO7wOyvWDHBRt3eGErV1YnjiQK7NYK33x9d1Lk+djFV49zbEprHn8lYBz5hX/JqQMCMNest7wNXJ5PH5mzPlNeAjrpQoNWNcECPgIE3K", 
		"answer": "24W0fYX8lgqq+JciWwqyzO6/PWLXC24I43qPXqpkZHjgVauAEDjou701176otGpuz3I6FA==", 
		"explanation": "25SrKIX71Fnl5YcpRg2yyvu/IWPVQ3IdonGGRrA0cWPmFKnNeq39wIVyMlCInxt552KGpqn8/kMbhqta5cLfZCoGPo9m28SI2efyhH5Hc/ZIj5R9pJwNc/kA2DWoNOfOLr5q23yJKUKwdzyvDXhxmDjZhDweoYb74i++Wpo+1FU7hcd74ccvOcSLmbycqFmwg0axyXXYCLR3UQbV4pj+q06VrI4xusPNvDvX8ee12vnd9J4KdkhTr456b1KzmehB8S94RsCxZlJC5aTZchTrITq3LwsO7YvlxHtkhpYhWCkH4REPwopFIpQ/g86y/D85M8FjGj36rk1MwodAHVeifLSrkG388Fk+fHQ4JZ5lvTl1kQOJPFs5iSuYRT9FlY5o+5AfhwtuPXtImTbTlzHLlmSddZbwq5P1gub5prBg860zJVjAN1nbV5gPYPPJM3QyxfuZBLIcOownHyvhNdk3vDz1LJ+EyzAO0dViIp8iSNjjJ2ZoRXxLdnQEzw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Pluto's orbit is highly elliptical", 
		"option_b": "Pluto's orbit is influenced by Neptune's gravity", 
		"option_c": "Pluto is being slowly ejected from the solar system", 
		"option_d": "Pluto has an erratic rotation on its axis", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010121", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUGXRL+yur2O2yKP2w9qmyXEoo0OFLrVbXDbfn7255iM1WKnhI7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sBe7YkLPN1pjHWdeNXVJep9h1KOdgvcZiu6AWNg1CHai3JTvMP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmejTqA34xkbCnDvRCP0kURTZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ4lIPNnDPJ58j3yLbw+N8ZYwtGupR2eV6416oQuCYxVsCgKBNF9aTUYEbmYCqiKQoOuYujljQphsJpfycC8RFTkb9YMY5Q34rnqT4xLY1mHDSytwRByZA8WxaEf/260Wbg8xV/NTprJcot/G114U/caBQ+2ivcDGwRt84r1MUJnBBmb1NOyDjMgy2MhXabPJ7s5I68xaiw4PkjsuNnaQHAdRyYFs1cJfOAZycyiqnbTeYcc98nV2KmfZVuvHm5YNbUnx1DkPQlPXTy5jOlnPH7Lm2zsJq5h8c2F7ASJNTG/ceu8HHGdSDpJHnRYZo2m7sDSRDeT+b1dP1bZw==", 
		"answer": "2+T1S92zglTJtX36A6BPggZzkeUtxbu8rf4=", 
		"explanation": "25+teJjn1Auq/pZgRhb3hfH+J2zVEHZRs3OCXKZgMHjtFKjXfK3txptwNRyalEhv93uGoqv0t1ocz6ZU/Y+dfCdDeIR9iNmdxKT1xX9FIIZLnMBh85MNcP1Oy32ueNvOJO0ijnmILkb4JzitFHV1hnHXmTxaoYSz4We6Wt53xBQgncd67MY4L5eI0a2dqFuxgxGH2DuFQK9rBFOR9c/o/0aQpZE7ut2I8QbT8ef82vrS/toYIglAusZ+I0m5hL0F7Go3V4igYBcL4ejRb1H5ZzvjJAEQ6cfmzjRoyIZpSXwm9gpKh41CIsFn25f3rDo1LcgomPsH2IG/o6lOLTAE7h1F9g==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1-C, 2-A", 
		"option_b": "1-A,2-D", 
		"option_c": "1-C, 3-C", 
		"option_d": "3-A,4-B", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010122", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEhPzzPO/M27RF3cDpj+XWqJgMHXqR7PLYOrrwIR5Ik/Jvlpv52TI46Pi+F5PgLxT7JzfYC4CcI5725CA2aTjzHQBIMlIm5Iy94MMaPFNk39ofEr7uez6u9jgdCfckeOV", 
		"answer": "25ysKJnywlnrt5YlRl79w73tPGXXECB3Yp+W9uSUdOiFb0EZ+EQq", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH+0BDkt4MlUwrn1/i/IWPRFyIVqmyXW61zZXjwXKLRLt7/3YJjKRyPn1R2snnSq6Dit0MDjqZe/Z3feSxDaoNqiMOG2+XlhGJYINJBl8B799oWaOcA3jSjc8ebE/9623yOYFawdTCzA2M0lSPTynFXrIb74Df7W9x3whw+mo5349t8M9Hf0KuWqF25lBKL33eUW/EkA1WXssem7AOVrsIrvNeI8TTJ+/m5nu3A5J4McAlbsZU/d1T8hKUI9CZ4XMe7ZgELxezVIUbkLi+wZw8P/Ivw2TRlx5AuWCkg/B5SwpdeZ9kz1Znq/DA1f95vED36pVZPytRZXgWCfP2v2XzsoFR/YX8nYJlusz0wnQGgJmd/jn6OQmtC1JJi8NcK1QVxeC9UlHn1hTefwHGAPJvi/YW8g+firbxnsrQvLE/ANBzVWYISJbzGZ1Rz3vyJA+ZLMownFTDpNtAgvCzpYJSNnzhN09YsI370/SWX0tr8LW36spz2mtxzBv8PNNvA6t/3hFTCISfkI2+adYvySwf9D2jw1k5ouBcriDIA+mfZDMlw4DlNl3CkRgRl0iPpf3fhl6xT/4yKP70wx+D+035Qmfp8357h0RMoUgW3gWYDsYueQ1lczlHSXsQJ0AZuGLwEVITY/GqF1WLYSmhNaMu2Eq2CgzhH3uLozG2S1Ki8xf7CuSQSTm+aWEE=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "It has a bluish-green color", 
		"option_b": "It has fiery gases on its surface", 
		"option_c": "It has twelve satellites", 
		"option_d": "It has a set of rings", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010123", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7n1+3wJm6QDGRRrH2QV7FieX/kFKaCffTt3ZJ8Z1OPzUhv83jCorf0t0cGgq0b4IDfdCsFeI59zd6dl+f40X9VIc9Bid8wOktw9MbyqVlsge8DpCczWA==", 
		"answer": "24G3KJL83gvu/oshRhuyxP7rPH3ZF2sUsD+CXKc0fXDoUefBYeDz3Jl4JF2dhFR1snPHsKz15REb1ur+0jojJ+hv9F5I3dgn", 
		"explanation": "25e9bp7h1Fn+/4BgWxDm1/L7IGjECm0f43CFErBgcX/nVbXGLvn3xJI9Z1mIjlM78XnLrrD+/kcWz7te/c6WZDFDcZxhiMSA2uG3xnBSNsIElY4y8JIaPORP3zS5fdvVYPFojnqIIgXjcjf9MHh9h3Hbj31YvMOv/SavFM4/xVUmn4p9rcEyfNiR3OiH51q2xgWNyXeVCL9hUVCQs8it+UaStMI+p8KA8SbT8bTtk/XWsNcFIhxausZxZkOo17wG7yR0Ec2ibRwL+OKQdVzoOWi0IhwYucTt2m0px8IvWH50+RZKh5AWY9ByxIykiDo5LI1pGia2pwRCwtR/UBmQYa6x3m+k4Vs7NX4idph4rDk8twrQaFFtim6fRS1dmJkr+N8L1QZ2bmZOmWXzhyzLgWuLPIfx6o7vlefitLh3+6wpaVKZJkjdW54ga4/OFHNzxO2aH6IcJ5ZqEmL1Mtk4+Sq5NJ6dzHkdwtYiI3LqtCiA0sn8L2y+upz+zsB+Ef8XOcPJ7Yu+vkjIITfoLHjTfMT6XBu8D3n50AYluB5l3ykZ62qYB4ts8D8bm23wSAR3mynnYHnhgrdR78K6d4cik/jt1jcD2P1s3572xxQ5VUSvgj9AvYuNS1VBzEDTXswE0AA4BaAIEYWR82OS1XXfRnEYccf1ALyCgy1LyOzinSFxsJ4JFYiHPw3ahN0j21XMgguuHbYzpIrKX+HIQjIL", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "To confuse travelers", 
		"option_b": "To coordinate activities and make communication easier", 
		"option_c": "To encourage changing watches frequently", 
		"option_d": "To highlight differences in local time", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010124", 
		"question": "2523f9H+xBrit4EpVBj31/jxNm6QCmxRr3CNVapgZXXmFLTHfuzsyIN0NByMjFhzskXSoqv09kELz5xS5IvfSi0Ne8tp2t+El/D/wTFPNt5QxcKM+oh25PKo8rn0YN1FUZie", 
		"answer": "2+TtuNOfJxqLLLPrOSitQ04gnFM8", 
		"explanation": "25C5a5mzwg3r+YEhQBqy0fTyMCvKDGwU43aQEvIhMHXmU7XHa/6+xpExK1OHilJv53LD46Tg9kEbz5xT4J3feTFDfI5sycWa0qTjzHQBFsdWjogy9pULfeBF333+IoSbJPtp3GuFNAX/aXm0EGM0lSnfmTxZpoC+tSKtUcgugEdm1o93+NovfOSQleiW6U6wxlfXkX+UT69hFBSVusCv4leJpId4t8yDtXLJ8eTrn+vW/soYIgdcusZ3bE6u16cPuD4xXM2IZi5F2evHZELoMmTjMwYY686j12ZshpEmUGx08QdFh5NCa899xdjws3IkN8R5VSGvr0EA4ZtuHxKOdbCo3G2ooEYweH9rZoV4sjknqAqPZBRtj2iUDC1C1Kll+tkY2URAdWZOnTqggzGPwFeab4Dq6sy8jenmpflu568zIFGMMBzMX4AZJanPKWJhiv6SGa5VPd9zHyfvL5Us8yv9JYSHnw0F2cpgJmSn9i+ak9jmPCWuu5fgzsN3GqtAIt6F4s6yoBzTaSahMnyeY4vgUAX1D3X2kwpssR4g2iQe/CLICZtr5m0CmD6kQUEkkSj1Ymizj/Ic75SLcc4l2/r52jpQjPx9htv2xhh8Tgr7iXZFtIGNSlJbjVjZEMoO0BwqCfQDFZjV4VGYqXjxR28CM47lDqWCgy9Hz+3lnGh4rNxORpmNJFnamZ4A2ha/Avg5VGnp6LXpPPUbRiQo9fJ/xfnhuMiocOGyKSUubgO7UOhR59VCaRRyHwydES1CZfiaXpQNAe1K03vZ1xNARmsJEVLJ4ugJTwHqpcrNLmLRdqNcDxbnYrdFHMi4Wk/KPOPp2yTICLudh0P+S00oS3qZNKIE6wCwboT3ZACmnmVh64HoPV9PTJArMhv9W328t6KPB0p6ayQgaI5OfEHQWRUqlzuDLvcngagOdxE5VKyiWVITggZKmjCSC1lGuAwNS6SjRFI1LulRKVYUjS26H6VfVQ+K129KilOb0CfpOrYLM1w3O3Cbil7l25N0mr/6jYOEStH6LrgLxoQMJqUZsYSu+vaCnY/M7xsMluTDJg==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "10°", 
		"option_b": "12°", 
		"option_c": "15°", 
		"option_d": "20°", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010125", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEgr7yPi/MWLWBWcDpnGAV+N2dWX0UaLMLsTwzZ5wKRy6mVp19nfUp+XE/l4Kz6lV7c64YicGcJxmy9jJ+uH2yjF1OstBxcIpNs138VceHTDIkuIVSbIn", 
		"answer": "2+D4YJ7mwwqqpNVgXxf80On6JikS93hLeIvImZcJlG/1ksYU", 
		"explanation": "25y2bJjy31nZ44QuVh/gwb3LPGbVQyo4kEvKEqpnMCSjXKjXfP6+yJl1Zw/ZzVZy/GPSpraw9lsKjqwb5ojfVzAGe4V4wdOBl8nyxX8BB89Jn8A6w7crNbR0xDS+NNneIfB9jnqIJlGwcDG4CjB9gHHfmTwH+tnrpWe1W9U5gBw81qBV2YR8NcPf0LvTvRfr1kay8TuYRv1NImClu/KmwnCo4Isr9cKDtHLU8rTtkv2T9tcdZ0hGtot6I0Gzma0auCM2EeG6bBtKsdDYZBTiNCCmNU4b9t7xlmBgy4dpR2Y68QwGg5FTOPx96pbXrjtwE8xkHjL6l01NwtQ0diSiNPb4hTu0oF0wYGg4LLZjkigloAPcHF1znyvUZR9l1Msrq4RM1QxsaH1T1UruoDeelGSBPKfq5oW8zcHDlPkosvVnIU6VJ0+RaoM/YL3UNWZ+isCVCa9dc6tuGiemdfwdyHmyYMfHj3kF38wyPD7b+gOXlsT0eWG1toG5gNtiVLACJdTX/873tF3ebSrmKWnTdcriUAb3D2jx3gsn1+zNxvHTRi/gxrv+LzMoZg==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "3 hours", 
		"option_b": "4 hours", 
		"option_c": "5 hours 30 minutes", 
		"option_d": "1 hour", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010126", 
		"question": "25SoeIP8yRDn9pElXgeyzfLodWbRDXtRsGuCQLA0dH7mR+fWZui+5J59LEXJulpisnHHr6To7hMMgKZP6IeRPGIUdo5hiNWRx/by12JEN4ZNlMBh55MacuBJyjSuNNrUNP96x2GOeAeiM+MzPERlZknCPco953W6", 
		"answer": "2+QPOcEqCFsVCYJbyYBNdZ1XNnl0Pbuu", 
		"explanation": "25ateoP23w2q9pY0QBH8yvD2NmrcQ2cCt3aOU7dxYzHwQaDFa/7qiYN5JkjJmVN+slvPr67pt2QOluhc6IKeaDtDfYRh3NGA2fe3xWFRIclck41z8J8TZbQRnG3tdt3XLPdhwC6TM0TidHX9E3h9lzmWiX1Y6IG+tSKjRMgy0wY3ksdx44gvP96a17ya7kS7xgiNyHqFQbJqUVWK9Z8fuhNFecDnp9zyzqSSgGfuMo/Ut9mN", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1×10⁷", 
		"option_b": "1×10¹¹", 
		"option_c": "1×10⁹", 
		"option_d": "1×10¹⁰", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010127", 
		"question": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxdR/+xOX2MHiQAnAU43yPR7BgdWPwFKjELv7qyIViZxzJzRtH/GXSorH1+lYBm+gJzo+TcToKe5gvy9+Hw+X+yjFAIIZCn5cy5YlfLaQQjC65dcbIYP9gyi6TN1f1Zj39C2Vg1CTYg3pZuo637Bu1aNQAyBwxnsdf5N45MpeszamH7UC9iBLC3WmUCIl2BFHG95ASaz7aYv3AZseuUK5BLeE=", 
		"answer": "26asaYX23Bzk48VxEhfhhentIG6QAXcF42yXU7dxfXTtQOeQLuTtiZl+Mxydn05+sPYJeqW7CsxntXkD8lF5XKI=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxEhfhhentIG6QJGMdomeKV7A0cWPmFKTOe/7qzIViZ1OPzUhv82TV4631+1dPm6dc7JqXdTBDfJIvz8KIwe3j3TF1O8Nd2oNz6tocc/pUzTSjNNXVOelmy3yFZ0PiaDT9BTBykSaWgmlYrJG+8We2XdY7yRo81pN3rdwuNduT0Ked+w23gEaRyHqDW4FqLVqqoc+87k6ZrpZ4542EonLd9fjqn7j08dIKegFXrMZ7bBuymLxJ+yU2Rcm9ZlJK4qTWZEOtITvjdl5Nudj312Z6hrYhWCkn+R5KjoZFdoB015TlpCtwNMNlAj36qlcA05x5HzSXerSrkEXl6lotNV48ZJhr/Co0rQ6EMRg+jWOVTyQRl49l6tEQmxcjfG1PiWKg02/bzDXfLNPw/4Hulqjdr6p3sqQmJUCYPFnLFo4Ta6fBLmkyx+CXAa9TPYwnGDCmP9wi8DD2LoXU0D9Nw80hPWTb+haXtcz5OH2ztoG5j8ZzVL4MJd6F58Sj8E/XcybgJT2cc9+0TAb5SXPq3gJ89ywtzThQ6XDdSIZ54SgD3n28XEl0i2uge3W1nv5P/oOcbM4w3fGs2jMD2Pd3kZjy2gkuRhC+iT9KvMSLR1kPzlHYCsgVhD0mCfQsHZra6y2hlG+QTH0BftbvTeiBzD4I3/vwg3FxutxOXY2dbBibidso3AWwDb17QGvqrcb2O7wGHmU+6fJi3/+zuN+1cfagbGczLxv3XeZK+NVebkJoBQrPFmRObrzuUZwNA+JSc0DAObyaGTjAX6OfDZI=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both statement 1 and 2 are true", 
		"option_b": "Both statement 1 and 2 are false", 
		"option_c": "statement 1 is true but statement 2 is not true", 
		"option_d": "statement 1 is false and statement 2 is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010128", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fLYK3szIRhIl+dzVR9smLOpuX89kEIirtPqZ6TcSwGastmxpCd3+G3135NMtQEiZlh8J8SJshO8DP8PeDTJb5iz3yHIlbkJymxBX5xgHHfhDxCoIb75ii3Vch30wwhgoJ1rcEvfP2KyaGH7V+EiFTL9m6BQalhAxSRtN3o6gOPr44xsYHNoz3Y/+25ie3B9t8IZzRc7M9Vdku1g60bvzl4dtqxaQYLw+HUIWf9LzzjLh1d+Ivu12d6z5QsHWEh5g1PgYJYZ4Bn3pnw/DoxLI1oEDa041ZBwJ1yWFeQe6/40Xyk7FA+Zm5rMdo9/DQwoB2PFFoq00GJXCVFkZIr9tEK1QJmampS3HvvjTGYwHGHfZ2j2IHokPr+nLdf/IsoPgGNNFLBFoIaJafIIidh3uiPCKtZPYt0VyXvK9AgvDj7L4CRnzgf1ZkjIGX18SmNzY9SgHiZWkz4291kSKCCGMF0", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUqol5tyMTgvamx+yDS5tdxxbQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH/0Avt8pY0Eg7+xPP6ISvZDSIFq3rDQax4cWOjR77ReujziZ5iZ3acnVJv92SG7uXE/1ocz7tP6JqafScNastm25CK2PblwXJVc+xRiolm4YhfdecAxTOpcdHfYOpmyy6MJlf3YiqpRGB4lT/TnjxfpsO04DX7R9U7wQdyhZ5r+c0xANmj14KG+ESsgxTC1HqCCLwkAluVvMrkq1GTo4kh9d6YozTa9/G517jn+NcYIhtGvpJ6bl6yg+gA62oxX8u7egBO8vCQS0H9KTymNU4U6ovilnNo1cIuVGg64F9HjIcWZs92xdjqsyZwN8x8EHO741dPy514E1eEe76zySj39Uc5dHkuWYRRsgcgsQaILUY5iSu7XilQgMBZ+9RZphRsaS9JjzbhwjKKk3aGapaj45Xul+HzobdmsrcvKFXAPV3LFo8ZYL2ANWZ1w+ecTaBTId9mA2LqONQ96HmtcMbUxjwMwspgYjfT/COK0t7hOHG/vpf3mpR/B/8DOcPX7Mij8GjPZGPGM3iScovGXAywfGz3x05spFgkiCwR+3HRHow/5jkCjHPwRkokuDLwZWikhP5I4oOaP4YwwLXu2Dce2Pt6jJ7lwhg4BwK0nz9CpsSTSl1c2RSCTp1H3QwvHqc9Gqrf2HiGnGLVWTwFft22B62Qxj4I1+z+gHI9q5gPW8y9LQ3OmNBmhVeFCfRqFXT5qZL8MPkbHiQl6fJ4xO6updi+dufkDXZqYBz3VPYZ/5RCfEJuAQ/cESEPabbuZZgOVeVC0HDY11UYFS4FRXDZ66EcWBbqosXMLj2HI7oSAQnsI74KHMDrAgfYPfilzXD6B6uJh0n+V0UhDmLOYZgC8gLmf56+ZAe7lnthuc/wP1NeVpBXPyjmeG/5raKVDkY5dy0rL49DOlDcXxhkmjvUZ/1unqQPZh0/SK20WWMCnx1D037GBl1c8E0MWuW/RV8mPqBTJVcIjTS5HrMaEFzZiXoZj0+VzCWsA+9bOF0maSSbjl+gp9BgmujskLLDStntIrMIkpkLKbgbd5vCCkkS2vr3r+/vBSw+A2NyPPnEUvuRsUz1B9jgp8eYAIsgTLH18Vcya63bTHIOlQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 and 2", 
		"option_b": "2 and 4", 
		"option_c": "1 and 3", 
		"option_d": "All four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010129", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fLYK3szIRhIl+dzVR9smLOpuX2+EYdm6Ab+YKeficXPo19x93Jw+zyhEJUPZx4lLx8tdMrdPEAyjK4ZsDTYO5iz2CFMwX2dTawRGR8kXHln3IWoZD72CapR+Y5klwfl5VrrcEvfNyR1r+dqEyrxhKK2TutCo9tH1OcsY6Y50KSpZYE9/GD4nv29ebq2vDS454fdQcSrIt+b1f8mqcG9jl4X8m5bRYLwezfY1v+YCmtI045/MLu2WdVyNZgcGgm519PkcNGcMl+14rtsCtwPMJnBTyppkAAyJI8Vw6SZrK/1Wak4Vs7NXIuaYN4sRE7nQG0J0M+l2qSVWxeksB/9tVZhhBiaWpNmXj0kX+MiXOKctPi6Y/qgKjxsrwj8aw1O0SDIQOaQVTNpk77bBzjEE/UpP3JKg==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz5Q7ltdLaeTtu7JQKX7mVx9Tcsd4=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH13gz4441gQhLzy/jrdW3CDG9Rt3eGEpBhfjHqR+fvb//tidoxE1SAnhto5nfSpqj1+UdPhrsb6oGNYicAastCycKal+3khHhPN8NBnsBm7J9fevtV3imlNMTXIfBr2i6GNUr9Jy21ATBHgT+Wg3IWp5aptTS0WNslgAYrhZN94PQyANmy2LqAqESrxg2M02yfCLx3UUCRsI6UqXGVroU9sY29vTPV8eDF2LiesOoDaxsSrJJ+d16xkqYduCMrEcG6ax1Z4+HTdRTeITy2NQBd8Nij1Xtky40nUXB0/xFJlY0WY9MzwpDh/A5yDcRkEja+43RMxpp5S1uqNv2233ykzVQtZkYlWYRAvT8m4QedOxRqjWTcXyFQmIwr898Wmxcjc25NmXKgsjeEgmqcPJLt78DYgOH9r6ojv+MTIUiTdU/MV5kZaLbOMyd72amYArRONpxzVw/nL8Zu9DjqYIKD0HkA39YuPDunxCKWkMLmeWS0t9Ldi917G6w8OO3LxMqloxzOcmPxM3SeZ9n9VRGwTHP1wwF2shxlxydQ4HvcGoZ48CNNn3C0CUxhni71YTzs1opU45HObJowx/Dh2DwE2P1r35L51xIuVQG4mT9us5aMD1VcjUTEF8AG1gAiFfQCG5vB/X6TkTbfTTwMP8P/GbyS0SkI1eWxi214spUAQZ/OIBDQj54v2hi/Tb12TX7qrYi1ff0bDiQ/8754yeKv98O1NfqwPyUpfQ+kTaMZ/pRffA5+XUvcCyAPY7e8U903VaBL3XDZ1wlHUz9BBEzJu6kGHQW+p8vbfmLbcbRcHgzrbrIXGsLhDkjJdfmwzCLGAbqS1UawWwQtSzaUNL1WpRP4e5iyMxymn2wk/cT2MUNSRoZXPWf0dXj5oqqCBRJ6cyUuLcptb1fcXxU21DHRZ8pmmbISflqJQwwLKBQOrcs5QPE3c+uy", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "only Three", 
		"option_b": "Only Two", 
		"option_c": "Only One", 
		"option_d": "None of the Above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010130", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUwXh/8wOnsdXzZF2pRt3eGEq1hfXPmRufNaK3byIVlLxyNjEJosmLOpryw41IEiuhP5s6cfy8Tco57zZCI2aT41nNIJ4ZFiI9n6p5faPxFjA64eo7nLsJg/mKBKUDkdHn9RDA01HyWpGlbqoaptSi9FP820gE61oN59Nt8KNjf2qee+EG9kgPC3XXRR69mGEDDicCU5WrS4K89p86YoyububS52tmdsIZTXgZ7lsg/VV6ygrtJtWp4EYj0SlwLorKFMwHRLgGKDkAw+NnwljkphsJpHSkXul8Q2tRqbOlFmLLxrDskOt8qWHP64wRkidQoE0TFJujh7GbY7mI3fHkjJYVr/Dk9pE+aJ1hylXyVQisRhIFi7MNZlBZmPWxPjmTlgSuHmSWCfYfg44X42qpj9hMvBc3AKsQbKZftwiGN", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz5RH48oBirVPQAbpQlL/cnFnlAasbQw==", 
		"explanation": "25i9epLmwwCqusUBEkaqn73SMHnTFnAI42uCWaZnMHDzRLXNduTzyIN0K0XJ1QM713fUt62w81IWnOhP5s6cfy8Tco57zZCI2aT41nNIJ4ZFiI9n6p5faPxFjA64epTvKPd9jmeTZ0b/dSu4B2RImg3YvHlYvZD7uGeZFIlhlUdnzMdM5cEvfN6MmaGd60KqlAOByDunTbNxAhSNtMWt+AOdsJIqutWEvDPP8fjg2qqBpZ4uYxpGt8Z7YkKv17wGuCk3XNi4bQZOse3EchTiMiqqM04c68T22HAp0oosHVoh+lMGjIxCIpMlg8qx/DYxJt5WGw+0jkVS1NQxHzTWIuXviijJ4UcsNW4qbo9+/CwlsR2TMF1zm3+ZQDURwtg8vvUYhxBrPWtBhWWgljDLg2qCbJ/m/4W8hOawr6th+7dnKFOPIFLcFpkUYPPzMmky/uGSHuZVIN9kGDD0ONY6wDfFLryBzzAZ1ctgYjfDtH7VwZ6nbDzg87jsnt1iEa1AItDO7Nj3sUzXcyz5KHCScs74QEikAy+rgVs89z0k2jUYqGbZEZoztSIf3n+yRlFw0naxNTyEl6xI4sKXeo8jwLmsyT1Qm/t1j5fywBh8Rgr7gm1Bu5DfTk5A2FrSXtkPwUkdGbpBIJ7Y4S2fhjbTRG4fes3iPaa7zR9HlqPlhmQ9vJ8cR4mNOBXCytMn3BS5BPk5RWbkupW5PO4QUFgixrxcz/+iotiiNb7kDSVyNya5dO5L4NUcKCE7R1OKOSpldainQpgMAa0P9jWe21QbFSoQRxjBf4VBAerPCKN5g05qO/A=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only One", 
		"option_b": "Only Three", 
		"option_c": "Only One", 
		"option_d": "Only Two", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010131", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9geAvizOn6JyvZECIVqmyXW61zZXjwXKLGLuvsxpoxKEiBiEk74nrHraDk5BMNluhZ7IeRd2IXdo4vxNGb0OHk0DFRP8dKn5Qy7ZRfaPxFjC6ieNXJYO133XqFKnn+WzePAXFnmz+MykheoZD7/DT7Vt80wQAhk8dS+Ng1KNKNmaGAqEC5ggPCzGmYRbx2GFiA9cGuq0qfpc54osWEsjqb9fj1le/AsNcfIhxd/4d8YE6xgqQI7C94XMembVJG8PfDIUDlISbjKBoV/NmjxnhoyIc9TiupQCsUp2IMZZBwn7lASbh6", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHSwgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/IXnFBi5RoWqXErd8dTHRUabRYeO+wIQxIV2Fnl45VDJZzHDmTX5NpZ+694VDFw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHSwgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/NmTCEWcStyTDeLZkeWXmRufLfa33x5N0IljJmVN+snrHsaL15EdPn6Ra54uLMCsNPp9nzZCa2Oj21jFSKtVQn40yzJUIeeJF3nHtYNzeYMxrz32PKQXgdTarDXRxkHHfmTxfpoC05zW+V8536gAin5N9/4g1L5eR1rzT+F+xiweQ1XeICLBlFVHZusjo4kCZ+8IxoY2EonLatPP4ibjU+d8FdkhfvoJ6I1azhLwF4Wo3V4i8cRZZ/uPVbxTsLizjLwsR8N7ull191cIlXHsz8V9Vi5lTIslglpzxuXIkMI1+HTb6okdD0plpUxaCfbK2kGfioFI+Zjoqa44tszk9pB3cLVh7l26SWD8RkJV5994e1Q13bi9Gk2TtgyuCj2vDPJ3s/8D1hu2yHKFP4epXK1EMIc4i6C+4pg==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both the Assertion and the Reason are true, and the Reason is the correct explanation for the Assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the Assertion and the Reason are true, but the Reason is not the correct explanation for the Assertion", 
		"option_c": "The Assertion is true, but the Reason is false", 
		"option_d": "Both the Assertion and the Reason are false", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010132", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fLYK3szIRhIl+dzVR9slPHsbH4sEBPgalP/JyefGIQf59qxNyAw+Gt+H99PZcKroh3pJQeaOFSzTHtZ9XPJfJix3qFZ0r2Jxy8FmR81DjFymhercOI4CmHWoh59B031qp34sZ8NNaMmamdqEysiwmRzHOUWrgkA12avY6h5QOTuJs/sMOxv2GVwPz82tXc/9BMcUhVrYdpak+9g6EG9is0EdihZB4L+PeQc1H+MCetNAcf9c6j0Ht7hqcoT308swwGlopSZ9NP2MyqiDo1f+BlGj36qlcA05x5HxSae669w3yk41AzcGk/bIth/C86pRbcPFs+jmOZDB9Emrxlwt4xmhMjcG5OhTbvhH+fiGDPb4fi/4XxgObks/lk+7UiJwGBN1POU80dd7aAJGhg2OyYGfkenL2+e6pGDfnFgA7VsJFxGg==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz/hfvtS2FTyUlprVQrGbvBLFVS5w=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH90A3/5YQsEg3z0fjzOWLEBiIepT+mU7FgeDHqR+fWZui++oJ/ZxHJuVNy4TbVt6Tk8l4Kgbwb4J3fWSwAcZl9zdOdl8H21mVJdNUElY5+/doRfeBV3jyhNMfaNPtiwmeUIgX5dHmpDHU0uT7ZhDxXpof7p3TjGINnkFU/n4t9/og9K9aGmamd7A2qgxCN0G2YRrokEEaWoMCsq2adspYwicOxvwbT8bTUlffdsNYKcUhTscZ+d1azhLgB/Tg9Edq9axoL+OqQbkz0Jy2tZ0NdzcPqxTR60oM9WGQx+gsGi5AWa85w2Yr2uTEkf/liEHOXrEtOh5x9TFeXNKu9wnGk9F02ezoqcYdirz09pB2ZZBR1lGSLQmxQh8Bq8JAcjQtwbWdFjnOswiiDiWaHPJrwq47zkajiqbprsqopaU6YLFvdWM0Td/PBKX4yxf2TCLQcNpNiGifoKZUH6H7qYIWbny0F2ddgO3/m4GqQho32OGv9p9Lqm8RmG60UdtnQ5Mq58FDOZyahLm/TZ8XtGQP5QXi43AgloB0k3CkV+l7WNIdL/ShNs3G/RwN30iDybWqogr9I442AfoJxw+Dg0XIZi7Rqmojn2xMvTga3iD9FvZbfal1d2VyRDY0TzQ0rH/RMVKLZ+37WhmLRX3kAesDiQaGUgy9HyPH0jXU9i5gLFYucLQ/Snt8ywRi/APE5RXLhpMb/L/MYSnAk//JcxeKv98OoNfLkP2wtYROxUOxY/YERbgN4BQTPRS1BILuvQ44XT+cPxn3P1xNBQ3paRVXCu40JTxCilsr0YF7WZvExARHsI7oWU9rwSwfMOf66zSPdRryZmUKtS00kQnqfLrQUpRP/Opj6IVOAhmYktIHROlhIBJADPTP2eW63seOKGEYzcS8qOphCeVOVfxgh1BPMKPcngrUCeQw+AY2mC0Qe2lFOkTqSK1lXpEReVrbtVFsiar1NKUkVjSe5EK4aSFzMlDUHzkKUx2LfPPQLBUEmaWGVgF7l19Jyl/qpr4GOBJTrPv0V3ZlDPL5eBJnaEEgZieek7OTsFH8tD2x7bvrHWvuRpEC2FsDx4vDPyx7lt/u+r7ZiOqjqoVaYjx10", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only One", 
		"option_b": "Only Two", 
		"option_c": "Only Three", 
		"option_d": "All four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010133", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUwXh/8wOnsdWLeQ04YsGvDe+NjeWXrFLPKa+TsiZZhN06GlVJ282LD46Tm8kEOiK0b7YeMZCMNfY4vzsKG2qTjzHQBANNK2ol8pLYWb+AA5RT3SNrnLtJn3XrADgW4VzW8CnVgh3iWnXVCoMOX/DSvFPMegF0Thpdq4tA1MdaL3Oiy/kiqhwGHnF+YW6llH1ec9ci65E7ctIo99f6Yv3LS+rT0k/Tf+dEFIgVbs4NsKhmGLIsJ7MJO6O/im9eXSjHN", 
		"answer": "25i9epLmwwCnpNNgXxf+yfTwOyvdCm4UsDPDZKZ6ZWKuAvCCY+TyxZ5+KRyEhFd+4TqGhqTi41tC1vsb5IeTfCsMcMtiwdyMxKi36XBTIIsVztIy6ZMTcP1Pwn2gfdjeM7wZOrVMjzuRpfIusGie7YVh", 
		"explanation": "25i9epLmwwCqusUDEk2kn73SMHnTFnAI7z+XWqY0c33sR6LReq3uxZZ/IkjJmVQ75n7D45bl+R9Phrsb6oGNYicAaod2iN2Iw+f/wXUBJM9QksAhstoSdfhMxTKjNNnSLPt9jlqILlawYzCuEHF6lzSWg28WqY379DerRtUvyRgzgo5344gzOpeWzbvT6Vu9lAeF2TuVQa5wEFqasI6u+UyR4JYwsI2+pDzn+sj3rP3d5c1LL0h2/9AoORuKkqYc62oxQoigYBcL4uHTblrpYDivJgAY7YvlxHtkhpYhWCkH4REGg41SIslnxdjlqjciPspvVTezsFBByZd5Hx6FNLyowHrr+FwydG4uaZMt6np1rAaQJF1xlCuRRSBUh8Bf9tULkAJsb2oM3H/0wjaYwGaAboHm6JTwnKj9oa1g+qYjaVaJIVSYEalcM+SHG2lOxMyaH7JUc9InNmK/bo9u2TjrNJ7U1ipNxNElb2Pv/Tid0t35OGu/p9L/nNt7VKsIM5H2/MX78F3JZWPoNW7TZ93xSwn3Sjz82h1xthYmzWEZ+yLZCoZq4W1UzT69QEhomyjuLHGomrtPpsKNcIM83PvgxHICnfJ9jYny0F0oSES6nj8S8qWMW05Aw1vbF84GyEkbAr0VVN7wxyTWvXPeSHlBP8fiQaGUgy9HyPH0jXVxptADVJiNJBzfyskv3B/xRtw5DDSqlIjFM9EUGHdst/JTirz15ZD7WPK2PylqexKyGelW5odFYEJrHQrTADAPZqqhW90KSeUP4WDE20dARmwJBFSM+r4NTwWtr4TMZ3nKYr8fC17tZfMEA97qQV/GOPC9zTzQRu7IxwezVkgpRzWTYb0E6QLjOorgKx7zh2BhufLwPBFvTIYFOSH8Zm715aqXSw8pPy8qOphCeVPZUlAplSrAL/xjzbAJZBBtBornSARE0VPhTGYd3EVOCu8+dBeqp2qp", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Mercury,36 million miles", 
		"option_b": "Venus,67 million miles", 
		"option_c": "Earth,93 million miles", 
		"option_d": "Mars,142 million miles", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010134", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRgmyQV7FgeX7tFKbMaq3MzJZiKFLTsVVH/FfVsKDi41oAgfIb3YaaMDAMaop7wd+Hl+vxhGVJNoZhm5Jm7NoQcrRJ2C7tdczSM75tz3uTIlawYzikRHF6kHHYg3tevL+1xyK6R9U5mlUGno5rrcEvfNWa2qmG+0j4kg6HnF6QWqlsUVeWuN6k7leZs8I3u8jNtyfX+LTrlezS5NcEbEhTr5ZtbEO1mqkd/SYhEc2ibQBSsbaEIVziNTqwa04c9cfswX1nwcItVG8y8Q1DjJcWcsFhwoukszRwK8VvVSO2okpF09RoUFeTbK29wmHh7lY6NWk+a4ZkuyUh4Q6SLBR6m3mXQilCh7xlwt4unQ1gdS9Pmjb0ijrLhmqDcJz04o77xeHj4Lps4LEiKlXfd7ffYR5yvW4SMLBFeONzFKM=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt6QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRt3eGEpFxcWLsWufDfOi+3YVkIhDJjFV/smLOpuXC8lIcgKYb4J3fZCoGPohg2sKM1PC3wWlRP8dKm5R765RfevtSjCmlcZT6M+1r3HqJKEuy0DJbs/RkNlvw07uDpMTPqg==", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gZhb3he/wIWrECm0f43CFErd8dTHGVbXWZq3xx9d4M0/JjENy4TbForDj8kBPi6lCqY+RdGINd4xn3OyH6+rDzHhSc89X2pRg8Z9fSPxFjC+iYNXPKfFgjmGGZ1H4YnmYBWJgnHHZhDxfvJD79D+yR5o+01UmnoI4/do1MdaNwOiB7UyriQjCy37RTaV0FEaQsMCr7gOd4IEhtsGI8T3dtPD4g7jS/tpLbAFVt5I/bFX8sqkb7CIEX/qxaQFE/76QVVzkM2iqNE4f/Mjiw2dshpYhWCkR9Q1SisNVbc1j2p3wuSFwMMNvVTWvr0gA1ZtoXgOfe7P40Xj08lonfHcqcY9hpW0wtwqOMRQsziuUQzlDh8wr/9wVmhNqc2gAmH/mhDqZhWubPIPi+ZTvxef24K1r9+M3JUCOMEiYQoJcYKvQInV7z+eYCOZPJpFrHiXuKZUv8j25JJeG1DcIw8ocIUvpwCKQgY38KiW7v4H2zsBkAbpAE9DX/cP3s1PKcS/kNXiAJsT6XEj2WnD0kxxqoxkxwS4eqGPIGJtw7SQAn2q1RV0klzHlfmXhxOoc4o2bbZ1x5/3lznICl+B5i5L42l09Swi0mmwDto2ZSVldyFrCXsoCyw48DaQJHZXQ/i2amnXRX3UCcd22FafHziNe36P4gHVy/5EAUcyBOQ2bhdhm2wK/DfR+XXOh6JLxOO4QCH1s+bNk2eSvsIqvffbkL3wpYx/3VukZ95RIKAN1FUvTDCNHdPoXP9MORjChENLxuX62NAVk", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the Assertion and the Reason are true, and the Reason is the correct explanation for the Assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the Assertion and the Reason are true, but the Reason is not the correct explanation for the Assertion", 
		"option_c": "The Assertion is true, but the Reason is false", 
		"option_d": "Both the Assertion and the Reason are false", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010135", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fLYK3szIRhIl+dzU90slPHsbH4sEBPna1N5oKKZCsMcMtu2t+c2eC30HlEc/VRlNpO6qYRLbp0xDjtUdXJNPYu3GuWKEnmYir9BWJ7gT/SymhercOI4Cn7XdR3wVUxn5V7+MQ9LpeQy6qa/HG21Ei21H7Rbbx2BVzepo67+0aZpMI8oN+EvzWb/eDq2urW5tEHdxxbsIg/YkmzgqYNuD4wVIiHfRwL+PeQMAy4YCWqKwsOudvmxDR6w4EmU20I+kwIrY1TIsN824jouSY1f99vAzy2tlBJyJo8UBHWYLW9kE3l8kE3NXs5ap9juG0hqQrcG0Fw2n+dRylC1IVz/9MNmR0jLjkV3HLhmyy3jjHBXZ2j7pjol+mwpLh6sqo0aUCEMVncFpkTJafIIidxy+WeA6JdId9iASf0JJUo8yzrYI+R3isekM0vb3bk9yWMnNm1P2qo84bxi5RTFa0UPpbWqdmyplPLdDfoLnPTcsr/UAb3D33owxxqrxEoyTUV5HuYW98qp3hNmn+pWnhqrinIY2vhm79S88KBec4l2/CsziYRjPF1mpXjx107ThK+gz9CsIuJShxO31GWHcIV1gwtGOtDVaaSTRUdllAONOcHtB1AMA==", 
		"answer": "2+f4aZ/3kU2ou//Q2AbZiGVbdoMovrUDhg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHW0Av+/8UyVwj9yev6JivREW0ErXvDRqtxMEL2WufLYK3/iZR4NV+cgVppsnnUoazktx5Pu6BS+s6MZCMXe4ZqxsTJ3ve3zX9CPNRWn4NmpL8ebuBIiy7te8bZKeoux33AKUrkJzq0FnNhmDDEyn5DvMO++SuyRM4+wxQ+qolE4/w0OZe62LqH4AqrxhWS2X6VCLlxA12Xso6h/1DcsocuusGYpTvU+rT4iPfG/tpLdgBX/7VqbRu1hOhYoH94XMG4bQEL4eHCIUfoIyetI05Quf/r32cp1ZYoSWw58RFSwopFIsN8xIrhvyZwHs5pGiG+qkpHh4BzHwOecf2o0Xrl50c+ZXJnJZ5luW0QoB2IIBRzlX2ZX2xQgMBqvsMJkAFnPWBG3Ce413+GiWmKb9Pz7pK8lu3zr7dnsqcyO0iOMhzRQp5cd7bWKGtn3uCUA5pSD5FIGSemPtoj7DX8NJPUzTwb39U1O37o+mqWlI3hMWD6lpPrmtw2Fa0PI9/Bqd+/tRz0dC2hNXyYY9i0XBDxTGj0yk424U1lzCAJ+yKVSL13/D5NjWqxXUFplyn0LHWy1rdS6Y2cbYsyx7XY1TdQiPVqnpzl1Q00BxeriHxKtI2aXBxbxVXCXsIJwUktA7kRGJPF9y2EkGDfR2kZdsH4QamE1zlJ1u/oznV8tJUdFY2MIwzPyo1wnUXkQfl4THSh6Ij2KbwQEmUv7r5oir734va1Sf2FIiUvdw6lWK9d8owRYRE7EA/ZACAPdLfuQpUbAeNO3nDEkwZaB3pfAEjVu64HSBbqs8HJfHmed75cDx3hbKYLB47+QVWPIfmsiBXIFKuU0lT+TUEzQTaINbkC60fke4f7KhTzknh06879O1xaUIYbJWegIj7r8OOHCh8pP2FlHIJOaQfGXxEwkTPGKe0nhLRAcxc/U62kDRAinhQPnjrWB0xMv0IfU+X9EgZnLqhcMxsByCX1CKUeTlzDlXoLjVWT1yz4LP4LN0YxO2aKz03kn5tomL/ojM6EEsDwLP0f05RDLaBeVoOWGVQJiLP96uDyAiB5DWN4OfaIX/GRsQ/aB8nk4vrfxE4JKYAtKW4jzuxvWDfnWMKAQQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 and 4", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3", 
		"option_c": "2 and 4", 
		"option_d": "2 and 3", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010136", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhb/+4FgWh/i1fjxdWLWQ0cQsWuLFbA0cWnqR+fVa//7iYd0NUyMg19y8WPKorew41xPm6BeqZ6TcSwGPoRpiNmdxKT41nNIJ4ZFiI9n6p5faPxFjA64eouZ4rDE975kR6lD6pPkuU+0PA==", 
		"answer": "25S0ZNHh1B7j+IszEgn90PH7dWPRFWdRpm6WU680fHTtU7PKfa3xz9d1JkXJjFV/snjPpK3kt0cHnadO7oaQZTZDaoNqiMmM1va1s2s0A4kyknaaIHcqxaLmIA==", 
		"explanation": "25y+KIX71FnP9pc0WlnhhfznPHiQFGcDpj+TV7FkdX/nXaTXYuzsiYN+Z0iBiBtr/nfIpuX/8RMGm7sb5pydeTZDf5lg3d6Nl/D/wTFyJsgI2pR64YgaPONP2TGpNNbeYPBhjm+YLkT8Jy20CGQ0tSKWizxErZCu+TP3FNs7zFUgk4Bx4sYvfNiRmY2S+lmwxhGNyXeVCLh8AVGLvMum6EbcpZMttMHNvTfV8+Dxibjc9p4PYxESvoh7I1W1kKAduD4wQ8ehbxpE5PCQdVzoYDGmJhxdzcPmxHEp0Y08UW109hoGjIwWdMFh35nwtT0+f8RkVSC1r0VSh51yTBiadamx32akqEYweXs5JZhsuCQ0tQaTJhRsn2iZRTpUkMkr/NEKkAAjcmEAkHf0iyuehGDDPJLt78DojeHj4K5s568jaUyFNFKYQoUdcfPUL2Jgz6mMArNQN99lEmLoMpU9+TjqL5iHnzgekM4lb3zp+z3ZhsXwNCWuvJb4l+h4KLEpOJHK/Nn3s0nVcybvNT2BY8r4UBzpAzzs2wsltgAsyS1Q/GvUHMl4/DsIjT6iQFdh0jPvLGqghKdV5IXOfoA23/D/nT0W2OdtkZf+0xUoBwWvzXtKtIKaXVlB2RTCF8AC10khCvQVHJOR62iXhzqQR3kMe8f4BuiTzGxb3+LigW9u/5EAUcyYLQvSi8ovxxmiQfR3FWPsscb1OPISHmxszbtlwuK0o4qvffq3bHEjYw77GftR/IZUKBR6AwLcES1AbqvuQZILTeQP3Hre1wJQTmxdSRrA/qkMVAqt6tDHLmuebqQfBl7vbKEAU9v2R0HAJ/zpyzzAC76IkAe/UUBlQjOaKaQE6wCweYP8IBqnmmdq6oHkMUNUV5BXKC/2NE64t7eLSTv4gxNUovnS9yY41ZV1ivA=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "The North Pole would have six months of continuous darkness", 
		"option_b": "All regions would have equal lengths of day and night throughout the year", 
		"option_c": "The Arctic Circle would have continuous daylight during mid-summer", 
		"option_d": "There would still be different seasons but of equal length", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010137", 
		"question": "25SsKIb70A2q9osnXhuyzO6/EGrCF2pWsD+CSqpnMHjtV6vLYOj6iYN+Z0iBiBtr/nfIpuX/8RMbh60b7I2TeTIXd4gwigIRskKeUEoTthQpFm51TDc=", 
		"answer": "2+frPUGxR9Hr5HODfNiDlUaLcHTu9w==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHyyRD5t4omEgr6wL3aNHnECyIYsD+KXKB4eX/mUOfWYa3qwZIxN1CIg147/XCGt631t1YMg6FL/YecMCMXPophiNGH0OjyhH5Hc5QXz8B24Z0NefFTgH2je8Cbdqg6jmqFIFf1Yir9MHh9h3HCg3BC6IqotTW+R8o4zgY7lIt9rc4zLpeL0a3T+0i5lQmMzzueRv1BEEaNvfKm102oqId4sM6BuCLP/fe5ivTS/ttLaxsSq456I0uwlqYMuCU+Ee21egZDtveQbkbvKTzjJhwS7MXnlmBhw8IaSGd03QsGi5AWY8xg2djwtDdwL8FrGzb6qkoA0Jx1XB/WYLW9kEXr71t4Zjokd4hkqG00swCJJlA+v2qOWCQRmIlu7ZAtnQEjaWZMiDbvhH+ugXebdNTwq4HkjPuwqaoj/KwzaUKPO0/MV4MIJZrUZ2R6y+ecCLUcPIliBWLyNNgrsHnuKYKcnzhNwNwyJnjjtCWf0sz3NnCu88aowoQmRP8ZM9DX+oufv0vCdybzbT2Hbs60Wh3iXXn2x05xvhQxiC4WqDCLXcl78Cofm3ujCUxlgWfiaXmv1qxZ5oOadpg03+ysziYRmvh93534xl0oTwH7nX5QpsSZSksPwF3aEsQIykk3CbUTB6rfzmOinXOQSnIKc8u2Dq7HlXocmuf0iXN4uoNOXJ/OOBHeyt8ozxu0Qf98QXDorYi5KfQQSkEt6KZ5jf7httKyZrOlImFqexKyGf9c4YVUZgZyEh7RBDYPdLfuQpUbAfBD03vP1whOB2tBABrJ+KQBTRCjqYT8ZmPNI7ASCRLnI7oWU835QkvKMbG9wDWJCb2QnFarVlA8DjWbYaQF4Ef1eYD7NAe6kChQ8cSlPVNXTZICNTPqNGS/5beLDkY/fCAsOJ5OeQfcWFAqmyqDM/FizbQBfR1tQLvnDVgT1gVGkyqSAV4FlU0MS63qUxMmMqBWYp6OIXMJY2oEVee0R4ku43k=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "665°", 
		"option_b": "235°", 
		"option_c": "90°", 
		"option_d": "45°", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010138", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDbOLr3ddlL1nJnlRu5n7Dsauw/1YChrtL4YuNdWIKbctpydya0rvLylAIc/FMn44y7Y5fdecA3yigedHJYPdgjnqIIgX+aCupDHVmmnHej3Ffu5Oz8DW+GJo+1FU7hcdv5MYoOcXf0KbT/EW9xhWNyW+ZTa9qUVycuMe7+0uZsocEu+/E8RPPtODxn7jg/8sfakhisIp6Lxuon60b/WovWMS4KBBOsffZeRTgLya3Lx1d9s2j1Xtn0osnSGYh519Cg5paa8d7wtjtsnIjKsBnECGGrWcJh6B0WleVe7O82Xzt71ssNXMlJZ5luW0mrhqIIFFslCuUSSFYh5Bj+8Ic1QVxeC9B3HvpkC2EkiWGcZLk7sDzg6jkqLZw9+MuJwGUPVmYWIIOcbvFNWkywuyWBLVMO5p1Eh7oGZxu0TD9bYWB0jQIwpkhOzfz/C/ZvMLnLW36g531i5R1G7YONdjB7Nj3p1XTaWPsKHnedd75VA3iD33skxptslgWxzQE4CLoB4V6t30khIfHYstRSfOOFm4diAA=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz3hfvtQQBK6FoVpzvW6f7i+bSuw8=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHg1Bj5+IszEhf8hen3MCvDDHcFq3qRXON8dXzqR7fKa//7iZZjIhyGnUt04X/SpuXk+BMbh60b+oueYy0NbctmxpCd3+G3yn5TJ85BiI4y7J8SdedQxDi/cZTvKPd9jmeTZ0f1ZDioF3U0gDnTyllXupezsjT7VcI+01U7hcds5MQoOdPTmamd7A2sjgPC73SEXLVhA1rZncul4lCMqIcqsI2EonLP/fjtn/yT8ckKe0hUrYlyI0+0kug67SR4Vd2mYRxMsfDYZBTjLzq3LwsP94vr03lg1ZIhWHsxswwGkZZbb8Vh6pbYsgE/c419HTa0401Uh51vHwSDebC9wijt7hUrfX9ra4V/qCUwswHcIFFzk3iMRClDkcwr98RZnBcjamZOiHPywjaFwHGHedPw5JXoje3irvlr964uOlGIME7dFqwIJafIIidBxfyPBeZsPJNiW2LyNdA8+XnuKZqYnzsIkMopNzfq+ySNmt61NmP6sJ33mt14AbAVJZHB6NK7uVvPdWPoLz2Ac8b5XBq8D3321052vgBlxS4e/GrLSIZ5tS4CkGq5R1FrhzSgaH2znbBZ+ZHOdoBxxPziyTcC2MBwmtv02xM4ThCygnFQ8o2RD0hHyBTFEdgTzAw8AvQJEZvY4X2ekGTVC30feo73QaWO0T5HyKP4g2B6utABU8yaJBbIj54vxlelCfg5W2j/vI78L/JVAmEh86Fhwuizsva1Sf2QJGA4ahy4S+oVs4FZbUJ0HwfERTdbYayrW5gQVaBb2nTe1w5bB3lICUnJu6EbHUyO44TlZ26TcKQRAxvwI7IRU9rwSwfhOuO9wHD5CbOZ1UOxWldlQDWJYbMC7Anzc4j3ZAS6h2Ak9Mjhf0JOSY4SLmfyYCutrabDOAkvayRlGIVLfwf4QhRphyvOKvx1zaYUMAwlROiJFkICnlF/kDLXTlFW8E0MULCjRBMNP6dAYAlAgXeiGakTWVzHjz5HnUORzyf+aftfcV0rfiSggFn0k9JWkPPswoeSStXwIqgV1s0nLbVeSZjTDRtOy7H8Mkk8jERSBG51iKUa1sp9", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only Two", 
		"option_b": "All four", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "Only One", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010139", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sU0Vwz/1sHxGWLDFyJA42iKRqs0XHjwQOeQLAMFYnwJQL7FxhVc5ZU9/ug=", 
		"answer": "25i5eprgkQ3i8sUuXQzmzfjtO2bfEHZRs3CKXLc0Z3nmRqKCeuX7iYRkKRyInUt+82TV46H55VYMm6RCqYGJdTALe4priNScxe35wzFVO8MEg4Vz9tpSPMBSwy2kd5TUJr5Nz2CDIle8Jxj9FHhxmj7bj3JZpsOs/SKpUZo2zBlyhoZq+dt8M9HfzaCWqFq3lAqGnHOQXrgkFEWMtMLo70KFs8I5u8nNvzvc/ODq2rWT1c8eawZdp8o/T1S/lrwM/Go5RYjiPlweIdeQdlzoMi3jIw8P8sXmxWcpyoM6SXp08hBUwtUWb899wpD3/DM+O41uFCq2qkNI09R1TFeVe7Os2Wbx70AsNXwkd8p5tCh1swqRKV1wk2WbDCRQmIYr8dZZgQxmPXZFnWSgz3+qjnGObpD34oO8puHio7VmvuMTIUTAJlPNQoUZd73NKHRmivmUBKhIc4hvEjDjfcEm+XnqNZjU3ikd1dgyPDfj/Tickdn5ICW1pZfrhtF3EP8EI8PM58z3pFTCITrkIG/TK4vASwfgRn+43AgllBk12igT53DWSlLzpO6JoJhEMR+yvIPbJUY=", 
		"explanation": "25CpfZj93gGqv6dpCF7Gzfi/IW7CDiIt4VqSR6p6f2nfFufLfa36zIV4MVmNzV1p/XuGj6Tk/l1Dz6Ve6ICWfiVDOY5+3dGFl+r+w3lVdIZgj5J76p1fffoAySy4fdrUOLIu2maFZ1blaXm0FzBwnSPTiWhascO04yKpXN82xFUmnoI46NkpPcOQy+TT5UyzjwiFnH+QUf1lH1DZu8ev41fcrIc2stmFonLa5OTrleDa/d8fZwRL/4Nudlqw16kF9Go3R82mKAZD9KTHbkbhJGiXLwcOucTg1WF71cI9SmA38V9HwppTY9I/loz9rDszPsFmDHO7sUtVyZA8chaEd7X4gjmk4Vs7NUkudZ5osS8ws0/OeWhwpmW9QjhQhoN/99NZtg1xfmNF3D7Dy2XLs2ybaZL37oS8hPywoalz4Kw/IEyBIVnUT81KM+YQFCd+y/2SGbNYNtMnAyrjffQg6DjrI4Kd3Hku2csjI3Kn8TKJl9/8PGu5toG5jdt4ELYUP97L+oukuVHObSLzYWmcJt/8XEjRXX/s2g0llBE3yy0VqGDNHMl2+20ZlnvwWktxhi/lfnLhnrtR45Ged4sj1rXY1TcCnbRxjNv02xMoTgqugmpQ8oCeXVdByEfFXssI1kkvDrsUANbC+3XWmHneX3QeP8/4BeiEzCJc0+3kgXRu/5QPTICHKxHPytgp2lelCfg5R2LgqY/3NPISSmwt9rQxxevho8K+NeqhLXcWYSa5bf1W45xSKA19USjcCydKcvjmd9REAcxA0XTekgMIRmsJBErc6acQVAmrvsHEdyqMMOTMIF7uYqcMB9v8SwuPIfmsiATbCa+VlgexWQQGTzSeJKJN6AbicZ+yMBu202Zr69XtN0NVSYwEKGfje2K3seOUAwMoemwxII8HaVLbCxE0hDvCNeonia4SdRs5TbHnFkYThBlKnjqSCk1XuUIZH7GlRRM+L6hXYG8ZxCT1GaEPTBnElXoLnFmJzCasA+9FNAlxKijThELvjJwmnuyploaESv73I7hb3Z9DO6NWSZ/EX0gTluDw5uLlUWo2FC1jJv2IUO3DpEfzEMa0qsbXzE9bwbsaM2M1GTe/m5DJ+TktIKMPTHFar3oao9jcIk6OkNIZ5lllWVnt5wHwTic1vhQzWoHketTfapSjsHNeGCfCRfUDmulsnSXqdcvZYVosCHYhmQKCeJLCwjmKLrzzxb8MSVi235yLcZhi/EF6jtO0g29Buyl8jHPwBTbTcaf54BsUMXNtX7yaCFNQiQQ2lTawylr8KIuvx7EBi6JEmKEb5Ezkty82jk6cSkvccDPu1+SbtHLKpwcu369xVGOiXzNZxgU3BP8o8Wx8U20gW65hsrK1CLTHm2ytK474n95BpVtVVKzDIbr7qd35ZbDQIqjpy8CQIH7y5ZpqAbWpKsxFNH7IJC4Qsar8Z5bKLQGWMWKXwrOdAC7MhvLMHKNJrnGXWVduypndcQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "A phenomenon where all parts of the world have equal days and nights,Equinox", 
		"option_b": "Marks the northernmost point where the sun appears directly overhead during the year,Tropic of Cancer", 
		"option_c": "The southernmost point where the sun appears directly overhead during the year,Tropic of Capricorn", 
		"option_d": "Located at 66.5°S where darkness lasts for 6 months and daylight is continuous for the remaining half of the year,Antarctic Circle", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010140", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fBYeP9zIV/LlKOzU9z9zbjorfk/xQcz6lD4I+TMDYKcp8vyd6Nl+3j1zFENcBBmZRhvqYRQPoRhQmlcZTPJexjjlLCFEr8dC20B3VI1nHEj3pTupD74Sj7QNIygAE7m4I4+sA5MpeL0a3TzUyqkg7FzzuQULR3UV2K9d6p+UKQrIc09dmC8TvP57T2iPra5J4KcAdHsYI/d1O515sc9hY2bcbmITZe4+3eZhT5KC3jNAER6t/q1XElhpYhWCkw9QYGi5AWbs990Z33qHI5MY1lGzb6q0FNzodsVxKEcf253myk810wZ24udp4ttSN1tQeZaFtuimSPRThU1Ihu89kKhQxmb2p8kkru0Xa/iGDPXYHg/4n/xcv5srpv9+MiMVGFJ1XdWI4ZdvPDKGlmw+eOArNPc5tmBSnoOMY9vD/2MtaV3TYYxJkzJm+n+SWXhsXmeWS0t9L6gdpiHbEVOcTWqc+2qVDOZiv1YXucdIvgUQ2wXXn10gdrvhYiiCkR5GSYB48/4SUI3me1SFZYnBvuODWWn6pU44zOa4Y0k9T+3iYZm7Rblon02BhwBxCziD9Qp4rfXVVcyEeWG9UEwRk6BbsPFZrd6y2enHHYC3UDP9r+BOiUyDUI3vbjh296/4QGUMydJBbJnp413Rq8BO9FW1vjgInuffEUBH1s9bQx3uWk99mvdOehIWAkewn3XuZP9psRaQB0Bw6dBDZKILuhRI8bQvQQkI+We7vU4nDN7OE+K7O8AfQ=", 
		"answer": "2+f4aZ/3kUqoTRikMfo2huO6iLkTw9A3OA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHg3hX544wjV17zxunqNGfcGiIeoHyWQLA0Z3nmWufWZui+7JZjM1TOnht66n/V46zjt14AnLwb/YeTZCcHPp9g39Gb06T41jFAJMdd2oZg65dfaPxFjA64epibLvF6jnmIIkuwbi36FzBklSPXhnBTpMOv+meyQMl3zwcwn5NE4+szLsWa2rzTzFiqjwiFnG+ZTf13HliKocer7g/ctIo99cmMqHLS57T1lfbU9c0fIgFc/4lxZhu0kqUA6zowVNqxKBNF9aTDaVv/NC2wM04U94v33nEpyZYhWHt4tBtDkoZYZsl90djrsnIkN8gqATq2twRPwdRoVxLWUbyqxGCj8xU+bXM4WYROsz8npAyIaGB2nyu9Xi9FnYMr3dkLlghmPWpYjHPyizqFg2CcPJDs5ZT1i/3/taoj9qI1Ik+FJk+YUIIOJbLCKHJmivqSFeZRPJFzHzGmPNsqvDr2LoKd0SwCxcpgK3b++COemtm1P2qo84bxi5RkEbIBP9/M58z3uF3LZ2PuJz2Hbs60QA3xXUD25wZspFgs22EZ5mHXGpt69jlNqXekQU1q0jPoaTyAhL1I44HOXIcj0PnpkXIVjvF235/ixhQyQESvhXoDoYyQXUgP3kHbE8gViEk6BLFBB4PfsmOTg3PCC24EbMvlQb6C0TUI0ur2hiF0sdAaXYnOPxLCyBJIbtGVeEOkTmor26Esj/c=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1,2 and 3", 
		"option_b": "2,3 and 4", 
		"option_c": "2 and 3", 
		"option_d": "1 and 4", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010141", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gZhb3hdztNn/ZACIyqm2AXqY0dWnzUbXLa+P9zIQxJFOHmVJ153nTsOX09kEEga1I+s6ZfzBDf4lg3cTJxO3vhHxOPdJMicBz6p5ff/tO2DSjYdvOM75qz3eMLkL4c3m7C2I0gDnTym5TpYKy+y61U5o/wRk01oh+rdw0OZeG3KmB1EOEiDSH3WieRuckJVyQpo6h+AOepYE5oN6I8SbT8bTYiPvH+d1LQQFAvIp6I1e1krtJ7yMsWcG6KAZD9KTAbljsMmixIgkU9sWjwXxs1IdpSWExtDpHkJdeJdMz14Dtr3I5LI1nGiCu41BJy4B5W1eCe6q5wmyk9F06NUk+a8hmVbnTVf6cXuLzwJMMqSnS", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/NmTCEWcStzPDULZgMGXrUefQa+ztxpkxLk/JhFV4/WTUpqbktflzKV8u2LhkdIqUtrpVGmo=", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gZgznwL3LPW6QInASt3aAEoB9YnLvUefGYejtiZJpN1mbhF518XOGoKr+41oBmqdO+s6bcTAIcI5825CP2Pa3xXNOJtIEiYlqpJcQcuBI332setCbI/Fg2meOMkrldHm5BWl4nTbenjxQp5H74S++FMgyzRQ7mI526og0PduZmaeVqFmwg0ab2XqDdLNYH2actN2n5Rncl4oxucjNuCab/ee5jurG9Z4faglG/5J3Zhudhasd8Sl4csGmax5OsejZZEetKSbjMwYYudvs2nV7hpAsWmA7+lMGlotTItJ214vrsnI2MN8qATu/41RIwppzUhKYe7P42Xuk7lorNW4jZJ4tqCUw4SqdOkB23XjcTTRYh8Bi7ZAUmhd3PXtJkGLlhn+3wnGAa5Lx77y+xfz4pflQ561nPUmFJ1mYZIwIbbbSayd73q6ITaRZMJ5yBCemKd0rvBz4MoKcmCpN0cEpLnun4COVho32OHCptoG5mtxzB7pAJNTC4MS5oxzTbmPjJD2Hb8fgXAywTmv5yk5jpRcoiC4CqHbXH4ht8T5Nina1CXdxnGfmY27hk6ZI74yKeopxw/D+1D0Ui7g4jZ7kwREoTgq8zXZN8oeQQUhGw0HZC95HwAg8B7oEB4WR/X/WkXfJR3UKd9q0PbTYwJ/7X1eauuUae7ytEg==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the Assertion and the Reason are true, and the Reason is the correct explanation for the Assertion", 
		"option_b": "The assertion is correct, but the reason is incorrect", 
		"option_c": "Both the Assertion and the Reason are true, but the Reason is not the correct explanation for the Assertion", 
		"option_d": "Both the Assertion and the Reason are Incorrect", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010142", 
		"question": "24KwbZ+z0Fn+5YQ2VxL31738J2TDEGcC42uLV+NdfmXmRqnDeuTxx5Z9Z3iImV473n/IpuX25VwCz61a+prfZC1DaY583JzJw+zy3TFNPNVB2oEy4JsGPPBVyX25e5TkH8FR8VG/GHrPWAb/JN0UUYpcYK/y4V7K9JCVqg==", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHH2BTvt4EpVBj31/jxNm6SgVYqZ1RODK6nrgfmeK2XeQ==", 
		"explanation": "24KwbZ+z0Fn+5YQ2VxL31738J2TDEGcC42uLV+NdfmXmRqnDeuTxx5Z9Z3iImV473n/IpuX25VwCz61a+prfZC1DaY583JzJw+zy3TFNPNVB2oEy4JsGPPBVyX25e5TPKPsu2meNIgX0bj+7AWJxmjLTyIlopClMej973ttzdLqs80w=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Th,e T,im,e d,if,fe,re,nce", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010143", 
		"question": "26KwbYP2kRD5t7EoV17by+n6J2XRF2serX6PEod1ZHSjeK7Ma6332td9KF+ImV5/simEcqG4WLBSiTmbH1JexZqb7w==", 
		"answer": "2+TgOEHWni6o3MljEUDNnkjxOj4kIAjXPw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3w3v5YshRhf9y/zzdU/RF2dRj3aNV+N9YzHvW6TDeuj6iZZlZ0iBiBt292TPp6zx+RNe1/iLzMGoPGIUdo59zZCd3+G3wHBVNoZHkoF8458MPPZZjDi1ddfPLOcuwWCFZ0HxfnmqDHV61DLEhW9FrYf5tM1b9hgpFsk60aMaBbrbmg==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "180°E/W", 
		"option_b": "prime meridian", 
		"option_c": "meridian 0°", 
		"option_d": "Equator", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010144", 
		"question": "25aqZ4Lg2Bftt5EoV17by+n6J2XRF2serX6PEod1ZHSjeK7Ma63425h8Z0uMnk875nmGpqTj4xMdirtO5ZqMMCsNQbRQ9++26NvI+05+cX+tCdK+yUe2gW0r+EtTDBk=", 
		"answer": "25K5YZ/63x6q9sUkUwewvvnH0jruyv9I3EZReYT/Aw==", 
		"explanation": "25aqZ4Lg2Bftt5EoV17by+n6J2XRF2serX6PEod1ZHSjeK7Ma63425h8Z0uMnk875nmGpqTj4xMdirtO5ZqMMCsNPoxuwd6A2eO3xTFFMt8I2pd67ZkXPPFY3DGsfdrIYOpmyy6ULkj1Jz20AnZxhjTYiXkWv4u++2evXN93wRwglZV569x8LtKLzLqd+w2+lAmPnFOQX7xtGBSNuo6f7k+QqYw/ocKD84IN8/7crWInrU2yWx74Pqs=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Gai,nin,g a d,ay", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010145", 
		"question": "2/2ZIdHSwgrv5ZEpXRCo7PO/ImLeF2cD7z+PXa1zdWOjWq7FZvntiZt0JljJmVQ7/3nUpuX48lIbz6RU+p3fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLQA8DORepzpab5HwC6XLkvkYivxRHx7mjbTmDxYoYSz4TT7WN82xFUmmcd14to5fN+a2LzT5EKrlUrC33SfXK9tE0GNvMCvq1eT4IE3ucmIo3LP8fnpn+rS5MsZZxsQ9KLtFswrMG9MjQcu92GM1g==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzmTijt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZR603KEpFxcWLsWufDfOi+3YVkIhyIg187ukSP46zjt1AAnbpe6prfdToTcophycSA2Oq3y3cBe+cN2Ar2TyFa/57u9Sx5zdoyvRM=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCy1un+IW7DQ3YZomvDXqx6d3TxFKnLaeXq2td4KRyehFVv92SGr6Dx8xMbgOhW5pyaMCoGf58vxN+axKTDzHhSc89X2oJ355sKb/EA2DWoNPHaMupmjnyFJED5cTyuRHxxhyKWmWlYpIq8/TP7UM8lyRs11pNw6IgrNdmL3LrfqE+9hQeXz37RXLVhUXqWp9qg7lGS4Ko9uMSeoTre5vG5k+uT5NcHdg1W/4doYkL8kboG9WosWc30WwdFsdDYZBThLyakIhxd98Lk3mB6ho8sXGd04BdHlsNCasUz85n2qDpwN8x5VT+/sFcA051xWleCe/250nvr8ld/Zm8laYNqtDl54RiUIVd22meZTShC1JRkvt0WhwEjdWpBiDbsjSyYvGuzcqfr7sDugOnjr7cj4bcmPUSTdUjQV5lcabzOIGJgiueSCq5IIN9rEiPifcEhvDT2MpPU1zwMxJksIGT0uGqancPhK2y4pobwgNM2ALBANd7J7c6l8EjCbDPkM3yHc9nxSkjER3Xrkwd29xogyyAF+2eYHIF6tSUIn2rwXUxlhmfpfzytma1IqoabbYc/1LX41TdQlv1/l4+31xwySQuvzX1G8paaX1BOzlHSXs8ehBo7ArgIE57FsmmDh3/eTDwZd8u2BamegxhA0/CxjW5zq4IHV5maKQqbntFm3B+0Qf52WWPousbtOPEFD3Yt7qdjz/7hvsT7YvqqOGA4LQc0MMVZrdNiQMnYpBTq6DE=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both (A) assertion and (R) Reason are true and (R) is correct explanation of (A)", 
		"option_b": "Both (A) assertion and (R) reason are false", 
		"option_c": "(A) assertion is true but (R)reason is not correct explanation of (A)", 
		"option_d": "(A) assertion is false but (R) reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010146", 
		"question": "2/2ZIdHywgrv5ZEpXRCohdTxdXzZDXYUsTPDRqtxMGL2WuDRLv//0IQxJk6MzUhr4HPHp+X/4VYdz6kb5Y+NdycRPop9zdHJ0/HyhGVOc9JMn4lgpJUdcP1R2TjtddrcLPsijlKOG0u4VXCvAXFnmz+W0DwWvIu+tTSuWp0kgAczj5Q47No5fMSPy62S7A23kAOQnHrRRLx2FlGL9c+67kLcpJc99dmC8SbT8f3r2vfR/Ncadw0Svoh4b178ha0a7SYsWMazKBtFsejVcketKC2iM04c98+jwXV7y8I9WGQk8Q1HlpZEZ9MxdWnI/qzMrsB9hWK9nQS4YQ==", 
		"answer": "2/2ZIdHywgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/IXnFBiIQrXvDGpE9MGPmVbTNYK332tdyKE6biFhvsnPes6nx+VIbhqdVqYGZMGoiN8tu28OMxfD+y38DF89nzk/54vsyAb1QxXv+Cw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCy1un+IW7DQ3YZomvDW600Z3jtQKLQIq3qwZIxNEmHykg74HffsOXx5VZPnLhJ7I+bMC0Ve5kvyZCF1vbwwWMBMtRBm8B28Z9faPsA2DWofcabL/xix3+VIgXxaT6xATBAnDjFynVF6IG+9iauR9931B031qJ5/9w0e8Tf2LCa+w2xlUaW1XeFTbkoUVWXsY6840bcjo0qocWIozyb3PH0k+vD+NsZZ0hbrMZraleokqxJ+T05SIiyeh1GsfDYZBTeNSbjIxsP8MXklmBhw8I+VGcg8Q0GtotfcYB+05nqr3IkN8x+VSeypgRT0po7TFeEdaSrkGDt9BUrfX9rQIt/qCV1oBvcKRRtkmqQQCNGkZIr/94emQEvPW5OmDb0ijqSwGSdedPw+5L5hOywr6x3sqwxLFPANBzUV58bYKGAJnV3y9WVMahoO5onBSfnLtogvCrtIYKRzHkZ2Ng0b2Pv8WqKh8OyKiWosovqztVkEf8TJsPA6M/3v0rCc2PgYXGSdMzxS0jxXXn5kwpwslgxx2EE4GfRGslw9yEEj2u1CUVqlSvlIDyzk61J5paHcYlx2vus0TcDi7RwmprjlBwyQ0SsjG1O8pCaQkxK31XCC98C10kaBL0SVJ/Csm+TlnfFWHlNa8bzQbuSzWtbmvHwl3I9voILFYKBOFnamZ4lxxmyBPNtR2b5rYK5KvQQBCQ48rdoiuyzsoqoZeGhLWFqYA+jGeBP9ocRaUJ3EBnaADYPYaqrV90qSelcknjPlglbB2tBBE6M76ANRESupYTGYX6ea7gITgrqZvMgEtzsRgfYPOWhiDHaRrKJlk/+VkoxSzSOKKQUqUfxdIiyMBu2iihg9oHrPUUbUJEWMjT1cXn5pLDDBhM5d2wtLYtTOnPdQgNklzHNM+tuj7IUdQttVafnDVgT1hJAkzrXHBhRtUEOWresVEY1L7oFKVVR2j67BaUNHt4jMbox0/z83eKo/16GVnQ=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "(A) assertion is true but (R) reason is not true", 
		"option_b": "(A) assertion is true and (R) reason is correct explanation of (A) assertion", 
		"option_c": "Both (A) assertion and (R) true", 
		"option_d": "Both (A) assertion and (R) false", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010147", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRpX6ARqxmYzHnW6LRLsPR/ddyKFKdn1J552LD47H/t1sGiKBe+86LdS8Te5lu3MWb0ve3zX8BINNJl4VgpJsMPPdPwS2sZtHfYOphjnmJKVH1dWaBCkx6tXiWvnRT6JCu+2eyR5o/yRI6k5U45MZ8KN+ambuY8Q28kxSL0nzRW6hpHFGLicCKogOoqId4ptiD9iGb5vXgibjV8dIHIglesolsdxuqkrod8Sk5XcStKB1FsfDYZBTIITq3L04Z7Nnq2HMp1ZckUGwmyBFly8N3ds18xYjsuSA5PI1jGCOvsU1UzpFvHxaYcP2v0Xzh8hUpdGokd8psvj46sw3cJVtsnyuUSS1F1IllvsMMmAlmb1NOuD+gpj6SkyWObpaj54/ygu3i4K1r861nJ0iHPUjLFoQSJaDVKmp32KXbH6NPJpNzHizhfdwgvDi5LpOAnz4M2ddgJnmn4CWNk8G1MWC7p9Lri9dzHakFMpMNyEIILV63gdeABSem2c3t", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz3hfvtQQBK6FoVpzvW6f7i+bSuw8=", 
		"explanation": "25SsZZ7gwRHv5YwjEhf/1ejtPH/ZBnFRonGHErR1ZHTxFLHDfuLsiZZzNFObjxt2/WTD46319kdPhqYb+puSfScRQoVTxuSB0qTk0X8BOtUEkol17J8NPP1OjCmlcZTIK+cuynuSLkv3JyqoCX1xhn2WmXMWvIu+tTSuWp0kgAczj5Q468kwMJee1aWc+1n4kAOQyHKSSbFoCBSWu46840bchYMqocXNhTrS57T0n/nd454faglG/5J3ZhuvgqZO62oqUNGnKBNZ9KTebkCtMzixIg8ZucT2wjRo1cIkSGo8uF9HjIcWdsh2z9jstSZwK8VvVRa7sVBIh4N1Sx/WebKq1Sjt7kE6e2kicZMtiCU8sk+OLUdrln+PDCVf1Ihi+dgch0R3eGJQmWThliqZhXbNAyIvZ4Z6V2rJHeyanFdvuw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only Two", 
		"option_b": "Only one", 
		"option_c": "Only Three", 
		"option_d": "None of the Above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010148", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Brp+JAuRg2yw/LtdX/YBiIdrGiGQONgdXzzUbXDevjszIQxLlLJmlJ15nPU46Tjt1AAgrha+4ubMDYMPph6xd2MxbvLyk1PEo8Eroh3pIkKcrNTjC+sbcebIexrjmOPNUCwYzC7AmVnkXHXhHgWu5Op8Ca/FNUhxQdyl8d//809KNKNmamB7Uz4jwjCy3KfXLh2LVq7/I6M6lqP4IMqsI2euT3J4PHr2vHdsMkCbBxXrco/b169k6EH/2osXoi4bQFYsezVYECtIi2qKQld687g031/w4YVU0p9tCtOh8NXds18xYjsuSA5PI1jGCOvsU1UzpFvHxaYcP2v0Xzh8hUpdGokd8psvj46sw3cJUF9kiuTSmxFnIUr9tUYgURlb2BN3GLoh3+YlWvIb9Ps6Yz1lP314Kti67AbJ2XJdX3UWs0TY/PUL2Iyy+uUG6MeIcv2l7PAQBZbkaURubNmKw==", 
		"answer": "25S0ZNHn2Ryq1ocvRBuwqKoeRYs5PtlJYE/mVvs30w==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHgxBet5MUyUwfhhfztMCvdDHAU43uKVKVhY3SjVanGLv7u25JwIxyGm15psneGpLf19kcKneha+4ueMCsNPpxmxsSMxaTDzHhSc89X2oJ355sKb/EA2DWoNPHaMupmiX3AJl35dHm0FzBgnT3Cj3ga6IK18WevXN937hoggo99/8Z8FNKS0LuD4Eiqg0aLzzuFQbFwFFDZtNmp8gOaso019dmFtHLo4fq5nu3B+dAMIhxausZoalWokrpJzCIxQoi5bRNF4qTEaVX5YDyrIk4O7MWkxTR7x5s6HWE94F9SioYWR8FhwpCkvSZwPo15HTK2r0tXwoY8XhmReLj0kGnq5BUrfX8yJYt/uW0msR2ZKVA+lX6IDCNHkZIr/5AVlBZkeH0AnWTlg3+/iGycPIHm+JXwkfuwqbcj/qY0OgGIMF3MFo8ZbL3HZ3V3yeySG6NYc49iBWLzM9w6vDjrJZeo0QUD9Ng5PDfm5i/ZgcX6K3G/odLwgJRhHbEUM8OJqceysVjObyShNXLTas7nSkj4Sn3skwxgvhYiiDMV62fRHox7tRkFl23wQFckkCLjbWmyk/5I4ofOWo8jx/2rznIfivZxi9v2xhIpSQD7mXdG8reKQRxG3hTYEdlHxUk+CaYHEZXFsm6fh3XcTjw5d8u2JKmV1yQPyaP+nGN0q9AHRsydIBDcgsoq0Ve0DfFwRXPkq4f1cbwUBGBs86Yxw/7htMa0Zva3OCU+YFqjUeoZwIBfKAt1USHcCzFOcqHuHo4LTO1KwDXDmUdcT3oJFlXZ76ANTwrqosHFZ3nOa7QOC1eiYr0BU8j5XFPHMOK9iDbbCbLcgU+7H3cwQHqUL/An8AvpOsTlLR2nlnok8M+lJlleBJAYKTP7cXm35auGBg8pbyQgOo8OOnPdQgNkmTvCKeonma8BZFg5Sa3nN18EghlKjTCSJl1IuV8OV6C/RRM1L6pAKU0U3ne5FLMMHA/fiDYDiV6Igiviae5DNAk0cmqHil6s25BjnP78kYvBA8CiJK5b1IwRPL5eVtrXCFoF2vX24OygBWQ8Rl5iIMTGYuzluEq2A9z5rdDKzVlZwL1IP1IrMCuCnZbc43psIaEPeHFeuGFZusvCbRTq2IpK2kJqEFj59kmkTmFhohl2Lpvua8mcLImq/RBLHiGHRKxN3+840i7oPM7EYVotBnom0TOYc5LL0zmMLrzzxb8MRRut2Y3KTIR+rEk52N2gyklUsnt6iTzrBmbPcO754RtHbjxrXreXWlxOxhM3xi79nkDlMoSvy+YIgLQBz7QH5B63tCBmgEzMe0LLcHaq1/uOonTPqk4k2upiXnWsSXEt3QMpQbAk9Dl6SChhQaR1qPbzPr7J3nWnK9yr2IJK9hZGR77ZY/2stdz/LePXKqH52oWQb2bp9NNoCfq6K8pFL3CNbDgesP7gaoXQLRuWPWiM16jYBiOLZQVa/G1m3XHORw1+K2GwTovJqQAa21fmeViMKyBt66fA", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "A and B", 
		"option_b": "B and D", 
		"option_c": "A, B and C", 
		"option_d": "All the Above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010149", 
		"question": "24KwcdH6wln+/4BgQhvgzPL7dWTWQ3YGqnOKVatgMH3sWqDHfK33x9dlIlGZiEl65nOGr6Tk/kcai61IqY2QfTICbI5riMSGl+XjhGVJNoZBi5Vz8JUNI7YD8334hMokUzEramXZRrSS", 
		"answer": "25e9a5Dmwhyq440lEg3ny73tPHjVECIQrXvDQaZgYzHqWufDYK3xy5t4NkmMzUt65n6GorGw41YCn61J6JqaMC4CaoJ73dSMxKYK27O3QhwZDYa4Rm1amz/h", 
		"explanation": "25y2KIX23Anv5YQ0V17+xOn2IX7UBnFd42uLV+NnZX+jRq7Ra/6+yJl1Z0+MmUg7+3iGoquw+FEDhrlO7M6PcTYLMstq0MSM2eD+ynYBJ85B2pB39pMQeLRE2S+ketObN/ZnzWbANUD2dTi+EHVw1D7EynhfroWu5iK/FNY+xx0m1oFq4sV8KN+ambuG5g2xlUaQ2XiUQathFRStvce7q06dq4cr9dmFtHLP4/31k//b5J4bZxpbsII/b1SykK0buCM2Edy8bQFOseXCZFX+YCusKh4c687nlmBmhpYhWCkx5QpHloxELoBk3p32uXIkN8gqBia041ZJ1JFvHxaYcP2r1Xz3oFgwZ39rc49/qCQ2oAOQMRg+l2qXRSJW1JRj+5ANgg1vdGhIiDbwhy2Cj2HPb5vs+ZT5l6rzkqI2ccsef1gMWj5c3PlW", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Because the sun rises and sets more quickly at the equator", 
		"option_b": "Because the earth receives more direct light at the temperate latitudes", 
		"option_c": "Because the sun rises and sets in an oblique path at temperate latitudes", 
		"option_d": "Because the atmospheric conditions at temperate latitudes refract more light", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010150", 
		"question": "24GwbdHj1Avj+IFgXRiy0er2OWLXC3ZRqmzDXqx6d3TxFK7MLvn7xId0NV2diBt382LPt7D08kBPjKdW+Y+NdSZDaoQv3NiMl+Hm0XBVPNQEmIVx5Y8MebRUxDjtZ8HVYOxn3WuTZ0T+Y3muAWRn1DjYyn1Y6LyEyhiEa+V30BQmnsd5+YgoOdqP3LqS/Ej4igeW1W+ETLh3U+1O5JTSyFUywPx5/+6dipw=", 
		"answer": "27q6ZJjixByod1Ri/wAwpsETci8ruIE/TQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHj1Avj+IFgXRiy0er2OWLXC3ZRqmzDRqtxMGXqWaKCbOjq3pJ0KRyamFVo92KGoqv0t0cHiuhe54rffyRDfYJ5wdzJw/P+yHhGO9II2o9gpI4XebRUxTCoNNbeNOlry2DANFD+dTCuATB1mjWWnnRT6IG+8i61WtM5x1U9kMd75N41MJeLzqGf4UqwkkaryDuYW/1oHlqesNzo4k3ctIc1pcifsCbetPj4jvHH5doOcUhRsItvYkm5k+gd92osWc30bQNe8PDfcxTvJSuiMh0Yud/r0zR604xpT2An8QwGg41SItN2wouktTxwPsMqGjG2qlVVwtRsXgOeNLyskHzh7UU6Z3s/YMphvTk8tRqYLUc8+ggbyKYAzKB1JNIdyEfBwQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "obl,iq,ue,ten,se", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010151", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUGXRL+yur2O2yQN2cDrmzDfqpnZDHKFOfDYOm+ibt4NEjJpHI5SBSrMRr3IP0a6+QSUG7Aaw==", 
		"answer": "25C5e4Xk0Avut7EyUwj3yb2ydUzRCmwC437DVqJtMGbrUamCbf/x2oR4KVvJmVN+sl/It6Di+VIbhqdV6ILfVCMXe8tDwd6Mm6TAwWJVJMdWnsBG9psJefgAgX2Be8feM75vjmqBPgXnbzyzRHNmmyLFg3JR6Jez8GeSWs4y0hszgo5348kwfPOeza3TxES2g0rC8XqWTbFoEFrepo6L5E2atZExusPN/HL58fjwn+7W9J4fag1L/4dtcVKqkqxJ9yR4Ys2kfFIe5eyQY0H5YCG3Zxkc6ovi1WB8x44lRCkH8Q9SwtVCaowz8JTtuzokf8t4Gj76lEFMy51yWAOZev2s3yjM4UI+fHNrKMpMrj88twqPaFVq2jnMHGxBmcB/9tVZhgVueC9mjn/kgybJvWRwHlSByIyRRjkLTpt27Q==", 
		"explanation": "25T4TZDgxQ7r5YFgZgzz0/jzbyvnC2cf42aMR+NgYnD1UauCa+zt3YBwNVjJjFhp/WXV47H48hMmgbxe+4CeZCsMcIpjiPSIw+G36HhPNooEg49npJ0edfoAzX2pdc2bFPZn3S6JNAXyYjq8EWNx1CjZnzxXuob7+CitXdQwgBM9hJB5/8x8NdnfzaGe7XG2pEa12WiFX7x2FRStp8++7k/G4LUwsMPNqD3OtODrm+7W/J4cZxtGqIdtZxu9lLoG6zl4RcCxKDtF5eHCb1X5KSetJgJd3cr30zRFz4wsESkt+woGjoxFZ4BylpzlpXIEN8R5VTqp40ZFxJVpTBLWbbKtkGn25RUyemwia40tviw2qhidOlA+k2XcWCVckbxl09EekAhvfGEHjzbDjTGNlXaGc525q6b5l+z5rrht9uMKKEaFOVDZWM0LZKCAJidCxfuPGKFJNoxiVyf+Ldkh7jzrYIGc0HkB1d1gO3/itCyQgN7heWCio5f9h8B/G7FAIt6F6sKls0nKbyL3KHqScs60TQD1D3v03Axg9y8tzS9Q4GvLSJp3/D0e3n2iRld3lyOgeHSk1pdS/oeccY8l2vri3D5QvPVsmtvb3RM5C0SvhXpa8oiQXEgPzBTSH9RH8AEnH/QIB9bT926XgGXVC2gFete2Fq2VxmxF1fX4gGY9qJUdQZuPPh2Xyt8ozFelCfhgFW/srMbtMrwSBSQu+7F6iuSv996yePbkOGpqexKyGf9L9oNYZxdoUQ/cHBhBRrSnUZUKAeZd3XiKoAJES3ZHAk7D9egcUkSCq9PJZ2OEI4YZAhLrbbQRHMC4R1SPPP/p5jXeRoWZlEu/UUBpDi2VKLMFpQ7jOt2qZBu8hnp3ucDtN1BfBIwRfA/yY2qwrOOwBEp6fmwjJINAclOVTQIrmX70IvVrhKkHZBcjAbyoWXgXgRBGln7FAU1JtAwfTbekVlZnK70FcgtBjSe4Ua8RHAjCg3oZj1uZgibtMLh0XhPYm1tRU7xDmkfe4ZlZ", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth and the Universe >> Exploring the universe to international dare line", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Eastward Travel,Gains a day when crossing the International Date Line", 
		"option_b": "Flight from Wellington to Hawaii,Arrives at 200 pm the same Friday", 
		"option_c": "Westward Travel,Loses a day when crossing the International Date Line", 
		"option_d": "Magellan's Confusion,Believed they arrived on Sept 5th but it was actually Sept 6th", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020101", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEhf8y/jtOGTDFyIdomaGQON7djH3XKKCS+zs3Z82NByamUlu8WLTsaCvtf6hQHlIkNxEw5Kf4vRpO6s=", 
		"answer": "25i5ZoX/1Fu5FDLW0dGkX57hLDZmTwbZ", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH63xfv5YgvQQqyyfzmMHmQDGRRt3eGEoZ1YmXrFK7RLvn2zNd4KVKMnxt4/WTD7+Xn/1oMh+hS+s6cfy8TcZhqzJCZxe36xWNIP98ElYYy95UTdfAAxS+iepTaLvouwGeDLED8Jz2oATBgm3HCgnkWoIq8/WerRt8k0wAgk8d548x8KNKSya2B6VmtlAPAtpA5vEMrJx20C/C20caiRw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Lithosphere", 
		"option_b": "Mantle", 
		"option_c": "Outer core", 
		"option_d": "Inner core", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020102", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRXr7oAyEhH0hen3MCv1AnAFqziQErBgYmTgQLLQa6332tdjIk+ZglVo+3TKpuX2+EFPiK1V7JyeZCsNect7wNXJ8uXl0HkGIIZJm4d84Y4Wf7RGxTihcIuZSHyv07yXqc4sK1U6j1vYbw==", 
		"answer": "25qtfJThkRrl5YBiU1bjd9ZpFsZyvSRqkiZxhQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHW0Av+/8IzEhPzwvP6IWLTQ2QYpnOHEqpnMHbmWqLQb/n7zddzPhydhV47/3nQpqj1+UdPgK4b5IGTZCcNPoJ9x97J1urzhH9IMM1BlsB76toLdPEAwyi5ccabI/F8yy60L0zjJzSyEHl7mnHRj3JTuoKv8DT7UdYywwEgn4Q47t0uLtKRzbvT/EW5kkaSznSVXb5hUUCRsI6l6kSSpZYxto2LuDfX8LYpeBFtxVooRTDKZKwGCGSK", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Lithosphere", 
		"option_b": "Asthenosphere", 
		"option_c": "Outer core", 
		"option_d": "Inner core", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020103", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ3z54BgXRiy1vj2JmbZACIGommGQeN1YnSjRqLRfuLw2p5zK1nJi1RpsnXHtrb5+VRPm6BeqYOQYzZDaYJrzcOZxeH2wDFAPcIEk45m4ZQMebRH3jK4etCbM/ZvxWeOIAX0ciu0Cnc0kTDEnnRHvYKw8DTkFo9JdehOz/xos1evu/xNY1Q=", 
		"answer": "24e5cZ322B7it5IhRBvhh1ijRs64XRUcD8UmQCDh0t4=", 
		"explanation": "24e5cZ322B7it5IhRBvhhfztMCvDFnAXonyGErR1ZnTwFLPKb/m+ypZkNFnJmVN+snvJsLGw4FoLirtL+4uedGICcI8vwd6d0urkwTFGIclRlIQy95Ied/1Oy32pYcbSLvkuy2+SM03hcji2AWM41CLfh3VaqZH74Sj7W9kywRtygYZu6Nt+ZXNlOa19wv4+qcxTRvG3Zg==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Primary (P) waves", 
		"option_b": "Secondary (S) waves", 
		"option_c": "Love waves", 
		"option_d": "Rayleigh waves", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020104", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7gzPD+J3KQAG0cs3CQW7d9f3+jW6GCeuX7ibJwNUiBykg7/3fIt6n1uxMbh60b5Y+GdTBDcoRsycSM06T1wX9EMtJM2pR64docbuFT2H2setCbIfxh2GvAM031JzaoEHVm1DLZmHkJ6vDMsjCi9T6doKB0xcZ0auc=", 
		"answer": "24axZJjw0A3vt4gpXBvgxPHsd2bx9nV/CyORV0OSpNVuewY=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH+0Bf++4BgWw2y1e/2OGrCCm4I43yMX7N7Y3TnFKjELv73xZ5yJkiMzVZy/HPUoqnjuxMYhrxTqZ2QfCsHPoJ9x97J1urzhH9IMM1BlsBw4ZMRe7RQ3ji+cdrPYPdgjnqIIgX0YjytAWI0hjTRg3NYu8E+bBkf2ZgeAUUniTI9wRfR", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Liquid iron and nickel", 
		"option_b": "Solid iron and nickel", 
		"option_c": "Silicate minerals", 
		"option_d": "Hydrogen and helium", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020105", 
		"question": "24GwbdHe3hHl5Yo2W3P7or3bPHjTDGwFqnGWW7dtMDnOW6/NJ63zyIV6NBydhV478HnTraHx5UpPja1P/ouafnhBoRUCLlLAByn2pfpNnN8Fcg==", 
		"answer": "25aqfYLnkRjk88UtUxDmyfi9CE4M/XivyMU5KbFP674VUQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHe3hHl5Yo2W3P7or3bPHjTDGwFqnGWW7dtMDnOW6/NJ6332tdlL1nJj1Ru/HLHsbyw9VYbmK1e586LeCdDW4p93NjOxKT01mRSJ4ZFlIQy8JIaPOFOyDi/eM3SLvkuw2+OM0n1JxCpRHln1DLei25Xq5e+5y6hUd53wgxyl8d75ckyO9Lf0KbT+0ixlQuL3zuGSathUUKcucGr4leVpZF6zzynNS033U0Vv61WYHxMBg==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Crust and mantle", 
		"option_b": "Mantle and outer core", 
		"option_c": "Outer core and inner core", 
		"option_d": "Lithosphere and asthenosphere", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020106", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRXr7oAyEhH0hen3MCv1AnAFqziQErBgYmTgQLLQa6332tdwNE+GjlJ65nPC47L541tPm6BeqbLdQisNectgzpCv3vbyiE0Dc8cEiIV17ZURPP9OwyqjNNLUMr5n2n3AL0z3b3mrC3x3lT/fiTxXpof7tRu1FMkyyQY/n4Q47MsoNcGWzbHMqkVtNuCY7ecIRoKaZLCU6sw=", 
		"answer": "25mxfJn8wgni8pclEEhNi/+RKAKhn3O88DTzZ+I=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHPkyvj+YJgXRiy4/TtMFeSQ2sC43yLU7F1c2XmRq7Ya+m+y44xM1SMzUtp92XDrab1t1wJz6Va55ffZCcAaoRhwdPJx+j20HQBMclRlIRz9pMab7gA2zWkd9ybMvt922KUZ0z+Jz+vAWFhkT/CynlXupez5DK6X98kgBQ8ksdu4sQ/PdmW2uiS61mxkA+WxTuQRLJqFhSNvcvo7kebpZF4usvNpTretPjwjvDc484DZxpbvMZvb1qokrtLnexrHfSoHM/7fzCW5lyBfw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Mantle", 
		"option_b": "Outer core", 
		"option_c": "Asthenosphere", 
		"option_d": "Lithosphere", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020107", 
		"question": "24GwbdHjwxbp8pYzEhH0hf7wO33VAHYYrHHDXaB3ZWPwFLfQZ+D/2559PhyAgxts+n/Fq+X89koKnehU786LeCdDW4p93NjOxKTk0GNUMNJRiIUtpsElQd1zW1rgVe7ZgHbXWak=", 
		"answer": "25SrfJn23xb5540lQBuwUy+kzwOoaPrgn+qzZdFX9g==", 
		"explanation": "25a3Zof20g3j+ItgXR3x0O/sdWLeQ3YZpj+CQbd8dX/sR7fKa//7hddwZ0+MgFI29HrTqqGw+1IWirob5ojfZCoGPoZuxsSF0qTDzHQBO8NFjs129pMJefoAwTK7cdneLuouwWjAKkTkYiu0BXw0nT+WnnRfu8O39D6+Rpo0zxsmhI56+Nw5L5eL1uiH4Ej4iwmU2XaURqkkHlLZocur/0ySqYF4pcGMpTfItnNCX0MsoXSFyofZxuf/8mw=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Lithosphere", 
		"option_b": "Asthenosphere", 
		"option_c": "Mantle", 
		"option_d": "Inner core", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020108", 
		"question": "24GwbdHA2Bjmt4QuVl7BzPD+dWrCBiIFpm2OQeNhY3TnFLPNLun72pRjLl6MzU9z9zbStKqw+lIGgehX6JeaYjFDcY0v3NiMl+fl0WJVc8RFiYV2pJURPOBIyTS/NNfTJfNnzW+MZ0b/aimyF3lgnT7YyGsb4Cas8e5INFSUiSqaVjM=", 
		"answer": "24axZJjw3heq9oskEh/+0PD2O37dQThqzufhXCBsz3XsZExfgAU=", 
		"explanation": "24axaZ2zwxzs8pczEgr9hen3MCvFE3IUsT+PU7pxYjHsUufWZui+7JZjM1TOnht44GPVt+mw4FsGjKAb4J3fYisAdstmxpCa3uj+x35Pc8dKnsBz6I8SdfpVwX2efdnaYOxryGuSNAXkaHmpDHU0mD7Bj24WpIKi8DX7W9x31B031oRq+NsocJeI0aGQ4A2xlUaQ1XiZCLRqUUeQucer5E3coYw89cCMtjze5/3sl7pQ/o/NtMomajsdufdU2yCS", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Silicon and aluminum", 
		"option_b": "Silica and magnesium", 
		"option_c": "Silica and aluminum", 
		"option_d": "Silicon and magnesium", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020109", 
		"question": "24GwbdHW0Av+/8IzEhL70fXwJnvYBnAU43aQEqFmf3rmWufLYPnxiYR0MVmbjFc75nPFt6r+/lBPn6Ra/YuMMBULf58vzMKAweHkhGVJNoZJlZZ36Z8RaLRPyn25fNHIJb5+wm+UIlavJeeCQNihePZXZg62vS2pfgM=", 
		"answer": "25a3Zof20g3j+ItgUQvg1/jxIXiQCmxRt3eGEq51fmXvUeXGIbv3h1lNO9tHDHr8gE4E", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH+3g/v+oAuRl79w73rMGjEDGwYoD+TXqJgdWKjXbSCfv/3xJZjLlCQzV9p+2DDreXy7hMbh60b6oGRZicAaoJgxpCKwvblwX9VIIZNlMBm7J9fb/FNxXCreMHSJL5v3XqIIkv/dCm1AWJx2HHBgnVVoMOp8DSuWM53xgc9m8dw6MkofNCa162B6Vm9gkaAxTuFQLgkFVGatNfo5EXcsoM8vMKMsibS4vG5n/TW/dsFdhsQRNttF/VLUeC4szCFXPl9kA==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Gravitational forces", 
		"option_b": "Ocean currents", 
		"option_c": "Convection currents in the mantle", 
		"option_d": "Magnetic forces from the inner core", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020110", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRqmzDfIxAMHCjV6/DfOz93ZJjLk+dhFg7/XCGt631t3YOnbxTrp3feSwNe5kvy9+b0ru1QyBktPQ0+0VTmN/1gAHaFw==", 
		"answer": "25mxeYT61Vn544Q0V1ykYThqcSbXr5OiBFGcmNm/", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH63xfv5cUjXQz3hfTsdXjfD2sV43uWV+NgfzH3XKKCa/Xq25J8IhyZn15o4WPUpuX08kAfhrxeqYeLY2ILd4xniMSM2vTy1nBVJtRB2qlmpJMMPPdPwS2iZ9HfYPNvx2CMPgX/YXm0Fn961DDYjjxYoYCw8Cv7VdQzgBwh1pRt/9ozKdmb3KzT6lT4kg6HnHeYWahtFRSWoNqt+QOfr5A990uzQoSwm0CW2dLJNf0dns8=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Solid composition", 
		"option_b": "Composed of iron and nickel", 
		"option_c": "Extremely high pressure", 
		"option_d": "Liquid state", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020111", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kSr+9pElXxv80b34MGTcDGUYoH6PErN8dX/sWaLMb63u25hnLliMnhtv+nOGrqrj4xMLhrpe6prfdS8Td5lmy9GFl+HhzXVEPcVB2pNn9IoQbuBJwjrtYNzeYOpmy2GSPgX/YXmtCHFgkXHCj39Cp42y9jTkaNQLzjoigo5349tmANm+kOin4Ej4lhSHz36fS7gkHlLZpsel4k+dssIqus6G8TTU5vn4jvHc/s1LbQYSu495ZV6ukqYduCk3X9y9ZhdF5ffsb3akYByrIk4e9sXwwnVn0s5pW2As8RsGkoxFa9R62ZakszRwPMJkATq0pkpU1NRzSRKENLq932Tr51w8dHZrcYNguRE7gkbcHFx72mSfTzlDhoVl/dVZmgIjeG5SiH7xlz6AhXbPfZ/s5Ye8ke3ztLZt+6BnOU2BIVmYVIIJa7fBNW532dWVKe8cB5diVzfoNNMh7jS5JJ+HyysE0sw0JnjptCWf0tv6NWa7vZv6ztV1ALYWP8Xcqdy4olDDdirlJD/H2lXwNtX3kzlowS0/mNmo", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz/hfvtS2FTyUlprVQrGbvBLFVS5w=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn2Rzl5ZxgXRiy1fH+IW6QF2cSt3CNW6BnMHjwFKHXYOn/xJJ/M12FgUI74WPWs6ri41YLz6pCqZqXdWIHZ4VuxdmKl+n40nRMNshQicB94toLdPEA6Ty/YNycM75ix3qIKFbgbzyvATw0liPZgXlY6Iq14Sj7QN801Bo8n4Q4/cQ9KNKMmbyb6Vn4gAqN3W/RSalrARSNvcvo+EaRqc8+udiEtXLa5+Dxn/bc484DZxpX/4R6b1Sr14cH/Wo3V4igYBcL/OvDdRTpKTqmJBpd/Mbz32ZgxYMlHWwi/RtDjIBTcYBgw4j0syAkNsNtVSeyqlcA05x5UAWPNLSrkHzs5RUwdnk+d5hosi4w4QCaaFF/iH+UXTlQn4V4vtEVmgpkPXtFn2LvjDaIwHWDfYfmq4LzkOb0oatq97BnHUmFJlmYU4wOcbvRMmZ5z/rbAqVfJo0nFSflPMA9+Xn2JtaA1zxNwtwsLmPu4i/Zn8LjPGi/vYbqzttwVKsIM8LAqdu7sUjCclf2KXiHbs7mGRz4SmW40hxg9xws3iQC72vWD8U/9iIDiHuiTk1qlWugY27hhbJV7ouAeM4h0ub4nTcRm/w4kI//0Q98dBG4hT9Qt42MQlVMjVXVCsQRzR03TL0SVJje5i2ElHjURHFNfdviQamLyitGyaPmh3V1/4QGUMyLKB7emZ4pzlelCfhqUCf9pIftOO9ZSnAk/6B0yPThpN+5ZuelInEjbg6+V+gZ551UKBZzFATPHGRAZvi+WpwKRKBb13bemAlBRGwJKkrY8qcGHSXquMHEb37bcPEIAV7hbL0RGsD9QFPOObGt2jnPEvPcgk+3XExlRyndIPAd5BXkOoP0ZAO/knxhudXgMUVUSooUL2fxYX/5qaaQGEY+dj4gK54Hf1HcTxUqlzuDM/Fmg+cFcQo5SbmyGFsThVFgjyrbAVYFkgwXTOWkTlAoOLtAI09RzCT1GLRfXxPEkigLil+f1jGsPfJOcV0rfmuBlgCgmpxi39D5loeOBJTGbbQIkoQNK7lJVp/VCxsen/Dl+vLlUXo2Cm52IPHLHuPSpEbgC9zt4srJhVJE3f4dOFY9KiuGhYaZ9DN+O7dGbWVeuHdZrt/GIg+5mYtW21NtXkH+9FXhRScgolFjYpL/b53eJY6r9FFNHyHUF4pM1LxXzTjtOtGRR1o2FCMWnhWCc9HehYVWsARLM2iB0dPhst5qFsg=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only Two", 
		"option_b": "Only One", 
		"option_c": "Only Three", 
		"option_d": "All Four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020112", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ3z54BgXRiy1vj2JmbZACIGommGQeN1YnSjRLXLY+zswJtoZ06Mnkt0/GXPoan1t1UAnehc7ICaYiMXd4VoiMSB0qT6y2JVc89KjoV8959fcPVUyS+seJTUMr59x2qFalH/Kiq0AHU0kyPZn3JS6Iey5je3VdkyzRA8gpQ46d0uNdmYmamdqEi5lBKKzW6QQ7g7UwQbDJkNHA3CmjEbACnzIkU=", 
		"answer": "25m3fpSzxhj88pZinmOYFa+iLGSYsYvH93PHCg==", 
		"explanation": "25m3fpSzxhj88pZgUwz3hfy/IXLABiIepT+QR7FycXLmFLTHZ/7zwJQxMF2fiBtv+nfS46bx4kAKz6BU+4eFfywXf4cv29iM1vb+ynYBPslQk498qNoNeedVwCmketObKfAu2maFZ0j/dC39F3lzmjjQg39Xppf7+SavUcg2zFU9hMdr5Mw5ccOQlLua7Ej4gRSNyXWVCLltAkSVtM2t5kaStMI8oN+EvzWb9fq5n/nB5NYadwlZusZLa16vkuge+Tw9Qoi1ehcL5PfFYFjhOWixIh0N9sXw33Zlw8IvUnt04BdDwo5ZcdQzxZ3yuSA1f8lrGDK9pgRByZA8XgWTNLm9xG3n9FQ9eX9rapxorm05oB2bLRR6k3iITSJSkZMrzsIQmAVxZC9XnWDlkX/DsCiYfYXm+Mm8hPr14Lps/7M1LFKTPFPWV4FccrLWInQy3uGaGeZIIZ5xEi6mKd0rvD/4M4KRzC1N0sw0b3PotCSWho3hIHWzsJP1gs02F74VJdSF+sKwvlXBaCDgL2nTYdn7TAb0D2/w0gVsuR9l+yQT52zcCZtmtToMiHujCQxX3zDhenmy3/5Y5cKNcIAlwfzuyCYV2OB335zl2wgyQ0SohX5Iu4qYD15a2RTXDMhHygY6TKcREZXY82Gfj3PUC3UDP8L3Fa2VwiAI1+zlh25zrNA8VJWCKRDcgp4xyQG0Er1wW2P4q4O5PPJVD2gg86Jlw+6gu4q2euetI2tqbQ+jGe5L9tVfZxY7BQPYRSlOabbuVZIQVfJG0GDemBVbB2tGRVbN760aXAjqrdbHe2TaI7UVHQ7uYrAAHsv2Wgf7PfS7zTbGFLrQ1WuxSUFlWTuLJKNN5BX1Opj6IVOwnHp2/MLxclBVV5QSLmVTgJuyNxC1vTkeSlMH+VG/", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Primary waves (P-waves)", 
		"option_b": "Secondary waves (S-waves)", 
		"option_c": "Rayleigh waves", 
		"option_d": "Love waves", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020113", 
		"question": "24GwbdHW0Av+/8IzEh391/i/NmTeEGsCt2zDXaU0ZGbsFLfDfPntk9dlL1nJnlR3+3KGqqv+8kFPjKdJ7M6efiZDaoNqiNyAxvH+wDFOJtJBiMBx64gaPMBIyX2iYcDeMr5twXyFYFawajarAX1xmiWWhXoWpYy34SK1FNMlzxtykYJ26No9KNKMmbyb7Q2dhxSW1DyCCIJbLmumivGX1HzQ4IN4pd+CpTfY4P3vn7jA+NcObgwSvoF+alWvg+gB+Tg1V924KAFE/eXCIUbsJCGiMwcS94kmCvXQg4rZ5Oo5OzkubAGh", 
		"answer": "25i5b5/2xRDpt6MpVxL2h2ljcj3SuW2dGpO51j7s5V4=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHW0Av+/8IzEh391/i/PHiQDmMVpj+WQuN7djH3Q6iCfuzs3YQrZ0iBiBto/XrPp+X5+V0KnehY5pyaMCMNest7wNXJ2+3m0XhFc8lRjoVgpJkQbvEA+DWoNNvONPt8jm2PNUCwbir9BXJ7gSWW2DAE+NP7/i63W9cy1BAghcds5cE/N5ee16zT4V74iweG2TuEWP1rFxSUusK87k3cqZA3u42Mvzab+v36kf3fsOoDZ0hfsJB6bl6yg+gG/mosWc30ZR1H5eHeIV3/LybjLgBd7cPmlnt80oc7HWo75hoGhYZYZ9Jywp33/CY4Oo1PFCGuqwNTh5l9WBmTYLS7kG7t5Vk7SXQXa75luW0QoB2IIBNt2madSyJUgIlovtYQkAhnPWZT3Hegki2ElGCMaJr17sDvjeH1rL0j86QmIE+TIRzQV58RY6bMZ3R9xuiJTbRdN5ZmAyvpM5UH6Hn9JZCY2joZw5ktIGTztCWf0tn9PCWpvJ74nJRhHbEEepHEqdijolnGbGPuJz2QbsrmXg30D2z5wRpstBQg22EW+m3VSJ138G0+i3D8CUVzkz6gam6um/5I4ofOWo8jx/2s6ToV2Od3k5rllAo1SQD7jn5N8oCeQl1IyBTCFshH4Qg8GLxGB9bQ5mCZhmbYTm4IP8/4BeiDyj9az/PlzmRxupMaR4OAJRqbmcc13BK8Er/is5gChNrDIjs6er8SK1Ff", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Ma,gn,eti,c F,ie,ld,w,av,es", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020114", 
		"question": "27i5fJL7kQ3v5YgzEgz3yfzrMG+QF21Rt3eGEoZ1YmXrE7SCbf/r2oMxMFWdhRtv+nPPseXz+EEdirtL5oCbeSwEPo9q29Ob3vTjzX5PIPpKtZBm7ZURb64A4DS+YJTyYOln2mbAC0zjc3mULTLkF4VrdFKIPLheR0nSMD97", 
		"answer": "25mxfJn8wgni8pclElOy9/T4PG+QDHcFpm3DQatxfH2jV6jPfv/32p5/IBydhV478WTTsLGw9l0Lz71L+YuNfS0Qastiyd6d2+G7hFBSJ85BlI9h9JIabvEAgX2ecdnSbfNhwnqFKQX8ZiC4FjBjnDTEjzxCoIb7+CitUdcyzgFymYE4+c0/KNiR0KvT+EG5kgORnHSSS6h2AhjZgcur/0ySqYF4hcGMpTfItLm5tvnB99tLcQ1Rq49wbUj8mK5J7CI9Ee21egZDtveQYkb4MzzjMwYc7Yvu2WJshoMnWSk9+gtDkIJVdoJx0uftPr2zlZaAWUYincyj", 
		"explanation": "25mxfJn8wgni8pclCF7Gzfi/OWLEC20Cs3eGQKY0eWKjQK/HLv/3zp51Z1OcmV5psmXOpqn8t1wJz7xT7M66cTAXdstG3JCAxKT6xXVEc9NU2o90pI4XebRD3ii+YJTaLvou2maFZ1DgdzyvCX9ngHHbi3JCpIb7wS++FNY+1B09hZdw6No5fN6MmaqB50a9iEaL0m+eCKlhEkCWu8erq1OQoZY9pvGDkCHP/PH3levD+NsZZ1ISi456I1qvg6AM9iUrQcCxehcL+PeQdVzoYCSiPgsPucTllmBhw8IMXHsg/FhVwo5XbNR/09jwtDMkf8R5VTG/r0tXh4B0Wleafamw33v06FAtcDoCccpkr204oAuZaEFu2mSaDCRegMwr7dUUnElucmNUmXigkDCIiyW7dJaj6pPoje3+r6pz+qY1LAGJJhzMXohcabLZInUy3eGeH6McJ5diVzbjPsEh8jD6YIaY3i0Iw5ktIGHiyCStl87hNmuzsNLJgtViEaxaduXA6t+4vlXEITPtIGmWdYv1Sw2wQ33q1AslpB0m3Cgf5nGYB48/4SUI3luxW1Bs1TSgb260haoc/oqPa8483OPpnTMenLRxkY/yxhw/U0SPhXoDv4uJSlFKw0CWEctH0AwtGLsPHZWR4mGXgXPDC3UeP9zzEriIzT9B2O/0zmdyrdAaXYnOKhbJh98ywRi/QfJ/FWrivYjtPPUbGShs7L19yeyvuM+oObOlImFqahulTedI5pRabRE5iptZLjkTVlwKWfOm1ggDcA==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Lithosphere,Rigid outer shell comprising the crust and uppermost mantle", 
		"option_b": "Asthenosphere,Semi-molten layer where the movement of tectonic plates occurs", 
		"option_c": "Tectonic Plates,Large sections of the Earth's crust that move and interact", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020115", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gZhb3hdj+J3/YRHFRoG2WQbc0cX/nFKvLeuXx2od5Ik6MzVpp9zbIrLGw41sKz7ta5Iujfh4NTI5u29+HjaTDzHQBP89Qko9h9JIabvEAxTOueMHfJe0u2maFZ2DxdS21Q2M0lyPDmWgWqZD74iK3WJo201Uz1pd3/9w1M9nf1q7T/EW9xhOSzH6DRbJ3BRSUtMC850bQ4IM2sY2EpXLZ8fz4jP3AsN8YIgkSg4g/cVK7nqxJ9z8sVNr0expO/eiSEZOcbS4AXo2yUnB6x7VmxA==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRt3eGErFxcWLsWufDfOi+3YVkIhDJjFV/smLOpuXi8lIcgKYb4J3fZCoGPohg2sKM1PC3wWlRP8dKm5R765Rfc/IA2DWoNNXIM/t82mePKQf7Tohs58DQBb8tv3cmf+/q", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCyxvLtJ27TF24I42yXU7dxYzH3XKbWLvn2zNdUJk6dhRxosnXUtrbkt1IBi+hX4JqXfzETdo59zZCIxeG3yn5Vc9JMn8Bh5ZcaPMBIyX2/cdXIL/Auz2KTKAXzaCuvAXNgmCiWj2RGpIKy+zT7QNI21FUmnoI44cEoNNiMyaCW+kj4gwiB03aBSa53FEfZocatq0COtZEs9cyDtXLatOT2iOza/9BLbQ4Sq456IxuAmegc6Do9Q8W7ewYL/OXedVjobGihIgYc78Lt0TRo1cIoHXs98xZCwoxDdsVhlovsuT48fRxqO95KXyRYO7qejqBAxC4=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and the reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and the reason are true, but the reason is not the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020116", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ3z54BgXRiy1/L8PivZECIXrG2OV6c0ZHnxW7LFZq3qwZIxJFOGgVJ19TbHraGw5FwDhqxS74eccTYKcYUvx9bJ2uv70HRPc8tFnY1zpJUNPPhB2jzyNr5qauyuF2qTWoLH3rEsN20=", 
		"answer": "25y/ZpT8xAqq5YojWVxm4ooyXkR8KGZzNEKLZu+V", 
		"explanation": "25y/ZpT8xAqq5YojWQ2yxO/6dW3fEW8Upz+FQKx5MGXrUefBYeLywJl2Z12HiRto/XrPp6z2/lAOm6FU586QdmIOcYd7zd7J2uXwyXABe9NKnoVg44gQafpEhX2iZpTXIehvjiaPKQXkbzz9F2VmkjDVjzUUIs3R3WA9Rw8MR+eSzVB4rQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Sedimentary rock", 
		"option_b": "Metamorphic rock", 
		"option_c": "Igneous rock", 
		"option_d": "Fossiliferous rock", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020117", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQn4+IYlQQ2yzPPpOmfGBnFRt3eGErdmcX/wUqjQY+zqwJh/Z1OPzV5j+2XSqqv3t0EAjKMb4ICLf2ICPoVq35CdzvTyhH5Hc9RLmYsy8JINc+FHxH2lcdXPYP9gyi6QNUDjdCyvAS82HqWY/qMKUvL8WMRdkHD45A==", 
		"answer": "25i9fJD+3gv6/4wzX1zrTeXNv/UFcvxOzDQrq1cG", 
		"explanation": "25i9fJD+3gv6/4wzX1771r3rPW6QE3AeoHqQQeN2aTH0XK7BZq370Z5iM1WHihtp/XXNsOXx5VZPjKBa54madGIKcJ9giN6MwKTj3WFEIIZLnMBg65kUb7RE2TjtYNubKPdpxi6UIkjgYiu8EGVmkXHXhHgWuJG+5jSuRt97gAI7go93+Nx8MdKTzaGd7w8s+7XJad71AmjOwpqfnZZs", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Weathering", 
		"option_b": "Erosion", 
		"option_c": "Sedimentation", 
		"option_d": "Metamorphism", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020118", 
		"question": "25mxZZTgxRbk8sUpQV7zhf7wOGbfDSIUu36OQq9xMH7lFLDKZ+72iYNoN1nJgl074HnFqPqy7WnkX9wQ6n55Bzs2krgN4A==", 
		"answer": "24a9bJj+1Bf+9pc5Egz9xva9sZl+n7YVOHoHH2JDNMnscg==", 
		"explanation": "25mxZZTgxRbk8sUpQV7zhe76MWLdBmwFom2aErF7c3qjUqjQY+j6iZFjKFHJmVN+snfFoLD94l8Om6FU586QdmIAf4dswcWEl+f21nNOPcdQn8Bh4Z4WcfFO2C7vBNKGi6/IXexnIixoIbyL5Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Igneous rock", 
		"option_b": "Metamorphic rock", 
		"option_c": "Sedimentary rock", 
		"option_d": "Carboniferous rock", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020119", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsXCAWbA0eWKjV6jMfeT6zIV0IxyIzWc58GTDoKb59h4biqtP5oCWZCc/PMtr3dXJw+u3zWVSc8JNiZR76pkLdeJFjDuiZtnaNPdhwC6QNUrzYiquWzKyS4jYdJiOW4GMZrU5oBMG", 
		"answer": "25a3Zpb/3hTv5YQ0V1wrZJw0NFsZn3gDfTQwNFsV", 
		"explanation": "25T4aoP20hrj9sg0Vx3myvP2IW6QCnFRoj+RXaB/MHfsRqrHaq3425h8Z0iBiBt94HfBrqD+41IbhqdVqY+RdGICfYh6xcWF1vD+y38BPMAEloFg459fbvtDx32rZtXcLftg2n3AMEzkbzCzRHE0mTDCmHVO6Iy9tSGyWt8lgBgzgoJq5MkwfNOK3OiH5w2sgwWW03WYS/1iHkaasN3qozvNi0F5RC7DG3yndJvYJw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Granite", 
		"option_b": "Gneiss", 
		"option_c": "Conglomerate", 
		"option_d": "Schist", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020120", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yQEW0SqD+XS7NxYzH0XbPKLvn2zJ5jZ1iMnlhp+2bSqqr+5AkzgYtU5ZuSfmIiPssviJDJl6S3hDFiPMpRl44yxqYRXboA4Ty/dtjeYL4uji7AZwWwJ2jzRFE0mTTCi3FZupOz/CT7RtU0y1U9hI5/5MY9KN6R3uiV+kK1xhKK2TuFWrxqAlKWp8Op/0qTrsI3s42BuD/e5+D2lP3v/vxFIipTrIdzdxv81+hJuGp4EYj0KEAF0OqQaFPjJSe2NE4P9sjolnJm1I8sWSky5hBLwpBZbsl3357tuTZwMsJmATa040hB0ZVAUTTYNJqq0Wbt9FB/NTprJcot/G118kG9aFdxm3mPSWFWhoFi8NUd1Q1kc2pPiWWgkDCIiyWddZDrq4nyxfnloat36OMmJ0XAM1nUUp4MZKH8KUM8itqXDLJZc98nV2KmfZVuvHm5YNbAkRhN1tAuKjrg5iuQnMjxeWi/p5P0gcZmHLYDdsPK6sD3tFnVaDXkJT2VdMT5GRv4TnD9kcQ5BkyuDI6XgkxcFI7e2Og=", 
		"answer": "25T1Od2z81S4u8UDH02+hdmyYSlSamX2STV3ViBon6vXe/GJ", 
		"explanation": "25i5epP/1Fnj5MUhEhP30fzyOnnAC2sS422MUag0ZHniQOfNfOT5wJlwM1mazV1p/XuGt631t0cdjqZI74GNfSMXd4RhiN+Pl+j+yXRSJ8lKn7x8xpsMffhUjDS+NNXVYPdpwGuPMlawdTa+DzBgnDDCynpZuo6otSGpW9d30hQin4N09IgvM9uW3aGV8US2gUaO3W2QdLNDA1WXvNqtq0qP4IN4tsKMoyHeufPrm/Hd9dpLaw9cuolqcBuumKsCuD4wUNz0YQEL4+3TaRTkLmiyMg8P7dGj13pthoQsUW0n5B5Uvo1lbsFn09jtr3Ixf8tjGzb3pFZBzpp5W1ebcam53Wf28F02djo5aolm/Dk9oBvcJ0Z3nWKSTThUh8Bt7N8U1RdrfGNF3vyF4tuWlMmIijYu/XPd8qI=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "A-1, B-2, C-3, D-4", 
		"option_b": "A-2, B-1, C-3, D-4", 
		"option_c": "A-3, B-1, C-2, D-4", 
		"option_d": "A-4, B-2, C-1, D-3", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020121", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQvl9I5gRgfiwL32JivWDHAcpnvDULo0ZHnmFKbBbfjz3JtwM1WGgxt09DbQrKnz9l0GjOha+obfcSwHPoR7wNWbl+L+ynQMNNRFk4534NoJc/hDzTOkd5TWIepr3GeBKxqyp1QZ59MHVVs1XRcF5nV1tg==", 
		"answer": "24awaZ32k6mEoiGC57USzRnQ5fLB4aY=", 
		"explanation": "24awaZ32kRD5t4RgQRv2zPD6O3/REXtRsXCAWeNyf2PuUaOCaP/xxNdlL1nJjlR24nfFt6z/+RMAiehW/IrTMCEPf5IjiNGH06TkzX1VftVNgIV2pIoebuBJzzGoZ5ad6IaDTrvNKxoVWOzpum5h", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Granite", 
		"option_b": "Conglomerate", 
		"option_c": "Shale", 
		"option_d": "Gneiss", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020122", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ3z54BgXRiy1/L8PivZECISrHKTXbBxdDHsUufDYOrrxZZjZ1qbjFx293jSsOX/8RMZjrpS5puMMDEKZI58hJCL2PH5wDFVPMFBjoh39todZbRBjDuketHJbfl8z2eOIkGwajipFnlsy3Phnb7AgEAu6b2Yk26B0s2w", 
		"answer": "25eqbZLw2BioBB3FHq34GNMSNZG78tYUpg==", 
		"explanation": "25eqbZLw2Biq/pZgU17hwPn2OG7eF2MDuj+RXaB/MHLsWbfNfej6iZh3Z12Hik5382SGpbfx8F4KgbxIqYGZMCYKeI1q2tWHw6TkzWtEIIoEjYh755JffeZFjDWoeNCbNPFpy3qIIlewZSD9BTBynT/TmDFRuoKy+yK/FNc21Ac7jsWIDs1bcc1WLzkKeyH2PjHp", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Breccia", 
		"option_b": "Limestone", 
		"option_c": "Quartzite", 
		"option_d": "Obsidian", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020123", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ3z54BgXRiy1/L8PivZECIepWuGXONhY3TnFKbRLuy+yph/NEibmFhv+3nI46jx41YdhqlXqYqKdWIXcctm3MPJ0/HlxXNIP89Qg8Bz6p5fb+BSyTOqYNyEYn1r1QsVKtvVJxNU5bARL0w=", 
		"answer": "24a5ZpXgxRbk8scGA6wLHiclGr2+ZFpfwDP4", 
		"explanation": "24a5ZpXgxRbk8sUpQV79w+n6OyvFEGcV43aNEqB7fmL3RrLBeuTxx9d1MlnJmVQ7+2LV46Hl5VINhqRS/ZffcSwHPph72tWH0PD/hFhVc89X2oEy958bdflFwimsZs2bMvFtxS6DKEjgaCq4ADB7knHFi3JS5ZCy7yK/FN0lwRw8hcWTDJbYnV+MJ0l96rjMzu7v", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Limestone", 
		"option_b": "Sandstone", 
		"option_c": "Slate", 
		"option_d": "Marble", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020124", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQn4+IYlQQ2yzPPpOmfGBnFRt3eGEqFmdXDoUKjVYK3xz9djKF+Cnhty/GLJ47b99l8Dirob75yedy8GcJ98iNSc0qTjyzFRO99Xk4Nz6NoZc+ZDyS7teN3QJb56y2OQIlfxcyyvATA0qD+WiXRXpoS+5me6Wt53yRY31oJg/ckyL96Q1/fRRh43rjuIRgIRIfOZfdWWGw==", 
		"answer": "24K9aYX71Avj+YJiDdEAUe2ASf1i1BrzBWt+Eg==", 
		"explanation": "24K9aYX71Avj+YJgWw2y0fX6dXvCDGEUsGzDULo0Z3nqV6+CfOL9woQxJk6MzVlp/X3DreX0+EQBz6FV/YHfYy8Ccodq2pCPxeXwyXRPJ9UEnpV3pI4QPOJB3jSiYcebMPZ33WeDJkmwZje5RHN8kTzfiX1a6IW05yS+R5gZ8w1qX46RkLuQQWoznXUs", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Erosion", 
		"option_b": "Weathering", 
		"option_c": "Sedimentation", 
		"option_d": "Metamorphism", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020125", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsXCAWbA0eWKjUqjQY+j6iZFjKFHJmVN+snXJrKn5+VRPgK4b5IGTZCcNPodu3tHJ2Oq30HlEc+NFiJR6o4lfb+FSyjyucYuZWWo5QqzC1qRXfzhoStWrWQ==", 
		"answer": "25e5e5D/xVtYTnUARZrDPr5hQJzbf9fb", 
		"explanation": "25e5e5D/xVnj5MUhXF733fzyJWfVQ20X436NEqpzfnTsQbSCfOL9wtdlL12dzV104HvV46Pi+F5Pm6BeqZyeYCsHPohgx9yA2eO3y3cBPslIjoV8pJYeavUAwzPtYNzeYNtv3HqIYFawdCyvAnF3kXMk+VlDLsWHJOa6nA8yX3QZ", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Gneiss", 
		"option_b": "Schist", 
		"option_c": "Basalt", 
		"option_d": "Quartzite", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020126", 
		"question": "24GwbdHjwxbp8pYzEhH0hf73NGXXCmwW42+RV+5xaHjwQK7Maa3sxpR6NBydhUl053HO46319kdPjqZfqZ6NdTEQa5lqiMSGl+L41nwBPcNT2pJ955EMPP1TjAGjNN/VL+lgjm+TGHrPWAaCO09Lq3OifkWy+maDsV5d/EIwPx9/", 
		"answer": "25i9fJD+3gv6/4wzX1zrTeXNv/UFcvxOzDQrq1cG", 
		"explanation": "25i9fJD+3gv6/4wzX1771r3rPW6QE3AeoHqQQeN2aTH0XK7BZq370Z5iM1WHihtp/XXNsOmw8lobh61JqYeYficMa5gjiMOM0+36wX9VMtRd1sB99toQaPxF3n2gccDaLfF83maJJAXiaDq2Fzw0gT/Sj25Rp8O4/Sa1U98kgBEnk8ds4og0NdCXmbyW5V29lAeWyWmUW/1lH1DZpdyt+FCJsod6jP7F+RuH7NnZsc4jNykWyQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Me,ta,mo,rp,hi,sm,sn", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020127", 
		"question": "24qHV67M7iaq/pZgU176zPr3eGzCAmYU43KGRqJ5f2PzXK7BLv/xypwxM1SImRt/+2XWr6Tp5BMOz6xS+pqWfiEXPoluxtSA2eO3y3cBP89DkpQy5ZQbPPBB3jbted3VJexvwn3Cno+ysY8pqSEaZaG4xMHbnQ==", 
		"answer": "25K2bZjgwlvQxH/GHHnGoE0sKCefpm6w", 
		"explanation": "25K2bZjgwlnj5MUhEhb7wvWyMnnRB2dRrnqXU657YmHrXaSCfOL9wtdlL12dzV9y4WbKorzjt1JPi6FI/YeRczZDfIphzNmH0KT4wjFNOsFMjsBz6p5fePVSx32gfdreMv9i3SwCH/Q9jg8b0yCJnpQu293I", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Gn,ei,ss,se", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020128", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gYBHxzu6/NmfREHEYpXaGVuN1YzHwUaPLY+jw3ZZjPhybglhw4TbHsaCw50EGgqlJ4IKGMCQMbIZqzJCd3/b40XZJc9JMn8Bz55kKceFMzSmke9qbIfBqjm2PKlXxZC20C340mzeWykBY6I6y+yKpVdZ30BQggo574c0vfOWa2Luc5hf4tQOG1XaURqllA03Zp8Gr4FDcsocroMGZ8TTJ+/m5jvDWsNoOcgdBtpJ2bFX8lqYNuCk3X9u7ZBtP8PDZblqtLy7jNAsZ8Mbm2GB6hpYhXH10/B5Qh8MWXs4zw5bguSA3MMNvVSS/olBIwoZ1URDWdbO8kG3270Y2enRp7tbwE67GR8xeSSZUHrVWLA==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRt3eGErFxcWLsWufDfOi+3YVkIhDJjFV/smLOpuXi8lIcgKYb4J3fZCoGPohg2sKM1PC3wWlRP8dKm5R765Rfc/IA2DWoNNXIM/t82mePKQf7Tohs58DQBb8tv3cmf+/q", 
		"explanation": "26a9bJj+1Bf+9pc5Egz9xvbsdWrCBiIXrG2OV6c0ZHnxW7LFZq3qwZIxJl+KmFZu/nfSqqr+t1IBi+hY5oOPcSEXd4RhiN+Pl+n+ynRTMsoEioFg8JMccPFTjAmlcZTJJf99wWDAN1f/cTC5AXQ0nSKWi3BFp8O4+jWpUdkjjFUzhcdr6Mw1MdKRzamB8Q2qiQWJzzuVR/1YHxSQu8qt7kfcsocroMGZ8TTJ+/m5jvDWsNoOcgdBtpJ2bFXw16sG9jk3XcGwaQZC/uqcIVXjJGigKAMN+Mj333tnho0vHXox8BZLh41CcYBn3pnw/DoxKcgqAD2+plZHyJp5HwCTdamw1Xrt7lJ/dHQvJY9/sz48rgHeNI5ccSl+J8q6QY1bgV5J2Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and the reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and the reason are true, but the reason is not the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020129", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gexn8wPLqJivCDGEasD+CQKY0dn7xWaLGLvn225hkIFTJmVN+smXJr6z0/lUGjKlP4IGRMCMNestsx9+F3urwhH5Hc8tLlpR36toSffNNzX2fcdXIL/A0jkOBIEjxK3mBCjBjnDTYynVC6IC0+iuoFNs5xFUhmYtx6cE6NdKMleiG5km9lAGN2WjRSf1nA02Koc+k50qGoZYxusPNoSDU9/HqibST/NsKZgFcuMZrbBuon61J/iUqXMmgYR1FsevWIV3qLi2sMh1d68Tg3WcroSbZBBsyUTQMBZ/JR1V02g==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRt3eGErFxcWLsWufDfOi+3YVkIhDJjFV/smLOpuXi8lIcgKYb4J3fZCoGPohg2sKM1PC3wWlRP8dKm5R765Rfc/IA2DWoNNXIM/t82mePKQf7Tohs58DQBb8tv3cmf+/q", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCyxvLtJ27TF24I42yXU7dxYzH3XKbWLuT5x5J+Mk/Jn1R4+WWGorf1t1UAnaVe7c6LeDAMa4xniMSB0qTky31IN89Ck4Nz8JMQcrRBwjntd9vULPdgyS6PIQX9aDWpAX40mTDRh30WnIu+tTW+Vck4zlUihIhu5Mw5OJeWyuiS5F63xgWNzmmUS6koUWiX9c+7q1eUpcI7usKBuDzctPv/2vXS99MKIhpXrJNzd0j8nqZJ+Wo7Q9GnfBNH/e3KYEDkLybjNxwS+s7wxTR+zoc7WCkg/BoGj4pYZ9Jy2oukqzskN8RkVSeypgRNxpNxXleFe7Gx1GHi+RU+e35rZJh/vSMypE+IIFFziW6QWilC1Ill6t9ZlERwcmNJmDbzli2eg3Gabpavq7zyxe7/srRq/KRnIEaOMFPNRc0OarDLNCUb0GNRLtEBBy+UC1qWBb5I", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and the reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and the reason are true, but the reason is not the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020130", 
		"question": "2523f9H+0Bfzt4omEgr6wL35OmfcDHUYrXjDQbd1ZHTuUanWfa3/25IxJFObn1545jbUpqLx5VcGga8b/YucZC0Nd4gv2NyIw+G3yX5XNstBlJQt2JQjcsdUzSmoedHVNL4/lC60L0Cwdyu0CXFmjXHVi2lFrcO082evUdkjzxs7lcdo4ckoOZeS1r6W5Ui2kkaLzzuSR7NyFFeNvMGmq0CJspA9u9me8TvVtODxn7j28cwfak9B/4t+bU+wkuY19hY2Yty1fBdG9OrEIQa3YBymJBoS98LglmRlx5YsHWQ74hpLh41CIsNyw4vhr3IzMMN8EDCuqktOh5dpTQWTeqmrkGHqoEE3cDoOZJh5tGom4QKdJkBynyWgQhBfp5Rq6tUUkAp3PTwa3ELlgSuEjmyMPIPv6pT5lqj9r69msqwxLFPAIVTdFp4ZaLqNIWtnw+3bDLVIO5ppGDH2NdA8+Xn9NZPUyzZNxNElb1Lm5j6R1d61Pne7pZvtj8B/G7EBOpHV/Me7/mDJXS3SNXyHY8bxVxywGya45wtmoxcrwSJQ+G7ZHIw/+CIbm3O1R1AkmzSgfG6om79O446XP4oj2uPp03ISgbR7kJXh0R4oTgu1zXxWoJaaQUhcgRTVH9gUzQcpTKAJEdbB/myCkGWQX3NNcsHgBOiI1Slamvf5iyFuup0HGIqCORDfyt813B+0D/JqRW/ouoO3f2sUKqeMNzhhawiX+P2c4qo=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz5Q7ltdLaeTtu7JQKX7mVx9Tcsd4=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxEh/8wb3MIWrEBm8UrWvDBuN1YnSjV6jQfOj93dkxE1mKmVR1+3WGs6nx41ZPgqdN7IOafjZDd5gvwd6N0uHzhGFTOstFiIl+/dobbv1WyTPtds2bI/Fg2GuDM0z/aXm+EWJmkT/CmTxfpsOv/SL7cdsl1B11hcd17MYoMNLTmamd7A2sjgOR2TuSXa92FFqNpo6r6laPpcIsvcjNoT7a4PHq2uzcsNMEdA0SsJB6cRuon61J6y81WIWyZAdC9aTRckDlJSasNB4V/NnmmDRa0oM9WGQx+gsG0MNfcYB62JvrriA1PNkqFCD6qlAA1ZFqWgWFca74xGDhoFY+YGkuKI9ruig2tU+OLVh/jmKTQj9ZnZAwvtkN0hcjaWdF3HXvjCmOg3GGc52j6JXul+3+tKoj5qsmPQGDNEnLU80MabLUIid/xf+eAKNSJ9MnGS3yfcEm+Xn2NJ6RzXka0cBgLmXo4SSd3I3GLWSutp/8gMA2R/8BMtXWqcq58FXJYizzM3iQcovmXAnjQHK4mytkpQwtjzJQ73DZHoBr9DkEkXCxRQR0hyvsJTynmawc/oqLP4M+xfDh2DwE2Ptumom3wBU5BwWomXdGvIuMX1RK31GYXuUCygorQPQOGprIsnmBmjbDX30ZesPzD7yUgy1a36PygXNvupMaG85pAoyhXeD3vb7Xg4O04YWL", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only One", 
		"option_b": "Only Two", 
		"option_c": "Only Three", 
		"option_d": "Only Four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020131", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fLfa39xoVjIl+dzUl+9XfUp6z+8BMbh60b74GNfSMXd4RhiN+Pl/D/wTFpOstFloFr5YlAQPp8whzjNODTJb5Gx2OBK0TpZir9E3VmkXHQhW5brYf78TK+FM44gAE6k8d74sQwNcSW1qbT50v4kg6HnFqEW6l2EFiQtMDo20+dtId4tMOJ8SbT8bTcj+rS49cKbEhis4drZhWAmZQH2mR4ZcCxKDpC/OXcYE3sM2i0IhwYuc3sxHlswsIvT2Y5tAlJjoBXbMlwlp32qSIkNsJkBnOpqklJy5VuHwOZNKmw33vhoEE3dG5rZphovTkwpU+IIFE+qmqfRSpYl8BC7dwYmwAjfmdBlXjzzAOFvGusMtPX44W8reH9obVi66I0aVaFJ1mYUIIOaLbEZ2Nnz6mPAuZIO5onFC3qMdw99Tb3YJmSny0F1ZkJIXPu9STZosH0LWD6spz9zsB+Ef8lI8PE+sK2vhz3bSL1JDOvaPf6fUawe3T9kyZsuhkpyTgR+yLPDZt6tSsCjHO1TQRmi2f0ZHnhhate7peNa4c+3bXj23IEkPE4tpXz3RwyBzS3jGtG8oaaQVlO2VyWCsUChDkvD70HHZWRwmGXgXOeCagAANqsxP3Jqn2DzYJ1XUU=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz8lvNZVVVGS0brA2j0aqjhLVI", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHb2BTr+4Q5Uw2+her3PGjYQ2MDpj+CX6x6dzH3XKKCd+Lrx5B0NEjJgFRu/GLHqquw5VIBiK1IqYGRMDYLe8t/xNGH0vC7hGZEIcMEnI9g6Z8bPPZZjCmlcZTULvlhx2CHZ1H1ZC2yCnl31DLZhnBfu4q0+2e5Uc4gxRA81pNw6IgVMtOW2KbT2EG5kgPC3XWVCKlsFBS8oNyp+EqdrsIIucyZtHybwPzwibjQ/9IHaxtbsIg/YV67lqZJ+Tg3RMawKEcbsenZbVjkLybjPgsc69ij13NmhoMnWSk3+xFSi41DZ9MzwpekqDo5LI1uFCr240dB0od1URDWYLW9kEDt7VQzdGMqdsp5s20nqByZaFU+nG6LDCFYmIxi89UNkBZwPWpBn36gmzqKkivPSJvmq4Pzl/r1o60j8600PkSSeRzMXpgPKfPJNCdd2v2SAqgcENEnIyrjfdo69DzrYJmEyzAC3spgP2Xo4iOdl438N2S5sIfrj8BzVLoYJt3E58qjuVPJcmPnLm/TcsPxGQ7/XXH5xwdquVgqzmEE4GeYIIBy9CEMh3+jBwZMo/GK58J/bIIrS8Hz+3DY", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only B", 
		"option_b": "Only C", 
		"option_c": "Only A", 
		"option_d": "Only D", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020132", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRr36NVqV7YnzwFK7RLuy+25JiMlCdzVR9smLOpuXg5VwMirtIqYGZMCcRcZhmx97WlTq8dVsgsKE9p60UU6vLzqs=", 
		"answer": "24P1e5nywRzut5MhXhL33L8ZkHF64n9aT73iv9BJOHtf", 
		"explanation": "25T4Xtzg2Rj68oFgRB/+yfjmdWLDQ2QesXKGVuNgeGPsQaDKLujsxoR4KFLJj0I74GPIraz+8BMYjrxe+8LfZyoKco4v3NiMl+vjzHRTc8lUjol96olffeZFjC+oeNXPJfou2mHAM0DzczazDXM0hCPZiXlFu4aot7H8NXMr6MezLr3v+qHTLMs=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Delta", 
		"option_b": "Fault", 
		"option_c": "Fold", 
		"option_d": "V-shaped valley", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020133", 
		"question": "24GwbdHA0Beq1oskQBvz1r3ZNH7cFyIYsD+CXONxaHDuRKvHLuL4k9UKxGTBPcz0GuPu1xDCLQwU", 
		"answer": "25T4fIPy3wrs+JctEhjz0PHrd4I149RxwfYU1ZXp6KB3lQ8=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHA0Beq1oskQBvz1r3ZNH7cFyIYsD+CErdmcX/wUqjQY634yIJ9MxyLgk519nfUuuXy8kcYiq1VqZqXdWIzf4hmztmKl9T7xWVEc8dKnsBm7J9fUvtS2DXtVdneMvdtz2DAF0nxczz/wJZDJE2i1dLoPaD832sHZA==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "A fold mountain", 
		"option_b": "A rift valley", 
		"option_c": "A volcanic island", 
		"option_d": "A transform fault", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020134", 
		"question": "24GwbdHUwxzr48USWxjmhcv+OWfVGiIYrT+iVLF9c3CjXbSCfv/3xJZjLlCQzVh652XDp+Xy7glNtaKS7T+Zudjo7MaushbG5w==", 
		"answer": "24G9a4X83xDpt5cpVAr7y/q9WwP9mb11taS3n7qsTE6tjQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHUwxzr48USWxjmhcv+OWfVGiIYsD+CErFxY2TvQOfNaK3qzJRlKFKAjhtp+3DSqqv3uxMYh6FY4c6XcTFDfYp629WNl/D/wTFkMtRQksdhpJkNaedUjCmiNMfLLPd6jm+OIwX2aCuwRHE0kDTGmHlFu4q0+2UtsxHxKpmyzdytt5TKs/xs", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Folding of rocks", 
		"option_b": "Glacial activity", 
		"option_c": "Tectonic rifting", 
		"option_d": "River erosion", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020135", 
		"question": "24GwbdHjwxbp8pYzEhH0he7qN2/FAHYYrHHDXaB3ZWPwFKbWNK9UYo6EUFnc4M6igJlkzdvr", 
		"answer": "25a3Zof2wx7v+ZFgUBHny/n+J2LVECCPn/B8ExYJyxlkVdqVuxoX", 
		"explanation": "24atapXm0g3j+ItgXR3x0O/sdWrEQ2EerWmGQKRxfmWjVqjXYOn/2550NByehV5p9zbJraCw41YMm6dV4I3fYC4Cao4vwcPJ0evlx3RFc8RBlIVz8JJfffpP2DWoZpTSLuphjnqIIgX9ZjepCHU2p4Gu7KPQC44xCpQoJLGvdA==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Transform boundaries", 
		"option_b": "Divergent boundaries", 
		"option_c": "Convergent boundaries", 
		"option_d": "Intraplate boundaries", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020136", 
		"question": "24GwbdH13gvn9pEpXRCyyvu/NH/fD24C43aQEqB4f2LmWL6Cb/7txpR4JkiMiRts+2LO+ecULRQRJ6kMtrgaf5LZhpWH", 
		"answer": "25a3epD/kQvv8oMzEPjRrk77g+hGN9//UgifvsI=", 
		"explanation": "25SsZ53/wlnr5YBgVBHgyPj7dW3CDG9RoHCRU680YnTmUrSCaf/x3p5/IByIn1Ru/HKGt631t0EGguhU786MZSAOe5lozdTJwev7x3BPOsUEk5N+5ZQbb7aZpR1ynGDkT6ZftSuM/4+R", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Volcanic activity", 
		"option_b": "Glacial erosion", 
		"option_c": "Coral reefs", 
		"option_d": "Wind deposition", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020137", 
		"question": "24GwbdHjwxbp8pYzEhH0hfTsOnjEAnEI43aQErFxfHD3UaOCeuKki4HxvpU6XGz9uFxzlm+2EHE=", 
		"answer": "24O9eoX60hjmt4gvRBv/wPPrdWTWQ3YZpj+mU7FgeDbwFKTQe/7qiwfy5dhqk5ZPoL77foPOTrA=", 
		"explanation": "25yrZ4Ln0Arzt5clVBvg1r3rOivEC2dRoX6PU613dTHhUbPVa+jwiYN5IhysjElv+jHV46bi4kAbz6lV7c6LeCdDc4ph3NyMm6TlwWJUP9JNlIcy7ZRfavFS2DSuddibLfF4y2OFKVGwczb9CXF9miXXg3IWrZKu/CuyVsg+1RhwCGAKKK7rvGyECE2fZ+I0EQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Plate tectonics", 
		"option_b": "Mountain building", 
		"option_c": "Vertical movement of the Earth's crust", 
		"option_d": "Earthquakes", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020138", 
		"question": "24GwbdHS3x3v5MUtXQv80fz2OyvCAmwWpj+KQeN1fjHmTKbPfuH7iZh3fR6LSNQiDkBJ3BU+HmmRbElE", 
		"answer": "25T4bp7/1Vnn+JAuRh/7y7+28kok1NdInP+BDhC7e+mC", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHS3x3v5MU3Vwz3hfvwJ2bVByIVtnrDRqw0ZHnmFKTNYuH32p5+KRyGixtv+nOGkKrl41tPrqVe+4eccSxDTodu3NXJ1urzhGVJNoZqm5px5dovcPVUyXHteNHaJPdgyS6UKAXkbzz9An9mmTDCg3NY6Iy9tSG0WN53zRonmJN55MYvfhiirLrY6H/xLCBGz6ThJYI=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "A fold mountain", 
		"option_b": "A volcanic island", 
		"option_c": "A rift valley", 
		"option_d": "A transform boundary", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020139", 
		"question": "24GwbdHUwxjk88UDUxDryvO/PGWQF2oU40qwc+NjcWKjRLXLY+zswJtoZ1qGn1Z+9jbEuv+yobNUweQ8N22agxy17ng8cA==", 
		"answer": "24exfpThkRz4+JYpXRCwMjEoWXxLdbl+C6NDtMnjCA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHUwxjk88UDUxDryvO/ImrDQ3IDqnKCQKp4aTHlW7XPa+m+y44xM1SMzV5p/WXPrKvx+xMOjLxS/4eLaWIMeMt7wNXJ9Ov7y2NAN8kEqIlk4YhdbrlsIdYVysHwRT3+PCvAoA==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Glacial erosion", 
		"option_b": "River erosion", 
		"option_c": "Volcanic activity", 
		"option_d": "Wind deposition", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020140", 
		"question": "24GwbdHw3hfp8pU0EhH0hc3+O2zRBmNRqmzDU7Bnf3LqVbPHaq3pwIN5fR4PWDVKc5znR+9cBDNd7p2t", 
		"answer": "25a3ZoX63xzk44QsEhrgzPvrd8XDF77B1nH/ZwNhnjZoThA=", 
		"explanation": "27mIaZ/00Bzrt5IhQV7mzfi/Jn7ABnASrHGXW61xfmWjQK/Deq370Z5iM1mNzVZy/nrPrKvjt1wJz7Fe6JyMMCMEcctuxtTJxPHn1H5TJ9UEjoh3pI4XeftS1X2icpTYL/B6x2CFKVHxa3m5FnlygHPLQGIcQSsBsrxFPNnKi5DP", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Continental drift", 
		"option_b": "Earthquakes", 
		"option_c": "Subduction", 
		"option_d": "Volcanic eruptions", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020141", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ3z54BgXRiy1fH+IW6QAW0ErXuCQLo0eWKjV6/DfOz93ZJjLkaMiRt56zbSq6Cw9EEKjrxS5oDffyRDcI54iN+K0uX5zXIBMNRRiZQtps3l9nHGo2s9kqJIUjXr+DU=", 
		"answer": "25GxfpTh1hzk48UiXQv8wfztLCkjscoRyZd5+4BRfA3ROZ79", 
		"explanation": "25SsKJX6xxz48IAuRl7wyujxMWrCCmcC7z+XV6Bgf3/qV+fSYuzqzIQxKlOfiBt65Xff46Pi+F5PiqlY4c6QZCoGbMcvydyF2PP+ynYBPsdDl4Ey8JVfbv1TyX2setCbJvF8wy6OIlKwaDq4BX59l3HVmGlFvMFlVa3uqsiDTxCahtbsQRO7", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Transform boundary", 
		"option_b": "Convergent boundary", 
		"option_c": "Divergent boundary", 
		"option_d": "Subduction boundary", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020142", 
		"question": "2523f9H+0Bfzt4omEgr6wL35OmfcDHUYrXjDQbd1ZHTuUanWfa3/25IxJFObn1545jbUpqLx5VcGga8b/YaaMCQMbIZu3NmG2aT4wjFMPNNKjoF76olAQPp8wg65dcDeLftg2i7RfQXEbzz9FGJ7lzTFmTxZrsO+5yioXdU5gBk3l4NrrdwzfMOX3OiV51+1hxKL03XRR7skF1uVsY6l5FaStIMxu97DjTzn+sftm+zW/dsFdkgA5cZZbFe416UG7SQsUMG6e1JK4+GQcUbkLSmxLgIEuc3sxHlswsItSGx04BAGlotTIsN82pTtrzs/MY1lE3OupkdUyJp1XFeGeLys1Xuq3FsDe0k/ZJ5osSg7tU/PchRKkm7cXD5el4V47ZAWk0RlcmNElXjnwjuEhXbPcpz3q5DwhPGwoflw+6QpIEeJNl3WQs0Oar/FZ258iv2TCOZaPI1qFjbvMttu8z+5JpmY23kA38wuO3bu+jnXrsPJN1ausob8g9F4AP9UbJHj5sez8FHIdC31IHSddYv1Sw2wW3T9kxxgpA0p3GEf7iLMAIw/0Cwfinb3WgRngDLzeDyjk7dS7cKNcIMhwfD/zjcU2PV2m9vx2xE4QgD1zx2H5VwnFB+g0bk9t/JwkuY=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz5Q7ltdLaeTtu7JQKX7mVx9Tcsd4=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VyEh/8wb3MIWrEBm8UrWvDBuN1YnSjV6jQfOj93dkxAVOFiRt2/WPIt6T5+UBPjrpeqYiQYi8Gest4wNWHl/DgyzFVNsVQlY5759oPcPVUyS7td9vXLPdqyyLAK0DxYzCzAzBgm3HCgnkWjYKp4S/8R5o00gAhgsd66MEyO5ec1qWD+kirlQOGnHqfTP1iHlidsMro/lOLoZA8poPNgiba4PH0n/bHsI9LaxsStoh8bEmukqsduCsrEc2mZwFC/uqQaEetLie3ZxoV/IvzxH1kx5AwHXkm+xxDkZAWZM9hlozsuXI2MN9nFCezrEoAyJI8WRiacP21333q9FQ2e2llJbl5vTkwrAqSPBQt2mKPDC1dh48r994amhZxeGxU3HfzwiuDhSWfbpzg7pPvxef24L9s/qcuJ0bAPE+YVYgScaHBKydmxamPBaMcNZB1GiPyNNogvDb/YJCb0z1N3dY1IWPm/SSK3I3dPGu5tt65gdp6Df8UId6F+t+2pFnKZC31Mj2SdM60WgfiXXn7x0An5BbdDtwdgwKiKmIjGxmB4A==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only One", 
		"option_b": "Only Two", 
		"option_c": "Only Three", 
		"option_d": "Only Four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020143", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRqmzDfIxAMHCjQL7Sa63xz9dhK12diBt5/WPIp6Ti7gxNMPWnXNPt6t56Yy9/10Mxcw==", 
		"answer": "24W5epD/3Rzmt4cvRxD2xO/md+GjEx3if5xU6rbbk6YRgxM=", 
		"explanation": "26W5epD/3Rzmt4cvRxD2xO/mdWLDQ2wetz+CErFxc37kWq7Ya+m+3Y5hIhyGixtr/nfSpuXy+EYBi6lJ8NXfZCoGPoR7wNWbl+vn0HhOPdUEm5J3pIwecP1EjCm0ZNHIYgKixChKyGVAhDfyCwu7R0k=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Convergent boundary", 
		"option_b": "Parallel boundary", 
		"option_c": "Transform boundary", 
		"option_d": "Divergent boundary", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020144", 
		"question": "24GwbdHM7ibVyLofbSHN+sK/PHiQEWcCs3CNQap2fHSjUqjQLvn2zNd8KEqMgF515jbJpeXk8lAbgKZS6s6PfCMXe5gvzMWMl/D4hHJOPdBBmZR765Rff+FS3jijYMebKfAu2maFZ0jxaS2xATIxsNfVMvCSnsO+EIS9A8jm", 
		"answer": "25i5ZoX/1Fnp+Is2Vx3mzPLxd2hQeW3mVBs/cIgFPkd6DBc=", 
		"explanation": "25i5ZoX/1Fnp+Is2Vx3mzPLxdW/CCnQUsD+XWqY0fX71UarHYPm+xpExM1mKmVR1+3WGs6nx41Ycz6xO7M6Lf2IXdo4vy9mb1PH7xWVIPMgElYYy958SdblGwCikcJTWIepr3GeBKwX5aXmpDHU0sTDEnnQRu8O29CmvWN91/PNsTFmmsTi1Q9Kgry//PA==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Ma,ntl,e c,on,ve,ct,ion,ian", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020145", 
		"question": "24GwbdH13gvn9pEpXRCyyvu/M2TcByIcrGqNRqJ9fmKjW6TBe//tiZNkIhydghtv+nOGs7f/9FYcnOhU786gTx08QbRQ9++26Nu3y3cBJ85B2qVz9o4XO+cAzy+4Z8CZBXPuGJFE4GnzjhAxWJXglw==", 
		"answer": "25O3ZJX63x6oALYczmKkz/tuGKq+LIwBlA==", 
		"explanation": "25O3ZJWz3Bb/+ZEhWxDhhfztMCvWDHAcpnvDVrZxMGXsFLPKa634xpt1LlKOzVR9smTJoK6w+1IWirpIqZuRdCcRPp9qy8SG2e30hGFTNtVXj5J3pq4fkUh4bj1PEJ6hGutoQwg=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Fo,ld,ing,ong", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020146", 
		"question": "24GwbdHM7ibVyLofbSHN+sK/B2LWFyInonOPV7o0eX+jcabReq3fz4V4JF3JhEg78zbUprbl+0dPgK4b/YucZC0Nd4gv2tmPw+35wzP9gZdvPxneNvOlMt481TGt", 
		"answer": "25KqbZDnk17DNqNNXSvv1Tum+aqUFQo=", 
		"explanation": "25KqbZDnkSvj8ZFgZB/+yfjmdWLeQ0cQsGvDc6VmeXLiFK7RLuvx25p0IxyNmF475nmGt6Dz41wBhqsb+4eZZCsNectgzpCd3+G35XdTOsVFlMBx65QLdfpFwinvUtcrYO2Su6UhB17Ps/6TNw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Gre, eat,go,od", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020147", 
		"question": "27i5fJL7i1nJ+Ik1XxCy5L2/ImLECyJRgHCPR656MFOhqNkkdgAd7eEfhPhSfEsQlw==", 
		"answer": "25O3ZJWz/Bb/+ZEhWxDhhbC/HWLdAm4Qun6QHuNHZXPnQaTWZ+Lwia1+KVnJwBta/HLDsOmww0EOgbtd5pySMAQCa4d7iPKGwurzxWNYc4sEqYF8pLsReOZFzS7tUtXOLOoijlyJIVGwUTixCHVth3GbyltErYKvtRWyUs539hQ+moJhrwkVjRTnESWTDixi67dY/OE=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHb2BTr+4Q5Uw2yxO/6dWqQE3AernaNV61gMHT7VarSYui+xpExIVOFiRt2/WPIt6T5+UBPiadJ5IubMCAaPp9nzZCP2OjzzX9Gc8lC2pR64do6feZUxHq+NNfJNe16ji7AawWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3/BsGnoI4zMY4OcTf9KeG5lm5jwiRnGyUWrgkF1uLuMusq0eJpcIsuo2ZuTeb5+H7nu3Q5NcEbEhducZra178uakT+yt4YcS1fBcL8+HeZFX5KGi3LwtdysT2wnwp548sT2A39REGso9XdsUzlqTqiDo1f/5rG3ObrUBSwpVvHzGXYbGskGH3oFR/Yn8nacdmsiIir0+IOlVwiW2TXiERkoF+8sRZlwt2c2tBjm+swjyDgXeOf4fm+YnmgOywoqAj+qw1IFuPO0jZWs0RaqXFKmJ83qmaAalSNN9zEiHyMtsn/3npLJeA2ipN7NcUJ3Kn0zick9m1C2y8p9LPj9h6EaZAP9+FzMqkpBzmZzHoInzTb9i0WAawSmT53h5pslgqzmEC4WTMSJ9++SEIh23wT0t2nyLkLHi0k/5I5cKaeo0l3Pvl3nICkfJslpXwlm0g7FBQI3peuWpxQLqZWOY=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Fold Mountains ,Himalayas", 
		"option_b": "Subduction Zone,Andes", 
		"option_c": "Transform Fault Boundary ,San Andreas Fault", 
		"option_d": "Rift Valleys ,Great Rift Valley", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020148", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gZhb3hdX2OGrcAnsQsD+CQKY0c37tR67Ga//7zdd3KFCNzVZ053jSoqz+5BMzgZRVqbyacTEMcNEv/NiMzqTgwWNEc8BLiI134NodZbRUxDjtd9vXLPd9x2GOZ0T+Y3m+C31khjTFmXVZpsO082evUdkjzxs7lcdo4ckoOcTdrTJzfih9GYQxHTK9yCKl8w==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRt3eGErFxcWLsWufDfOi+3YVkIhDJjFV/smLOpuXi8lIcgKYb4J3fZCoGPohg2sKM1PC3wWlRP8dKm5R765Rfc/IA2DWoNNXIM/t82mePKQf7Tohs58DQBb8tv3cmf+/q", 
		"explanation": "252xZZD/0ADr5MU3Vwz3hfTxMW7VByIXrG2OV6c0dGTmFLPNLvn2zNdyKFCFhEhy/XiGoqv0t1AAgrhJ7J2MeS0NPoRpiMSM1PD4ynhCc9ZIm5R399ZfbvFT2TG5fdrcYPdgjmiPK0GwajaoCmR1nT/FyMZVxKlvS0/sjrDDLRGRbwc=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and the reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and the reason are true, but the reason is not the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020149", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gZgzzy+75OnndQ2QQtnOXQeN1YnSjRqLRfuLw2p5zK1nJi1RpsmLOpuX2+EECjrxS5oDffyRDeIRjzJCE2PH50HBIPdUE2rx82JRfTvFB3zKjLpTvKPt3jmGDJFDiJy61AX40gDTVnnNYoYD75Su6QN8kgBg9gII47N89JZeZy6eeqEi5hQ7C02+ZTa8m7eixBmoFk5zMn52tijBxFg==", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/IXnFBi5RoWqXErd8dTHxUabRYeO+wIQxIV2Fnl45oLDgcbBIQ1kx++Pbe7CGMA==", 
		"explanation": "24GqaZ/g1xb4+sUmUwv+0e6/NHnVQ2wetz+RV7Bkf3/wXaXOa634xoUxM1SMzV104HvHt6z/+RMAiehd5oKbMC8Ma4V7ydmHxKi3xX9Fc9JMn5ky4JVfcvtUjDKud8HJYOlmy2DAM0DzczazDXM0hD3XnnlF6I604yL7Vc022VU0hIh1rc09P9/f1ryb7V/6koidDNgJnPe+Im4sGeW/3g==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and the reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and the reason are true, but the reason is not the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020150", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+cV6Ejfhyu7rNHjJQ3AUpXqRQeNgfzH3XKKCeOjs3Z5yJlDJgFRt93vDrbGw+FVPm6BeqaueYjYLOZgvy8KcxPC30H4BPsdNlJRz7ZRfeeVVxTGkdsbSNfNSwC68KQXCYjiuC34u1BjCynVF6Jez8GepUckizAFymYE44MkyKNuamauc5lu9hRKL03XRS6h2A1GXod3q6bBp8pTq5VgE+oAaovFsXA==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRt3eGErFxcWLsWufDfOi+3YVkIhDJj05vsmLOpuXi8lIcgKYb4J3ffi0XPp9nzZCK2PblwXJVc8Ncioxz6psLdftOjDKrNMDTJb5v3X2FNVH5aDf/urUQPfrwRmyfGAvgBuwGug==", 
		"explanation": "25yrZ4Ln0Arzt4EvVw2y1/j5MHmQF21Rt3eGErVxYmXqV6bOLuDx35J8IlKdzVR9smLOpuXV9kEbh+9IqY2NZTEXMstt3cTJw+zyhENEMtVLlMB799oRc+AA2DWoNNfUMuxrzXrAIl3gazizBWR9mz+NynVFp5Cv9DSiFNMkgBs9gsdr4sQ5MM7f2OiB7V6tihLC033RRbxqBVic9c2n5VWZo5YxusPNsifJ5vH3juuRC8jSb8fLDgIQ28+q+CyQ5Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> The Earth’s Crust >> The Structure of the earth to Earth Movements", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and the reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and the reason are true, but the reason is not the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030101", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt5EoV17m0vK/OGrZDSIFum+GQeN7djHvVbHDfbK8vBtzM25fVVZ+6NJkKkGieg==", 
		"answer": "25e5e5jwkRXr4YQzEh/8wb3+NmLUQ24QtX6QEANTDAgp5CY3P4TgwLxe4qU=", 
		"explanation": "25e5e5jwkTXr4YR6bhDQxO72NivcAnQQ7z+CXrB7MHrtW7DMLuztiZVwNF2FmVJ4snrHtaS8t1sOnOhaqYKQZ2IQd4dmy9HJ1Ov50HRPJ4YMm4J98Y5fKKENmW/oNOfSD6wnjm+OIwX5dHmvAXx1gDjAj3BP6I+04meyWpohyQYxmZRx+dF8CN+WyuiV5Fixgg+WxTuQRLFrBkfZvNro/0zcpo43oo2IsCHS+O25m/bXsNEdZxoSs4lxZBu4nrsd+SQ7VNv0XxpO/6TZdRT+LySqIwcb8M7wmjRg0sIvUns5519Eg5BXbtQ/lpmkuDMiNIBpGj+1sUFEh4ZzXBzWSLOE3knn6VE2djoHZJxs5hE7gAyVLF192medWi0d1JB5990Yhw1vZC9SlG/vjjafiWbPfZ3nq5PziO3kqbRm4eMmJ0WFJlXMX45cbL2AJGh/2uaIBLJVPJErVyrnLpUvvDHwJ57UzDAB2dohb3To+j6cnNm1cWKotpPti8Y2ALcBOJGTuo73g1XoM2PnLm/TdMPtVgT5W3X7mk5Rvx1lwCgX4CLLAYV29ixNnXG+XUFqhmftbXekhf5I4oudP4IwxfSs0CcTkLR1kInylAs1VAe0mGwDpoyeQRxNzEffHY0LxR8vTJYEF5fE4WjWmnCQQmgeP9r+CKuMgy9H1PD4nXV4sZMXGcyHOFnfhds1xlClQft1WnCtrYfqNPAMSmUi/vJyy+Pho9i6ZbOjLXYvfFb3VepY95xfb0JvHkvYHTRDb6unQJheRPJawmHDmAlbBcBOwmgcSOXbVGNGYW5S3H8=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Basic lavas and composite lavas", 
		"option_b": "Acid lavas and composite lavas", 
		"option_c": "Basic lavas and shield lavas", 
		"option_d": "Acid lavas and shield lavas", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030102", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxQD68sUvVF7+xOv+JivWDHAc42yLW6Z4dDH1W6vBb+PxzIQuZcmRID5fpCcm2rMEwW7gHXk=", 
		"answer": "25e5e5jwkRXr4YQzEPcYzMEaqFwm1AfUhK5Bzdc=", 
		"explanation": "24awYZT/1Vn8+IkjUxD9wO6/NHnVQ3IDqnKCQKp4aTHlW7XPa+m+y44xJV2ajFdv+3WGr6Tm9hM7h6FIqZqGYCdDcY0vxNGf1qT+1zFNPNEEk44y95MTdfdBjD6iesDeLuoijmOBLEz+YHm0EDB5myPTynpavYq/tSa1UJo7xQYh1pFx/sszKcTf/b2WqFm3xg+WzzuXRKhtFV2NrILo6UKPoY4svM7NvTPN9bT6m/aT9tIEdUhdqYNtI1ezma9J/CMrRcm6axdYvaTRbVjiNyGtIE4U7Yv32TR61pAsXG10+wpSwopYItd60p2o/DU1MdlmEH6pr0tQzpp7HxuXbbiqwySk9102dnJrYoN7uT51sgeVLVh62n2TQC9Qmo9u7ZANnQFqby9DlHfygzyfhXeGb4fq6MD+l+fxpPli/KdnLU6NMBHLXowMYLeAJndiz+iJDKhfNt9CDyPrLdkr73n2JtaH1zAI3N1gOXjr9yuXncjmeWy0sJ7sitE2ALcPJdSF78SivliHaC2hNXWWJuP1Tgn5Rn32kyd2uxkrzDJcqHHNC4E/9D5Ns3+lR0UkvijhLH2vkv53446PaoswkU5HopTtw/L228c59XB7klg=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Basic lavas", 
		"option_b": "Acid lavas", 
		"option_c": "Composite lavas", 
		"option_d": "Cinder cones", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030103", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxQD68sUvVF7kyvH8NGXfBnFRom2GErd8dTHrXaDKa/7qiZZ/IxyEgkhvsnXJrqj/+QxNSx8ktlK0jj+6nkN4LSAVzA==", 
		"answer": "25a3ZYH8whD+8sU2XRLxxPPwMHiS1fxnjRkCgnxAD6l3aMd4eg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH72B7i8pY0Egj9yf7+O2TVECIQsXrDRrpkeXLiWKvbLv7q25ZlKEqGgVh6/HnDsOW4+EFPjKdW+YGMeTYGPp1gxNOI2evy1zgBB85BiYUy5YgaPPhB3jqoOJTINPtr3iOTLkH1Y3mrC3x3lT/Zj28WvIu64We6Rt93wgA7mpM44s58PduL3Lqd6VmxiAHC0HqITa93UVuf9cKp/ULcpo43ot7B8STU+Pf4lPHQsN8YakQSvoh7I1Son60buDw3Xcu1ZhtIseDVY0bkM2iHMgtd7cSjwnxsz5BpWHEk+BBVi5VTIs5ywo32uXIxMckqATu/41BZ15FvHxiQNLC512XloEE3dG5rY49ouG0hqQqRaBxxnH+ZQmxQmoRu7dkNnAcjaWAAjn75jTOClGyMNd+j/4j5nKjzobcj8LYuJUXAJlXfWIQabLDBKXMyz+WeG6dIOpBpBGBkE7VWab8JBLU2SCkApJJk", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Shield volcanoes", 
		"option_b": "Cinder cones", 
		"option_c": "Composite volcanoes", 
		"option_d": "Lava domes", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030104", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq9sUwUwzz1vTrPGiQAG0fpiDBEG4rKziUl2VUnW8gpSICtQ==", 
		"answer": "25T4e5zy3RWq4YosUR/8yr3rPWrEQ2QesXKQEqx6MGXrUefRZ+n7iZh3Z13JgVpp9XPU47P/+1AOgacZecTE7Vk2JkF6J6PQFy9svg==", 
		"explanation": "25T4eJDh0Arj44wjEh39y/i/PHiQAiICrn6PXqZmMGfsWKTDYOT9iZR+KVnJmVN65jbArLf95BMAgehP4Yvfdi4CcIB8iN+bl/f+wHRSc8lC2oEy6JsNe/FSjCuieNfaLvEu53rAJlf5dDyuRHZmmzyWj25DuJey+imoFNUxgBkzgIY47MY4fMeGy6eQ5Eyrkg+BnHaQXLh2GFWV9dqg+UyJp4p4ucyZtCDa+LTvn/bH454EcEhUrYd8d06ukrtJ9yR4RcCxKB9K+OqQd1vhIymtKEJd68r33nF7hpYhXGd08g1Jj8NCasUz25ntsnIjKsBnHCf6tUFO09RIVxKFcf2732bh8xU8dHRrYJh4rDl1sgaRPVhqm2WZQzlCmJkr6dkNnUR3dWoAjGTpjz6ZmSWZc5/g6o7zxefi4LRq9aszaUOFNlPVU80dZqfJMWIy3eGSAaMcJ5diVy/nNNtu6jb1I5ea0Hkf1dQhJnn0tC6WgMD0N3H6nIT8nJRiHbIFepHEqdi+vlvLZGPtIG+UY4viVgTzTnL3kw1kuVgkyyIF5XfUCZ16tSAYkmq5WUhh0jfhfn2yn6pV6cKNcIA0wLms2jsGkfp/35Ljx10vSwuriGwDs8SNQElIxRTXEMlHzRs8CbMUGJfDsmyGhXPRWX0DfMu2MamVwj9BzuryzmJysZUdFY+PIlnZj541zRK/QfJ3FWrspp+5LugHC3Aj7L19yeyvuM+oNfKqKCU5ZxOyVesZ5ZpdawN1Hg7ORSVdb62gUt0KSeUPxXrYmwMKAS/W24yNh7k3rOrKIpcZBw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "A small volcano that forms on the side of a larger volcano", 
		"option_b": "A large volcano that forms on the side of a smaller volcano", 
		"option_c": "A volcano that forms in the ocean", 
		"option_d": "A volcano that forms in a lake", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030105", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq9sUjUxL2wO/+ailxralfdAZqCKDkjtvjcD0E", 
		"answer": "25T4ZJDh1hyq84AwQBvh1vTwOyvEC2MF43mMQK5nMGbrUamCeuX7iYN+NxyGixt6smDJr6bx+VxPjKdX5Y+PYycQPC1LWT+AeFlQK93nyN8Rbco=", 
		"explanation": "25T4a5D/1Rz49sUpQV7zhfH+J2zVTyIEsGqCXq9tMHLqRqTXYuzsiZN0N06Mnkhy/XiGpari+lYLz79T7IDfcWIVcYdsyd6Gl+Hl0WFVIIZFlIQy8JIacrRDwzGhdcTIJe0u+maFZ0b/azW8FGNx1DjFymhPuIq49Cu3TZojyBByhIJr+MQofNiZmbyb7Q29ixaWxXKfT/1rFxSNvcvo5kKbrYN4tsWMvDDe5rT7n/bW8coDIhxausZpbFe/lqYGuC4tQ8G6b1JK/6TVeUThLzuqMQtd/Nn2xmBgyYxpamEx+l9SiopFIsN715XmuSBwNt4qBjq9rU1Gzpd9UQOabf293Xjw6VA7OTo/bY9/uWom4QGTPBR7lGSJSyQRh5V77t8LgURlcn0AiH7lwjCdhXeDZZrt7MDuiuv77Plv96IjIE+HdUjXFpkUYPPHNWhnxO3bHrNeIJZjHizhfdQg+Hn/L4SZ1jcKkNhgI3b18y/ZlsjlK2CpoJv2gJY30tDqOQweMmqawdJN/JRJ", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "A large depression that forms when the top of a volcano collapses", 
		"option_b": "A large depression that forms when the side of a volcano collapses", 
		"option_c": "A large depression that forms when the top of a mountain collapses", 
		"option_d": "A large depression that forms when the side of a mountain collapses", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030106", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt5EoV17m0vK/OGrZDSIFum+GQeN7djHqWrPQe/7335IxK12HiV104HvV/OdDArmmtRydRtRvl62RXQTu", 
		"answer": "24axZJ3gkRjk88UkSxX31r8Mjhn0RQGZJAKnEaxYWRD2", 
		"explanation": "24W0fYX83wqwt7EoVw33hfztMCvcAnAWpjPDRrpkeXLiWKvbLun7zIc8NFmImV5/snTJp6z15BMAiehS55qNZTEKaI4vwdeH0uvi1zFTPMVP2rR64YgaPPVSyX2pfdLdJexrwHrALEz+Yyr9C3Y0hD3DnnNYu8/74i+yV9J3yRsxmpJ86JIAMuuR+6mH4EK0jxKKzyHRfLVhAlHZtNytq1eUpcI0tN+KtCHPtPv/2uzb9Z4bbh1GsIh2YBu+mKwA/Tl4UMawKBFE5+HCIVXjYCmxIg9d/tnm12Bs1MI9VWg6tE4W0sNFc9VyxJ2ktzs8MMBvATaosAR0z5FlHxSXev2+33rpoEE3cDooapho/CIz4QKdJk0+l2SJQjhQnY4r7NEXkgFwQWFziHnjiSzRwFGHeYDmq4HugKjjqbRq/qI1aVWPdV7ZQoUTabrUL3QyyPyPTbVRMpNrEjCmNNtu7zDjJaqa8zgO09YsJmPv53DZpsXwKmD6soD8ztljB7cSOd7IpNi/sUzCZWPoL2mBc9j9VgbjD2jw0holsRc3yyRQ/GrdSIZp8D8Bh3e+TgR2nSTrLHCgj7tO+cKacM4wwfbknScAj/Vqm4jL2i41Swio1z93uoGMShxO31GWDcUCwR1jAL0KEdbY/HmEgGXZRHIeP9r+ALzH0Dxa3+L1zm5oq4cPR4idbBvenskjzRnxDfxgUHX+6In/fewHDykp4rti3uSvsIqpevCvYCU6bgi2VeNc/9VFZ0JvGQ6dCSVWZaqnWJoiT8RG2XDZzUd8T3paABrN6a1IXAi5pYTbZm/bd/wQBxXnI7EQB477W1OPNPK7xyPaRquUkAeuTUFoSyKUMqQE6wCwaIPxL1O/knFh68jrNW1VcowbPyb9fWj5i6aAABV6NyM3aLpLb0DGAkpkoDbGNPwnjLUFMBs0TaGpHUIflRBD3zPTHUtAowwRWeWkTkc1P7pMNl5R3zi2GrNfSBTLknoFgFWZgjDpOehOIkwtb2GXz1jontJlkPHtl4eVGZTtP/0P2p8MKaJIBJXQX00TlvDl4e7lAiwWEGhlbuzBU+ed8Fv+B4jnt9HIyklFzbcGMRN7KTyYmt/L9SlkPLFOYWQKq3wVr8vcawXq1IlN0EJhUVms8FPrRWIl9hBkb4qnKtHZK42s/lcfGSrLTvlXkPk4ziPoPNvYYhM6AyM4kACdd5LayyGEfanj0KIaABzguGWAL4U+j0vxPE15/RqYFA==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Sills and batholiths", 
		"option_b": "Dykes and batholiths", 
		"option_c": "Sills and dykes", 
		"option_d": "Dykes and laccoliths", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030107", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq9sUzWxL+mr+U1A45dXhs70XMWXD2Xz0N", 
		"answer": "25T4YJ7h2APl+ZEhXl77y+ntIHjZDGxRrHnDX6JzfXCjQK/Deq332td3KE6KiF87+3jSrOXk/1ZPja1f7YeRd2ITcophzcPJ2OK313RFOstBlJRz9oNfbvtDxy7vCuDNatur9xRAD7KY8c96UA==", 
		"explanation": "25T4e5j/3Vnj5MUhEgrzx+jzNHmQS3EZpnqXH699e3SqFKXNavS+xpExLlKdn05o+2DD46z3+VYAmrsb+4Gce2IXdop7iNiIxKT+ymVTJsJBnsBi5YgecPhFwH25e5TPKPsuwm+ZIlf5aT79C2I0ljTSjnVYr8Or+Sa1Ucl3zxNygo99rdspLsWQzKaX4UO/xhSN33DRRLx9FEaK9eyt6EKJs4d4usvNpTrS57Tpm+rS/NIObkhdrY96bU+9g6EG9mZ4QsG4ZAEL8uXeIVboYDyrKBsa8d+j2XIpx5FpVWYm/QVJjJdXboB62Iz2qSE5MMN5VQeypl0AwZtuUleBfLi2kGXl51g+NX8zdYZitTkm4RiZKV9wn3iPST8RloV/6dUcm0RweGtJkXPulj6ZmSWAbtP15Iz/hOb5o/lv87oiO1LMdU/JQ4gZf7rOICdwz/2MCKNSc4tvEi+mPNsqvCr2LJ+Q1j8U2dcnb2PotCyWgMC1OCW2sov8nJR5Ev8JMd/A5t6k8E7IYiijSrGu2zKwEHAciC0CHmUyUQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "A horizontal intrusion of magma that is forced into the bedding planes of sedimentary rocks", 
		"option_b": "A vertical intrusion of magma that is forced into the bedding planes of sedimentary rocks", 
		"option_c": "A horizontal intrusion of magma that is forced into the cracks of the rocks", 
		"option_d": "A vertical intrusion of magma that is forced into the cracks of the rocks", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030108", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq9sUkSxX3mr9CQ6iDoEW64T9iJDjrlfUs", 
		"answer": "25T4fpThxRDp9olgWxDm1+jsPGTeQ20X43KCVa51MGXrVbOCbfjq2tdwJE6Gnkg75n7D46f181cGga8b+YKeficQPoRpiMOM0+36wX9VMtRd2pJ955EMPveHC0Naw4sojOjPb/zB2D0=", 
		"explanation": "25T4bIj41Fnj+cUhEgj9yf7+O2SQCnFRoj+QWqZxZDHsUufRYeH3zZ53LlmNzVZ69XvH47H49kdPjL1P+s6eczAMbZgvx8SB0va31n5COIZIm5l39olfVeAAxS7tdZTPOe5rjmGGZ1HxZSyxBWI0myOWmXRTrZf7/CmvRs8kyRo82sds5ckofNKWzaCW+g27kxKRnHqSWrJ3AhSVtNet+VDcqYx4tI2dvTPV9ea5jfnf/J4ZbQtZ/5VrcU6/g70b/Tl0EcemKBtF5euQYBThITGmNU4S64v22Hho34c7WG10+R5VkcNZZIBh2ZvvgDwMMelzHjap40dBydR6UAWbNLS2kGmk9lQtfH8/fMpium0ioBaPZBR8j3/cWCRUjcBq7NVZmAtwaS9Dk3vtjTGHmSWJc4Hu7oS8kuD1rvlu86QqKAGSPE/dRc0JdfPGNWh/iv2TCOZ5Mo1zH2X1fdgv8i31JdaV0T1NxNElITfk+yWVgY30N2H6oJ31h9B/ErYFJZHS4N+/uVKHYGPiM3yQbYv9V0jkR3m40BxwpAxl/CkVqG/ZD4R+tS4MkD6yTARhmzPoaW7hlL9P646ado1x3OeszzoJl/hxi5L0mF09SQD7mXdG8peWVVkPwlKWCsUChA0nB7FBF5ffsnuXh2+QTG4Iftr6GOi0zCFNmufohWRu/5EcUMyBIhXCyt9mzhKmQf58W3PkpYPtOO4GSnAk87F6hq22v8O3cLOrOG0vfQn3Wu5Xs5dUKApuHw/PACBcILeoFpAbVeVdwTXenw5LTD0vjABD6V54EinL1DQ4VDDk", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "A horizontal intrusion of magma that cuts across the bedding planes of sedimentary rocks", 
		"option_b": "A vertical intrusion of magma that cuts across the bedding planes of sedimentary rocks", 
		"option_c": "A horizontal intrusion of magma that is forced into the bedding planes of igneous rocks", 
		"option_d": "A vertical intrusion of magma that is forced into the bedding planes of igneous rocks", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030109", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq9sUiUwr6yvH2IWOPQVIgi/YbmjNS/DxrJF10ht8=", 
		"answer": "25T4ZJDh1hymt4wuRgzn1vTpMCvSDGYI43CFEqpzfnTsQbSCfOL9wtdlL12dzV104HvV47L48l1Pgqlc5I/fcy0Mcpgvyd6Nl/f4yHhFOsBNn5My65RfaPxFjC64ZtLaI/ssnqtbvvFwFrbeIH5CWerGVQ==", 
		"explanation": "25T4apDn2Rbm/pEoEhfhhfy/OWrCBGdd43aNRrFhY3j1UefLaeP7xoJiZ06GjlA7/3fVsOXk/1Ibz65U+4OMMCQRcYYv29+F3uD+wnhEN4ZJm4d/5dobefFQjCqkYNzSLr56xmvAAkTiczH6FzB3hiTFnjxioIb78yipWdsjyRo81oh+rcl8PtaL0aef4VmwxhKbzHKSSbFoCBSWts29+VDctIoqutiKuXLatOf1le+T89EEbgFcuMZvcVS/krsauD4wUNz0fBNA9PeQcVjsIy3jJQsT/Mr33jR9zodpeGgm4BcBkcNFd9J115vh/AY4Nt4qFD+2rFNTh4B0WlebfbO9wmno8xUofG4jbIQtqCUw4QKdL1l/2n+TDC9DjZN//9wVnB5mPW5OmDbmjS2GwGaAfYHw7s37l+n5rrxnsrEoKkqTdXPOU59ccbrNIisyz/uUHq9TPd9mGSamKdAt6Db3KZXU2TYf09wzb3Tm+mqcit36KmD6p5r8ztZ3ALcPOtjR4Yu2pBzTaSahBHyBcsOzSkjjWm7+0g1g+1gqzjUV5iLZG8l+tT8IjWu8XQRrlGf1fHCokKoc64yKP4sj3Obl0jxQl/I4i5PylA4pVRa0mHFHu4qYD05Azl+WEswewRs9Tq0xcqOT3eghDU/JArwT85Q=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "A small, intrusive body of igneous rock that forms when magma cools and solidifies within the crust", 
		"option_b": "A large, intrusive body of igneous rock that forms when magma cools and solidifies on the surface", 
		"option_c": "A horizontal intrusion of magma that cuts across the bedding planes of sedimentary rocks", 
		"option_d": "A horizontal intrusion of magma that is forced into the cracks of the rocks", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030110", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gZBH+xvzxPGiQAG0fpmzDU7FxMHfsRqrHaq3pwZJ/Z1CIm1o783jC46rk/1Ydz75U5Y2efisAPoZu3NWb3uX71zFAIcMEn4p3544aeLRG3jKgNNWbNvtg2i6BKUGwZSy0CHQ0gSGWizxVp42+uDSzVcoyxFU6n4t0rccufNqQzKaH6US2ugi+0kmUSa5rHw7Zgcatq1CUoZI99cKL8SbT8bT6lfbWsNoOcg1cu5U/bFX8g6AMuD4hQc30ZxQL/eXGYBTsLizjMwYYucru2WFn0sImWyk15xcGg41SIs9n3p32/DY1Pd9jBnOuq0VUh51vHxKccb6s1Wyme34wO4+GgLQLc6nJe6DrjQ==", 
		"answer": "2/eUj7p7v2OmqkEH6QMkWnQs", 
		"explanation": "24O3ZJLy3xDpt4YvXBvhib3+OXjfQ2kfrGiNEqJnMHLqWqPHfK39xpl0NByGnxto8XnUqqSw9FwBirsXqY+NdWIFcZlizdTJwOzyyjFNMtBF1sBz95JTPPVOyH2iYNzeMr54wWKDJkv5ZHmwBWRxhjjXhm8WqZG+tSKxUdkjxRFykJV34Ig9fMGa17zT7FiqjwiFnHqfCLh2BESNvMGmq3eUpZE99cCMpTfJ/fX1ibjS890ebx1evpJ6I1qumL0H/GosWc30fhdF5aiQY0HkLCyqKQld7Nuj1zRqyYwsEHo89Q9DhsNea8x/lpf2/D8/KsN+FDq0n0p8yaB0WleFfLyo1Sjr5hUrfX9rZoVjuW08sk+VJlB7n2/cRSJXmJVu8NMckURhZC9WnWTpjSqYwGOOf4fs+ZOwxeH+o7V29qopLgGUPVmYQpQMYPPPISd+y/+aTe5LO5pzHyf0fdw6vDDqYJSVzDgBxNAjYzfm+i6cgcThMGb2853rzsZ+DbAMP8XM6oL3sVLDITfpJD2Sa8ThVxywQHq40h1t9xkrzGEf/GrdGsl78C8fl23wXUxlhmfpfzyknLtf/oeKP6g+wbXpxTMdiPh909v11Q49SxCyjj9Ps5KeD0hKw1DFXtkIhA8iA6NBGZnD9y2TlGXZR2VNfsDyQauGzWxbyvH0j2U9sIUaFYOYKQubi54qyQW2BO85VHXoqcq5L/kGH2g487x2iuSv98v7c/+lOHEvfVq0VuFcs7pfKBZzFEvSESxKcvimV5MaDaBC3WfP1xFBVHxGEEmM96keXBfqps3DayrfbbUZHRf2arBFHNy4XE/WOv2g3DnKRquZm0P+S0tlTC+ULbRN9hP1f5z3NlOwnGZh6oHnN1JaUZASfDP7cXL5oayNTBJ6eSAqP8pGaQfQSgMtmCf/KcVpvqhMMAwlROi1HFEFmR8PjyzdGFFBtV9eXuW7QV8uLulAOEsdzDm0BakQUlzMiShKml6ZgiTjO/dKJUAsdSSSgUigiJpnj/qpjYjBHNvuLrwV245DK7lVQYmUsd7FnSisrYm3WUFHSwSMDw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030111", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gZBH+xvzxPGiQE24Qt3qCR7A0cWPmFKHNfOD7zddmL1mHzVd65HeGpan/4EBPgL1PqYGJdTBDf8t4wdSMl+XlwXABMshA2oN965YMQPp8wg+odcfULqQu+maFZ1f1dCyxEHl6k3HGhn1CrYKutS6oFM4u0Bwxl4t09Ig6MNaLmaeBqEq9iBKOxTuCRLJ0GFqe9zRM29jxhQ1N4TnsLlnTPrU=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiIQrXvDYON9YzH3XKKCbeLs25JyMxyMlUt383jHt6z/+RMJgLobyMzhe6ddeFdnLLMGFYjfRT4E", 
		"explanation": "24O3ZJLy3xDpt5UsUwr3xOjsdWrCBiIYrXuGV6c0dn7xWaLGLvr2zJkxK12fjBt9/nnRsOX/4kdPgL5e+86eMDUKeo4vycKM1qT2ynUBMMlLlpMy0JIWb7RDzTPtfNXLMPtgjmiSKEiwZnmuDX5zmDSWh31Fu4qt8Ge+Rs8n1Bw9mMd3/4g6LtiSmaWG5FmxlgqHnH6DXa1wGFuXpo6n/UaO4IN4pcifuD3ftPv/2uza/dtLVgBX/4p+dVrw178B/SR4WNz0ax1E/feQYFrpYDusKwcZ8M3q02clhoE7WGgg8QwGg8NaY9J009Skuj4xK41lB3O9pkpUy408TBuZZLS21yjh7FApdG4uYcphvSMxpwCOJRR1lGSLQmxQh8BqvsYWmQdic2ZD3GbsgyuOgXCzcq/t34j5xfr1s6xv5qopLgGQOV3MU4wJJbrTZ3Nr2uCYDKpQKt9hGyPyfdo8vD78LoKYxnke3NYwJnngtCickczgKmD6p5r8zth3Ar5AMN3K/tj3pFnJZWP1Lj2AdtnxWAywQGnskwtzshYp0WEf/mfKSIg/4iQJmz6xW0Fl0hPoaTytmalZ+MKYdp0y3OblyStQl/I4kpr5zV0oXhS+nj9MtMSPQ11byFXDU8sI1gQnArNBGJfH8y3ehmPTQzwMbI70ALuGzzhB2aP9j3d89tAPWYCBOwqbntYjxVelDr16WnHousb8JegQBHcl7Lcx2OimvsW1ZrOzJXEiLwiyVe5N+oNUZBs7FwfcEWRcdaqoV54bUtxB7nv5mEsIU3dMRUjJ+rsHU0SrqcfdfGvKZr0FThv6c78EGsDrDlDHLLG/xzzKB7GVlgeuU0UxSzuIMvAZ4An0Opj9ZBuyhW0k/83kJhFUVsMQOSnneHL5tq+MGw80eGwxLZhVe07bCZJDtPQvgJzym8Ut9yXLOc8=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030112", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gcR/+wfjtNHiQAnAU43OCQKRxPDHhW7DOI/72yId0IxyNiEtp92XVqqr+5BMbh6lPqY+NdWIFcZlizdTJwOzyyjFVO8MEjo9ipJUZPPUA2jKhd9XVL75twWKMJlXjYiqBCkx6pjTXmXNY8sOY9Cu/Ucg201Uxl4k47818L9KJ3LqS5A21jwqHzzuGQblhUVWXsY6r6k3cood4s8KfvDfftPbg2vmT5t8Zaw1GpsZwZRushacK/TkrVNv4KBtF8ujFZV3jJ2imPx4R9tjqwHEpw5A8TX09+xFVzsNCasUzwZHwtDYiPtprGXO1pQRNxpNxXleQZrK1kGrh7lA+YXJrcYJo/Ds6rQydJlsy2mSODDhZkcBo8dwVlBRweC9Pmjb0ijrLlmqDf5Lt5Mfvxfr/r78hKJcNbRP1wTq9yqbWq9Gdxg==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiIQrXvDYON9YzH3XKKCbeLs25JyMxyMlUt383jHt6z/+RMJgLobyMzhe6ddeFdnLLMGFYjfRT4E", 
		"explanation": "25a5ZJX2wxj5t4QyV177y/n6MG+QD2MDpHrPEqF7Z32uR6/Dfuj6iZN0N06Mnkhy/XjV47H49kdPjrpeqYiQYi8Gest4wNWHl/D/wTFVPNYElYYy5doJc/hDzTOiNNfULPJv3n2FNAXEbzCuRHN7mD3Xmm9T6IC6+2e0V9ki0lU2g4I4+cd8KtaN0KeG+w2olAmB2WiCTa4oUV2XtsK970qSp8I9rd2BviHS4vG5n+rG4MoCbQZB88Zra178gKEd8C4qUN+1ZFJE96TdYFPgIWilNQEQucnm2HFo0oppSWExtAlJjoBXbM8/lpf2/CY4Oo1pGj+2olRTwtRzWVeCfLj4xmfo41Qxej04JZhisysJrzOSC1Vynm6OTT8Rl4FlvtIc1Rdma2pSnXqgjzaHhXbPa5rn7sy8hOb04K1r97pnJkeUMFKYUIIOaPPBIXN32KmaTbZdIYtuFDfqPMci5XnpL4GRzT8Y3JkhIXOn8TKJnsLmMHO/84T2gtd3GrYDdtTT7MWj8GjPZGPiLnGfZ9vnXEj8Sn3u1h0ltR0twS8UqGOYBIht8ihB3n25W0dxnibyLHikhqxZ+ZGHcIB9k+Lk1DEY2Pl5htvywhgyUxG6gXNa8oKWQ1AP2l3CFo0QxR0rHvQVG9bX/X+b1XeQSG4Ma8vkQaSGyCl01N//vW4x/4QGUMycKRjIhdBmyRSyFO94QWLhscb8JewZC20i6fJ5xfrhtMu3cfa2LXZqbBu5GelW4ZgRfAppHh7aDWRLab6oU48bT/QP1XDFmwhPTnxICRrc6acLWBe5r9eKcOF5jGyNmY0717jVbIf1zw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030113", 
		"question": "24GwbdH+3gr+t4YvXxP9y732O3/CFnEYtXrDXqJ6dHfsRqrRLuzszNdOGGO2smQ783jC46Hp/FYczQzN399fBDWtKFBFPjZapGk=", 
		"answer": "24axZJ3gk5arFAnxtngjxVnc6JJavWc=", 
		"explanation": "25T4e5j/3Vnj5MUhEgrzx+jzNHmQS3EZpnqXH699e3SqFKXNavS+xpExLlKdn05o+2DD46z3+VYAmrsb+4Gce2IXdop7iNiIxKT+ymVTJsJBnsBi5YgecPhFwH25e5TPKPsuwm+ZIlf5aT79C2I0ljTSjnVYr8Or+Sa1Ucl3zxNygo99rdspLsWQzKaX4UO/xhSN33DRRLx9FEaK9eyt6EKJs4d4usvNpTrS57Tpm+rS/NIObkhdrY96bU+9g6EG9mZ4QsG4ZAEL8uXeIVboYDyrKBsa8d+j2XIpx5FpVWYm/QVJjJdXboB62Iz2qSE5MMN5VQeypl0AwZtuUleBfLi2kGXl51g+NX8zdYZitTkm4RiZKV9wn3iPST8RloV/6dUcm0RweGtJkXPulj6ZmSWAbtP15Iz/hOb5o/lv87oiO1LMdU/JQ4gZf7rOICdwz/2MCKNSc4tvEi+mPNsqvCr2LJ+Q1j8U2dcnb2PotCyWgMC1OCW2sov8nJR5Ev8JMd/A5t6k8E7IYiijSrGu2zKwEHAciC0CHmUyUQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Laccoliths", 
		"option_b": "Batholiths", 
		"option_c": "Sills", 
		"option_d": "Plutons", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030114", 
		"question": "24qHV67M7lnr5YBgRhb3hfXwIX/VEHZRr36VU7A4MHDhW7LWLryymcch93/JxQo3qiWWc4O5t1IBi+ha+4vfeCsEdod2iNaFwu3zhjmVrRWaIKklVEMfuLl73Yw=", 
		"answer": "25e5e5jwkRXr4YQzEPcYzMEaqFwm1AfUhK5Bzdc=", 
		"explanation": "25e5e5jwkRXr4YQzHl7+zPb6dWnREGMdt3aAEq91ZnCvFKbQa63swJR5Z1WHzVJp/XiGoqv0t14OiKZe+oeKfWIUd59niNyGwKTkzX1IMMcEmY988J8RaLR0xDi0NNLXL+kuy2+TLknpJz2oATBgm3HahWsWvoqo9iioXc4ujFUxhIJ5+cEyO5edy6eS7AH4gQOMyHeICK5oHkSQu8no+EuVpY489duCvTHa+vv8ibjx8c0KbhxbvMZzYk29hOgI6i94VcmmY1JK/+CQYlXjYCqmZx0Q9sT33jRm1MIjXG4z8RsGhoZGZ85335bj/D0+f85lGj+zrUMA85x5Rleedau9kGDt511/YX8mdY9/vTkgswqPaFVwniufTSIRgJJq6NUV1Qhsc2gAmH/zlj6Fg2CcPJHm7Y/ugKjjr7Vq9qohMEiOMhzsXogFJaPMJn4yy6mQCL8cIZBrEmLvM5U99DjpKZiTny8C3NohIX7ktCaYnMnmOmSqtoG1ztJ5BrIJONaF7862pEnVZDChLXSYY4vnUQH1Q3i4xQFptBkrxyQDqGPWDMlz9DsM3m68SFBhkzLzLF6ghbdfqo6PaY8ik/T+2HIRlOd335L5xwkuUgm+g2tCvsSWQRxbxVGWGMIVyQg6BbsPVJnXsnuXh3/fXm9Ndsn4BKeS0Gxa1eD6nSFor58AFZ+BIBDfg9gvyxalCPJ3F2ZKxkTS9c3fcI+Il3SFfac=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Acid lavas", 
		"option_b": "Intermediate lavas", 
		"option_c": "Ultramafic lavas", 
		"option_d": "Basic lavas", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030115", 
		"question": "24qHV67M7lnr5YBgXh/gwvizdWnfFG5csHeCQqZwMHXmRLXHff73xpliZ0iBjE8782TD46P/5V4Ki+hM4YuRMDYLe8t7x8DJ2OK3xTFXPMpHm459pJkQcPhB3C6oZ5YC8vPK4uuczMCtYINnWbWl", 
		"answer": "25a5ZJX2wxj5tesLdqRz1VHpQQSfg7LWJlQ=", 
		"explanation": "25T4a5D/1Rz49sUpQV7zhfH+J2zVTyIEsGqCXq9tMHLqRqTXYuzsiZN0N06Mnkhy/XiGpari+lYLz79T7IDfcWIVcYdsyd6Gl+Hl0WFVIIZFlIQy8JIacrRDwzGhdcTIJe0u+maFZ0b/azW8FGNx1DjFymhPuIq49Cu3TZojyBByhIJr+MQofNiZmbyb7Q29ixaWxXKfT/1rFxSNvcvo5kKbrYN4tsWMvDDe5rT7n/bW8coDIhxausZpbFe/lqYGuC4tQ8G6b1JK/6TVeUThLzuqMQtd/Nn2xmBgyYxpamEx+l9SiopFIsN715XmuSBwNt4qBjq9rU1Gzpd9UQOabf293Xjw6VA7OTo/bY9/uWom4QGTPBR7lGSJSyQRh5V77t8LgURlcn0AiH7lwjCdhXeDZZrt7MDuiuv77Plv96IjIE+HdUjXFpkUYPPHNWhnxO3bHrNeIJZjHizhfdQg+Hn/L4SZ1jcKkNhgI3b18y/ZlsjlK2CpoJv2gJY30tDqOQweMmqawdJN/JRJ", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Lava tubes", 
		"option_b": "Tuff rings", 
		"option_c": "Calderas", 
		"option_d": "Nuées ardentes", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030116", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/PXbTWI8SkidcxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc6zeTEXM6JGkpC12aTWhEdOP8VFlIlxpJkQcvFTjH3tNJSKYNhiz3rAKFewYDyzEHxt1CLahWxfpoT75Su6QN821VU0mZV16Mx8Ps7f1amF6Q2+igmVz0efCJ8kJ1uVts+m4kDcsI45ociMpCGbprTalfbWvc0DYxhXu8Z3alew16cbuCc3RMagaRtFseLfc1noJGihPk4R+N3ilnVnwsImSWEx5l9QjY9VY8561djpvSY1LcRrGSCGrQRjh7d9UxOTZryrkCikoBV/NTprJcot/G118k+wKUZ5nyfcTiNGmM149tEJkAAjeWpQjnPzkTaEjiWJc4Hu7oS8kuD1rvl3+qZnPU6QdVPeFoxcc7zMJGZ8xamYAqpQMo90EjHaM5UKvBX4NpfUyywP1cpgbzentGrZ0o21eTH6h4f3gNF6B/8GOcPI7M/3p1TCb2PtIGuSJs34Vh/jD3793QtkoxBl3CkVqHHNGo9+9ihNonCMR2xrhWftbXK41rFaqpaGes4w0fr62HIAmf1qjNv2xhh8RAupn3pAptvd9YNM2m340odiBuwxPu98hQ==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "2//4Xp7/0hjk/oZgURH8wO6/NHnVQ2QesXKGVuNjeHTtFKvDeOy+yJl1Z1OdhV5psmDJr6bx+VoMz6Va/YuNeSMPbctu2tXJ0u7yx2VEN4ZCiI9/pJtfavFO2H2setCbIutnwmrAMlWwZnm+C35x2SLei2xTrMOz/Cu3FNUlgBg9g4ls7MEyfOOX3OiA4Eyog0aN2juFQLgkEluXsI6s7lOZroYr9cKD8SbT8bTtg+jWsNENIgRTqYc/YlW417wB/Wo5XMehZgYL/uKQYEflYCmtI04S7cPmxDRtw4A7VHp04BdHlsNfcYB23J3nqDcMMYcqIzy2oEVOzpc8TxuXYLi5xXuk4Uc6NXwkd4douG0iqQqSaFh/jGrcSiBeg5Mr8cUN1Qt1eH0AnTb3izuOwGSdeZKj6o74xev/r7VwspcvLAGSME/NWpkVa7SAN2tz3uyaGOZVIN9zDjLvPtQi8CC5JpqVy3kCwpknKnnz+DPZgcH6KWy0tK73xJRVFbMEM8PE+ou2olmHbSLzJnjfJsn7TgS9XHT5wwth9xwg2DMV+3HRB4dstTkFn2rwSFZh0iHvfnGkkv5L4oeAP5o51rX40iJQl/I4ntvh2xE/Rgq0zXxMvoieX09K3hT1H8EDwRsvH/QCFZiR8GjWhnPGTm4Mc477CKSC0Gxf0+f0zmBzu9ANVILOLhybjNE0xRK1Qf9gFWatvofrNPkBEyQj/PJh2OKistmocODobGwkbBaiXeZX9NVUcBJ3HhjUEyEPZaq7RokXTu5cnjXenwIIUHZdDV7e+r8JUUSlrITFb23TYvEaHBHvI7EAHcv5Wk+PIfmsiCbGCrydm0jyH0s3Di6VJPAO6gv8e5zhIVO8lShw8cSlJF5XR4IZM2DgNHm2qqW/BUx6Uy0zKcpTb0XQWFAlhjuDM+xpg6IMY1g5SamzWVEEk1FJkCzfC1wFp0QbUeWhQUUmaq9JL0wCjTWwH6UeSBSKkjIPzkWJ0CTtKv8LHUg1eiSHmk7liNJlnvGpgIvBGdH0KK8a3s0OIbpeV9raEFUb2vLq66HjEGJ5Dmh7PrjcUaLFok74Edj7sNeayV1dyP4EOVE8ZT2CmovY/jloPOfTv8gTsfI13ymrqDbQ1bMZ", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030117", 
		"question": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiIQrXvDYON9YzH3XKKCbeLs25JyMxyMlUt383jHt6z/+RMJgLobyMzhe6ddeFdnLLMGFYjfRT4E", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "2//4W5n61BXut5MvXh3zy/L6JivREWdRt3eGEq91YnbmR7OCevTuzNd+IRyfgld483jJ46T+8xMOna0b74GNfScHPol2iMSB0qTy1mRRJ89LlMB94toJeeZZjDuhYd3fYPJv2C60L0DpJzG8EnU0kzTYnnBT6JC3+je+R5o2zhFyl5V9rdwlLN6c2KSf8Q2+iROM2DuYRv1rElGYu8erq0KOpYMricPH8RHS+vD8iLjQ/9AOcUhTrYM/cFa9m6RFuDksVM2kJQFC9eHUIULiLCuiKQEY6ov33nV9hoM7WCky+w1Lh4cWYNkzwpDh/DciKt1+HDy040tGh4RlTRiVeLyrxGHnoFg+YX85bIthr20BqQqFaFVsnyuIVTxYl4Fn8slZkwt2c2sAlXiggyyYj2aGfYfq5I68kuHkqPls5qsiOwGULEzdRc0TY/PWKGtxy+eUCLUQc4xyFCqmPMZu7zHwJZqQny8C3NohIXji5xaX2I3WNmiqvIHwmtE2ArAMNdDL5s6k8F3VZGP1KXjTa8TnTUjzQHH13AAlowE1zWEf7iLOB4V89CMC3n++TQRlgCKganOzm7tYqoCXP5o51rXpzycAjP13kdv40l0+SBCzzXNCpIXfTlJLjUTPDMIEyAg9GL0CVJvQ5miEnHfcWDw5d8vvQamVxmxcw/P4jWBxs4lOQY2CIFnahNpm2w68DPhtR27uqYq5PPIRSmct9PJzz62nuN+1cbOtIiUoYA6/GeBa9pRfYQE7EAXZRSdAbqynWJgQVeFDknTYkgZbe3EDRXbN7alIWQunr9eIb3jbI70TGVKiZ7wIFoPrRkbfMPXp3j/FBb6SmkKtH1AtTy7dIKIIpQH/aIH3IFOxiihw8cSlN0NOVJceMymze235s6aREkY8czksLMpLe1GVfxghjX7CNfwnmb4QeRssTaS+WVYZgx9L3zfcTllWo0MdVqS5SVwpar5MNFNRwiO9FLJfSAXagylKgVDc1C3gKvtFPkwwNySAmk/o25N13+zhi4uNDpT0IrEY04MMLaUZTDmNeaXrrPb89DLW1MewTA==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "All the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030118", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH+jeK7ReqDXk9cxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPstDwcOdms3enjF9PYZl2qhz85sWdfVOjBS+eNXVJO0uji7AZwWwJ2j9KXlw2T7Vj31YoYD75y6/U98LzlUQ1qR5/ss9ONLf9KeG5lm5jwiRnDvRCO8kI12Xso6n7QO6qZA9icPNknL6+vD8ibj+/8sFdglbsZU/Ixv81+hJq2obXsagYRxO//DRbRT/KS63Zxgc9cfmz0hnhqZpdGox+B5IhsMWIoAzltik/HJwf40qVXP64wQAh9Q8C1e+e6mrwGfwoGkxSXQXa6Jiq204oAGFaFt42n+USWxQlo99+5AJlA1xbi9BjnOggTCZkmCMaMyheHWxbxm5Fpq+UJbHo9Khag==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz3hfvtQQBK6FoVpzvW6f7i+bSuw8=", 
		"explanation": "2//4XJn2kTHr4IQpWx/8hdTsOWreB3FRom2GEqV7YnzmUOfAd63/iZ9+M0+Zgk83smHOqqb4t1ocz6kb+4eMeSwEPohgxMWE2aT4wjFMMsFJm8Bm7JsLPOZFzT6lccebNPZrjn2VNUPxZDz9BX5w1DfZmHFF6IL74yi3V9s5zyk83MdM5c18H9aM2qmX7Q2ViROMyHqYRq4kEEac9d6p+Vfcr4R4ocWI8QDS+vO5lf6T1tcZZ0QSqI52YFP8nrtJ+Wo6VMSgKB1NsfLfbVfsLiemNE4c98+j03V70oo4SGg/8VJWkIxYZ4ByxJ3lr3IkN8x+VTa0oE1SxJh5TFeCfLj44Gnn6VM2djoEZo9sshE760+oIFE+u2WYST8RuY9+8MQYnApwPW5SmTbhwjyEjnGGcpbt/4HwxeX/tbd386opaVOBO1vdFpkUZKeALnQyzOaJAKNYc51+VzbuOJUt8zX1KYWd0DdN399gO3/itASYiM70eVW2sob8ztV4EP8UPtSF2sSipFSHQC7kM3SQZ8W0aQTxW3nE3UQlnhsgxCAe7CLRG8lz+i4Minu0CUtq0iagYXWl27Ff74OAdo1xwfzo2jdc2ONwlpj/lBQvBwX7nm9Rt4WbRlJIjVfTENkC1kk5BLETEdbf93rWmnXVSnIEfI71E72U12xByaP3gXNwutLPfuEffLEFzaHQGbw2Uxdn", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030119", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/PXbTWI8SkidcxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fXCsQasZG4YrJ6+rWhF1AJccEnIx984lfPLQAjH3tNJSbYL4/jk2BKQXyciukRHh7mTTFyn1YrMOr8CirWN8Lzjdypp5q4sswPcSL0KvT7kG3kRXCnCnRa7xqUUCLtNit5wOar5B4uMyDqHLW/fj8ibjS/tpLYQlc/4R6I025hbFJ/C8rRdqhawZC5+Hsb3fMMyDjIQ8R9dijljQphsJpHSl0tF8GwsMWMYBQ15akvzMlLMgqBzaps01SxoBzTQ7WZK+30mTh7UYDe14fdp9jvSA84U/caBQ+2ivcDGwR1MArvpBN1Sdicy9CmTbjgyqYhWHPfoqj/4j5xev/rLVi4rAiaU6GdV2YQIIQZrLOKCBhiuqaAaJZIZ4nKyzaM/0h63n0IZiNnzYLkM0oKjfm9iWPl43lOGyooNL4nNE2F7ASJNTG/ZT1StjG/K42mjJFWthxiyO+wQ==", 
		"answer": "25S0ZNHn2Ryq9ocvRBuwTFEBCg9dupS5SfARl++4hA==", 
		"explanation": "2//4RJDl0Fns+4o3QV7xxPO/N37CGiIZrHKGQeN1fnWjRKLNfuH7hddwNByeiFd3snfV46H15EcdgLEb6pyQYDFDf4VriNmH0fb212VTJsVQj5J32JRVPMRZ3jKueNXINPdtjmiMKFLjJzq8CjBghjDAj3AWroyptSq6WsN3zRw+k5Q47MY4fNSe1+iR7Q2ugxSbnH+UW6l2BFeNvNitpwOds8IsvciU8THa+rT6m+rB6Z4DbRwSvpV3Lxu7lrtFuCs2VYimZxFAzeqaIXX+KGilJgIR6ovg13opxYM8Tmx05hpVkopEY9R8xIGkrCA/PcFvGCD240VTh4B0Wg7Wd7y2kGrhoFwxfXsnYI4ttSMhrk+IIFE+ln6SSz9tmsorysMMmwVudHwAn3fuwj2OwGaOaYDm78D+nKjkqLwj8awrJUCQJlmYWYtcZPPWKGtxy+eUSrUcMJ5rEyf0PJlu/Sq5N5OY03kMw5kiNjfi9TiNmtzgOG6/oNL4gNA2B6oCO9DX4MWy8FDGbyfyLXSXY9i2yrlqsQ1ZdX6EREUlCBs79Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "All the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030120", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy+65ZiLl/JgVpt82WGorf1t1sAm7xe+86LeCMNPopswdTJ2+XhxWJ9PZQEuIFh7ZlfcPVWzS7tdcbeYPNh3GvAIUnlbj39EHh1mnHXiXVS6I+64yaoaNRkgDczhY57rcQ9KtaMma6c+kD4kAmO33qfR7h3UUOQocbo+FeZpZJ4psGCoTfIyPqt2tnQ+dpLbglEvpU/ZVSumugf9yY7UMa7bQEL5u3EaRTqJSa3Kwtd6sfsxnF6+ox8HUg4+F9JhMNCasUz15rrqjcMMfFkIjuzoEwAyJI8Sx+TNLy6337hoEYrdG4uaI9jqD51qBzTKUZ72mKSTyNDhoVo6o9bTJfDK3FGB+W/0i8mOj++wA==", 
		"answer": "2+b4Z5//yFtHIoXS+8L1n+t46019wTFK", 
		"explanation": "25e5e5jwkRXr4YQzEh/gwL33On/EBnBRt3eCXON1c3jnFKvDeOztk9dSKE6biFhvslTHsKzzt18OmalIpc6TeSkGPolu29GFw+30hH1AJccI2ohz8p9fdP1HxDi/NMDeLe5r3G+UMlf1dHm+C31klSPTjjxCp8O69i6/FNY21hQhqola7Ns1P5eT2L6S+w25lAPC0XSDTf1iHUGQsY6840KS4IM7vMnNvTPN9eej2tvc4swOYRwSnYdsalj8m6kf+Tl4WcmibVJH/vPVcxT7KTugKB0U7dKvlnlozYsnWikg/BpLwo5ZcMUz0JTxtTZwPMJnBTKopkAA05s8XhSfcP200X7l82kxV3s4bIktsCwjoBzcLltslyuKQyBSlY5k+8NZgg13dS9TiHPlkn+YjGqfeYC5q6nyhufisrxg5uMFKFKJNhzUV5sddv+ANHJxwqmaHuZIO5B0EmLnLsYh/zD4NJOQny4ExNFgPH/u8Sad0tv6NWa7vZ38nZg2ErASO5HT5se0sVLIZDChNnSHbovzXAbkQ3m4wAJqpx029C8x62vcSIV+4ywe3ni/W0kkhCjsb32vmbtPqpWHa4Zx1PDiyT4V2Od0kIvyx0d8ZAupn3pApsS+TFVLjVjXCMwUiEksCb0PE9bc/X+T1WDZWH8Cat26QbyCzSgIzuyxiG5vstAYWoCNLRfUj81m3x6lCb1+UGn5pIPrfe8ZBXQp6Y5/6+Gt98W9NeesKSUrbRWhXLUZ2ptSZxBpFAjJRRdbYayrW5gQVaAcknzZ1w5GRHBbF1/P7+pDn692vHczVjkB8BMfer3U", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1, 2, and 3 only", 
		"option_b": "2, 3, and 4 only", 
		"option_c": "3 only", 
		"option_d": "1, 2, and 4 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030121", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy+7I9lNUmahE1+snrHraH2+EECnOha+4vfdi0Rc45riNKQl/D/wTFEIdNUjol96toQerRMzSusNNXVJL5h2maFNQXmaDW+BX59l3Hbi2hTuoq6+TSHWoh36RsmhJJr5N45fNue16yV51+1lUaDzn7RTrJ2HFGd9cyxq1eUpcI7usKBuDzctPX3nrjA/9ICZgFUtoV+d1KzmegG/mo1UM+5aVJc+PDYaFqtNCCmZw0P7Nj36no6hqMlUSki+xNFg41ZZ9Mz14rh/DcoK99/BjqspgRMxpp4WRiEea6E3jyk01oycDo9aoZuvSM6pBzcKUZ72mmTWCQRkZh/7MUKnBJmPW5OmDbpjCuZlXaGapaj54Hyge7/srRwzq0bJ3aIPF/QFoIaJafIIidzyOaNCOZPJ55zEi/jM8E9vDDqb5eG2nkO38syKnTzq2jnVts2se8FuO5Q7wI3Ye1a", 
		"answer": "2+T0KMO/kRjk88V0EhH8yeS93El2f01dZw5dOZKCtE3Qyw==", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7X3entIHjZFWdRr36NVqV7YnzwFKbQa634xoV8IljJj0I75n7D46Di4kMbhqdVqYGZMC4CaIovyd6Nl+vjzHRTc9BLloNz6pMcPPlB2Di/fdXXM75axmeTZ0zjJzqyFmJxlyWWiHlVqZao8Ge+TM4l1QY7gII44ckyONGQy6WAqEyqg0aE02mcTbkkBlycu46l6kSRocI9p9idpSGb8ub2l7jSsMgEbgtTsYk/YlW416sG9yYrEcm6bFJY/ujZZV3rKS2wZwETud/r0zR605AvXGoxtBBAwpdeZ4BW14rwtA4+A8NZATKupklFyYA8DU3WXbOswn336UM6NXYqa45rsz84sk+dOlE+nGSOQSlV1IJyvsQRkERgcmBMlXjnwj6FhCWcc5/q74n6jOvxtLBs/OMoLwGNNFvVV80LbKfILmky3uGeTaVOJoxzVxbuNMZu9Sq5IZqH0HkO38syKnTztCickczgKmD6upztnMFlHakFdt3E58+xv07KcmPgM3jTYMTmVA30D2vw1gAluhkixSBQ623XBJo/9CMJ3m2/RU1gmyHpaW/hgbdI4ouAP5o51rXJ3CAEkLNr35jlwQ4oewqHg0xXs5CaQllB2RSFRI0myAVuGrsNF5ff/WiF1XfCTjwIZ9rkFLuO1SkI1uL/imdyrZ0dFbiGJQqbg81mwRmyDu9rUGT56IT8Pv0AGWFs9L1liuytu4qtev+nLWslagn3WP1cs5BJfBBuAgLLAGR8b7WrFosRTeNO3HrPhEsIVGpKDRrN6OgKXBCipcjBemLNL/EdHBuiar0RAdvrR1HKdf2oxjTPCa2RhgecXlAtQTaUNbgepQbif8z+JQG0liQk8NP3N1ZOSIIFMD6zZ2O4taaHSw80az4wO4NRfwfcTB4hmyvQZ/toia4FY1g5SamzWVYZhBwPiDbXABhIsUsTXuWuT1wrOelELl9R3ji5GKQWWhXPlXodh0KUyyysPfJOcWwiaXCbyF+gmIBzjOvVjLKPOcDjObgW14MXaOIBBKnZEl5cjPzo7ODuHmkqRmxlK7jKUfbZ8EruFtrhscrMwBxKx7pIP1EvNyyYgIncsDZsIaFJYGJHrjMtpMPBIg+5mYtWx0JtU0Gs90TnQHIys1FgYZ7uKsvTJpik/l9aBWTPVq9G2P53ySSkMMfFdg8sDnUw0QaecpLDySCRKL/y1qhJAx2jw4zZQJktykdrjtmqwkFQpz45z32iCHnXcuj+4QpRYmp3R7eeFFIdjwRi1Hqn0V/rPIGlx7IBj6QB0LQAoQ23oS54ihOfR0veZneqzeOTum/S/lMpyL4jVXXjWWZkwhhkUeBr8GAuQSE1TLN6vaL8IraEkmC2K46rjYMLpVpVUKaKLrO//cXlN6zGI6T/zYmAb3/g5ZZ7DfSjZeoNJTbBZSse5Lj4bZPXLQiBOSuByq+KBziHMyUb4nhgnmSBRhV/YSCkQ8BRG3ZGmIc2M6ADq83osVlxdWmAF7B83LMAmlcZBUMZS/KhkX9ZCu1xMJiZMlNs8VIaBv0YKC1ZCcic/3RgQ4u+OJwbY+c=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1, 2, and 3 only", 
		"option_b": "2, 3, and 4 only", 
		"option_c": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_d": "1, 2, and 4 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030122", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy++p94IlCNzU10/nXHrar15BMOna0b/YaaMC8MbZ8vy9+E2uv5hGVYI8MElYYy8pUTf/VOwwGjJpT4L/N+wX2JM0CwcTaxB3F6mzTFyn1ErcOv/SL7QNs7zBAhgsds9Ng5fNiZmb6c5E65iAm+0ijRa7RqFVGL9c2n5UaP4IMqsI2ZuTeb5/n4lvTW48pLdhFCusZwZRuqmKQK+SQ3bcaIZjpE5qTdYFr0YCelZxoV/Ivi1Ht/w8I6SWgg8RJDjJdFIslgmZn2uXIzMN94EDCu/AZIKU9qS133IcxZ496PMEdI", 
		"answer": "25S0ZNHn2Ryq5JEhRhv/wPPrJimcCMiQJIgXtFpcQui+AlC7", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7BzfT6OW+QFW0doH6NXaZnMHDxUefWZui+xJhiMxyKglZ2/XiGt7zg8hMAiehN5oKccSwMPr9nwcPJ3ve3x35TIcNHjsBw4ZkeaedFjC6lfdHXJL54wWKDJkv/Yir9BWJx1DfZmHFTrMO57GevXN93xQcnhpNx4sZ8M9Hf36SG4Un4igeU3TfRX7VtElzZs8Kn/FDcpo0q9cGCvzWb8P3qjvnd89sYIglcu8Z9dlKwk7tJ7Tp4U9q7aRYHsePVb0DhOWiwKwEN8MXklnlm04w9XGA65yNIvo1ldsFn05XhsiZwbZcqNjy3s0tTzoB5HwGZeL653mfh8xU+Z39rcYJo/Dk0rQOZO0A+jnKMSWxeksB98dwalApsPVtIlWWgiyzLgWmcc9Pg5JLugOvk4Ltm8aIyOkTANlPVRoIPbKfFZ3F9xuqaA6lZIN9mBSemO9o88Tz9YJSNny0F1ZklPWL34COWnI36PyW7v4b8nNp3ALYOMZHJ6NKyok+HbiWhLXyFZ4v1VwywX2Xq3A1ptgsxwSJQ5WPMDZt29CFNqna1CUhlhCaganCuga0c65CLP5w03/T41CQVlO04mZfi3Rl8Rgq/zXxCvMSZQ1NYjVLZDI0LywcpTLAIB4LQ/G6ThjqQXHQEc8u2FaCCgzxRyOzygmBuq5kNFYGPOBzJg98qiB6iQfB4UWKtvZa5MvpVC3cktvJyw+OlstioObOlImFqYA6/XP0Z9YdQbw9+Hx/ORStJIKqhVZZeVehOxjXLhQIIRXNIFk7J/+gBUxCl6tDAayrfaqNcCgvwar0CU8/2DkLdIOG9wT/HOrGgm3SqXlAgQz+TNfBev0fTc4L2IQHzkGdq/NKlM0NeBJcfOWfgeWq1qaaQH0YuZjwgaIVBOlHaRxMlmjGDE/FunucJY1gsTbuoWVMZhANKnCqSDF1GsVkNWuWuSV0jL7sFI1QfyCT1ELIaHBrFlDcPihae22L4If8LNFs2a3CagEKglJQmj+b7jY2NC8f2JL5b34wXLaRSRZaaX0wUk/Dsr+jzUW41B35jK/yIV+zFvw/iCs20o8rIhVhe27cGMR86K3mOm4rJ5DNiIeVOYXQKqXscoorUYwqmyshb1FNjEEHjtVXsRCcmpB5mYJerXtXZaou84l9cGiXUQ7BA2PF5ySn2PN7dJBMsR240lQLQY8KKyDLDPL/zjO0KDBam0ovYCcps4kw5wci6xl4ArSl0iHHnBWLJIujrqAxbIXc4X7yeDh1clBJixz+930fhK4qmnuYag7FN1PerUo+GLbF3N50v2EwSGmyd", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "All the statements", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030123", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy+6JRlLkqMzU10/nXHrar15BMOna0b/4GTcyMNcY58iMSB1vC3zHBXNoZBiJVi8J8bPP1OjC+od9HVNL5mx32UKFfpWzfvRFR7hjzXhGgWvoy39ia1W98kgBQgk8du4sQ/PdmQ3LvT/EW5kkaK3W2UCLNrBRScp9u4/0aY4Is29d+IsjfV4LTxk+vH/8wSLkhQqpI/Ykm517sd8SY0Ecu7ZgFC9eHCZFCtNCfjJQtd6cT303p9z4MlUXB09RxSi5VTXs4glr38qDs+PNkqAzy2oEVOyJFvHxaEcf2u32Tn4VswcGlrcYJsqG09oBmZaFpxjiuZXjlBgIVvvtkX1RZmfmpOiDboiyyfj3eWPJLt78D9l+2wrrZ3sqAoJ1KJMVnKU4lccbyAJWIy2uaPCKhIOp5rGzumPNY69S/8HJio0RECx5ktLnn+tCWf0tn9PCW7sZ3vi5RlAL4UM9zA59+k8FXULiLzJD2aaMj7Sxr1TGinkVFSOYYHeWitrp6cTGTH+Y0=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz3hfvtQQBK6FoVpzvW6f7i+bSuw8=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7Txun2I26QFW0doH6NXaZnMHDxUefUYeH9yJl+Ik/JmVN65jbOorP1t1YdmrhP7IrfeSxDbI5szd6dl+z+12VOId8Eroh799oWb7RDwy+/cdfPYPxrzW+VNECwZjqpDWZx1CfZhn9Xpoy+5me6Rt931ho+lYZ24s0vfMOX2LzT6V+9xgWXzmmURqloCBScp9u4/0qSp8I3p42FsCTetPHrj+jH9dpLdQFGt49xI0+0kugZ+TksEZnkJEIboaTJZFX/MxStGwAu7cr303lsyJZpDzN00BBUj4JYdoBl2ZTnvTw/Ot4qFCG/41JPy5d9URiTZ/2s2GnwoF0+Y39ra4V5/CgntB+ILVA+k2XcXilSkY5/vtgQhhBsb3YM3HT1ln+KkmDPb4fq54y8huf+s7Bn97EiLQGUOhzaU80MaqfFKXN7y+WXFOZdMItuASemCd0n73nwM9aV0yoCkNovPWXi9z7ZkMj2OHCpttL9gcZ7FbEUdsfK5ci2vlPCcmPgM3jTcMT4Wgn+QHnrkxpttgxlwCAG7SLWB50/8D8Yjmq1TQRtnGfyaX+kmKoc4ouda4Ejyrms3ycE2OBwmonylBQvBxevhHNP8oXfX1Nc3l3UF8EO0BBuGLwAANbF+miP1XXfXnAJP8vkFLiTgyVGmvf5iyF7qoQbR4myIiXVucon3BK8BPNtFTS36KPhKfUbCXBs7L19yeyvuM+oNfK2KSU8YBa0WOFW9oYRfAp6BUvVBDJKILahQt0bU/VfxnDO1w5GB21MBl/C7+gAVBe+pdbRLmvQZ/EdHBuibbwRU833QFTGMfS7zTSJErDcl0L+T0sxSzSJKLEB6R6we4/mLQW201xs8NKlO0IbTY0UMzXhcWit5aGGCAcvbCllLZxCdAfcTVAl1CjMK/pmg6hAeBk+AaaoDRAThARfizvWTlFL8F4bXKCjVBMvI7pRL0kIgXe8BeAcUwnGgnoZml+QzmLuLLpbPl0mdXCajkDsgtJnnOvglIvBPtznP7hb058GaLtaSoOWGVofjvz2/KH0GW0tRm54IOzaV+DEpEq2Fse0tcvf0VRO2/4HJB81Ki3LiN/P/zZuLqtAL3lZ/XAWotnbZgO43IwZwV8oUlCs8FnwSGkiol0zb53vKsnUL9uk8kNaGCfCF7ZF2O593inqIZ/Udg8vE2o6n0eZZZLEyCDDPKDswbQaRRnixZzHTItv4E05x9K2yk9BvzRnzdRQ39r0gNFUH5MTgwumr94=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "All the statements", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030124", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy+/5h9JF2HhFg782XO46zjt14Oi60b/J7ffyRDbYZuxNzFl/f4yHhFc9ZFiJR755Yab7RPyn2/e9fQYP9gyi6EMlbkJy21BWQ0lSPTynlcrYCv8CP7Usg4zVUz1pF34cs9Mtjf3b2B4UO/xgeMnH6DXa1wGFuXicD6q3WTrIE5u8SO8TDU+fbq2vnB9Z4HYxpVuso/cFSwnqxJ6CM9Us2nKB1NsfbfYl+tNCCiM04c686j035sxZYsWSky5hBLwoIWdM9/1Znqs3I0Kt9jGzT6okoAwoZpTwOfe7OE3juk1lozdnslbIktsTgxpwOTP0c+m3mZDCFYjJR+7NUK1QtlPXhBiHPyzn+Kk23DPJLt78DzkeD1svln96E1IFLAIVTZQs0dd7aAN3V9zvyYCKIcMYYnFmLwMtkt/TfwI9aRzSwdxNAvIUvpyCSxndq1NGS0qtL2iJRiHLpAN9PK/873o0jGdSbsJHOHdYv9SkfxXXm40AF3pR0m3H5Syw4piw4TREdH7beKTIQfwQ==", 
		"answer": "25S0ZNHn2Ryq5JEhRhv/wPPrJimcCMiQJIgXtFpcQui+AlC7", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7EyvH8NGXZACIQsHfDW7A0fXDnUefXfq3xz9diKl2FgRc74XnKqqGw51Idm6FY5YuMMC0FPplgy9vJ1urzhHVUINIEjohz8NoebvEAyTeod8DeJL5o3GGNZ0SwcTaxB3F6m3HSn25fpoT79Cn7Ucgi0AE7mYk42cA1L5eWyuiQ51+qgwWWnHmUS7xxAlHZo8Gk6EKSqYF4tN6F8TvItPn4nv2T5c5LbQ4Sq49xehu6hakO9S82Rdv0ZxQL4+vTahTsLizjIAIc6tijwnxo0sIoT2x09hNHkZdTZoB62Izr/CY4Oo1rHCH6p1FSzpp7HxbWYrK002nq6VZ/cGg+dZ5ksyN1lQeZaFVtkiufTSIRloUr/dELhw1meS9ChTb0ijrLl2yBeNPl5JK8ief+p/ln+7AzKE+DME+YV4MYJbDBKSdxy/yICOZONox3HjDnKdo85XnpMpmW0zwAw5khIXOn+z6Rl9+1MWC7v4bxzsRkG70MM9zW1cWLvm/TYDfkLHidcoumA0jGQHD70gBstFgnxywS+yLZGow/+SwfmXv8CVdrni7kLGyok71Z+cKBec4j3PbnnSYYmeA4nonylBg2QgeviHsDtJaQQhxOjULZEs4GygZuCKETHZjWsmyY1XPCXmwZdsH4QZyPyj8I0/Cxj21usNANWp6cKRrPytwjyxakEvg5Q2jhq4f3NP9VCGsh+KExy/+k98a6Z/ShbGYiehS8Sq9W9dVdaRR6UR/VBDAPYaqrFpgURONb13GKkRVHSj9IRUzD96sJUwvqrtHaZ2TZI7ASThvwdqMRGsH2DnPHMLGrxz3LFf+flEn+XUFlTyndLbEf4gKwe5+yJxKhgChl98WlMVBVBIAWKTT2NHiwoq2KDQ85fiIxaI5Gd0bSTlAznDvNZ+1viL5AfBkjRZSpJV4lghBbmjPXAEwF4xZeaaqhQ1IpI6oFLU4Vyzu6BrNfXQ7PxjcDlkKJ0Cf/afVNcV4ib2GBwwzhiJoq3/7nhs6OHtznP/0f148RIaUbUJLXCxsdiPak//PvFXk6A2k3LOGIX6LHv0P1A8b9oYPf10lb3bcHOB8PLTCYyZbKsDthPKoPbH9Yr3YauIrQZwWrzJtclUZnXFbt+0jnAWo0shd/YYT4Jp3dJoiqsFtRGTPJF7hQ2PB51S32JpORZQg6R2U6gwqVcpLdzzGNfbv61KgbRRWrz5zYBZ1k+EA52NO+wE1Oojg1jm/qS3fUZqfi/BZRMDx8TraNE04dsh8nlTek2lXkMpi5x6UIgPBD3fUF5B7u4id3nErBQkXYan3tnveQsybFv0lhyqt2T2PjSHpqwAUiTfMq/G0uRCwsSKZx/lYACC4X+Lk2mFFgTkmJ448=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "All the statements", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030125", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy+6pZ9I1mbjEg782TD46nx5VQKw+hZ5pmTPTELf5tqzJCN0vTlwWJSOslKicBm7JsLPPVSyX2re8bWJfou2WaFKQXkbzz9EH9k1D7Qyn0Wvoy39ia1W5o0zxk+l5dr6NsAMoXf+rqS/EiqlUaDzn7RW7BlHVicp4Lo6UyLrM8rvcydtDab8PHpiP3A49cEbBsSq45+dxu9ha1J/iUqXM2wKBNfsfDYZBT+NSWuLhpd9s2j1zR/yY4qXGc7yBEVwqJaboBw15TguSAxLI1rBzb6pUtSypF4HxWPNKu33Gvl7lw8NX85cJp5tSI7sjOSfBRflmfcTz5QgIV57ZAYhwEje2BSkXPkwj2SwHOAcJDi5Yn/xe3ital3+6wpOn2OCVLwWZpcaLLOPid9zKmPBaMcMp1oASemLsEv6Dz0JZiAzHkEw5YhPXKn/SSand/nPGau7NAwC8gFqSpx3SMTsp98kwSF", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7RxPH7MHnRECIQsXrDXqJmd3SvFKXNeeGz2p9wN1mNzV9+4mTDsLb5+F0cz7xT6JrfcTAGPo1g2t2M06TgzHRPc9JMn8Bm64pfc/IAzX27e9jYIfBhjm2PK0nxdyq4FzBAnDjFynVF6IC05zW+V853whAxl5Jr6Ig/Pdub3LqS+w25lAPC2nSDRbhgUUORsMDo/0uZ4I85ssCM8THT9fn7n+qT8tsFZwlGt8Z+I02zm6sI9iV4VMWkfBtO4qiQYlX4MyGtIE4J8c6j0WZm04wtHWg2+wlDwopCItR8lpvrsD4xL95vKT2GrXdUxoB5UhKYYP3qiijH8lQrcGg4JYt/uW0mrA6QJFFs1iueQztd2ZNj/8AckURneH9SmWXzizCFkyWbdJL3q4HugKj2r6tu96dnKFXAIVTdFp4JaL7JMyd9zKmaTbBTP5xmGS2mCd0n73nwM9aV0yoCkNovPWXi9z7ZkMj2OHCpttL6nNViEa0TdtDX7Iuxv07KZCehNnWWaIvgUQ2wW3PokwFj9xll3i4c62PWB8l8+iEBn26jTFco0iX1eDy1nrtFqoOces48xvbknSEdmfh0mom3wBU9SUS4jHNHt5aeXGBB8VrlCswTwQQrAqBBR8yR02Ga1XXRR3gIbc/lQamVxmxO1fH8i2U9vYlOQ4OCLxjVg91mzQWkEelwWmn+6LLxNO9VA3ds87xyxf+zssmvNfGhL2Q/fB/3V+BNs5RdZEJ4EAfZADZOc/ivRJheR+9d33DO1wVRB2lGCVnN9aELHQG4v9TcZ2XQcPEvARPnI7AEH8r9XEbcdfC7zXDPCa2RkEP+XV1lWjKYYbMC6Qvxap/3ZBy1031q/cT3NUNUUY0TfCryc2a45aCLCgs4ej42ZMpQck7WQ1AnlTCDJfwnjqYVYx0pAaq+WUQTlQVAkTfRTllGpEUIVrG0AFw1aqZRKF4DjTG0ErQQTg/2iAYEvUKd1ifhLPRfcR15O0WfgwzjiZNymu36wo+TD5TkIq8W14lDKq8bUpXaHFoSk/Ck6vP1AXgwCWNkbszAV/GRuVy2A8TnrYPTy19E26wNNUt7JzyIiIrK9XpjILEPbnxG/XALrd7XcBXq2JpclVZnQljp8QHmWCc3uR1wb53iaZ3ZOI615FlQGDeHZLZOnbx7zy3wMM3CJBstAiMznhWdc9aKxS3DMKnvxaIbDAynl5DGVYtu+Fs7M9PY6NfQXHNdM3EkYY7YmQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "All the statements", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030126", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy+5JhiMxyfgld483jJpraw9kEKz6RU6o+LdSZDd4Uv3NiMl8f+1nJUPot0m4N74pMcPOZFyzSieujVcr5axmvAD0z9ZjW8HXFn1DnXnHkWpoz79CSvXcwygAM9moR548c5L+uR5aak4ES7jkaN2juFQLgkEFaWo8vo+FedtIc1sMOZonLS57v4iP2T89EZcA1Rq9k9c9yogUw0aglSr6jJoptKOg==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzwg3r44AtVxDm1r3+J26QAG0DsXqARuFHWosaz7YKfQL9HtNMqfmx", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7Gzfi/FmLCAHcc7k+CUapyeXKjRqLFZ+LwhddwK0+GzVB1/WHI46Tjt0cHiuhp4ICYMC0FPq1m2tXFl+3khHABO8lWiYVh7JUaMedIzS2ocJTZJfJ6jmGGZ1P/azq8Cn9xh3HXhHgWu4ay5iqyV5o2wwE7gI5s9IgoNNaLma2d60SqhQqHzzuFQLgkIVWavMih6AOzo4c5u42kpXLS57TxlfXWsMoEIglQsJNrIwzp0ugG/mosWc30fx1Z/eCXchTsIzyqMQtd78Tv1XVnyYc6YWcI+ixSg5dTb8V9wti25nIEN8gqPTq3okhB3pVvHxaEcf2s2G2k91oteX5sdspltSo9pByIaFlxj2WITSVf1JJq8Ncc2URic2sAiH7lm3+KkmDPcJzg6pT5gaj5rvlC4aomaXWIMEWYV58ZJb3PMydiy/uPTalac4tvEmLFNMct6TS0EJeX1j8E05kyKnDu+yTV0sz7PSWuu5fri5R3BrpAON6F6MijuUrCITXuLX6SaMTxSkj5QTzs2wslnxEoyS0R8WPLNIdX+joIiHuiBQRwmiLyaTyghLsc7o2cco8/x7X60j4Tmfp3moi33RN8Uwy+zVdKv4WTTkVO3hT3XskI1gQvAqBBApnd8WyYmjbZWDwMP9j5DauGzSMIzuvwmiF1voNOW4OabBzJn84yzRPxCPM5R2LurYjtffQcGXAj6Ks9iu+0o4qyZrO3OGwmY1q0VuFK+pFUegd/UR/SRSZKIKihQpgQVelO3nnT1wZLU3ZfABr4860aWESruMGIb2jRdqVcXE6iZ7wXHs/2WgfZOv2qyT7GA6zcnEn+S0wgDhKULLEB5B7xacCyJR2303xs/NPgclhIBIJXLCjgZ2K7rK+KHx96ayQkPMpUdUrQCx8i1CrLIvQnjqgVfBxtRLqyCURWnx8PizbXTl5QpFkMWudECfW6o53BOOkIZX5qQtJy", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Statement 1 is correct", 
		"option_b": "Statement 2 is correct", 
		"option_c": "Both statements are correct", 
		"option_d": "Both statements are incorrect", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030127", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy+7pJoNFmbnht64HOGparl+UcOhqZIqYGZMCoMast4ycSMxaT2ynUBINNUn5J64ZsLefAA3ymoddnnLqwu5mGUZ1bgdTCzA2M0lSPTynpZvY2v9C61R5o4xlU6mZM4+skoOcXf1qaf8XG2ugi11HKSQP1rFxSNvcvo6kGTtod4ptmMpTfW8frtibja45EKcA0Stoh8bEmukqsdp2jdfgs/hSCr6CxORfGBxfgg", 
		"answer": "24asaYX23Bzk48VyEGMnxG+ss8xYCf9hOX8GLR0=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VyEhfhhfTxNmTCEWcStz+rXbc0Y2HxXanFfa39yJkxJlCaght+4GPWt+Xj41YOgpRV1YC9fzYLPoxq0cOMxfe3xX9Fc85LjsBh9IgWcvNTjDy/cZTdL+xjy2rAME31aXmqBWRxhnHVg25VvY+64SKoFM4/0honkY84+cA5fPKey7ybr174hRSXz2/RSbNgUV2K9cat6leZpMI6rI2AsDXW9bTRle/W5tsZLkhVup9sZkmv16AI7i94UIineBdI+OLZYhT9LD2uJQcT/ovwz2d9w49pSWE14F9Hjo9ZddMzwpDhsXIkMI1vByaqtwRJyYB5TRqfYKm93nzo+RULfXM4JZphqSA3qAGbaEdniX+ZQWxSm45498MNhkRsey9B3H7vln+cgXGKbtPx7pP5l/7/qasvsqJnJ0CSJ1PPFoIMYL3JKWA+iuiVCeZdc5xvFi/kOMdu6zH8MpPUyzEIkM4hO3L1tCiMm8HxKiWvo9LpnNFlB6oSM5Hy4c658EjPZGPxM3iAdd7mXEjySn/33gt29wwqx2EX+mfZHMU/4SUI3mmxXUF20iLyeWy1hfIc+YeAe4c/1LXtnTQfjfpsnpL5lBI6Bwy0mT9Us5CaXRxOw1CWDdkCxQRuBboVG9bF+mjWlH/Cd3Ixceb5FeiU0z5B1OTizmVy/54BQcyGLQ/eysouwQTxEu18Vm7roYW5LfAAB2Yl9LUx2fSyo8+2ObO3IyU+Zx+uGetWs5tefEJ+Ax7NEWRGbqyrRJAXVfRK3GHGjkdgSGhME1/et+gcVQGz6sfJYCrNd7gQAl7ncaYVB47rWkLOOLGdwDnaRraP1UW7XEUwXT/dNbgIpRDxbongZBq902Br7YH2IkNSSoQEfC7gNGS/saaNSxM0eyk3aJpVf1TGXgIh2H7CKf0nmq8Fflg5Sa3nCUIThQJajTuSB0sFokkSWqS+RVdrar1NJRsGzCOwA+AcXRKKhDUDghadzCasKuhOMF0mO3eHik3t2dcfmg5tcCJMMXeSPh5Groo=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Statement 1", 
		"option_b": "Statement 2", 
		"option_c": "Both statements", 
		"option_d": "Both statements are correct", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030128", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy+7JZjM1SYmFpw92WGorf1t1AOmrte7c6daWIXdo4vxd+f0unyymUBPMAEjoVx8JURdfcA3DGsYNHIHPA8jlqIIgXYbjS8CHFtlSKWi25T6IW05yq+UJo12VUmnoI47scwMN6M0KedqEK+xhKK2Tu4RrltEFrZtMCsq2aJsoMrvMyD8SLX9eD8icTdzNA8agFRt8ZwZRuon61J+Sg3R830ewZK5eHdZFr5M2iqNEEc686j1Xt71IcqSTZ2pSWgZMsofW/zlQyrZR+t9Q==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzwg3r44AtVxDm1r3+J26QAG0DsXqARuFHWosaz7YKfQL9HtNMqfmx", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7XxO/rPXrFAmkUsD+CQKY0c3D2R6LGLu/niYN5IhyEgk1+/3PIt+X/8RMbiqtP5oCWc2ITcop7zcPJ4+H00H5POsUEioxz8J8MPPVSyX2hdcbcJb5+x2uDIlawaD/9EHhx1BTXmGhe75D79jWuR8531B0zgsd5/818P9iRyryS5lm0n0aP022YRrokJlycu46840aPpcIoucyZtCGb+fvvn7jS998CbBtG/4N+YFP8mLwB/Th0Edy8bQsL8uXeIVP/KSana04O9cLn0zgpyZBpXmY4+BZCh8NiaslglpXrqjc9OsN+VTC7rQRDxoFvWleFYK+9w3uk9Fp/d28iaY4tqT11qAHcPFx72nmTTydC2MBq8NRZggxmcy9UlHOgkSuZhXacPJrwq5L5ie3xs7xnvuMuPQGDNFKYVYwJdraAJmkyz+iJGa5NJp5sEh7oAdsd6DjtJZuR0S1NgoNgG3/itAKQn8z5OHy7oNL4nNE2ErASO9TBqcmu8EjPZGPiLnGfb9j9VgawQHq4xwZg9zErzCgR5iLZBo0/0Dgfn225SEokgivheHmy1opU78KncYo40vuszT4RjPE4loi32RIqTgq8zXFMoJCXD11bjVWWDMwTwUkhCvQAFpnE5i3D1XXVRWgEcsviBLqUgzxNyKPoi2Bv/6QGXJ/OIRbNj9MjxgPxCO45Vmb4u4/3OrwBAmFs07x1w+yv99q3dOehbHElLxm4VeNQ95ARfwtvGUvJDSEPRa28V44XQO4PwnnLgwIIc3dMRVnD96QBTg2lpITHaCrKa7QPC17yb7IRFt24R1SPJeS6wDnHAf+JhQeqV0FlZjOQILwM/AbjNszlLBqwmyhl68SlJlleBJcWMCv2Z3/5qKyWBRI7diI2aIVJOmLUWQQs1muV8ReA8V15RabPkPGDErY=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Statement 1 is correct", 
		"option_b": "Statement 2 is correct", 
		"option_c": "Both statements are correct", 
		"option_d": "Both statements are incorrect", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030129", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YK2viaN5Ihy5jFhy9H/F45f5+VRPgK4bz4eNdWIKbct7wNXJ2uvk0DFSNs9Xl4lx5ZYTZbRBzymkYtGbMvtpx2GOZ0z+Jy21ATBjmyPajkBY+sOP/SL7ed8zyQE3hJV54809Mpq30KWS5EyhhwjC3n6dXP1tAhSNvcvo+Eafr4w89cCCoiab5/HwifXa898HbhESvoVrak2517oM/yM3X4i9ZlJf+eGQdlv/LCyfKTITzsPq1XwpyYRpSWExtB5EjZVTItNn14zhsTc+K94qHCD1olZFh5dzTQWTd6nnknez8PX07ebLM52ZFZx+jjs=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzwg3r44AtVxDm1r3+J26QAG0DsXqARuFHWosaz7YKfQL9HtNMqfmx", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHD0Brj8YwjEiz7y/q/Om2QJWsDpiXDW7A0cTHrW7XRa/72xpI8NFSInV5/snTDr7Gw+FVPmadX6o+RfycQPophzJCa0u3kyXhCc8dHjolk7Y4GPOBIzSntcdrYKextwmuTZ1H4YnmNBXN9kjjVylNVrYK1tQ6vFNMkgB09m4I4+cd8PdWQzLzTvxj9xgmEnG+ZTf1zHkaVsYm7q0KftIsusI2bvj7Y9fr2n+uT8dAPIgFB/5R6cEuzmbsA+iY9Ec67elJK8+vFdRS0cG3jKAhd7cPmlmNm1I4tGnp08R5UlotHd8F404ukgDwMMfliEHOXpkBJ05FuTRaYcby2nUDt7VQzdGMqa8pvuSEh+0+VOxR/2mmZQDgRm4Yr7dUQhglqfi9Bn2LplDafmSWbdJL3q4Xkke3+pKoj9LEoJAGUPVmYe4gYbKfFNXVzxOyaA+ZvNp4nAy2mKd0rvBHwLZeY3iAMw5kJOzfu52qRncDweXG185P7gcFiVO5Vc5HK74ujuFmHdizzLXnUdYv1Whz5WXm4xQFptBkrxyQDqGPWDMl25m0fm22gRkp3myXsaTynmawc64CBappxgqWpnT0W2OBwmtvg2w8wQ0OozXpCoJCXXklOxlHFIsM7yj0mCfQsEZLY5miEh3feTn0DMub/DKmLwjVJ1KPzi21p/5kdFY+BIgrSjts0zRPxFfI5V2KtvI78fe8QCWsi/vJ8xf6199m+fOCpJWYrYxauGe5a55xHbUJpFAzUCioPabbuQpUbAfdAwHnO1wVNRH5cFl+M8rxIVBfqpsvLb37bZ/ELBhvwZvMWFtj9XEbDdeWsyyTGCLaf1VeyXlAgXXqQJLUZpTP4f5/3ZAO/knxh6oHkIFQbR4wZLzPyen+1vOOOBBAzcStlKYRDOkTaRxwtkDfNILUnmq8JcxBtQqmpWVMXgwJK3zvTHExNoVkfVKC+Aotk2ewQOa9wLOYndKOlhuw=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Statement 1 is correct", 
		"option_b": "Statement 2 is correct", 
		"option_c": "Both statements are correct", 
		"option_d": "Both statements are incorrect", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030130", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy+/Z90Z0uGn1d/tWWGp6zj40EGjb1P4IGRMC0FPp1gxNOI2evy1zFCPM9KmYl24Ylfa/1UxH25fNXPYPFojmuBNVH4diy8D3VnqD+EykhercOT/Cq6WNsuwQZynoZu6IgyM5ee2rya/kj4kAmO33qfR7h3LVqlu/mg4kCU4I0+9dmFtHLa9vvvn7jA5N8fZwVXsZJsI1Kv2Kkb/WoxX8u7egBO8vCPI92hmkxj2kyNxszuvFrmIU4=", 
		"answer": "24asaYX23Bzk48VyEGMnxG+ss8xYCf9hOX8GLR0=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VyEhfhhfTxNmTCEWcStz+3WqY0WHjuVavDd+ztiZ9wMVnJg1Q783XSqrP1t0UAg6ta54GaY25DfJ57iMSB0v23wH4BO8dSn8B264gSffpUjCuieNfaLvFr3S6hZ0H/dTS8CmQ0gj7aiX1Yp8Oy5me6FMw4zBYzmIg4+cA9KJeX2LvT5kKsxgOQyWuFTbkkGFrZp8ur7k2I4IoxptmCoyuXtPbsjrja454YdgFes8Z8bFWvnqwM6i88Edy7KBBOsfTfdVHjNCGiKwIEucrgwn1/w8IdVWwm8V9HkIYWY8J8w4yk7mJwO8J4GDK0twRWyJh/XhmZca742Wak9F06NVIiaIthvTQ0skPcKVp62n+UST5U1Il4vtFZhQtwbmZClXrplibLlG2OaNPw5I35xef24K1r965nKk6VOViYU58JdaeALmky3uGeTaBJJ4p1Eh7oAdsd6DjtJZuR0S1NgZkpPDfk+ziLl87heVGyttLugcZ6EPgTdtXM+t+luV7SdSruLz2cYIviVgTzTnL31h0ltBcsxiIZ7GfLSJ524SVNinaxXQRrlGflbW61nq9J64mLbM4z1vbtyCEV2PZ3i5O31Q85Bwe6mGxGtsSdVhxbxVGWE8IRwQQrAqBBG5CR5miVgXneQn9Nb8L3Fa2UgxhN2ff+gGh+/4ACVJiLP1namNtmxBajBvg5RW7oq4PqffMTSnAk//JUy/+1v42oNfC2OXY+Lw6/WPsZ8odUKAF0HxjJBCpbbKHuW5IISO5IkkLCkgkIU3dMFl+M66QJSQG56snHeG+eYrYdBxDxd/MAEs3wDkjbPfS7hHDdDrqF1US/UQQiXDOTJfxN9gv5fom+ZByh02tr9c3sNlQbcIseL2f+e328qKaNH0Y5fiJlK4tSaUKVWAQ2kS3QZ+1ozaUVeRQpAb23WVkY1gVHmn7AAVtOowBeXqupAEQvL6cFNFMUjSShA6UMT1zDlXoYi1qZwzHpLbYLOF1jeGWdz0/hjoFj3/7nwouAGMDqPKga2YhDJ6QbRdrAEFcfm/3rr/XvUWkrE31jbAOYaduG7/lX4E5rIMeDBoA=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Statement 1", 
		"option_b": "Statement 2", 
		"option_c": "Both statements", 
		"option_d": "Both statements are correct", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030131", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy+/Z90Z32Tgkl+4TbHsaCw9hMInadO+c6QdmIVcYdsyd6A1KT+131APcJX2ol8pI4XebRh2DGsesDSI75BzWuBKXn+NXmUB3V4lT/SynVF6IL74yi3V9s5yRZyn5R07MY4fN6Rmbyb7Q2ZkgqD0m+YS/1LElGYu/Km102rqIs7vY2Ct3LP/PG5m/rc5ttLcRxTq4NyZlWohOgA62U5Q830ax1Z4+HTdQuvhQbr+wyuEaaRgFrq1dncmQ==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzwg3r44AtVxDm1r3+J26QAG0DsXqARuFHWosaz7YKfQL9HtNMqfmx", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHSyxb48pZ6Eh/gwL3+dWzCDHcB43CFEq19fnSjQqjObezwwJQxLk+FjFV/4TbPreXk/1ZPgqFf7YKaMC0FPp9nzZCow+j2ymVIMIZrmYVz6tordPEA7SeiZtHIYP98yy6MKEbxczy5RH961CXejzx7oYf21DO3VdQjyRZypI586s1wfMCX0KubqESrxgfC2HKHTa9jFFqN9cyn/k2YoZAh9dqFtCDetODulbjH9d0fbQZbvMZvb1qokrtJ+Tg9EcW7fhtF9qTRcVX/NGiXLwcOucbswHFkw4w9HWo14QxDkcNbY8d+19jws3IiNt5vVTWorEkA05x5HzKXZqmwl3uk7VQxYXYuJYtjuG0wsxqMPBRxlCuIRCkRh5V5+NEakEgjfn1FnWLpjDjLjmCYPJrw54HygfuwnLdf/IokLE2BO1iCFoQPJbKAMWh+yeiVBKUcOoxrFizifdwgvC3xJda60CsZ2JkBO3vm+j6QkY3aOmC7vdLQjdF6FbEEdtjWqce4s13TZCehLnPTcsPxGSX5SzHZxwJkuQwsy2Ei4WbfDcU/9CMJ3nekCU130ijuaTyukP5I4ofOcoEix7X60j4TmfpxnJr72AR8RgevhGlG8pSTTl9K3hTfEI0TzAxuG7sTGJKR226TmXfeTzwEbI7+DqWCgzhHmuLzgXRp/8FdBcyYIxXYi9ApzQT9Qfx3USfsqonsKbxGWiQj/PJlwuis98K6Y/bkKXc/fw6yXa9Q/dVZYRFvHhnUBiVDIKynW5gNAdxB7nv+nwIIZmVGF1/fu6kGWUSDqcHEb2TaI7AOC17gbKcNU8vgT0rfOfS6iD/PRrCfkEawVkdlRymRIL4J9kuwbYT7Jxvzknphucj2PlBVQJBXKC/yYCu4t6bDDQkocikhaINJOlPdTlArlzvCKblIjqIBfhEuAaG0FVEYkgIPnizXTl5KokEbW+WvWRMzIqwFJUkE3SO8Hq5fUxqKkDUGjVeSzSf/afVFcV0rfiScjEnhldJgk/DmkM61AtGiILwc34xDPL5aUNrTDU4MjuCk6fPvHCwtDmg3OPfEXePfv0rlQsv7rc/JhV1Fzf4bOVMyITCNgJrKvHprILdCZn5N/X0cu4rbcQqr14xKl3g1c2EDuhnan7fEUpV8vsU=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Statement 1 is correct", 
		"option_b": "Statement 2 is correct", 
		"option_c": "Both statements are correct", 
		"option_d": "Both statements are incorrect", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030132", 
		"question": "25y2KIb72Brit5clVRf9y73+J26QF2oU43KCWKxmeWX6FKjELvn2zNdmKE6FiRxosmDJr6bx+VwKnOhX5o2eZCcHIcmCaQaWCJYN1WvukfGocrkW", 
		"answer": "24W5a5j12BqqxYwuVV79w73ZPHnVQZwS1TeF6ryyiFJrF/lycyU=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH+0BPl5Yw0S179w73rPW6QFG0Dr3vEQeNif33gVanNa/6+yIV0Z1CGjlpv93KGqquw41sKz5ha6oeZeSFDTIJhz5CG0aTRzWNEc/JMk5My9p8YdftOjDS+NNWbKPF83WuTL0r1Kiq1BWBxkHHXmHlX6Iq1tTOzUZoHwRY7kI57rec/OdaRmaqS+0S2ykaB1HqDSb5wFEaQr8usq0GF4Is2ociDojeb5/HwifXa854KbAwSqYlzYFqynqtJ+SksWN69fAsL2PCQaFruLD2nIh1d+sT22GB7z4c6HWU9/xoGqIJGY84/lrHquD0+Ot5jFH/6k0xJy51sTx6Yca70kEbh9xUFcHsnZIRp8G0WqQaQLRg+m2WYDD9UgoV5/9xZmhBreH1T3ELoiyzLgXeKfdPq+MD9lvv/o7Bi5qYjaVaJIVSYV80QZKHHIid83+SZCLQcPJknEiP0Kd0/6TjyJYXU3jcJkN8yKmby8SSN0tv6NWa7vZv6ztFkAa8UP97L+ouzpVmHdSyhNXWWJsb7Tw39SnLskwFj9wwgyzUf5mvbSJlz9DkIjTzwLjqXBmEjOEzZCjkNjIWi", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Mediterranean,Himalayan belt", 
		"option_b": "Atlantic coasts", 
		"option_c": "East African Rift Valley", 
		"option_d": "Pacific Ring of Fire", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030133", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0hj/5IAzEhn33O76J3iQF21Rpm2WQrc0Z3j3XOfKYfm+3pZlIk7JjFV/smXSpqT9qBG4XpypDZnFImqqI6X9cYIK", 
		"answer": "25G9bYGzxBfu8pcnQBHny/m/JXnVEHEEsXrBLrmgTV4uTnlCium6OLT8kw==", 
		"explanation": "25K9Z4X71Avn9olgehvz0ae/EW7VEyITpnGGU7d8MGXrUefnb//qwdBiZ0+cn1168XOK47H48kEKz6lJ7M6NdSUKcYV8iMeB0vbyhHxANMtF2sh/65YLefoA3jKuf52bKe0u3GuMJlH5cTyxHTB3mD7FjzxCp8Ov/SL7V8gi0wFyoo9x/ogsLtiH0KWa/FT4jgODyGjRXa0kAkGLp8G95UeVroV4p8KOunLa+vC5nerc5dAPdQlGupQ/V1O5178I7C8qEc+xfAEL4vHAZEblJSm3IgpRudnm13dhz4wuHX0x+Q9DkIJCd9J2xdjzuT48f8xoGiW/401U1NR+UB6afbO/kHjr6VsrSXQXa6lisj4hswafPFF62ludWCQL1KFp8cYc1RBreC9SmWXlkCmEiXfDPIfr7pL5wvuwoflt87E1JlbMdV/XWJ4Id7rDM2J2iuqTDKhSNpMnGDCmLdw++XntKISbyj4FkM4oJnTvtD6Rl439NnH6pJPti8Y2HaxAMN7X6s6z8EjIITHoMnjTUsP9SkjzR3323Qtp9wg3zTcV5nbLSJ138G0an2q1WwRigCjtLG6ohbdS7cKacM4l2/CszicCnvV7mtv+2RA5Qw26mXpPq7iRc1J82ETTDMUCxR0rCPQ2FYLU4DfWoX7VC2sMa8vkQaGJgzhA36Pji3J4rYYBXJ7OLhzYhdMj21eiFO18R2/oqZL8ObBVB2Et9Lt/za2oo4qpcP6lJWs5LxO5GeNQ4oBYbEJ9HhnQRSFZZbbuQpURVOdHknze0BQIRmsJBBrY/qUYWBarvtHaayrJZr0QTh/gbKUAU8fsXQfNOvilwT7ORq+TnEmqH3AtRyndKbEd9QL+aczwIRCyhnthuc7jckVTQcMfNSD7NHuroLCQHhQ/PyUraJ5PfwfHTgMhhijMLutbg5sOQAooUruyC1VWtARGkzqfO0gf8G0NH6iiUlZnIqZRYEwQ2TKnUaURSBnYlXoehlPc0Cf/LOhdPkAxNySHh0mgi4BjjOz8kIvBA9rhP7gawYgQaIJTTYmWD0kZieDx/eSgF2MrBWhkbuvHU+eRv0m2FsDx4tDP1VlZwbsJIlo/ZS6KnZrLsC99b7FHajBEvGELo92SYQ6r14Zc2WxmbFvO+kjoSGkm9hB9atPOcs3dJIis/14FVhPPUrcDjPR9nT/xJdrDbB8+E2Yx0RCRYtfYhzGNPqPuzrkMFwvi25bcQJgt/Fp83c+n0UkAqig1hmiiGX/JZ/ShqBdAYm9tT7CaFFFExhUt3DainlLmOc+vn7YIgLRSmIEb6B+3sCBmhlrMTEXAdXb4zf+RuSbJuActwLt2VWLjTHJ5yx5kUP9r4W1rQSBhSrNxvaLwP/HF3nW9K5G9w4gC8EUUQKjYLLiHs+nyALHQP7Hl1o7Zb0bp9NNvC+esIJ4KJjbZbDhfoabkY4rAZAeUfHiQ17qVUjucKjBe4moumyKNWxR5IG7zRM8dFjlG0JV3N7wD5M/qtAp2aG/BF/F9yeEIlV8ZA0VNCvPn2GVFHbhlPJePd00q7BYKDOEBJi2lbFlja8hP1WT0Sinv6if8hqh7FMPimho7sysK7U2PSZNrVLL9ZQosxw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Gases seeping from rocks", 
		"option_b": "Dissolved minerals", 
		"option_c": "Deep underground pressure", 
		"option_d": "Volcanic eruptions", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030134", 
		"question": "24KwbYP2kRj48sUhXhP91um/NGfcQ3YZpj+UXbF4dDbwFKDHd/7724QxK1OKjE9+9imEfG0Dmiec/TtFlnLNoUToJA==", 
		"answer": "25y7bZ3y3x2mzoAsXhHl1unwO26SLtb9eQ791IJHSRtimZ7lFA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH+0BPl5Yw0S179w73rPW6QFG0Dr3vEQeNzdWjwUbXRLuzszNd9KF+ImV5/sn/I45z1+18AmLtP5oCaMAwCaoJgxtGFl9T21noNc9FMk4N6pJMMPOdJ2CisYNHfYO58x2OBNUz8fnm0CjBgnDSWv08Wu5e64SL7W9x39ww9m4526oR8PsKLmamf+0L4gx6W2XWVW/1tH0CW9eOn5VedroN4tMOJ8Rvf9fz22sHW/NIEdRtGsIh6I1Kv17oM9iUvX82wKBRE46TZdUetJy2sMwYY68bi2jRvw4M9SHsx51MGi41VbtV335bj/DU1Jt5vByD240xP09RvTwWferqrnCji9Vg+Z3UnYJkh/Cw7pU+RPVA+imSIX2x4gMBo8d4NlA1tbi9Bnnn1ln/d0CjYLNaj5Ia8keD14K5s4K8jblLAPlLXQYNcYrbZNGJg2aXbBKhfP4pjHizhfcEm+Xn/IZubyipN7JsPI3On0iuQhsXzLGmG8dLWmtxzBv8OOcXE68ey8FvCeDDkMz2SdM71Skj1V3Xrx05suVg1xCAT7XGYBIB08G0knXu8SEpg3mfOaWvhrLtd5oOAe8Jx0vvonSIRiuBr35TxlC8pVBeyjDMDsJGLD1JAw1GWDMQRxQVuGLwEVJXe/G6Tm2LCSmgEcMC2B6eSzSgI0+2xt2Rxs58ZRpiBIhyZg2qMt7ifMQMdPluKKQ+fTA==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Hawaii, Japan, and Iceland", 
		"option_b": "Yellowstone, Hawaii, and Japan", 
		"option_c": "Iceland,Yellowstone", 
		"option_d": "New Zealand, Hawaii, and Yellowstone", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030135", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7gzPD+J3KQAGMEsHrDXaU0fXDpW7WCa+zs3Z9gMl2CiEg7rTQhNfKXw4zo3ab104jyFV2V", 
		"answer": "25i3fpT+1Bf+t4QsXRD1hfv+IGfEECAibVPSESGQflDHzqls9CJy", 
		"explanation": "25i5Yp7hkRzr5ZEoQwvzzvjsdXnVEHcdtz+FQKx5MGXrUefRe+n6zJkxNVmFiFpo9zbJpeXy4loDm+VO+c6LdSEXcYVmy5Caw/by12IBMspLlIcy4psKcOBTjDSjNMDTJb5Lz3yULwLjJzqvEWNg1AXeg28Wp4C44DWoFMolyRgzhI509Ig9KJeP1amH7Q26iROM2HqDQbh3SxSausC+7lGbpYws9YWdvTPP8ee5mfff/NcPZ0Ee/4J2dV6ukK0H7GpwQcS1fBdYsenfd1GtITiiNRpUtYvi2HAp0pAoU3oy+w1LwstGbsFn04ukrz45O8gqBTKptwRFxpd0HxiCfLiqmSjQ6FB/dHkocId4sCwhpAvcO0Bsn3iPDC9QgZNu7ZANnQEjfn1Vj2KgljDLhneOf4f2+YW8hOb04Kpr+6UzZQGHMFLdRIwIbL3HZ3R3w/qWBKUcJJ5xEjGmEsEm+Su5I5eBzDwekNAuLHvy8C/ZhML5OmS0upG5j9diHakJIsiF6MWz8FTSbCLvYXyQcsL7VxuwQ3Xz1k5ovhYsxiZQ53CYGoxs8D8bkXeiBE1qljLjaXjhhbtV+Y+HfIclyrdv4BGUOKxlEyeQ8nB7WBDo", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Ocean floor subsidence", 
		"option_b": "Volcanic eruptions", 
		"option_c": "Movement along faults", 
		"option_d": "Landslides", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030136", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQvv8IwvXF7zxv7wIGXEECIXrG3DRqtxMHnqU6/Hffm+2ZJjJFmHmVp89zbJpeX19kEbh7lO6IWaY2IUcZljzMeA0+GohkMst3mECz9vdIZZT5mKjEY=", 
		"answer": "25axepLm3FTa9oYpVBfxhfztMGrDQUljJFgpDvW/O7gkkJy4Rb4=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHh1B7j+ItgRhbz0b3+NmjfFmwFsD+FXbE0ZHnmFK/LaeX72oMxN1mbjl515nfBpuX/8RMKjrpP4Z+KcSkGbct4x8KF0/P+wHQBOtUEjoh3pKoef/1GxT7tRt3VJ75hyC6mLlf1Jw21DWM0nD7EmXlFoIy+uDSzVcoyxFUzhIJ5rc0yP96N2qSW+w2sjgPC7HqSQbttEhS2tsup5QOdroZ4vN7Nsjra5vX6jv3B+cQOZkhQpsZ2bU+5mbsMuD49Uty7ZhtIseXTdV37KTy6a04U98jvw3BgyIVpW3sx5QpDjJcWZ8FhwpD1qTM7Ot4qFD2+41JPy5d9UR6VNLiqxXjw6VoxZjoIap9jqD88pBzcKVhxlGzcWCRU1LJi8NdZmgIjW2ZSmTqgkSqIiCWOb9PJ6pD9i6Swibdn/a0iOkiBeRzMXohcVbvJK25i2uCVCLUQc7xvHi7jcZUv8j25NJ6Rny4Iw80lPXmn9yWYgdnmeWq887z2nMB+VL4OMpH25t6juBzmbCbzKH6SKovxQRj1XXX93Q1g9xll2ygX5mveAYp++zlNkGu9S0F20ijmLG+kn61R44HOepg03eH/nTYFnbRskNvj3Bh8TgqviG1CsZCWQFJcjVvQXtkCxx0hAr0CVIbd83mThjbZRTwZd8flQbqCxCVH1KEqftrvXlPqFLp3CRc7sg5b", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Circum-Pacific areas", 
		"option_b": "North America", 
		"option_c": "Europe", 
		"option_d": "Africa", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030137", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRfr45AyUxKywfTsNHjEBnBRqmzDU7Bnf3LqVbPHaq3pwIN5Z0iBiBt9/WTLorH5+F1PgK4b/Z2KfiMOd5gwipxx6guS3KbpRX/GTYGBoto=", 
		"answer": "25C5eoX7wAzr/IAzELIFuvylO1ecWc8cSOLqYVU=", 
		"explanation": "25C5eoX7wAzr/IAzEh/gwL3rPW6QDWMFtm2CXuNweWLiR7PHfP6+xJhiMxyKglZ2/XjKuuXx5EAAjKFa/YubMDUKaoMv3NiMl+L41nxAJ89LlMB94toLb+FOzTCkZ5TvM+tgz2OJNAXzZjf9BXxnm3HUjzxCuoq88iKpUd53wgxygIh07skyNdTf3LqG+FmxiQiRkDudSbNgAliQscu7q02ZoZB4ut/NpDzf8ea5mPfX+dsYIgdU/5F+d16u2+gG6mo9R826KB9O5eHfc135JWiqKh4c+t/wln1nhpYhWCk79xpHjMN+bdd2wJ328HI1Pt9+HSKvok9F1NR9TRLWYLW9kHj26Vg+Z2NrZIRp/CA6shvcLkZ7i36ZQjgRl4F+7dVZmgIjaXxVknftiyzHwHWObofq6JXwhPr8ufl3+qw0LAGUPV3MFoIfZqbSZ2ZmiuaJTaRZPZpmAyqmKd0rvDb6JZeanz8B39Yyb0Pv8Tmc0tj7PWCopJPti8Y2B7oJJdzM6ouyplnJdTChInydJs/9Shj8Tn/9kwJkpR8giDcf5HfVDZo/+itNiX+kTFYo0iDlYnmzl6pV5IXOb4Em1ufqyD5Qmfp834v4wBgyUw26gXNa8oCaXEhd2FfCF9sChB09GboAGZ/CsK485IKfYbCNiiUU4OTVvds=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Volcanic eruptions", 
		"option_b": "Earthquakes", 
		"option_c": "Hot springs", 
		"option_d": "Landslides", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030138", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7gzPD+J3KQEWcQsHCNEqV7YjH3XKKCYuz9wtd+IRyIjk9y5HOGtar89FIBgK1IqYeRMDYLe8tmxsSMxe341jFONYZHlY5m7ZQacuBTk3/eUUMcBzMGh1uQCqrpu97M", 
		"answer": "24asaZP63RD+7sUvVF7mzfi/EGrCF2pWsD+AQLZnZDPHqv+5jgTEhyiodcZVoRR9", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHjwxDn9pc5Egz3xO7wOyvWDHBRt3eGEq91c3qjW6GCb+7qwIF0Z0qGgVh6/HnDsOX5+RMbh60b4ICLdTAKcZkvx9bJ1Ov50HhPNshQicB799oLdPEAzT++cdrYJb5hyC6UIkbkaDe0BzBkmDDCjzxUp5a18SapXd8kgDg9hZM4+8cwP9aR0KvT6U6sjxCLyGLRR75nBEaK9c+8q1OQoZY99c+CpDzf9ebwn+ufsMkDZxpX/5J6YE+zmaEKuDo0UNyxe1JC//DVc1XuNGiCM04e9sX102Zuw4w9HWs74RFCg5FfZ9M/lpfquXIgM8x+EHOptkZE0pdoTFeUcbO90XzsoFQxem4jYJgh/CEwoAuVJlM+jmTcWCRU1IZk7N0YgQ1scy9Pmjb2jTOIgWuGf9Pi+YPvxcnk4L1q5KY1LkSOIRzaWZgSYbLSLmJhhqmLAadINownGi3wOJUv7DjrNNrU3CsI0c0pIXCn+i+O0s7nLHau85P3ipR3GLMPIdjL7ou6sVvKYGP1Lj2BY8r3UUjkR3m4wBt3sRkmzWEk+mPWG49w5yBNnHGlR0BlgC7lfzyil7Ac646dcM491vTonSYf2OJ3k5j22hQ/BwW4mXZVu5CGDVce+8KKQ4bTyMHot17LTLQ=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Intense folding and faulting", 
		"option_b": "Coastal mountain ranges", 
		"option_c": "Stability of the Earth's crust", 
		"option_d": "Oceanic regions", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030139", 
		"question": "24GwbdH+0BPl5Yw0S179w73rPW6QFG0Dr3vEQeNzdWjwUbXRLuzszNd3KEmHiRty/DbSq7f18hMCjqJU+86eYicCbdEv4dOM2+X5wD0BAclQlZJn5doWcrRuySrtTtHaLP9gyiLAJkv0JwaCO09Lqw7pyM3i2vmRnvlWfpOvBN1F7/Q=", 
		"answer": "24y9ZJ38xgr++IslEAjYU9dHFj41RfletCsLv7M=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn2RD488UtUxT9173+J27RQ2kfrGiNEqV7YjHkUb7Ra//tiZ5iZ2WMgVd05WXSrKv1t30Om6FU54+TMBICbIAvwd7Jw+zyhERPOtJBnsBB8JsLeecA5SnqZ5TJJfBh2WCFIwX2aCv9DWRn1DbThWherZG29Cv7Ut821AAgk5Q0rcEyP9uK3aGd7w22kwuHznSEW/1jFE2KsNy7pwOUr5Z4pt2fuDzc57i5m/bXsNEfag1A/45mZ0mzg6AM6ic5XYiybRNf5PbVchbH4E9CH9JldhEKun5mOlTN", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Ye,ll,ow,s,to,ne", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030140", 
		"question": "24GwbdHh1B7j+ItgRRfmzb3rPW6QBHAUomuGQbc0c37tV6LMev//3Z5+KRyGixt68WLPtaCw4VwDjKlV5ouMPGIIcIR4xpCIxKTjzHQBdPZFmYl07ZlfTv1Oy32icpT9KexrginALkvzayy5AWM0lz7DhGhEoYaotSuyX9936hQil4k0reEyONiR3Lua6QH4hwiGnESud4JbLmum9zkkSKFmGPHmb5pPYJQ32dU=", 
		"answer": "24WwYZ36wQnj+YAzEDo1dmYVqAYH3mL16Btx0MI=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHh1B7j+ItgRRfmzb3rPW6QBHAUomuGQbc0c37tV6LMev//3Z5+KRyGixt68WLPtaCw4VwDjKlV5ouMPGIIcIR4xpCIxKTjzHQBdPZFmYl07ZlfTv1Oy32icpT9KexrginALkvzayy5AWM0lz7DhGhEoYaotSuyX9936hQil4k0reEyONiR3Lua6QH4hwiGnG+ZTf1UGV2VvN644k2Zs8IMvcSe8TrU5uf8ifDc9ZMYaglCuoI/Ykm5lugM9ikxQ8u4bQEL5ezVIWTsIyGlLg1d1sjm13opx4wtHWAntBxOg5FXYdR2xJH+uTZwPdQqHD2upkpTwtRoWhSCe7Ox0yjl40E2Y3M/fMYttSM2rRqYIVp52m2OST1EkY5/vtUYhxBrbHpBl3Pzwj6FhCWZc5/g6o71hqj1sqxz5qooJ1LCypvz1rprU8/FGZjdqMUBLw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Ph,il,ip,pi,n,e,s", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030141", 
		"question": "24GwbdHQ2Avp4ohtYh/xzPv2NivSBm4F43aQErFxY2HsWrTLbOH7iZF+NRyInUtp/W7PrqTk8l8Wz5dk1rHaMC0FPp9nzZCe2Pb7wDZSc8NFiJR69Y8ed/FTgH2gdd/SLvkux3rAKEv1Jza7RGR8kXHbhW9C6JC+/DS2Xdl30hA1n4h2/opXpMP8CAEbPn8oh9IO34Nx", 
		"answer": "24a9fpT9xQCo9ItylqgZYgc6x+GCMo79og==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ2Avp4ohtYh/xzPv2NivSBm4F7z+MQONEcXLqUq7BLt/3x5AxKFrJq1Jp9zqGpqvz/kEMg61IqZqXdWIzf4hmztmKl8v0wXBPc8dKnsB799oXdfNIwCTtZ9HSM/NnzW+MK1ywZjqpDWZx1BjCyn1Vq4yu+zOoFNw40lUgmZJ/5cQlfIDPnOic7g2/igmA3XfRTbx2BVyIoM+j7lDcpJc99dmC8TvV4PH3if2T5NsIdgdctoU/c1e9g61J8SQsVNq1awZC/urDIWf4Iiy2JBoU9sWjzHtnw5FlHX488Q1DwoxYZ4Bj2pnwuXIjNsNhBnO4pkpFxoB0HxaYe6mw1XqooFEweHMlZJ5o/Dk9qBzcOlF5k2SSAGxShoVq6tkXkkRqcGJFkmXlwjiOj2mAe5rg6oy8lvzipapwspcvIFLAOF3TU55cbKeAKGl3iuadTbJUNt9qGDHyfdAv7i3xMYOV1DxAwMsvIXKn9Tick961Lmqov5buh9BzVr3YXdoIcnD7GBLHPzL4Fkw=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Se,ve,nty,ei,gh,ty", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030142", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gdx/g0fXuIGrbBnFRonGHErV7fHLiWqjHfa3/25IxJFCGnl536zbUpqnx41YLz6FVqZqXdSsRPo9m28Sb3ubi0HhOPfpKpo5A4ZsMc/oajAmlcZTfKe163GeCMlH5aDf9C3Y0kTDEnnRHvYKw8DT7V9U+zhY7koJrrd81KN/fzaCWqEmxlRKQ1XmEXLRrHxSWs46+5E+foYw3sN7PyZs+SMWyR09z+erh8LA4Wg==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiIQrXvDYON9YzH3XKKCbeLs25JyMxyMlUt383jHt6z/+RMJgLobyMzhe6ddeFdnLLMGFYjfRT4E", 
		"explanation": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRt3eGErFxcWLsWufDfOi+yphjNVmKmWd1znjjorfk/0IajqNe+s6efiZDaIRjy9GH2OHkhHBTNoZHlo9h4ZYGPOZFwDy5cdCbKfAu2maFLlewYzCuEGJ9liTCg3NY6Lez/DT7Xcl3whAxl5Jr6Ig+M8OXmbib7UO3iwOM3TuQWrgkAUaQuM+64k+F4IYqvNuIv3LZ7bTtn/vH/9ACYUhCs4drZhuxmL4M9S82Rdv0XBpOseXDclH/NCGsKU4e9tnx03d9yptpTn014BpVwpdeY9QzwpDhpXIxLcgqFj+1sEFM3tRuWhuXYLi87GbY7mE3cDo5YIt+syN1qBzcKVhtlSufQz5DkYN/vuQRkERndHxUjn/ilyuCj2vPc5Wj7oHukeDhtbho97BnLU6FJhzRWIkZYLeAJGh7xOqSCaMcJJZzH2LyNdBu+DDqNISd3SwZ2dYub3jhtDyWns70N2q/oN65ntVkALYDI93E+8eu8F3Lbi3mYW2fZ9/xGQr/WnL80hxssgtl7i4CqGfACYRv+ShB3mq4TARUkyTpanWi1oxV5IXOcIhx9fz+2H5Qj/xxnJO30RM/Tha4gXpQ8pCXShx/zFffGMQEhCYtCbUPWNbY4S2X1WTVTHUCcY79D6eQzWxO1fGxjG5pt9AIR4mfORzVnp4jyQWlCexsVGzou8b4M/hVHGsg+bN/w+7htsmvfOWtOHxmLxO7VfpK54dQfAt1FkvJDSEPY7ShRZheU+VD02HDmAlbT3ZZRVjJ778NWArqvszNLn7JbPEMBhvsbL4AHc+60mejvnS+j0A7536C1g9KiA==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030143", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gdRvr1vjtJivREWdRrHmXV600cWLwW6TLb/n7zddmLkiBzU9z92TLoqmw+EFPmadX6o+ReSFDbI5owd+HxNj5+H9zNsdXlY4opL0aZedF3i7tcdnSNL59236FNU31Zi24ADBngDTXhzxXpof7/SivFM021BAg1oNt6IgoM5eL0a3T4Ei5kg+M2zueTv1zEECcp46q7k+Tt8I6usSBuDzctOT2k/bHsNcFIhxaupV6I0m5kKEG9jl65UVuB99DOp9STcMDo4Snxg==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiIQrXvDYON9YzH3XKKCbeLs25JyMxyMlUt383jHt6z/+RMJgLobyMzhe6ddeFdnLLMGFYjfRT4E", 
		"explanation": "25K9cYL2wwqq9pclEhf8wfj6MSvfBXYUrT+CQbB7c3jiQKLGLvr33Z8xM1SMn1Z6/jbJseXm+F8MjqZS6s6NdSUKcYV8hJCe3+HlwTFVO8NWn8B799oMdfNOxTukd9XVNL5py2GUL0DiajixRHF3gDjAg2hP6Lez/DT7Xcl3whAxl5Jr6Ig7Oc6M3LqAqEi1jxLCz26BTa9sFFWNsMro+FeZoY94tMOJ8TrU4LTum+zW4p4Pdw0Sq4k/d1O516AM+T4xX8/0ZxQL5uXEZEatIi2vKBld8N/wlnZmz44gU2505BBPjJcWa84zwpDhrzdwLchtHDy0sAR0z5E8VhmCcbOr1Sjs5VQrNXw5aoctqiI5og6SIVc+lXncSylegIhu7N0YmURifntJin/0m3+JhWuKfYfrq5T0gKjVoat3+uQ0aVKVJ1rZVYhcZrLOZ2Rz3/qeTbFdJ5p1Vzbpfdcr/zb0JdaHyikIwtElLmPi8GbZnsj0PWy0tNLtgZRiHLpANdnE+8q0pFnVaDD1KH7TY9nhSRz5QHLrkwFj9x8g0TIV+nGaAI9uFCkY8Ht7eqt70wvSvA==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030144", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gZhb3hfD+P2TCCnYI43CFEqJ3ZHj1UefUYeH9yJl+Ik/JjEl+snrJoKTk8ldPhqYb/YaaMCsNao59wd+bl/byw3hOPdUElYYy55URaP1OyTO5Z+jVHPBcy2+TKEuqJw+yCHN1mj7TmTxXuob7+SKoR5o0zxg/mYk47MQzMtDf2qeS+1m5ikaP026fXLxtHxSLtMCv7lDcoYw89cKLtyHT++b82vHA/N8FZhsQDMgrvHL9agYE8ZLrkdyDzw==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/M2rcEGdTMGpJFXhmL/SRcvUWGeF7zw==", 
		"explanation": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRt3eGErFxcWLsWufDfOi+wJlyKE6biFhvznj6rZH48hMCjqJU+4eLaWIMeMtuy8SAweG30n5NMMdKlYVhpJsNebRBzym4ddjXOb5iwW2BM0D0JzixC35z1CXTiWhZpoq4tTe3Vc4ygBc9g4l87No1OcTTmb+b4U6wxgeQ2TueTqlhHxSfutum7wOSpYMq9c6CsCHP+P33n+uT/8xLdwZWupQ/d1O516cK/Ss2Efy8bQFOsebfdFrpITqqIh1d8MXg2mFtw8IqUmci8Q1Bh41CIsJ8w5bgvSA5Ot4qXSSyplZFh4RwXgOTZ/2732To6VE6PDZrYYN7uT8ypAGIaFZxj2WYTT5YkZMrtscRkBZmPX9MnWLlkX+Gj3OKPJLz6pLozKSwobdnsrc1KE+TM1PKW80eaqbOI2Zgw+yITe5LO5p1EmL2MdQ6+Sq5M5qd2zxNwNgzOzfi9SmR0sLhMWCo+q73stpAG7MDN9/K7Nj3sU7CIS7uM3jTZcT5VAf+D3303ABi9xsqyTIE6W6YBYZq+zkMl3DwW0VqlSLzLH2vkv5T7ISdd4Ej1rXlzj4RlvBr34vl0R41VAG3lD9Bt4eeWk9KjUDeG94ChAg8CbUSVJfD9y2Zk2LVRTwMbN35AqGG1ylMmvT4mmk9q5UNQYOAJRqbmtIn3BLxA/JsW2Psuo/8LrwhAmE+/7R+2Ojt996zcLO2KWQ5YBT3Sf1W5ZxVbQY7FQTYFmRBb6zuV54dVPJOxnDGjkdbUm9ZCkjYu7wAWESrudfNfH7XbL9eE/IjFK6LEKuJ77GLkSV0Iw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "Both A and R are false", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030145", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "25i5Yp7hkQ/l+4YhXBfxhe/6MmLfDXFR7j+gW7F3ZXzTVaTLaOT9iZZjIl2awRtc92/Vprfjt1IBi+hT5prfYzIRd4Vo252w0uj7y2ZSJ8lKn8BC5YgUMLRlzS+5fMXOIfVrg36SKEv1Jyu4A3l7miKWuXNap460+2eSR9Y2zhEh2sdZ7tw1KtLfz6ef60y2iQORnHKfCKlsFBS4ocKp5VeVo88VsMmEpTfJ5vX3n/ndtvYCbwlevp9+bRu+kqQdtGjyj6fM+t3E7MKDowl/tMl/", 
		"explanation": "25axepLm3FTa9oYpVBfxhdztMGrDWSIlq3aQErFxd3jsWuuCZePx3pkxJk/JmVN+skbHoKz2/lBPvaFV7s6QdmIld5lqhJCM2ef+1nJNNtUEjoh3pKoef/1GxT7tW9feIfAuz2CEZ0zjJzq1BWJ1lyXTmHVMrYf79z77XdQjxRshk8du4sQ/PdmW2uiS5kn4lQOLz3aYS/1lEkCQo8e88gO1tMIxu86BpDbe57T6le3d5MwCZxsSs490ZhuWlrgI9mZ4eMawZxxO4u3RLRTsLizjMwYYudzmxWBs1IxpXmY15wtVwoxQIu58xIzs/DM+O41ZGiauqwRhypFuVhSXSLOE3k/h+UY6Z2lrZIRp/AU6tU+vOEZ3lGyPDGERrYVn8t8OhhBsc2oArHfyiWXLuWCDcJz0+JTzi+2wjrh3+6wpKE3ABV3KXc0Va/PUL2Iy/+eSGaNYc6xzFjbjLpUn73n/IZubyipN1tYyb37z52qel8LhMWCovpP1ztJzFasVJNTWpYu+vl/LdCfoL3rTYc7tSg3iXDz02gVg9yRn5y0UqETZAZ138zgBojzwSEpg0in1YXmzmatPqoqBa84iw+fl0zUDpPpEkb72xgk0VhG6hnoOgpaQQVkP/1HRF8IJ10ljTIcOGJnc/WPWvGXcSnIJbJS2NaCO0GxBye/wgGU9sZEaXIOAbBDVysouzVeCDuhtXSfdqYXwO/UWSm0/uqJw2PnhuMz7YfuhbG0jaBK7QK9K9pxCZQt4EAfRHGROY6ynQJheQPJK0zXBmQhfST9IFhrY861IbQWpo8LBbSrsar8bThHkI5UMAcu0DkrOPvinz3DAEv+Mh0iwWgQxQXqYIKIZ7Rble4f3N1OynWwk787pMVBVTYBXOTXmZH+wqq2QNwgGcQ0mPINRfwfjRBwnlTDMIuonhKlAZBAoAYmzFVEYghhM0hPXClFRtV4MXquoQV1nbOltKVYQwTasEK5ffhnGkmBKul6V0WLuLPZfcUwteGuen03ziJd13+3shYeOBMeiIbQQ180XILMbaZPSUnoIlvLq++jjUV4wAmpyYrjlW+bYpErkEMn6p8LUiRxKx7pIIlc+ZRGChJ7V8SNsPOV7Z3VZuDMYvs/TcUary40Z3l5nR1us8072AWUuohkzb5D/Y8vZao2q/FNeGCvCRPlClvg4zintJtLYZ1o+BHc8hw6Eb56K1zWRKaX41aEIFxS7l5jZSp9j6Ahtxtny7klEoi9wnW7jBXPbbKfs5hoUK3I4WbGYE1JTlVct03ql21D8MoGjhOYZgrFV3fUQ7gLhpzNxilCPSgrCanjvnuKWsibut0ogxat6XXXhaCni0u256/+5QiS8Mtq/vg==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Major volcanic regions , CircumPacific areas", 
		"option_b": "Geysers and hot springs,Yellowstone Park", 
		"option_c": "Earthquake,prone regions Solomon Islands", 
		"option_d": "Active volcanoes in the Atlantic,Mediterranean&Himalayan belt", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030146", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "25a3fZ/nwxDv5MU3Wwr6hen3MCvdDHEF436ARqpidTH1W6vBb+PxzIQ8F1SAgVJr4n/Ipra8t2UAg6ta54ecMDAGeYJgxsPJ3uq30HlEc+dQloF88JMcMd1DyTGsetCXYNtv3HqINlDxbDz9AHlngCPfiGlCoYy1tTW+U9M4zgZ/tY5q7t0xDNac0K6a6w25lAODzzfRYLJwUUeJp8em7AOJtIs0vNeMpTvU+rnQmf3f8dAPIGBtZWIHsxf1cUxTHWV9/9Y=", 
		"explanation": "25a3fZ/nwxDv5MU3Wwr6hen3MCv9DHEF416ARqpidTHVW6vBb+PxzIQxahy5hVJ3+2bWqqv15AlPu6Beqb6XeS4KbptmxtWal+3khGNEPclTlIV2pJwQbrRJ2C7tfN3cKL54wWKDJkv5ZHm8B2R9gjjCkzxSvYb74Sj7Xc4kgBk9lYZs5McyfNaT1qaUqFmwg0ay3XiYTrRnUWaQu8no5EXchosqsIHNsHLJ8fPwlfaT59cfakhT/4p+cVy516Yc9Sg9Q4i7blJK8vDZd1GtNievJA8T9s7w6npVyLQmUWo1+hZFwrFTZcl82IuktTxwK8VvVRKur0VO051/H1rWXb693Gnq5A9/XHkuaYtjuG08sk+QJ1d/jm6YDCNf1JRj+5A0nAAuXHtMnXj0izzLsmyLe5avq4G8ke3ztLZt+6BnK06VO1jZRJRccrvFNWIy3uGeTYhTIYtvVwPrOMcn/zj3YJea23koxcshPH7m+mqJnszhPHb6vpf8mpRCHLYTdsPA+t67pE+HaC2hMnSUaMLyUAvxQWi4xQFptBkrwSJQ6WHMAZ924TRB3nOxQk1qlWfJb3mtl7BYqoPOcYEl0vfg2HIGl/h7npX+110uQgOygnF/vLiRal1d2VzHC8wMwUkKBacVBp/T53mfmniQeXkKdsH4EujKgw9ByODkgyxNvpMHU4WNbDjJj981kleFCfg5dm7/q5P0cMwUCW0q87Ex2OimvsW1ObOlIHYlLxG5VvhXs5RCKBZzFEvtBCdGZrGtFq8XT+cP3XOKsQ5aQjMJAFTP8roLUQG56tDAayruYrIVCBfhI5wGFs/2DkbBMbGg23DCCLCLmwe4UFZlRy6OYbgE4g+waYn7Nx66kChl+tXsJFhPXc9XNSnweH69rK2ESwAoej0wLYRTOkLUWQQshSvCLPx0zaYOdFg7TqSkGF4flVFKjSvCGlFKvl8iUZmjaFwzappVMlIfyneABakTVQbLkjMFgBbRggvvLPZKP015O02QikDhlZYmluypiYCOHdqiK7IJkogFLrNYUJPAGlcF2ubw5u3pC2U3AS1+OuuIX+DEvkv3DNy0pcbV0VRO27MJOh8+KzyZjoaVsDNjLKlaa3lEujMRrdjcZxW50IZelVhnRBX/5VPtT2Ay9hd8fNPjb9zII5WisFFREmTCW7xAjO5x3iXwLJ/WYRQ6FWIhmAieNubCzifDNaX8yKEAAhC2xNniRo9h7UZ9ic/yxlRQrilhhm/nS3/UIuDo5wpcJ251SrjfH1NYlBA7lS+l11/hJ46+jqkHzF33HB5En6gQ4VIWcecxxBI=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Countries with the most active volcanoes,Philippines", 
		"option_b": "Volcanic regions in the Atlantic,Iceland", 
		"option_c": "Earthquake distribution regions,CircumPacific areas", 
		"option_d": "Hot spring utilization,Iceland", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030147", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "25i5Yp7hkQ/l+4YhXBfxhe/6MmLfDSJc41eKX6J4cWjiR+uCXOj5wJh/Z0uAmVM79HPR46Tz41oZiuhN5oKccSwMe5gi4d6d0vb+y2MBIcNDk49899oQerRDwzO5fdreLup9gi6lJlfkbyioBXtx1DDQnnlErYW98CSvR5cD0wA8l4px/oR8FNiLmbuD+kS2gUaXyHKdQadlBV2Wu4OA7kKIqYw/9cWCpCHe57YgrWewzW5ignL9qqRuNJcC", 
		"explanation": "25i5Yp7hkS/l+4YhXBfxhc/6MmLfDSJc41eKX6J4cWjiR/2CWeX3xZIxM1SMzXNy/3fKorzx5BMOna0b6M6MeSUNd41my9GHw6T6y2RPJ8dNlMBg5ZQYebRSyS64eMDSLvkuyHyPKgXkYjqpC359l3HGhn1CrcO4+iu3Xck+zxt+1pNw6NF8PcWamaac/A2olA+P3WmYRKQkGlqWosDo7UyO4IM7ocSbtHLN+/j6m/bc9c1LSwZBq4N+Zxf8g6AMuAIxXMm4aQtK4qTHZEboYC6sNQMY/YvhzzR9zodpXmY4+BZVi4xYIs91lozsuXIZMcljFD36okpEh7FpTRaFfby2kHzh40Ewe3MoJZphvTkwsjOSFFpMn2yVQyIRg4l/9pA/kBMjXGxUlWDlwgmEjGaOcpzm+MCxxcH+tLxx+6w1aXOFMlXXWJ5carWABGh83uCVCKhIIMUnIyrvLpU96DjtJZuR0S1N2cpgLHj15i+aho3BMWD6upzti8Z/G61AJNTC4MS5oxzIZ2PiLnOHb8XxVxzjD2jhwwdmthQp0WEY6XTdSI964igf3n+zXU1yl2f2Y3Cil7BT75HOfIE8w/T+2DZQjPs4nony1Q58SQG6nz9TvoWLShxNwkHYGswVzQw9MLo9GrPQ4HmehGPRQHlNXsjiBLqCxSpN2ffiziw9i4MbW42DJQqByuo13RmwDPRqFWTspsb7OLwUBCQt/KZ02Oinsc+4YbOrKiUpagijWOZXs4BfbAdpBgrJADYPZbm8QpUPVOFE12aG1xdJVWtABk/A+roERES+osvbayrfcKITDRfjd7YBU9nxWk+PJuSrzCXKEraTmwekUEogXXqpKbVN9hL0fon8ZBe6gHho+MLgP1RVUMMYOmf8d264q+OUChI/bWwmKYQHfULbTgIlgDuDN/ZwiLUGZRRtUq2mWUcXgBRcozDuAHBKpAwtT7ekTlRnH71MLFILzCO8Hq5fEVzigzseh1ibggrjPOlOIhNjU2uHz1/wiZtomOypg5yESt3sKbge1s0WPL9XTYDTGxsaleGk6OTvBWQ8FGB2IrjAW+PFuUHxTojko9HOzF9exb8aOkZ7LDfLm5re+TVjPOVYZmRC/XQco97aZxSn2IQZx1V7X0D+9kT3AVMpvwIzZ4Cra53PP4ix8VlRFybLUvlClvg42C/reNnDbR8xA28s0RCRb5LeyHSWLqm7zqwdEAqj29nDQIt5rE523Jykwl5JpC5mz2z3GWbVceL+pF5dLH90XrCWFFodjhIjwTO/2RPgMoKvlOSkAuswqLS7JTdAtLnLIIZE", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Major volcanic region , Himalayas", 
		"option_b": "Region with few active volcanoes,Interior regions of continents", 
		"option_c": "Earthquake after effects,Tsunamis", 
		"option_d": "Hot spring utilization,Heating houses", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030148", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "25axepLm3FTa9oYpVBfxhe/6MmLfDSJci3aEWuN3f3/gUanWfOzqwJh/Z1OPzU10/nXHrar15BNDrrxX6ICLeSFDfYRu28Sal6m34nRWc8dHjolk4doJc/hDzTOiccebbNtv3XrABkPibjq8CjBGnTfCyjF7qY2itSO0Rtc2zgFymZU46NAoNdmczeiF50G7hwiN2WjTe/L5Vg3gPWv74RfO3vsnMw==", 
		"explanation": "25axepLm3FTa9oYpVBfxhc/6MmLfDSJc41eKVas0U37tV6LMev//3Z5+KRyGixtN/XrFoqv/8kBVz5xT7M68eTAAa4Yi+NGK3uL+xzFTNsFNlY4+pJUNPMRBzzSrfdebEvdgyS6PIQXWbiu4SDB9h3HdhHNBpsO9+jX7Xc4kgBw8goJ2/s18KNKczaed4U74hwWW1W2YXKQoUV2XtsK970qSp8I2oMCIoz3O57TvlfTQ8dAEZxsSi452cBu0mLoa/TkwXs35expK4eHUIVX/JSnjIgAe8Nng2nF6hpYhWCkE9RxPhIpVIu9w05nqgDwMMex+GTK0t01Dh7dzXgSCZ/31kE7h9xUedm4ic48tiiI5og6SJ1FtwCu/QyFBlZJu+pANmkRib2pBjzbsizSOwHGHedPT6oP1g+Hz4Itq/KRnJkfAE1XKU8FccbvFZ0ZmxuiVGa9fc5xoFjHyLpUp+Tf8MpeY0yBN2Ng2Kjfh8T2cgI30OnGzpZe5mNt6F74OOdTWqf+/uU+HaDChI3iQZ97nXEjkR3m4/gdh+jkxxCAe/GvbSLt28SoI0j6nQU1ol2foZXupmqcc/I2CfI8/2vagnTsD2Ph5jZzy2AR8VA2vmH5Xt4DfWlJLyEbBH9kC1jUgMLogEoTY8WzRhjb1Sm8ZP+/wE6GEwiII6Or3miEw/70PW5XOCBbJh98o3Fe+E71cTXPkpoXtfcoaBmct9L102bfhg8K+NdalP3FqThylUOxY/dVjYQRvUQLORS1BZL2rUt0VT+9Y3DXMmBUITmtaRV3J9KQHWg2pq8iIb2nKaqcVGgeuI7oLEMLtSk7BMrGn3T3MFLCJhgeoUEgmTzSSJKNN0g/5domyNxy+lihl68SlNl5JSYIZKGf8Ziu8vbeKBQUuM2wxII8HaE7TX1Ath37CZ+puiqkJdhEuQKazWVEEkxAPmTHATkhKpEkQS6ysTBMhP71QMl5R2zi5EqERVR+Khzkeh0CV1jusLe9OcV0sO3CbigzvlZVplvHuwpqECcDtI7QYkp0RJ7VeV4nTDBm4HMiFsf4/rTnSsORm69cr", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Circum,Pacific region ,High concentration of volcanoes", 
		"option_b": "East African Rift ,Many dormant or extinct volcanoes", 
		"option_c": "Atlantic coasts , Few active volcanoes", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030149", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "25K9cYL2wwqquqAyRw7mzPLxdWTWQ2oetz+UU7dxYjHiWqOCffn7yJo9Z3mIn09z42PHqKDjtx5PuaFZ+4+LeS0NPpxm3NiA2aTSxWNVO4FX2oNg8YkLMLR03yijddnSM74jjkmJIET+czC+RGR9kDDaymtXvoaouWeTW8538wUgn4l//ohxfP+QzeiE6Vm9lEaQ1WiYRrokBl2NvcG9/wOZuJI0ut6EvjyZdMKxpPKl8mgrlSmv7X30Ew==", 
		"explanation": "25K9cYL2wwqqusUFQAvi0fTwOyvfBSIZrGvDRaJgdWOjVanGLv7qzJZ8fRyuiEJo92TV46Ti8hMMh6lJ6I2LdTAKZI5riNKQl+350HRTPs9QjoV88NoabuFQ2DSiesebL/guxmGUZ1LxczyvRHF6kHHFnnlXpc/7+iGvUdR30Ac9hoJ04c04fN+W3qDT4UOsiUaW1H7RSbR2UVCMsI685AOMsocrptiftHLd5vv02vDW8coOZkhHsYJ6cVyumL0H/GovUNyxei5Fzer1YEb5KDm2JgUY6ouulkJgxJAoSWA7+l9Ri5dea84z85n2qDp3LI1pByaptx4A4pVuSx+HYbyz1Xuk8lAsYHY/JYx/syB1tQeZaEdrnm+ZQmxDkYxu/8Mc1QtlPWpOmWTnm3PLg2Sab5rt7MDqjOrioa1q/a00aVaJIVTRWM0IbbaAAmZg3uHcHuZfIYp0A2LSNdw9vCv8LJOVzDxN399gKnni5i2A0sTmeXGjo5v6j9h6Df8EI9SF/cT3pFnEdSzvKH7Tdsf1TQ2wQnPu1gNguQw2iC4CqHTXBIp++yQO3n+zXU1ymzP5UHKdmIpP/4yPcocik7is+jsXmfpslpi3wBQ4Rgj7mn5Vt5fFD2hc2FrXE8QUhAg8CfQNFYTW9y2ZlnPRRTwaftjzEuiT0SVP3ebji2U9vYlOQIKKKQvMi8oj2le1CO5tQHXvqYj6OO9ZSnc5+boxy/7hssupYfu1OWQhagn7GflW/5ZQZgt4UQ7PEDRbabegRdFeTvIP3nTEkxRETntMFhr4860RHQerpITEa2vaI6UTTg7tdLYXFdv0DkbBMbGtzSbIFaudgU6wWAQyTyyYMvAC60fzdY3hMBK/03ts9tPgIW1VeI0/MzOzR3urrK2EGEZ3PwQqPMpQe1PQWVA2nS3KKf4nmq4UeBc4VeiiAUAamQJGkDCITnBKpAwNT7ekTlQ0aqhXJRsfzCOgA6ETHBrPhy4fnFOPgjXkLOhOcU4mdHCbil7tmp5qhr/hh4+VD9CiOrwP159DLqRUSdrCF15cv/L2++mnAiwwCHlyPPHHTKLDuVzzEYjgrYPOzVkL2qsaMF44IHm+h5PQ+z8tKKBWfHVYrj9ZpMXGIhW6y4FX0kMoVFqs+07wAWI5phRhZ5bladicL4O1/F9MHzLCF7xRjexs1CPqJoSRcBI6HiMnlAuVd8HPhzyMKezswbkMF1ixw5zKQYNh9QrZFTii7efz6L2RoOs6C2QG", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Geysers ,Eruption of hot water and steam", 
		"option_b": "Earthquakes , Vibration within Earth's crust", 
		"option_c": "Tsunamis , Gigantic tidal waves", 
		"option_d": "Hot Springs , Hot water rising without explosion", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030150", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "24awYZT/1Vn8+IkjUxD9iNvwJ2bVByITuj+XWqY0dWP2RLPLYeO+xpExK12bil475HnKtqj15BMAiehd5ZuWdGIPf51uhJCq3urzwWMBMMlKn80ywpUNcfFEjD+0NMDTJb5r3HuQM0z/aXmyAjBkjSPZiXBXu5ey9me2Vc4y0hwzmss4zscxLNiM0LyWqFu3igWD0nTcbrJ2HFGd9cyxq1eUpcI9p9idpTvU+rT2nLjR/8oDIgRTqYc/YlW417gQ6iU7XcmnfBtIsenRdVH/KSmva04++Mfn02Zoi4AmSmV55xdHkoZSIsR2xorhryE5MMN5VSeyolAAwZtuUleBfLi2kHzs5RUsYHcmbJ4tsyt1oE+KJ1h9m2WTDC9emIxq7sMchkbqQlzRnTcvgrRB+9d9xKrv", 
		"explanation": "24awYZT/1Vn8+IkjUxD9hbC/E2TCDmcV432aErd8dTHmRrLSeuTxx9d+IRyFjEl89zbQrKnl+lYcz6ddqYiTZSsHPodu3tHTl9f/zXRNN4ZSlYxx5ZQQeecAxDy7cZTaYOlnymvMZ0L1aS2xHTBnmD7Gg3JR6JOp+iGyWN93xAA31pN3rdw0OZeNzKad8Q22hxKXzn7RR7skBVycvNzo50KKocIMvciU8TPJ8bT6kvnB8d0fZxpbpYN7I1ml164b/TstVMagJFJF/uqdZEz9LCewLhgYuc7xw2R9z40nTlU6yBFli41SZ9Iz1ZfquXJ9f+tlBz6/pwRC3tRoVxLWca+twHzt71t/enxrdZN/sy45oByIIVc+l2qIST5YlYwxvvMQmwBmby9Dk3jlkX+KkmDPb4fm7pCxluH0pb0j/6wyJ0WTdVPKFoUVab/TZ2F92OSeCeZaIZBqVyfsONY6+T25NpmY3DgD2dpgKWXm8yecnNnmeS25upz9i8ZlWP8BJdmJqcq5tBzFbi7jMjTTcsP1TUjxTH/t3htptgwgiCAC53fWDMlr/ShNiHu+XQRghzXpYnvhm7FY75CPa4s9yrXpxSIcl+dxiZ630Q8pVxCygnFQjoqjQX9AwETZDcQTwUk4A7gCFZjesiDWs3nCRnkJP8zvQbyPxmxNyPbhmmhysdABU8yMIw3TytIn3hbxAPN9FXf0uon6Mf0GHm0vur9w3uizvsu3L7OFIHYlLxG5VvhXs5RCKBFvAwrJCjJAbLuvWJIbUqwPxn3PhAIIRm1MRU7N96REHRe+r8HYI3nXZ7QYTgjtb7AEHcH9XQfMJ/So3DXNRr2F1UayS0E3QDuJKL4KpQvxY4ngN1O8lSh39s3sNlhdTYYTfCvyYmr5o6+MHBV6fiIhaJpeaEjWRxE3gDfAZ/1inagTeQw+AZyvHElWlRBB3zbTGF0FskMKV+WoWEMrJbpMNl5RzDmxUaUZWgnZjywPzlOO1zL4IPVFInUtR2qwjkDknoBn37KpoIGWBpnxJbwL14lDLLNLVp/FDBmX3C3vOmgqCPd4RDgeHyod", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Shield volcano,Formed by the eruption of large volumes of fluid lava", 
		"option_b": "Cinder cone, Formed by the eruption of pyroclastic material", 
		"option_c": "Composite volcano,Formed by the eruption of both lava and pyroclastic material", 
		"option_d": "Caldera-bowl,shaped depressions that form when the summit of a volcano collapses", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030151", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "25S7fJjl1Fn8+IkjUxD9iNjtIHvEECIXsXqSR6Z6ZH36FKjQLuX/2td0NUmZmV5/sn/I47f19FYBm+hP4IOaY25DWoR9xdGHw6Thy31CMshL16hz99oRc+AAyS+4ZMDeJL5nwC6SIkb1aS39EHl5kSKWiGlC6I667Ge+Rs8n1FUzkYZx44g1MpeL0a3T7liskxSHkDu0UKltH1eN9din50Cdro11ncye8TzU4LT8iO3D5NsPIgFc/452cE+zhaEKuD4xXM2nKBNF9aTZchTjLzzjIhYN/Mj303Ap0o1pWHsh5AsGg4RXa84/lrTlqjNwL8FrATa7tglsxoZ7WleXZri5kGfioFk+e35rcYJsqG09oBzcKlF7lCufQzpUhoVvvtIA1Qhia24AmnrvlSzJ4TTZns8CCTK/Akodm8TAvQ==", 
		"explanation": "25S7fJjl1Fn8+IkjUxD9hbC/EHnFE3YC43mRV7JhdX/3WL6CYf++wZZiZ1mbmEtv93KGqquw5VYMiqZPqZqWfScQJMtOy8SAweG30n5NMMdKlYVhpJsNebRD2S+/cdrPLOcuy3yVN1H5aT79C2I0nDDAjzxTupar4SK/FNM5gAE6k8dq6Ms5MsPfyamA/A2MjgObnHOQXrgkBVyc9d6n/0aStIs5uY2ZvnLe5uHpjrjS998CbEhbscZra178kb0d7Tg9bcaIZjZE4+nRb0CtNievJA8T9ouullxo1cInUn108Q1TkpdTZoB62Nj2uTE1MdkqATq3plcAxYFoHxqXbf29wn309BU+cnsia8pksm0hqQrcLkFqj3mZFmx1m5Jm/94N1RJscWxBknnlkX+KkmDPf4bx+YXykeTp4LBt86AzIFeFdV7NQs0UZKXFZ2Jg3/mPCKIcOpEnAyrjfcUv7y25IZiQnzoCxdUkb2fo4C+XhsT0NWmj85frm8RiVL4HN9jLqcK58EjPZGPnNGmGdM7IVzT+amTs2gBmo1gzxy0T6WzXSMQ/3Swe3nC/XQRhgDLweHml1rdSqoqHbJo+wfzvnSYZlfFr35r50F01VES1gmsDt5yPSl9byFCWCsJHwRs7HKBBFZHQ+2PM1VPIX3UDfNq2F6eLwC1G1ebizml8qZVOW4OabBzJn84yzRPxCPM5R2Lup5T9OPhVAm0/7r1j062guc77dOGhbGsle1q2V/tQ8JxBaRZ+FUvJCmRKcq2+Qt0XT6Bb2nCKkRJcUm1MRV7Z/ugcUkStr8vEYW3XYLAQTgznYqAKHd3EQHvBGfC/yXDZCr6IkEarHwllYjuPJrVN5BX1e8z9IlO/kmZgudXtM0UbTIIEfCX2cWX5pqyVDhQ/e2wnMcpLe1HUCxYomynQfblLjLEBMAghQLyiGEUF1hBdmn7ED0tR/AwYU6S5AFY/OqhLM14CjTizUaweUhiKgDUYg1OYgiD1ae5DNAkieGeGglnsmoZvkPGpjYjBGcHhLrgIwYQVLfZXRYzXX10QleT3r9XoFHV5CWtjK/aITOfCpUPiQs7mrc6awFpN3K0BIFp7ICuemYvQ/zR+b6pJL3xFqj4PpdnRbRWjzZEZ2VF+URcs023nKhc1ZVsZpPqDp4e6", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Active volcano,Erupts frequently or has erupted in recent times", 
		"option_b": "Dormant volcano,Has not erupted in recent times but may erupt again in the future", 
		"option_c": "Extinct volcano,Has not erupted in historic times and is not expected to erupt again", 
		"option_d": "Lava plateau,Large area of land that has been covered by lava flows", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030152", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/PXbTWI8SkidcxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGIvd5h7hfmgjdj5hFAPc+pFjIEy8I8debgAjH3tNJSbYL4uji7AZxS+Jw2oCn5xmHHCgn1C6IqotSG0RtcyxFUlnoJ2rcQ9Ktbf36Sc/174hAOM2XqFQP1wGVHZptu67UKfpcI3s42ZuTeb8+b2j/bXzNBLQEYSj59tbFiwlrsd8Sl4V8S7f14LsaSQMxqtBimwM0MQ9t3q2HMpxZc7T2w64AwGjYUWas9nlpn3tH5wOMx5WXO7rUAA1Zt/VFeCfLyskGn25RUvZ3UvcIlouG03uE+KJ1h9m2WVT2xUhpV76tkWmxdfcy9j0jbDgzOPhXeOMNOjq8C8xaiw4PkjsuNnaQHAZhKYeowOYraMZ2V93eXWHq5dI5pjVybjLccr7yrwL5iHny0F0c1gKXj1+WqOmsj7eXGyttLqm9l7HatAOdeF6Iuhv1DEYC3uYX6casf1SRv1XED2kyor9yssxC1cqCKYSMk/tW1N3j7wCQQk0megLDzh1v4IpMKncZojxublyzdQlPV2m534xhB8Uwy6mT9KocSZQE5CyFCWCcUCykkjDbMMFdbY4S2fm3zVSGgIe47+DrqO2SNGzuL9gng9tp4aWsyaJBybr9803B/2Er16R3L+vLr3AfI9BXNs97N/062usYqvffbkLWcleR/3Se5Q4YYRaRB+UQLTBitdcr2tQsJcbcHqqtSeQcQVNhhj1awprw==", 
		"answer": "25u3ZpSz3h+q440lEh/wyuv6d9zw1yvjvQfBR2mrD6vVc9Y=", 
		"explanation": "25T4RJDl0Fn+4oclElOy5L3rIGXeBm5RpXCRX6ZwMGbrUamCaOHx3p5/IByFjE16snTDraDx41tPm6BeqZ2KYiQCfY4vy9+G2/e3xX9Fc9VLlol27ZwWeecMjDGodcLSLvkuzy6IKEn8aC79B396kCTfnjxioIaitSS6Wpoj0hQ8hZd3/9x8MNaJ2Oic/kiqxgqN0nzRTLR3BVWXtsu7q0KSpMI5p8jNsj3W+fv32vHdsNwKcQleq498I16ugrgd8SU2QvS6VBxpsdTJc1vuLCmwMwceuc3v2WMpi8IaSmAy4FMGkYBZcMN735bj/D85J9l/Bzap40tGh5VvV1vWZrK723uooFQxcTosZJktuTUlpAOQLVA+nn6ORSJW1JZk8tMYmw1gPWpSiWb0izCFkyW7dJb6q43zk+2woa0j+qogIQGTJVndUp5QJbbOIHJ+zOCVCuZZJZp1DjbuNNspvDD3YIKc2jAfkMkhO3+rtCuXlo30K2D6u5v+hthvVLsFJcXX/MijuUrCXS3dL17TRcr4XQ3iTjy1kyNkpAss3iRcqGDXH4Uy5iUMjnu0CUBhgjXlf2+ombBPqoSBbYM017X71Tce2PU4iZT71xwySEOozWxWv4mWWxxMwljaH90UwRpuCrsNGJnG+2OR1XeQRn0HcNy2BLqS0zhB1e2xuml4ptANVILOLhybmdswzQWwDb1yXGvipYPtOO4GSnMl/rcxy+Ol98upcLOrKnEvYVq2SvxW8JxQfAd/URzUESwPbLm8UZhTUuNO3nCKgQhERH5HDFmM/r4NUxC5lsr0YE6eULgQAl6vI5JFG8HqR13AO+WoxHDaDrqZgQqyVk8gDjOTNaIY9g7/dMz9IlO+km9p+IHxOlBPBJAYMC73fW2woLDDCQMuaCkgJspLe17QWQNkmziDIuFunrMJfh9tU6ekEhAlnx1DjH7THF0FtkMMUqCpAEYpLqxXJ0ke2DmxUaERWFzJhzRKjFPc0SfpJ7pcOUwtO2uFil7sgptomL/7jY2KStHwIrkewcFDLa5LS4nfEVxcjvvh4qO2xwmtoVY/E+wmnKOj22AG", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030153", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/PXbTWI8SkidcxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6TbzWJVfu9twLx8pLtRPNZB3zSuNNjaNv8iji7AZwWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tXb1eNMwyAF/lYh04t0uOdPf2KaXqEG3kUaL0juCQbFtElWlu46KpQO9o4s89cGMpzOXtLS52riTsJ5LIkgS/8Y/Ixv81+hJuGpqH4icYRVD/f2QZ1j4KSzjJgAZuc/ixH8pxY0lUnwm8Rt6jMN1LIBWzoz2qSE5KcgqGTK0p0JP1ZlvE1fWNP34kDuqoHk+e34taphgr20zrh2RLVA+mHLcWCRU1IV568ANnAttPWBG3HrhlD7LgWuLPJz344Xuxf7/rLpi/KokaUyBIVnKX4wQdo/OZ0M8isCVGbRJIJZxEmLqPNsq+jbrLYXYn3lNkJlgezmn2CuXlsv6K2ip85T2nNlzEP8CL5HR4c73uVLTczbyKHKdJsTyGQXxSHH5kwdroxdl3CkVqEfZGp13sj5NnWylWlBYnGfcYlSugf5R64yXP4E3k+Hk2HIRmvtumtvn1RQuVES6n3oDu4qcQE5dyFfCQY9QyYiLkqSIXGJOOoLJmAbv", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz3hfvtQQBK6FoVpzvW6f7i+bSuw8=", 
		"explanation": "25T4SpDg2Bqq+4Q2U16/hdHwIivZDSICqnOKUaI4MHnqU6+CZ+O+wIV+KRyIg187/3fBraDj/kYCz4FPrp3fdCMRdcZsx9yGxeHziDFJOsFMlpky4pYKdfAMjDyjcJTdL+xj3S6TL0z1az39En94lzDYhXlF6KC0+Cq0WtYugBQhhYh75MkoOdPfzqGH4A22iQjP2WOBRLJ3GEKc9cu6/lOIqY02poHNuCab9/vvn+rAsNIKcA9X/4dtZlqvq6Y19gh4cMu9bFJH8PLRIRmtCCGkL04O8Mfq1XUpxY0nSWw64F9Lg4hTcYB6wtjytSEzMNh5VTK0pwRMzpN0S1qVe7G3wm3goHwrNXwkd4d+/D4hsw6IJ0JxlmidQiNUh8Bq8NRZmgJ3eGEAkHPhhizLlGrPeYvz54/vjP714Lxx57MzIE6OJhzcQ4hccbyAM3Vz2vmeCeZbMoxiBB7oAdsNvBzhNISBzDAb1ZksLnnj8iWLn961dCWctpPtm8ZzB/8DJNTE/c6z8F7eITfpJD2WdN7kTQH/QTz31U5zuBQmyS8Z6yLVCZ165yQMkm3wRU1vl2fsbWqg1r9S7sKPbIZx3Pv40nIEkPE4uprlwBV7VESomG1Fs4eaD3lXzFnGEsgUhAAgD7gUEJOR5GKalnfeRHkeM476AL6GgzxE2/f0j3Ru89APW4jOPADJhd0qyQSlCP45U2viv5XFM8AbLiQF9KZj3/6ooc/7efKqKGMlfRekGaIZ1ZBQfBdpFBidAytdbb2qFp8HAfRH1zXPmhdERnxMCF/C7+gHW0Snq8PFbyrXbaUTTgrqZvMgEtzsRgDcdfK73SPdRpaSlkurW0E2DjySM70M8Q7/dJ+yKBq4lihg8MrgIR0bV4obMDS/NGq3oeOBChIycCAsPIJUOnPdTglklzHMK7lmg6NAYxchSKyuH0lWgx9LmizVHFdQvkheXaCrT0EiarpQMl0Qzj67FuLP3cfePYQHn2/fK4ztBLIF", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030154", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/PXbTWI8SkidcxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJCl3vfjiVhoafpK2qE8pKkWcPgMjH3tNJSbYL4uji7AZwWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwH5sOS+zOpQck+1hBymoZ26c4zLtrfzaCS/A2xlUaE02mcTbkkBlycu46l6kSRocIxpo2Evzje9+D8nrjb/8wCeAdcq4dzb0L8nqYd92osWc30TRNZ5eyXchTuMj2wMzITuemtllBwzYdlHSl0tF8GwsMWIoAzltik/HJwf40qVXPo7QRpyYBuSgSfYrj43Gnq5FMwZ3drcYJsqG08sk+aJ0Zzn2/cWyRUmsBm/9cUlERqbi9JknzlgSuOhCWZeYH34oP9ieTp4LBt5qxnPUmFdXnZRJkUIqCAJHVn2f2nA+Z/fd9FFjbuMtkn6DG1YNbUn3lNkJlgbzentGrZ0o2mdyWWsoD+i5g2HbEUJMTW4N2y8FDGbyfnLm+eJt/8WBywRm+41QF3uh0hiDYY7WyYBYh4+CxNnXG/RVckkynkLG+umrdY44SHep1xxPz41Tse2OBwmtvS1Q8oT0OozXxRp5eLc1IP6RqWMswExwYiBaAJWNaRsi3W1TaQCzxNP462QejTjWxh1Pfjm3J0qZVOWY2AKB/UmNNm3B+wFb1wRifrp5T0OPhVHWwp9PJ8y+qstoqyZrOtIm8vbA6yXa9Q/YFeKBZzFEv4BDZbaP+9Fp4MVPNbknTEk0dJVXxBAEmM7rhISQyv6svea3jSergSCV7xd6EEB8/EQHvBHf6+iD3ICKbcmkH+S0wgDjufLqYIpRfxc57hZBKhlihn9tP3N1JPG8GOMZgMm5Wtfngxoq4gtODc", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "25T4W5j/3UOq1sUzWxL+hfTsdWqQEGoUpmvOXqp/dTHqWrPQe/73xpkxM1SImRty4TbPra/19EcKi+hT5pyWai0NaopjxMnJ3urjyzFVO8MEv4Fg8JJYb7RD3ii+YJToKfJi3S6BNUCwcyCtDXN1mD3PynpZuo6+8WesXN85gBgzkYp5rcEvfN6R062Q/Ei8xgSHyGyUTbMkHVWAsNy7q0ya4JE9scSAtDzP9ebg2urc89U3bDRcncZbelC5zegouC4hWs30YQEL8KTGZEb5KSuiK04U99/xw2dgyYxpSWE14F9Fl5dFItR7xJfxuzpwK8VvVRa7sVBIgIc8XAWDZ6n49HHv5UZ/dGguJZ50rCQ2oAOQMRR4lXmRSSgRg4hu8JAUlANufC9JjzbpjDWOg3GKeNPq5ZTzxeviobpo4eMoOwGGJ13bQpgOYKCALmky3uGeTaVOJoxzKyzaM/Zu3jjtKJmY1i0FipkBb3Xm4CKWnsThMSWzoNL4zth3BrgFepHM59+lpU/OdyahLXydYs37SwWwW3T5x05spFgjxzMd7WaYH4F6+20An3m9SARnnSjsfzygmLoc+Y2Cdoo41fzpznIHkeBwlpW3wBU5ByG6n2tL9ZffTE5a3kCWPMwTzAYiBaAJB9bQ4GjWgW/AQn8Mc8LvQa6I0SFN3qP+mGRv/50HWYCHIxfIytEgiA60AO9qFWbjrMb6PPJVCGFs8qd/zv+ks9n7evXkJ2wmYBeyTepL4NVYZkJoGBHYOSpzbpzuepwdQu9D22HCzUdpB3NIBlnD96EcVUSjuYTJLm7RbrRRHRbjc7YBU8f2WlXaJvimxnDdDr6I1U6tH0IqXDeYJfAa7QL+OoHzIx6y02F3ucjrOFRYUIYTfC79YGT5sauGSyM7bTgtb5kHeVXAWARklTDHZ/h1jq8FY1g4UeizEVVWmQdKjTLLB1ZC8F8KTaS5QRMLK6pGL1cY2T+mUaENWVzenyoDjVeQzjusOvdKPUUmaSSHh03u25Bni/fmjoeVAseiLLMfko4CJvZZQdrXX10ZjbPv5u3vHGktA39kbvHGHvHYqkq0nmemwAa0vhl/jmdUPgd+Lw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030155", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/CGuf0YeH9yJl4JByZgU58vjaG4+WwtxNewYkb+pqadTJObYJrzdTJ3+37yDFOIYZHlY53pI4XfeAAxS7tctvJLftqjnmIIkuwazirBTBnmz3fjnVQoYaotS61FNt31ho+lYZ25Mt8KtKRzZSdygP4sAmO33qfQb4kH1GavoLoqwPc4MJq+42s8SDe+fr4lOyT/9hLY0hEsIp8YlW1lOgf/SQsEdy8aQYL+eXDIVboJSbjIhwS/c7nlnV+x5sVU0p6tClJjoBXbMlwlpzrsTd8f40qVWD042UAw5txWlqFfLyo1Wyk6FwzeTo/bYt5/CQm4QmTOll7niuLRClf1Ixq6NFZkwhsanwAj3rvlTOSwGSBeNPg5I/wltT+hPcjxKwrKkCOPF+YVZ8dcbbSaycyiqnPQ+Z9c51oAC6rLt0v7Dz9YJKRzysIw8opIHmn4CKYho38KiW8vID0i9A2FatAItnAqd+4oBzIZ2PgYWucasj1VwfMQUD2+wFy9xUkxjhQ52SYHIF6tSwPkWi1CVRlmzXzLH2zk/5f5ZCceo0ljLdjWoQA+i5XyCMd0Z7rH1Fl", 
		"answer": "25S0ZNHn2Ryq54QpQA2wD+w8USY7BXzWyZOR+YpLiA==", 
		"explanation": "24O3ZJLy3xDpt5UsRxmohdy/I2TcAGMfqnzDQq9hdzHqR+fDLv/7xJlwKUjJgl078zbQrKnz9l0GjOhN7ICLMDYLf58vwNGal+bywX8BNtRLnoV2pJsIfe0A5SntfcebNOd+x22BK0npJz+yFn1xkHHBgnlY6I+64yb7R9U7yRE7kI59/og1Mpeemb6c5E65iA+BnG2URqkkEFqd9d667lWZrpYr9cuYoybT8ea5n+rG4MoCbQZusbpxVVSwlKkH8Sl4X823Y0gL0KTGbljuISaqJE4T/Mjoln16hoNpXnA4/RFCkIpVY8wz1JfgpXI/OY14GjCx41BIxoA8VgTWcrKq3W3goEI3cHRrZMp7syE2oAGTaFFslW+ZX2xQg4FyvvkN1Q1wPXtZjH/jgzOHmSWbdJaj+YXxhOH+s/ls9OMzIUTAI1PUVYwSbLCAJGh8zvySGeocJJduFCqmNMZu6DH8YIaVzCoM19xgO3/1+z+emo3iMWy5u9L0j9N7Ff8SP8LA+oujvxzTaSahMmiBYMr3XDT+c3LO3AJmthYsy2EU52/dUsletTsCkn2xR01n0iPvYXnhn60c68KKcIM0nubk3CIVnLRwlpf7lAk0RhD7hGwDtIuNQllLjUPeG8NHyAg4DfQHGJnG4S2FmXnHR2VNfsDyQauIzCBbmsrlzmhu/4QXRYWNLRXXk54gxwW8BPk5Qm/opsb1POoUSm0/uqZ+xa23vtm4eua3bHElLxy7VvgZ9YdUbQ5iUQrTAWRGbqu6U5waAfBG3nDZ1xJYB3BHRU7E/ugbSBasq8fNUmTibYcTAh3jbboGU83qT1PKJ6vp6XDfCbOflEm3XAQmXDuJJKJN7BSwe8zwKwS/3nts+NHgNhFfQZMFOTTgfWS35beLChJ6dj9lLoVVd0LRCxEw1CrLIrlzgrdAfx5tQOixFlwVlx9A3xfGTlFW8FgHT6yuQV8rM+lDL0kcyDP1BqgaUlzejj9KmlmMgi3qafsLJ0YveGWdgAzjlJ5qnu/6h53BC9L2KK9b04NDLaROVI7fEFVeTQvNzyptgClrD2/qZCDGgg==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "All the pairs", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030156", 
		"question": "24O3ZJLy3xDpt4AyRw7mzPLxJivUDCIfrGvDXaB3ZWOjXamCNK3Fm8chdmHLCMoK6Qc6eXAhKW+28nCvFA==", 
		"answer": "25e5ZIX60lnZ8oRif5FABXHmmSihQ69SIXnjXQ==", 
		"explanation": "24O3ZJLy3xDpt4AyRw7mzPLxJivUDCIfrGvDXaB3ZWOjXamCeuX7ibVwK0iAjhtI93eGl631t3EOg7xS6s6sdSNDd5gvyZCE1vbwzX9AP4ZXn4Ey65xfaPxFjBy5eNXVNPdtjkGDIkT+Jy21BWQ0nSKWhnNVqZe+8We5Uc4gxRA81rR77MY4Ndmez6GSpA2dhxWW2WmfCJhxA1uJsILo6k2Y4Kw3p9mFtCDVtNHsiPfD9Z4idkhbrMZ+I0m5m6kd8Tw9XdH0cR1e/+OQclHsbGiiKQpd8N+j32cpyI09HWU79x5Sh4cWa84z15akvSA1Po19HTaopgRUwpdoUBmfd/2o3Gnw5UZ/dGguJYdiqiQ7pk+dOFVsjiuTXmxSm4xn99QQmwMjSWdJjzbthz6FkyWbdJL3q5T0gPr14LBwsq0oaUyBMlHZFp8VdrrOICd02OaWTbJUNt9CFjDyNZI9vDT4LoKY2nkZ35klPWL34GqWnI3hMWD6oIfriNV1EYMOCt/z5se0sVLOYmPkM2iDcsL7VxuwR33u1k5qtBsw2jMV7CLRBslr/ShNvHKxSk8koSLhIDyCl6xV6ICLfoBx4PDtkXIRlvA4vJrkxBQ9SUSIiH4DhoyaD35DzFfdXv4CxUknH/QNG5XQ5miS1XfEC31NfMH4F62VxClGzqPzgXRzu5EcTMyZJBzJj54ywBLxJOhrVHTkqYi5PPIRSkUq6Ltyy+Php8a6Yfa3bGQ4alq6VvlQ/ZIRfA18FB/VADYPVLCrFr4fU+lN0HDLmUd7Qn4JDEmM96cLXBCvroTJeirfI7UVGBvwZLYLB476QVLBMfC70XDeDrqOkAeqV0FlbTuPKLIP4Ab+Opz+JQe202F3uczqJFhVQ8MWKybqNG2rqq7DHw4/PwIqOp5POmbYTgItlz/NZ+lrjLMFMCwlROiEGEMGnxBB3w3XDxhMowwSUKasVFYjaqhRYFpR2SW0H7MZUw7HxjgFm1iYwzD1ae1DNFsmO3CbigzFjoBnjPbojM6ABNCiDK8a0IQCJvZLSJvCGkhcm+Hhr/LsGGgwCGo3PvnbSqLUsUz+QsfgqsbIhzvXApppeyXy7DSDMUgMbfc=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Baltic Sea", 
		"option_b": "Black Sea", 
		"option_c": "Caribbean Sea", 
		"option_d": "Caspian Sea", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030157", 
		"question": "25y8bZ/n2B/zt5EoV17xyu/tMGjEQ20Dp3qREqxyMGXrUefSfOL9zIRiZ1OPzUh0+3qLprf/5FoAgehd+4GSTCwXdo4vzt+F2+vgzX9GaYZ/yNAitaddBiZfPKaGZrlpJimHTBB45g==", 
		"answer": "24aoZJDg2Vnv5YozWxH8ib3MPW7VFyIUsXCQW6x6PDHRXavOLujsxoR4KFLFzXxu/nrf46Di+EAGgKYZy8eYa1OJfZVy3okO7AJPLg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0EhHgwfjtdWTWQ3YZpj+TQKx3dWLwFKjELv7xwJsxIk6GnlJ0/DbPsP/M+W8BvLhX6J2XMCcRcZhmx97Tl9D/zWIBOtUEjoh3pIkSffhMyS65NNXVJL5jwX2UZ0z+dDC6CnlynTLXhGgWroyp+Ge0Upoy0hohn4h2reEofNic2r2B+w2vjgOMnGmQQbNgA1uJpo6g4lfctIo99d6CuD6b5+HrnPnQ9Z4KbAwSu49sb1S4kK1J6yc5XcT0eBNZ5e3TbVH+YCelZx0S8Mff2Edhw4c9HWwm+wxPjY0MIvR734ukszEzKt95VSSypkoA0JVoWgXWcrG3x3uk70M6Zzo/bY8tryI8rU+PPUZ4m2iZDC1fkMBo/8ILnAFwPW5XnW+gkTKKjGnPbJLx/4n/ie3j4LZlsrAoIE28O27RWoFcYKHPNG59xLPbOa5VIN9oFCHzL8Zu6zH8LtaH1zwIxJklPXj0/SWX0s/wOmq3toG5g9tkEf8DOd/G7MWjol3TZCehIHOXJsj8WAb+SnDrkw93slgjxzMd7WbkBq5q+SEU3nuiRldtnSm6LEipn60c5YGNapwik+Lk2DxQiv10k9vyxhIvTgu1zX1GsYuSSk8PyELTEI0KyxsrTLcOGpXU/HmElGLVTzwMccq2AqCGzSJN1vCxjGR+sJ0LFYiLKQnemJ4nxhPxFvR9UHWvVN0pIH6RPkc6pohCfV3UmA==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Splash erosion, Sheet erosion, Rill erosion, Gully erosion", 
		"option_b": "Sheet erosion, Splash erosion, Gully erosion, Rill erosion", 
		"option_c": "Rill erosion, Gully erosion, Sheet erosion, Splash erosion", 
		"option_d": "Gully erosion, Rill erosion, Sheet erosion, Splash\nerosion", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030158", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/2CVb+umM88dmG1gwo7xn7D44fx5UEKgehy+oKefiZDaIRjy9GH2KT+1zFAPYZFmZR78p9favtMzzyje5TXL/1v2muEG0v5aXmpDHU0vT/Sg31Y6Je+5zWyQNUl2Sk8xMda7NouOdnf8Luf6UO8xgqL2WjRSb9rBEDZ5Jr4q0iR4Ic5ptnNvjSb0+b8m+yT3tcIbQpTrbpxMBuIn61J9CsrRYigYR9OsfDYZBTPITqxIgBd0Njv13pthpQmUWo1+hAGh5FDctR20tjzvSEMMcRkVWLj+hUAxpp4Hx6CNLW5wyj25Vg+fHQuYcpksiw2tQaKLRRtk2WfSWxFnIVlwt4unQ1gdS9Pmjb0ijrLk3GOaJbu7o7olqj3qa9m/OMmK06WMBzRRcIdd7aAJGhg2OyYGfkelComB4udBs4nrrfls4ct+g==", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUuocWEOEhwNBe0zN4qxEabNUg==", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7Gzfi/F2rCEWcf41aQXqJ6dDH1W6vBb+PxiZ5iZ12HzVp45n/QpuXm+F8MjqZUqYKQcyMXe48vwd7Jw+zyhFhPN89FlMBm4YgNdeBP3iTtQNzSM75n3S6DKFfiYjqpRFJ1hiPThDx/u4+6+yP7Xcl3wRtyg4lx48A9Pt6L3KzT/kK0hQeM1XjRQa5oEFqd9cemq1eUpcIZu8mMvDPVtMf8m7ST8dwEdxwS7tUnI1C1m6cE/T49Q9v0IEodsenZbVH+aWimJh0JucTlllN7w4M9HUc99xBEg5EWS9N/15bg/Bskf8R5VSeypgRPyZhlHxSZeruxwmXh5BU+dm4ic48tqiI5og6SJxR3lCuIRCkRvY5v99EX1Rd2f2xPkmLpjDqFlCnPfZ3nq4noxeDxs/lm4LY3PUSEdVHXRIhccbvBKSchmqmPBKtZIN9uGWL0ONYh7j38JNac1ioZ38s5E3nb+hmNk9nwNGC0p9Kr1JRUFa0SM9+FwNi7sVLDIS/oJG7TZ8n7TBywHiiokwVo9x0k2zVQ52SYL5t69DlNsHezRkZlgGfUZHWy1rdPqoOCbIFx0Pr+zzcTjLRanonl0RN8bhe3jHFH8o2MD1BAzlXCG8lHzQduGLwEVLff9myblHiQeHkMM473A6eS12wZibuxhWhxsJ0LQYmcP1mT0ohmxR69BO4wFWLsu5K5MvpVLXYp+6Yx5OSiuMi6Z7ONP2krYR6LV9NXwIFQfAd2FAXJRXcVIIymU90SQPNbkmHDmgIIU3dMRXjN6boNU0SDucjJYG6edb4QDR/sbPMAAdvoWkLLdeao23DACP/NzB7vH0UrSnqUNfAF5BSwaIn/JRq9lmwk8M/kMUVSUoZXLy79d275sauGBUYOdyU2aINUOk7bSB82hjvAM7lThaJAfBk+VeizEF0T1jNOjSzXABhso0AfUaHtRUEyOr1AJBsGzCT1GK5fDkyY1Ho+hlOOx2L7KOkLMAkwdmWfgwzliYd2i/bmjM6OBJTILLMO058aaOQNCNqETwlO1rPl4eWgECw1B39wK+qIW/DEoFv/Dca0rc2a6F1ZyrZIZw93ZWvb282bdGP59eBJ0rMNyxkuOojgig==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Volcanism and Earthquakes  >> Landforms Associated with Volcanic Activities to Earthquakes", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "2 and 3", 
		"option_c": "3 only", 
		"option_d": "1 and 2", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040101", 
		"question": "25y2KIb72Brit5E5Qhuyyvu/NmfZDmMFpj+HXaZnMHLrUarLbezyiYB0JkiBiEly/HGGt7zg/lAOg6RCqZ6NfyEGe48vxd+aw6TlxWFIN8pdxcKu3Un/zDy4s7ishzDXu6RA", 
		"answer": "24K5epyz0Bfut5IlRl7xyfTyNH/VECCbZfrdnmm0KiC4Gd0gVdfI", 
		"explanation": "25awbZz60hjmt5IlUwr6wO/2O2yQF3sBqnyCXq9tMGHxW6THa+ntiZp+NEjJn1pr+3LKuuX5+RMYjrpWqY+RdGILa4ZmzJCK2+36xWVEIIZtlMBm7J8MebRDwzOpfcDSL/B9gi6ILkL4Jy24CWBxhjDCn25Tu8O6+yP7VdcnzBBym4hx/twpLtLf36mQ4UGxkgeW2TuSQLhpGFeYuY667kKftIs3u97NpTra4LT7iP3S+54PbR9c/4t2bV6ulqQauCM2Edq7axlYsdDYZBT9Mi2wIgAe/Ivs0DR+x5YsTyk1+BNJlZAWZM9hlpztryE/M9h+HDy07wRI3pBuXgOfe7P0kGnq5BUwYXIud8putCg4qAydJBRuiGSfST9CkZMr6t9ZmgdgaH0AkXnyh3+OhmOGf5rm5ZTwnKSwrLxi9qopLgGUOhzeV54IYKGAMGJz3uGeH69SNN91FjbjLpUP+D3wNJ+b0TgB3MBsb3j18yuXm861OGazt4G5iMZ5Gf8EM9LE8MK5txzRZCTkNXyHb8T6GQvxQTz+xhxxvx03iCAT62fUDZt+4ShNnXa1RE1nkyuge3mggrZZ+IuAeM443bXkyD8ZnLR9kY3+xhIySgG1mWwB/kKuOpYrJ6ZpSfEfrGlptw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Warm and wet climates", 
		"option_b": "Cold and dry climates", 
		"option_c": "Warm and dry climates", 
		"option_d": "Cold and wet climates", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040102", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7gzPD+J3KQAGMEsHrDXaU0ZHnmFLfKd/73ypZ9Z1iAnlJ15nPBsaTk/lwBz6ddqZyQcykQPoJhiN2M1Oz2ynhCMsoEjYVz8JIabv1Oy2LviuMO51DEYbWFi/yvnmQoyg==", 
		"answer": "24G9ZYH2wxj+4pclEh36xPP4MHiSr4ohTT5aqULOwyEEldmCUA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHjwxDn9pc5Eh3z0O76dWTWQ3YZpj+TWrpneXLiWOfGZ/73x4N0IE6ImVJ0/DbJpeXi+FAEnOhS586SdSELf4Vmy9GFl/PyxWVJNtRNlIcy7YlfaPxFjDi1ZNXVM/dhwC6BKUGwZDazEGJ1lyXfhXIWp4X75yi4X5oz1RBygog4+c0xLNKN2LyG+kj4hQ6D0nyUW/1TGVGX9dyn6EiP4IMqsI2IqSLU5/H92uzcsMoObxhXrYdrdkm5174I6iM5RcG7ZgEHsfDYZE2tJTCzJgAZudzr03opzocoSWwwtB5IhsNVbc5nxJnnqHInN8hkVTC1rEhFw9RTSRKENKmx3W2ooEE3fGlrZoVjqCQ7tACJOxR7gnudQj9Ym44r/94d1Qdsc3tSnXX0izCFwGaOctPv7oH4xfz/4K1r9+MlO0SBPlXWUc0ddbLSMyd9zKmJAqVXINMnByP0Kdwt6TX4MpqNnzADkMslKH7o+jnZhcThMSW784XwitE2Br4OMdSF5s33pFnKcSbzIGmGdM60XwTlTGjt0hpsuBY2iA4E4GfKSI9+9jkCjG3wQEoknyLjZH2vn71d5sKZeo8l2/D+1DwX2P12nJfi0Bh8QRa0nmsDs4eLRlNBjRzQDMgC3gxjGLwAA9bS626akGWZBzwZd8u2BrqI1DhAmuz3znFxvp4aFZ6BIw3Ixp4nxhPxAP9rVHTkp4i5O+4aByQ787x1iuKz9926Yfa2bvuwIYkNx38ha/q8klFlFuw=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Wetting and drying", 
		"option_b": "Temperature changes", 
		"option_c": "Biotic factors", 
		"option_d": "Pressure changes", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040103", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQn4+IYlQQ2yzPPpOmfGBnFRt3eGErFxcXL3XajMLuL4iZhpPluMgxty/DbHqrew+EFPmKlP7JzfZysXdstiwd6MxeX71zFIPYZQkoUy9pUcd7gAwDiscN3VJ756wS6UL0CwYTavCXFgnT7YynNQ6Iqp+in7W8I+xBBt1N8xu6O7AMmDSouMrCy7H8w=", 
		"answer": "25qgYZXyxRDl+cco6+yBVxlnbGvh2ReqfdO9", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHjwxbp8pYzEgr6xOm/PGXGDG4HpmzDRqtxMGPmVaTWZ+LwiZh3Z1ORlFx+/DbPreXx/kFPgLob/o+LdTBDaYJ7wJCE3ury1nBNIIZNlMBm7J9fbvtDx3HteNHaJPdgyS6UKAXkbzz9An9mmTDCg3NY6Iy9tS6pW9R3zw07koI0rcEvfNSe1aSW7A23ng+G3W+YR7MkJVyQpo6h+AOd4IEwsMCEsjPXtOP8m+zb9cwCbA8Sr5RwYF6vhOge8C8qVIi5YRxO4+XcchTuLya3JgcT8MXkln17yYxlHXoh9xcGg5AWa9J82NXmuTMiNsNtVSCzr01DxoB5TFvWda+9kG388FoscH5rcYUtszUspgqSZBRyn2qYRSJW1JRkvsQRkERgcmFWmWTzizCFwGqJPJrx5I68jOf+s/kr1KZ1YgjAIVOYX58Ta/PPP252z/rbRYBZYNQuW2LlMtgj8zf1Odaf0TYa3pkhPDf14TmN0vn9MHb6o4D2jdFlB/8DN9+F6MejtU6HdSvkYX6casTmGQn+Szz73AN1uAss3Cgf5iLXDslr/ShNn3i2TEdwlyOgfnOinfy35wZrEGV1OBPt84mpY6TX", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Solution", 
		"option_b": "Decomposition", 
		"option_c": "Exfoliation", 
		"option_d": "Oxidation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040104", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEgr31/C/M2TCQ3YZpj+TQKx3dWLwFLDKa//7iYV+JFeazVpp9zbUorX5818Wz6xJ4IubMCAaPph6xpCI2eC303hPN4ZGn5Rl4Z8RPOBJyDi+NNXPYOpmyy6DKETjc3X9CHV1kDjYjTxCp8Os8CavXN8lyRs1ycXvylGX+IFeW26UH90tBPkR", 
		"answer": "24a5ZIWzxhzr440lQBf8wr9xA0qsYEliv3T5NI9DeLs2", 
		"explanation": "24a5ZIWzxhzr440lQBf8wrG/NGfDDCIarXCUXON1YzHwVavWLu7s0IRlJlDJikl05WLO7+X55BMOz6tU6J2LcS5DaY5u3NiMxe35wzFRIclHn5NhpKkafeNB2Di/NN3VJvdi2nyBM0DjJymyFn9hh3HEhX9du9j74i++Wpo+1FU3gIZo4to9KNKMleiA6UGsxgWQxWiFSbF3UVKWp8Pkq0aEpZAsvMOK8SLJ8efqj+rWsOoDaxsSvJ98b178ha0Z/SssQoT0axNe4u3eZhT/LyuoZwoU6sLtwnFu1IM9VGY6tC1HkopSIsRhz5Hqu3IyJo15AD36okpEh4N1URPWdrisx23h7hUrfH4udspsvy4wrQqOKUB7iSuIRCVC1JB58dMchhcvPWNFnXLpjDjLlGrPf5zi+JT9iajir7posqY1JlKJOlKaf3CWIE141sSNCmD7uIkf2A==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Frost action", 
		"option_b": "Salt weathering", 
		"option_c": "Temperature changes", 
		"option_d": "Oxidation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040105", 
		"question": "2523f9H33hz5t4YoVxP7xvzzdXzVAnYZpm2KXKQ0dX/rVanBa633x9dlL1nJnUl+4XPIoKCw+FVPnKdS5c6cfzQGbNQtO/lu1eIwp0SIqdlc09RXww==", 
		"answer": "24a3YZ2z0Bv5+JciQV7gxPTxdXzRF2cD4X3eDggeNEQTbAbUGp+3w+k=", 
		"explanation": "24a3YZ2z0hb88pdgQgz90/T7MHiQAiIDpmyGQLV7eWOjW6GCeezqzIUxJlKNzVRj63HDrf+wxFwGg+hY5oCLcSsNbct4ycSMxaT2ynUBPN5dnYV8qNoIdP1DxH2sZtGbIvF6xi6OIkb1dCq8Fmk0kj7Eyn9erY6y9ia3FM0ywQE6k5Vx4898C9aL3LrT7ESrlQmOyn6CCK9rEl+K9c+m7wORqYw9p8yBon6b9fr92vfL6dkObEhauopvcBuomOgG4CM8WNKxKAZD9Onsb2fiKSTjJAEL/NmjxmZm0IstWHp09V9Vl5FQY8N2lp7rrnIzN8hnHDC7rwRSwpV/Sx6Zeq74xGek71Y8YGhxJb5luW0mtB2aKVd72mSaDD9enYwr98NZkBxzcnxFmDb0jX+fiGDPfYfu5JPsje3ipfUj5asuKknANlPWQowVa6CAJGZgyOaVTaJVPIduEyemPNsqvDbtKJOGnz4Mw9wzb2Pv9T7Zkcz7eXe/spHtzsN/ALdAJN7G4tj3sVLDIS7oL3iBZ8fnZQbDQHX0kw1qoR03iDEC53TRDIxstSxNlnG9TARinTWgYXWihLFT+IWPcYci3ua2nR8Zm+Z3kInw1RM1VAmowT9Qp4eXD11cjVbXHdkC1gAvTLUPENbX52ORnDqQSH0DP8/6EqfHyylEyqPlgSF/rZUPXsyKIw7VyswpyxyiQfx3USfgoYj8L/0ZGVgiyb14xq2iuNy+Z7O0Pmo+ahmjSq9L/JZae0J9AwTQRTRHeaunVZwSAfdK02HCkhVBSXgTRWrE4rsBXgWm6tPNb37WZqMVABmuI6AQEMa4T1SPM+Om2ySJEbqdgU+7TU0rSXqcL7RN5AXie5/7Kx3/02tl94HnIFRaT8MTMzD9NHm2pqiQSzU1diBlK4VRf1WVWwIrgDvAM+onn6gDewttR7qoFBACnhRcmn7CHFdGtV8NWrbtQkpnKbxWKFIewz67FuALVBnHxjwYgVvc1irpafNGIUggbySciQzymptom+3mkp3BC9rmbbIP2ogRaLlZTp/VC0heBwg0TPnMSL2p+DPC1dK4bg==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Soil absorbs rain water", 
		"option_b": "Soil prevents rain,water from reaching rocks", 
		"option_c": "Soil reduces organic acids", 
		"option_d": "Soil has no effect on weathering", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040106", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRqmzDRqtxMGLvW7DHffm+3Y5hIhyGixt282XV46j/4VYCiqZPtsxto/jPxnvbWtWPNUzwzhkz", 
		"answer": "24a3YZ2z0gvv8pVi0pHbzIcgYZ4nzTIPMU2h9A==", 
		"explanation": "24a3YZ2z0gvv8pVgWw2yxL3sOWTHTyIWsX6HR6J4MHzsQqLPa+PqiZh3Z0+GhFc783jC47f/9FhPi6dM586eMDEPcZtqiNSc0qTjyzFGIcdSk5Rro4lfevtSzzjtXcCbL/1t23yTZ0TkJzj9FHF3kXHZjDxboY+3/Cq+QN8l01Ummcd76MYoNdqaza2B+w25iAiX3XedUfEkHlKNsMDo/k2Sr5YxtsiJ8RTa9+D2iOuT/NcAZ0hfsI9sd06ukugK9yQsVMagJFJf9OnAZEbsND2xIk4e8crt0XF6isIoU2104hpBh5dXdsl82NjtsjQ8KshkFjb6qlAA85x1TFeGfLi232Xh7loxNXkqa8phuSwx4RuTaEB2nyuYRT9BmIFo+90cmxAjcmkAk3TqhzyfkyWOcpej+JTukOvktati/uM0IUiGIU+YWZsZd/PULmp3it2eH7RdMJpzAyf1cZU98Tj1LNaA2isf0dolPDfo+mqKnsLlPHb285Pri5R3VKkJJdjH5c73o1XAb2F1luuJhqth70vXjSF4TEVt", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Soil flow", 
		"option_b": "Landslide", 
		"option_c": "Soil creep", 
		"option_d": "Mudslide", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040107", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRqmzDRqtxMHzsR7OCaujt3YVkJEiAm1475m/WpuX/8RMCjrtIqYOQZicOe4V7l5L61rx8aGesp5LsVtIlx/Ed", 
		"answer": "25m5ZpXg3RDu8scF0/lDhvMUFQnh3x8i6BxH", 
		"explanation": "25T4ZJD91Qrm/oElEhfhhfy/Jn7UB2cf436NVuNmcWHqUOfPYfv7xJJ/MxyGixt6snrHsaL1t1ICgL1V/c6QdmIGf5l7wJCE1vDy1nhAP4ZAlZd8pJtfb/hP3DjtXcCbI/9gjmeOMUr8cTz9F399mH2WmHNVo8/79Cm/FN4ywgc7hcs47MY4fN6MmbyK+ES7hwqOxTuFWrRjFlGLsMro6VrctoMqvMKYonLd9fftlerAvJ4CbAteqoJ2bVz8n60I7jN4Q8m9ZhRK/eicIVHsMjyrNhsc8s7wmjR/yY4qXGc9919DkJZGdsl82Iuo/D0if8V/GDK040VD051qVgOfca743GHv5RU6bXkqc4t5tSI74QCOaFdxlHiIXjlSgIlk8JA1lApnbmNJmHPzwjyKjiWHfYXmq4T5k+njtLh3+60gaUSGM1nbQp5car2AJGh/x/yVBLJVNowrVyHnKMYn8j65MISbzzwfxMBgK3bq9S2c3o35Nnap853/zth/ErpMdtDL7YuzuU/VdDP1KHOUJsX1TR3iTnC43w9rswsmyTEV+yLsAIxmtSwfmz6zRUV3gS7mZXml1rdS/o3Oe4c31fD+2DwE2OBhj57kmF0vUgezzX5Q8paQTFdJzFjaDYFH1gYtB6cNHZLU4SHWlHjUC3gIfdz/EuiBzyNfya+ximRtup4KXIKJbBbVysouzVelGO18FWjr6Iv4KfkHA2Ugurt/3OKtoc+/NfKqKCU+Zx/3VOBP9phUZhY7AQrJESFdbvqSLBKCOZ17y0FjfDoT/bLg", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Landslide", 
		"option_b": "Soil flow", 
		"option_c": "Avalanche", 
		"option_d": "Mudslide", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040108", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt5EoV17m0vK/OGrZDSIXonyXXbFnMGXrVbOCbeLw3YV4JUmdiBtv/TbLorbjt14Ama1W7ICLL2DCgUTu/ff4iexYVZ0E16K6", 
		"answer": "24a0Z4H2kRjk88U3Uwr317/owS/Tz4ICV611WV5SngJS", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHnxhaq+oQpXF70xP7rOnnDQ3YZomvDUax6ZGPqVrLWa63qxtd8Jk+azVZ05HPLpqvkt1IdiuhI5YGPdWICcI8v39Gd0va3931OI8MEipJ98pMbeecA2DWoNNLUMv1rjmGGZ0LiZi+0EGk0gDnXnjxVqZao8DT7QNIygBg9gIJ16MYocJee16zT/0ysgxTC33qfCLBlGlHZocatq1CTqY54uMKftHLd+OHwnrjS/tpLZwlBtoNtI0+z16UG7i96LW+dmNu0KqSLgu7mU9nFuw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Vegetation and soil type", 
		"option_b": "Human activity", 
		"option_c": "Climate", 
		"option_d": "Slope and water", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040109", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt5YvXxuy0vzmJivEDCIcqmuKVaJgdTH3XKKCfOTtwtd+IRyEjEhosnvJtaD98l0bnPcZmtLfN8gRNLsheM9P4uAghQ==", 
		"answer": "24W0aZ/n2Bftt5EyVxvhhfzxMSvGBmUUt36XW6x6MjETIo8pgYd3h2FKZhGnSAE=", 
		"explanation": "25K9Z4X20hHk/oYhXl7BzOn6dUrDEGcCsHKGXLdIfkfmU6LWb/n3xpkxJlKNzXd6/HKGlrb1t2MDjqZV4ICYTCwxe59uwd6A2eO383BNP9UEm452pKkLffZJwDS3dcDSL/Au/XqSMkbkciu4F0x6sCPXg3JXr4b7xj6oQN860yk8pYt3/c18G8We3aGd7w25iALC6H6DWrxnGFqeicCa5ECX4KA3udmEvzWb9fr92tXW49YCbA9usaF+YVKzmbtJ+SQ8Efq9eABK4djeRFX/LDHjEA8P98Lt0TRa35E9WGQnyBFjkIxFa899lrvrsiYiMMEqODa7sFFSwodAUTuXern46mfq6Vs4NXslYcpfuSogrQ6IIVtwiVeSaSFUhodu8NMA1TZmbn9PkmXlwg+HgWuBdZ3k147MkOr8qboj07QmO0SOME/LFowSYfPlI3Jxy/2SAqhgPaxrGDLjfeY6/TvwLJ+O3i0E39dgG3Lk/CSQg9jwKlm0gZfvi9NzAL4UP97Lqcq5tBz1ZCXuM3iAcsrgUAf+c3Lb2w9ruR0piCAe7CLrHZt59C4I3lqiSE1qkyDlLF+umKpO5Y7MDoeT2E37URLKVR0GcPh2nA==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Relocating people", 
		"option_b": "Educating the public", 
		"option_c": "Banning construction", 
		"option_d": "Planting trees and vegetation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040110", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ3z54BgXRiyyPzsJivdDHQUrnqNRuN7c3L2RrSCZ+O+2pl+MBGKgk1+4HPC46j/4l0bjqFV+tHd1+196U0FVryCXc1gqdCIpQ==", 
		"answer": "25SuaZ3y3xri8sdieXAVLgX7sekFuhB9iZ4o", 
		"explanation": "25S2KJDl0BXr+YYoV1771r3+dXnRE2sV436NVuN7dmXmWufBb/n/2oNjKEyBhFg79HrJtOX/8RMcgadMpc6WcydPPophzJCN0ublzWIBN8lTlMBzpIkLefFQjDCiYdrPIfdgjn2MKFX1JxCpRHN1mnHUjzxCuoq88iKpUd53wgxygIZq5McpL5eZ2KuH51+rykaL0nidXbltH1PZvcup/Vrcs4w3osuMvT6XtOb4ivHXsMkKcAVbsYEzI169hbwB6T85Ws2nJFJE46TEaVGtISynLhoU9sXi2jR+w4suVX10+xkGg8NGZ9Jg2ZaksyBwOtx/HCO3pkpUh7VqXhuXer6w1Xuk41QxNWguZIll/CU8pgfcO0R7n2+PDC1fkMBj/8Yc1RBreC9Qk2LljCuCgWnPaJyj6IHplu2ws7Bk/KohIEKBO0iYUogPcaHVJHN7xefbGakcMZBzH2LoPME77jj1YJqV0T0e09gwKmSn9SSd0sXgNGS084H8msB6EbIFOMXWqf+/tUWHYDHkYXzTdc7mUAflXDzw0hRkpRxlwS9Q5W3NBp1+/CMCi23wW0FjmyjufzygmLoc65CLP4E3k+XtzyYZm+F0nom31xIyRAGpgz9FvZbfWFVB2VHEXt4Xyxs6H/QEGoLZ536flGXEWDBNft22Fq2Lz2xJyaPlhm5uutACXJqHIh6bhcxm3xijCvR3Uifkpsb4K/0ZC2ov8rc82v+uuc/7dOGhLXZon0zZymLfOrxy796oqcXt0A==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Soil creep", 
		"option_b": "Avalanche", 
		"option_c": "Landslide", 
		"option_d": "Mudslide", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040111", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ3z54BgXRiyyPzsJivdDHQUrnqNRuN9YzHgVbLRa+m+y44xM1SMzUh65mPUorH5+F1PgK4b+oGWfGIUd59niMeIw+HlmzNSs0R0sGLH/2Apl5rAHYwi", 
		"answer": "24a3YZ2z1xXl4Mc1cK6pthds9Zvsrx2IBy63", 
		"explanation": "24a3YZ2z1xXl4MlgUxLhyr30O2THDSIQsD+QXap4MH3qRbLHaOz93Z5+KRDJhEg78zbWq6D++F4KgadVqYeRMDULd4hniMOIw/HlxWVEN4ZLiMBi5YgLdfVMwCTtZ9XPNexv2muEZ1b/bjX9EHV5hD7Ei25fpJr7+SioUcl3yQEh1pRs/80yO8OXmamd7A26gw6Dyn6CCLFtGlHZtI6+4lCfr5cr9cuBpDvftOH3nv3BsM0fcA1BrMZLa1Kv17wQ6CM7UMS4cVJE8ufFc0etJD2xLgAaudjm32dkz4FpWH8x+gtVzsNFd8N7lpn3/DcxLdliBCa7qEFTi9RrVxKYNKmw1Sjj8loqe35rdoJstygm4RmVJ1h7lH+QVWxlnIUr7dgYng1tei9DnWPzhyzLlG2KPITi/4Xuxf/5tLFq/OMzIUTAJlPRWs0IavPSLnR3iv2UTbJUNt90AjDgPNYrsHn8JpCR3C0ExtwsNjf18S6MkcT7PiWuu5e5iMZ/F6sJOd+F686jp1nCb2PyLnSfJtv1Sxz5THD9wEwy+fGehGEWp62S2dp+VfjE", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Soil creep", 
		"option_b": "Landslide", 
		"option_c": "Soil flow", 
		"option_d": "Mudslide", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040112", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ3z54BgXRiyyPzsJivdDHQUrnqNRuN9YzH3XKKCY+Lt3ddyKFGEglUksLXJVyRCIADOrEmPPa/WMpc=", 
		"answer": "24a3YZ2z0gvv8pVi0pHbzIcgYZ4nzTIPMU2h9A==", 
		"explanation": "24a3YZ2z0gvv8pVsEh/+1vK/PmXfFGxRomzDQa97YHSjV7XHa/2yiZ5iZ13Jnld05TqGpLfx80YOg+hW5piafScNastgzpCa2O37hHBPN4ZWlYN5pJ4Qa/oAzX2he8OWJ+xvymvANEn/dzz9LWQ0mzLVn25F6Ieu8GevW5ojyBBykIhq7s18M9Hf3rqS/kSsn0aD32+YRrokHlrZucGn+EbcsIMqocSOvTfItP332uzb9Z4YbQFe/7Nxb1K3kugE9zg9Edq1eBtPseLfc1n+YCelZwMc6tijwXV60osnWiV05wpFisNXcYB/15bgrz45O8h5VTyo40lVw4dwVhOTZ/H4w2ft7BU8Z38udcpkr202qQ6OKVdqn3mVVilV1IJyvtkNhkRwcWBX3Hfuhn+CjXWKbpDm+5T1h+T14Ldi5rY1LA3AOlrMU4NccbLLLml1ivmXDKVZc5BxEjCmMdog+3npJYSd0D0ekNYmb2Pu+S/byMVsEcpUl00my0lL/YKC8w==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Soil flow", 
		"option_b": "Landslide", 
		"option_c": "Soil creep", 
		"option_d": "Mudslide", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040113", 
		"question": "24GwbdHjwxbp8pYzEhzrher3PGjYQ3AeoHSQEqJmdTHhRqjJa+O+zZhmKRyLlBt4+nPLqqbx+xMdiqlY/YeQfjFDaYJ7wJCe1vDy1j0BPN5dnYV8qNoecvAAwymlccabM+ts3XqBKUb1dHm0FzB/mj7BhDxXu8OEyhiEa+UI/yoN1pB97Nw0OcWW16/RMS2/7M2ELmGZK7U0eUv5wg==", 
		"answer": "25awbZz60hjmtcFF7LXcvEd2sBlmS7IH/JI=", 
		"explanation": "25awbZz60hjmt5IlUwr6wO/2O2yQCnFRt3eGEqRmcXX2VauCauTtwJllIlubjE9y/XiGrKOw5VwMhLsb/YaNfzcEdstswNWE3uf2yDFTNsdHjol96olfa/1UxH2oeNHWJfB63S6MLk71Jy68EHVm2HHZkmVRrY33tSa1UJo2wxw2hcdM5cEvfMeN1quW+174hwqW2WmCCKlsFBSausO45FCVtIs3u42Mvzab5+Drj/vH5cwOIgdU/5J3ZhuumKsCtGovVMm/bRxC/+OQaECtLz6mNU4J8Mbmlldmy48mUyky+w1LkcNZZIBw3p3ptTExM419EDKuq0FSzpp7Hx6Yd7Gt1G2k5FwsZnUncJ5ksyN16RiULUZ72maVQilDlYx4vtQQhhdscXlF1TqgjSeChGSbdZztq8jugOnztLBs/OMwIFWIdVPAT4oZa/qMZ2Z8zqmTFKJOPJN+BCv1fZ0n8i38MpeXyzAC3pk3JmPvtD2YhsjncCe5wzTh27hFrNwOHUGYo5qo", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Ch,em,ic,al,ph,ys,ic,al", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040114", 
		"question": "24GwbdHjwxbp8pYzEhzrher3PGjYQ3AeoHSQEqJmdTHhRqjJa+O+zZhmKRyLlBtr+m/Vqqbx+xMJgLpY7J3TMDEWfYMvycPJw+H61HRTMtJRiIUy55IecvNF33HtcsbUM+ouz22ULkr+K3m8CnQ0gzTCnnVYr8O6+yP7UMguyRs11o5rrcMyM8CRmamAqHKHuTm940Sud4IkBlGYocat+UqSp8AbjNhWZoI45qqe1tCNxqap", 
		"answer": "24WwcYL60hjmtX/VJ7BgywMrvogRLB4KmSA=", 
		"explanation": "25i9a5ny3xDp9olgRRvz0fX6J2LeBCIYsD+XWqY0cmPmVazGYfrwiZh3Z06GjlBosnLTpuXk+BMfh7FI4I2efGIFcZlszcPJ4+H61HRTMtJRiIUy4pYKf+BVzSmke9rIbL5o3GGTMwXxZC20C3441DDYjjxBrZf28TWiFNkuwxk3hcd77N0vOZeN1quY+w2siUaEznqWRbhqBRSWo8u6q1eVrYd4k8Kf8TfD9fnplv2fsMkKdg1A/5V6Zku1ma9J8SQsXoi3ehNI+veQYlXjYC6xIgsH/Iej02x5x4wtVGcztB5IhsNQd9Jn3p32/DQiPs5+ACGzrUMA05x5HwWZd7b44GTl7kEsNXslYcp/syIhsk+fKVo+m2ePQ2xUjIV56pAJhwFwbnpSmTqggTCFlHeGfob34o77xfz/4L1q4aopPUSHJ13MX4ISJYfILnQy2vuUDqNPIN9uBGL2L9oj9Tf8LoLU1jdN0cslLmSn4yONmo3wIXGotp/8ztd6HbIBItTWqe6htVLTdCLtLWTfJsbxWgDxQXX70gIloB0k3CkV+mvWD8lr5ywDjXi/W0l30ivhfnuk1qxT6YmdP4c/x/qszj8RlPh9jdvn1Q8oTge3iGwP8oWWS1VByhTFC88UwRg7CboVVJHU/WGZkn/TSnBNb9z5Aq2U0ClbmHiAXTxJTDeHHTBL5SG1vJQ=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Ch,em,ic,al,ph,ys,ic,al", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040115", 
		"question": "24GwbdHjwxbp8pYzEhzrher3PGjYQ3AeoHSQEqJmdTHhRqjJa+O+zZhmKRyLlBtv+nOGoqbk/lwBz6ddqYKWZisNectg2teI2e3kyWIBOtUEkY5985RffecA8wKSS+vkH8FR8S6XIkTkbzyvDX5z1sqht/NFucwjnKbRXQWepA0=", 
		"answer": "25exZ5381hDp9oliyjAzEMeSD/hLp2s0BwNS0w==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHjwxbp8pYzEhzrher3PGjYQ3AeoHSQEqJmdTHhRqjJa+O+zZhmKRyLlBtv+nOGoqbk/lwBz6ddqYKWZisNectg2teI2e3kyWIBOtUEkY5985RffecAzjSieNvcKf1vwi6XIkTkbzyvDX5z1AXeg28Wp4C44DWoFM0/xRtyhot549wvcJee16Ge6UGrykaNzjucQb52HluLss+m4lCRs8I7usOZozvZ4eD82uzcsMoDZ0hWtpV2bU+5kLoI7CM3X4i7blJZ/ufbchTLLzrjIhYc9Nvv0zgp1o4oU3105hBJlpAWYcF9lp/2syVwNsN+GnO5sUFWzpd5TFvWcaW9wnzt7lJ/ZWgudpl4rih1oAGYaFd/j3iVQisRho9o9cNZgQsjfn1Bn32goCqZkmqYdZ3kq4HyjOXxrKoj8aIpaUWJJk7NRplcd7zDLCd0xfuWDLJVPJF0VwPiOdw69Tb3IZqYxnVN3dAjPXjl/SuV0sz2LWysuobgztV4EP8PJNbE58K08F3EaCfyYW+Was71Sg30D37hkwF3sBkrwTId+yLZAY0//CNNnGy1SE9tnCCgaHO2mP5R44yLbY89wLXO1D0cl/NxnJr7lAo5RhCziG1KvIPfX1BO1EeWH40RzR0vAPQTG5rUsmSY1WXYSmwEccm2DamJxz9L2/P0nSNCzqygowYYxhDJmuVs904y", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Bi,ol,og,ic,al,ph,ys,ic,al", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040116", 
		"question": "24GwbdH33g7k5IkvQhuyyPLpMGbVDXZRrHnDQax9fD2jRqjBZaG+xoUxKEiBiEk79nPEsazjt0YBi61JqZqXdWIFcZlszZCG0aTw1nBXOtJd2olhpJERc+NOjDy+NOvkH8FR8VG/GHqyMtzxdPzW7ALF5efIPVRweA==", 
		"answer": "25i5e4Kz3Bb88oglXAqw0+W+SXcIw33f01YpBWyQdA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH33g7k5IkvQhuyyPLpMGbVDXZRrHnDQax9fD2jRqjBZaG+xoUxI1mLn1JosnLUqrP1+RMNluhc+4+JeTYaPoJ8iNOI2+jywDFMMtVX2o198p8SefpUjBS5NN3VI/J7ymuTZ1XiaDq4F2Nxh3Hag3dT6I+6+yOoWNMzxQZ+1pV37sM6PduTyuTT6UO8xhWN1XfRS69hFETZk8+r/0yOs8I0vMaI8SHX++T82uvH9dsbbA1BrMo/cFS1m+gK9ycoXtu9fBtE/6iQYFrpYD+iMwsPucjs2GBsyJZpVGcy+ApDjIBTIslnxdjrvzElLd9vGzC/42lB1Ic8SBaFYLS21yjn4Vt/ZXU4YMp+tSo7qAmVK1VwjiuUTTZQhoR4vsQW1QdscGJVkn/0izqYwGSBeNPq5YbuhPvksqxg5rY1LAGJOxzZUIsZZqfFIydz2OyaHuTm1cIlJJGtEtCM1GgoDsML", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Mas,s m,ove,me,nt", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040117", 
		"question": "24K5fJThkQ3i9pFgWw2yw/LqO2+QAWcdrGjDRqtxMHbxW7LMaq3t3IV3Jl+MzVJ1smLOpuXg+EEKnOha54rfczACfYB8iN+Pl/b4x3pSc8dKnsBh65MTPP1TjDaje8PVYP99jlG/GHrPWAaCO082e7wQgb0IIstvGBPGBuwoug==", 
		"answer": "25KqZ4T91Q7r44AyEPTwhkZCECXGFy2CwyltGxU=", 
		"explanation": "24K5fJThkR/l4oskEhz3y/j+IWOQF2oU43iRXbZ6dDHwQbXEb+77iZ5/Z06GjlA783jC47b//l9Pn6dJ7J3fcSwHPo19ydOdwvby1zFIIIZPlI9l6toeb7RH3jK4etDMIepr3C6pMwXzaDeuEHlggSXTmTxX6JWy4Sa3FMk41Qcxk8d+4tp8K9KT1bvT6UO8xhWSznKfT64kJVyc9cKt/UaQ4I0+9d6MpSfJ9eDwlfaT+dBLdgBX/4FtbE6yk+gN/T49Q8W9ZhdYse3EchTsIyumNB0U+8Lv32BwisIoU210/QsGko9Xe9Mz19jnriczNsxmVSG1r0EAzpo8TAKFYLyx3mHq5xU6dnU4fJl5uSAm4Q6SLBRzn26IRSJW1Ih+89EX1RNiaWpS3HjlhzuYwjEBjEMu34sG4bsAeG6KZQs=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Gro,un,dwa,ter", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040118", 
		"question": "24GwbdHgxAvs9oYlEhH0hen3MCvDAnYEsX6XV6c0cWPmVefLYK3pwZ5yLxyOn1Ru/HLRorH15RMGnOhI/YGNdSZDd5gvy9GF2+HzhGVJNoZ7pb9N26UgQ8t/ji5Un3nGR0GmiCSYM8gkNNg=", 
		"answer": "24K5fJThkQ3r9YklEEB09u8JZ6/2yzoMVQWwfso=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHgxAvs9oYlEhH0hen3MCvDAnYEsX6XV6c0cWPmVefVZujszNd2NVOcg19s82LDseX55BMcm6dJ7IrfeTFDfYpjxNWNl/D/wTFWMtJBiMBm5ZgTebRp2H2/ccTJJe1rwHqTZ1H4Ynm/C2V6kDDEkzxUrZes8CK1FM4/xVUhl5Nt/8koOdPfw6ed7QH4kQ6Hzn7RW61lElGK9cyt/1SZpYx4p8KOuiGb9fr92uvc+dJLYxpX/4B2b1e5k+ge8T4wEd+1fBdZvaTRb1CtNCCmZxsT6sr3w2Zo0octHXM7+hoKwpReZ9J2lozsuSE1f956FDC/sARDyJpoXh6YNLyxwijQ6FB/Yns/YJgtqCw3rQrbOxRyn32ZQGxXmJVo6sUYgQFwPWtVmTb0jX+bkmCMdYPq/4HojOf+7Plm5KI3JlOBIVXXWMFcZL3EZ29nx+iVTadfJ5ZxHjbvOMZszTmNcMxslHHfBrEojWFgMQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Wa,te,r t,abl,e", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040119", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gcRb3yPT8NGeQFGcQt3eGQKp6dzHqR+fWZui+xJhiMxyAgEt04GLHrbGw50EAjK1I+s6QdmIUe4p7wNWb3urwhHhPc9JWlZB755sTPOZFyzSiesfnLsJg/GuBNEr+PXmJFn9knTLXhjxErYSy+imoFNI21hByno5/5YgoOdqP3LqS/FiqgxXC3XWVCK9lGFqftMKkpwOLqIs7vY2Mozeb9vvtkrjQ/9APdwtbqYM/d1T8lKAM9SM7UMT0fxdK5ezVc13jJ2ps+RgPKUe09TAsuIwELwrt", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiIQrXvDYON9YzH3XKKCbeLs25JyMxyMlUt383jHt6z/+RMJgLobyMzhe6ddeFdnLLMGFYjfRT4E", 
		"explanation": "25awbZz60hjmt5IlUwr6wO/2O2yQCnFRt3eGErNmf3LmR7SCbPS+3p94JFTJn1R4+WWGorf1t1EdgKNe586bfzUNPol2iNOB0un+x3BNc9RBm4Nm7ZURb7RXxSmlNMPaNPt8gi6PP1z3YjfxRHF6kHHZnnRTusOo4CWoQNs5wxAh1rt20cYILtiP0KuS5A2qgwGL03WCCLVlB1HZvcev4wOIpY8osN+MpSfJ8ee5m/bXsMwKawZUvopzLxurn6EK8GooQ8eiYRZOsfDYZBT6ITymNU4c98+j2WxwwYcnHWcx9xpVkYJEe4B12Yqkvzo1MsRpFD/6tEFB05x5TR6Yc/2s3yjr41YqZzofbY8ttCQyqU+ILVlun3mdWDlDkZMr/9wKmkRwbWpFmDb1kn+fiGDPf5vm5on/hOSwsrxi8bcuJk+TdwwQ7qXkwWi8HFRR1aaHg4c=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040120", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gdAz91um/Im7RF2oUsXaNVeN9YzH3XKKCY+Lt3dd4KkyGn096/GKGs7f/9FYcnOhU786IdSMXdo59wd6Ol+35hHJOP8IEiIV17ZURb8hO8DOfcdXIL/A0jk2PK0GwdTy6DX96h3Hei2pT6IWp8CKhXdQwgBQ8ksds5ckrNdmYmauK60G9lUrCy3OYS7UkEEac9dyt+FOTrpExt8GI8TTU5rT/iPfA5J4cZwlGt4NtalW71XRYYzTzMvlno6p9saEn7Ps=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiITtmvDYON9YzHtW7OCeuX7iZR+NU6Mjk87927Wr6T+9kcGgKYb74GNMANBtSDiju8xv13Ft8ybHRyYOQ==", 
		"explanation": "25OqZ4LnkQ7v9pEoVwz7y/q/PHiQF2oU42+RXaBxY2KjVr6CeeX3yp8xNVOKhkg782TD46fi+FgKgehf5pmRMCAaPp9nzZCMz/T2ymJIPMgElYYy85sLeeYAzS7tfcCbJuxry3SFNAXMaQWzJ394kHHEj3tfp42otS+6Qt93xgc3k51x4898Pdmbmbyb6VqxiAHC32KSRLh3XRSOvcer4wOMso0uvMmI8SbT8bTum+zW4p4FZwtXrJV+cUL8kacbuCwqXtugKAVO8PDYZEbkLi/jMwFd9sjgw2Yp7o0+WH8x5lMGlotTIsVrxpnqrzs/MY1lE3OtolBF1dR9TFefYP2+wm3h+lAsNXM4JZ5luW0lswaRKUZn2midWT9U1I9tvtYLmhd3PXhFnWLohy2CjmLDPJ3s/8Doje2wpqtm97kuJ0bANFLcFpkUZKTJKWAyyfCYAaNPc4tvEi/1ONk4+Sq7k8MwjcG8W4tBDYSCKABGmw==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040121", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gfxvxzfzxPGjRDyIGpn6XWqZmeX/kFK7RLuDx25IxLlGZgklv83jS47H49l1PjKBe5IeccS5DaY5u3NiMxe35wzFIPYZQkoUy4pUNcfVUxTKjNNvdYO1vwGrAI1D+YiqBCkx6pjTXmXNY8sOI9Cm/FN4izhAh1oZq6Ig6M8WS3KzT6lT4kg6HnGyYRrkoUUORvM2gq0qP4IN4pcWUojvY9fi5m//W/spLbQ4SqIN+d1O5haEH/2iKEZf12uQRXDQ4kiNBwEvw", 
		"answer": "25T4YYKz1xjm5IBgUAvmhc+/PHiQF3AEpj1H3esm/O0e/DyDhrhK09GF", 
		"explanation": "25i9a5ny3xDp9olgRRvz0fX6J2LeBCIYsD+XWqY0YGPsV6LRfa380NdmL1WKhRtp/XXNsOXx5VZPjbpU4ouRMCYMaYUvysnJx+zu13hCMsoEnI9g558MMLRT2T6lNNXIYOpmyy6XLkuwRDG4CXl3lT2WnXlXvIu+5y61U5o+01UmnoI4/dozP9KMyuiR8Q2vjg+B1DuDR75vAhSYp8vo6VGTq4c29cmCpjyb9u25mfDW/dcIYwQSrYN+YE+1mKYauBY2bcaHaRxPseDFb1H+YCmxIk4b9tnu03ApxJtpSWExtAhPjIcaItd735vs/Dsjf8wqBTujsE1Dxpg8XhCTeqn4326k91A+YXIud4Nju20drhiZPlFs1iuIRCkRh4Fl+pANnQV3PWJBl3PzwiqbwHaOcpej75XygPuwqaoj/aUzLE/AMVnKX5sZYfPGNWh/ivuUDq1Pc4tvFjamNdQ4+Xn7JZOany4I0c0oKmXi8Gqbi432MWC3upH4gpRhEb4UPtTX4MWw8nfrk3kwhMYRp3dkB9StRD8=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040122", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gdAz91um/NGjECm0f43aQErd8dTHuW7TWLuTz2ZhjM12HmRtr4HnFprbjt1wJz6Ve6oaefisAf4cv39WIw+zy1nhPNIZNlMBm4ZcPeeZB2DjteNXPKep7ymuTG0vMaQu4BWN7mmuWuHlGrYKv8CP7UsgyxQ87mIA47MY4fMOX2L+a5kr4iQDCy3qFTa8kGFrZttyp6EiP4IM2sY2OozfN/ff8ibja/p4ZbQtZrMZ8YlX8lKkc6y94RcCxZVJf/qTSc1HsK2iiNw8P7Ylbq+xcEQO62HzFFB4DkBVb", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiIQrXvDYON9YzH3XKKCbeLs25JyMxyMlUt383jHt6z/+RMJgLobyMzhe6ddeFdnLLMGFYjfRT4E", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/NmTCEWcStzPDU61wMGXrUefQa+ztxpkxLk/JjBtt83rPp+X170MDjqZa/YeQfmIFcZkv3NiMl+Xk13RTJ89LlMBU9pUMaLRBzymke9qXYP9i3WHALEv/cDf9BWM0kiPZmWgWv4a/8i61U5Z3yQZyn4l86M04fNbfyqGU5kS+jwWD0m/RWK9rElGKpo6n7QORpYEwtMOEsjPXtOP8m+zb9cwCbA8Stog/d16xh60b+T49EcS1fBtf5ODVchTfJTimJhoY/YvlxHFs3IsnWik1+hsGlotXdcl90djrunInPtlvB3OzrQRSyJd3HxGEdb6sxXrh8xU8dHRrYJJorjl1tR2ZJVFwnmSJX2xBhoV47cULkEgjfm5Vj3/uhX+fiGDPbpzg4JO8keewpaFz860jaUCOMRzbWYMId7LDMysyz/+eA7JJMpNrDmLqONQq9Tf+YIKbny0F1dAyb3H19S2Ul8PhOHGzvJy5utx/B/8QJN7G7Nik8FXUITPgM2maZd74WBr8Vjz91QhgtAws3iRQ4WyYGox4/CIDjT6nQFBs0iHseX+1g79I44yJP5o03uXpzzMEjeZ9jNe31xIyUxayj2pXu4qYD09GylrfGMQExQc6AK1BAJmR5mWT1XTCTn0Ge8HhD+iIxWxa1eD6nSF8sZROQYSLbBrJj98ywRi/QfJ/FXTorI/0OPIBSJNexDv8eisjICEswrGZlqE=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040123", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gYRH7yb38J27VEyIYsD+OXbFxMHjuRKjQeuzw3ddlL12HzVd6/HLVr6z08kBPhqYb/YaaMCQMbIZu3NmG2aT4wjFSMNRBn5NO6qYRTvFB3zKjLpToL/dijm2SIkDgJzCuRHE0kjDFnjAWr5G68TK6WJon0hoxk5RroYgrNN6T3Oif6UO8lQqL2H6CCLx2FBSKoMqs7k3coYw89c6MpTPI4Ob2ivDa85zLt3rzqSbcXISoR7WFHmax", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/M2rcEGdTMGpJFXhmL/SRcvUWGeF7zw==", 
		"explanation": "24a3YZ2z0gvv8pVgWw2yxL3sOWTHTyIWsX6HR6J4MGHxW6THff6yiZl+MxyPjEhvskLOpuXj+1wYz6VU/4uSdSwXPoRpiMOG3ui31HBTJ89HloVhpJ4Qa/oAzX2+eNvLJb5h2GuSZ0T+JzylEHV6kDTSymxTuoq08We0UpojyRg31oRw7No9P8Oay6GJ7V74lQmL0DuSWrhhARS1tMCs+E+VpIcr+Y2Cv3LP/PG5lezb9cxLaglcu8o/Ykm516EH/C89VYinfRZP9OqQYFrpYCuiMw8O7dnsxnxgxcIsS2w64AwGsYBEZ8Vglpn2uXIkJt1jFjK2r10AwZtuUhKSNL+hkHzs5RU+dnk+aJ9hvTk8rgHcJ1I+l2qIST5YlYwr+MIWmERvfGFEj3rphjqYzCWBc4ej7ZLziKjkqLwj4a8oPgGNOkrdW4gScfPPISdhxeCXTaVONpp3VWOfK4VuaddBXNC5O/NJKo8=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "Both A and R are false", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040124", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gZhb3her+IW7CQ3YQoXOGEqpnMHDvQ6bbfa34xoJ/IxyImRtv+nOGsKT98hMLirhP4c6ddS4Mact7wNXJxPHlwnBCNvpKpo5A4ZsMc/oajAmlcZTMIepr3C6UJkf8Ynm0FzBgnDSWhnlArY/79DP7Q9I+wx1ygo99rc8uM8KR3eia+w2rhxKXznqFTbkkBl2NvY6/6leZssBOr6OvQTYBJLNXkeAL6ScY", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/M2rcEGdTMGpJFXhmL/SRcvUWGeF7zw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHk0A3v5cU0Uxz+wL32JiveDHZRonOUU7pnMHfsQanGLuzqiYN5IhyajFZ+snLDs7H4t1EKg6dMqZqXdWIQa5lpydOMl83jhHdNJsVQj4Fm4YlfePFQyTOpfdrcYPFgjmiBJFH/dSr9CHl/kXHGmHlVoZOy4SavXdU5jFU3gIZo4to9KN6Q1+TT6UO8xg6X0XqfCLxnBV2PvNqh7lDclIo99dqMpTfJtOD4mPTWsMwOchpXrINxd0j8g6AMuD8oQc2mKBBE5OrUYEb0YCelZxoV/Ivw12B81IM9WG107hBIh88Wdch2xJ2kqDo1f8p4Gia0pwRJ1NR6Vhuacbn4x2Hw6BUodG4ud8Ytvjgh4QaIOxRyn32ZQGxSlY4r/dgYmwNmPWBWmWSgljaGhSfVPQK/MCE7E10m/Lk2Lukp", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "Both A and R are false", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040125", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gcwzmwO72NGWQFGcdr2zDUaJ6MHPmFLTKb+HyxoB0NRyGnxt/93PWprew41sOgehV5oDScTAXe5hmyd7JwOH7yGJ9PfpKqIVz95URJrRh3imoZ93aLr55y2KMNAXxdTz9AGJ9mD3Tjjxfppe0tSaqQdMxxQch1pNw7Nx8PcWamaac/A2tiAKHzjuBWrh3AkGLsILo/EuVo4p4s8KfsjfItODxn7jE8coOcEhGsMZtaki5170ZuD4wVIijbR5Hs9Q/lLai4j0IvfFeJKO+QqM=", 
		"answer": "25T4YYKzxQv/8sUiRwqy9732JivWAm4Cpj3Wwp/h42rtYypUKGgM3ijo", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJTg2Bjkt5IlXhLhhfztMCvUEWsdr3qHEqp6ZH6jVbbXZ+v724QxM1SImRt64HOGtqv08kFPn7pe+p2KYidPPophzJCd3+G31GNEINVRiIUy65xfaPxFjCqsYNHJYPdgjnqIIgXxdiy0AnVm1DfZmH9Tu8Ov/SL7Q9sjxQdygog4/8EvOZeKyeiH4Ej4kQOO0Du/R7MpEEaNsN2h6k3ct4c0ud7B8T3VtODxn7jc5NYOcEhavoh7Lxu9ha1J/DgxXcSxbFJC//DfIVX8NSGlIhwOud/r12Apx5AsHWc74F9TjIdTcIBjxJ33ryciOoEqBjz6t0xFh4N9SxKENLCtw3yk4lB/ZW8mdY9p/CIgtU+TLhRqkm7cWyldmLxlwt44hxBmbmZBkjb3hzOHkyWObpaj75L1ieT1pPlq/LcoaUCRIFXeU58PJafIJnMyy/ueTbNSN5p1VzL0OMY96Sv8YKKc2nkdwtwzPGL18WqWlI3hMWD6pJPti8Y2HbFAItnAqcqmpVXBZDGhJ3KBZc7nGRz4Sjzv0hpgpVgxx2EC4XHdSJxvtTkFmz6nTEho0III40javFvGIaC2DHs8gzQ=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040126", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddSK12QzVJosneGs6ri+EYcz7pU6oXfcjcXPoJ7iNmal+361HRTPsNFmIx32JRNNbQA6y+set3PJb5n3S6BZ0v/aXStC2J7gSKWmHNVo8O54DP7Xc53yQZyhoJq4M09Ptua5abAoQ34tQeM2GiFR7NhUV2K9c/o+0aOrYc5t8GI8SDU9//FlMTdx9YCYQASsIA/d1O516kL9zw9EdugaQZO/OHedUetKTvsJhwYucLt1Xt71IcqSTZ2IXtIW9yWNQOJ0JtRuoXgAQ==", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUuq+IssS1zFcTLAp79rBM9JHXd+bJt+", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7RyfzmdWLDQ2NRs3CRXbZnMGPsV6yCbPjqiZ5lZ1WazVJ24nPUrqDx9V8Ks6Zv4YeMMCsQPoJhy9+bxeH00DFiP8dd2olhpJtfbPtSwyi+NMbUI/UijmyVMwX5c3m0FzB6myWWmnlEpYa69yu+FO4/yQZym4J549t8KN+ezeiQ5Eyhxg6DzzuCRbxoHRSWpcum4k2bs8I6sNmatDfVtODxn7jU4t8CbBsSsIA/YFe9juRJ+j8sEdy8bVJE4eHeaFrqM2iiNQtd7cTslmdkx44lHW875l9Rg5dTcIBn2djisD0nf9liBzyvpEx8yahybAOXYLi11WbwoAdlNV05ZIRkqCh1qBzcKRRwlWXRXCNDm5V4vsIWlg8jf3pU3H/0wjaYwHWKbp7m6oLwgNT+lLFq4eMuOgGBOU/XFoQSZrzSNWJx3qm8H6dSOotiVyv1fdRu8jb3bYabzTYYw5kyIHTsuGqOmsT2MSW3tpP3nZRiHL4UdtjRqc+4tU+Hbyz1YXWScM60WAbpD3Po1gBsuR82iCMV/HXdDYc/4SUI3nmiSE1qgWfvajyzmb1XqraGepw01fr+2H5Qn+Z5kZLj0V01VES1gmsDooGNQllOz1jTXswJwEk5DaAEBtbS82OYmmKQTXACaI7iCbqI1itAmurlsm9BsaMaVJiLIRzVnp51kleCAPN9RnPipoO5NO9VCyQ8/6B8z+yju8/7Z/ynJ1kkWxK+Sq9Q4NVSZxBpFAjJRRdObry9QpIQRKBGwTXL1xdNVXJMBFjA/ugaUgeh6sbNbWvLcLRcBwqia7IWU8L5XEDKdf65zT7ACLiP1UW7S1MgSzTdNbgIpQDie4X8N1O8lSh3+M/hcmVTQZASfCjjcWWwq6SQSwc2cyMyaJ1GbkLHCwQr1DjPKO4nma8Sfw0qSeizEVVWhB5MlHz42vvGrKG8Tz16cSWxVyln", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 2 only", 
		"option_c": "2 only", 
		"option_d": "2 and 3 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040127", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddFL1nJmlpv92SGt6Ty+1ZPhrsb/YaaMC4GaI5jiNGdl/P/zXJJc9JMn8B19pUKcvAAxS7tZ9XPNexv2muEZ1L5czH9E3FgkSPqhC4f6MOP/SL7Q9sjxQdygoZ64c18NcTf2KSE6VSrxgCNyXWVCLxwUUCRsI676k6Z4IY9pdmF8TDe+Pvu2uzb9Z4YdxpUvoV6X1Xv3uhJzCI9EcyxeAZDsevWIUDlJWi0JhoY64v313Zlw8IgTik18hlDgZdTZoBxz9jwtDdwPsBlAD2u40tGh4Z9VhmQdbG07GbY7n0wYjomZIR0/CIz4RuULRR/mGSKSWxCgIF/+90cmxBwPWZT03fyh3+Ij3edeZD3tMLQ/ADu2d7oVoUypcOQoYuB", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7Gzfi/ImrEBnBRt36BXqY0eWKjQK/HLuH735J9Z12dzUxz+3XO47H48hMInadO54rfeTFDbYp73cKIw+HzhGZIJ84EjYFm4YgjcsBIxS7tfcebI/F83GuDMwXEbzz9E3FgkSOWnn1UpIb7/DT7QNIygAAihoJqrdspLtGe2q3T50v4kg6HnGGeRrgkHlLZps+8/lGdtIs3u4HNpjrS9/y5k+uT5NYOIglAuoc/YV6wmL9J7CI9Ec+mZwdF9aTDdEbrISumZxkV/NnmlnVlysI9VWx05w9HgYZFIsJ2wo/huTxwK8VvVSC1qkgA15VuSx6VeLirkGn25RU5fHYnYI4tqyQhqU+LKUB7iFeScCJigIF/+90cmxAjLzUAqH7lwiiKlGCdPIfi6Yz5xeHj4Lhv5aI+OgGGOknWUs0dcfPUL2Iy2eiWCOZYNo9zH2LkONkh63ntKJPUzCwf1tgjKkvpwCKQgY38KiWzvZH2nMZzF6tAAtnAqc+yoEjPISznYWmbY4vjWBz1XTzs0gxpslgmyS9Q/mPKEcl78D0IkHq5R0MknSmgeHSk1rlZ5Y6BeJdx3POsyToV2PVqmpq7lAk0QkS6gHBWvJDfQFoP31XfEMsGyAViTLUPENbF+mjWlHvfXnIZP8HwQb+G1ylamvf5j3U9toNOV4mHIh6bndcywBOjAOp3FWH/p4u5KfQQSmU977t3z/+dufa1RuelOGAnahSjGbwDs6FZbUJ/FBvJDWRAZvi6XpheVuFb12eKgwZKS3oJDEmM+q4OWAe+r8CIbHOed7kZTh/vbKYLB473SAfdNPinzjHFCoOSoU+3TAQsXXqeLqIf4ATkOr7zLR21kmRoudPgMVlaVoQSL2fnfG75pLKWAgA/bWBlP4JOeU+VSBExhzvQZ+1viOcXcQwoU+izGFIak1FbkH7AB0tA8GUQH6S/RVI0ar5MNFNRwTiiUbIeVRLMhzYGwhaIyiesPvtfNFtjb2WRg0mglpN/3/3swpiEGM2iKbgews0qJvZaVp/XDBsLk+fsr+npFmR5FGx+IP7JUu6d8Fv+B4jjo9ff1xxfyLwEMx82JCDLi5qZ8zZiPKAPe38KqXsc7NnHcACr2o0bvHWp8/huONa74tV7p0/X8Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040128", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddCN06Ag1xosnfUpuX2+EECiqwb/oaafmIUf59q2pCa0uHn1zFVO9RLj4d6pI4XebRH3jK4etCbIfBqjnyFJkb4Yir9EHhx1CLDmHpXq4aH+3XyFJoW0gE3hY5544grOduTyuiS+kj4gAmQ0X6VCKpsFFrZos+87lHcqZF4od+MoSLe8LTslPzW4p4bcA1BrJNtZhu1megI9mo5QN29bhdZzeqDKBStEzixLgAa6ovixHEpx44+XHAntBlJl41SIsFnlozsuXIjPsBvVT+1oEVUzptyYxmqepW3xyjp4VsmNXUtJZ5luW00owCKLRRtjmqISSFUmpR4vtkK2gVxeC9JknXvkC2Og3HQPpnzD8OPpMApp5TcD7rI+TE=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz3hfvtQQBK6FoVpzvW6f7i+bSuw8=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7B1e/2O2zDQ2MDpj+FXbF5dXWjQ6/HYK3pyIN0NRyaiF5r4TbSq7f/4lQHz7xT7M6YYi0WcI8vyd6Nl/byxXJJNtUEjoh3pIkKbvJBzziReuDTKe0ux33AJEridTy+EDBHhCPfhHtF6IKp8Ge9W8g6xRFygY9944grPcOay+iV+kK1xgeMnHqAXbRiFEbV9dmg4kCU4Isr9czNvTPC8ea5lf6T4tEIaUhGt4drI1izmbwI8SQrEd+1fBdZvaTWbVv6M2i3KE4J8c6jxWF7wIMqWCkA/BoGlYJCZ9Iz35akqDo1f8x7ADq8plYAzoc8VxKacP2x3ij07FQ8cDopfMp5tCh1shqOOltrlG+VQisRho9o9cNZogxmcy9UlHOglT6fhXfPbIHm+JPpl+2wqbcj5qsiaUCRIFXeU59cbKCAIHV3y/2eH+ZIO55pVzbuOJUv6DT2M4ac2isE05kwPXL05z+Ll4G1LW2/84X4mtFkVKgJOt2F78e4pxzTbmP1KXjTdd7mXwnzSjzs2xxqoh8tiCBQ63DZC4I/+j9NkW61R01qlWfpYjy1nrsc+I2NdJ0N3cni7iYRjPF1mpXjlE9mByWpmXpQu4WRD0tKwVjFXswVwUkoA6YMEZKR5WWTmzbHSmgIbY7/EuiT0S1Yyub1znRzu5UcFZycKQrIn8wjiB6/Qfx3FWb8vY//OO4pBFAk86Exw/7htsaoerOnI3c4ahmjGc5L55BCYQN1URzYCShcILm8U90fAfRWwnCKmAEIVG9bDFTLu7wAXBDqo9eIaGXMbrQYTgnqZr1FBM/sS1WPPP/pyT6JB66JnEG7TQQsXXqIL7QI90fgaInhNwahlihQ8cSlJVBPQZFXNSmzYGO85aKSHg88ej5lIZkHckLZT1Atmn7TK/hkiOcCaVg5Sa3nCkUEhB5akTrbAF8FokMdVLbtd1siJOlEYEwUwTv1GLNfWA7DijYPihaVzDbjae5DNAkianGaiUny19Jyl/qpkpyEGcf3P7hb3YtDPL5eBI3XC14O2vXr/eLlAiwtDmg3OfncW/CRpEC2EMHnp4PP1RxfwbtIIVo3KQWFtZHx/y1oOaBdIzB5qXINqcfXbBLqitIZ5kB6WVvr5gHlU2Jhtx1kb4r4KtvTP5WhsFFLVjDPUvlQmfF9nSDrNt7FbRUxO20JnzOYf8GKzifDNKL4z78bABu2l6rbV4Nj61s5zd28g0FPvT41gGrnGTbOa+roqBpBJzxsRPScElxTgRIxlTO/nkfgOM+9hrIMnPBV2bcf5Ez4sGFih1vMSE/Bb3ztx7aRsSbStkJhyLhmXSaFVGEtyxQlSeAn9zUuSSthXalx/KH0OLTW3nWuLJC9jYgf6kZHCufeJ7j7rsXuLK3Cb6jtwMCHPWuh5IMpK+fjZdcDYHeNYjwKqKq0bo3KaEmXOX2B3rSIAWfOMShermp+iGuAU1hhLHnzRsZLG3ZGn8J3Y7cUs47ov0lkaGPPFPNwIfHGku/3qklSe26srd4n", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040129", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddFL1nJiV5r5n6GrKOw41sKz79a/YuNMDYCfIdqiNmal/D/wTFSMstB2ol8pJsTcLRQzS+5Z5TUJr56xmvAMEriaz2BCiI91HHignkWrIar4S/7W9x31B031pB5+c0ufMOe26SWqESrxgeE2n6SXLhgUVaA9dqg7gOIuZI99cKL8SDU9//qpvaAuZ5LVgBX/4J6c0+016cPuD4wVIijaQZO46TEYFbhJWiqNE4c/83m1WBswsIrRCkg/BoGkY9ZcsUz2Z6kqDo1f8FrGzeGrXhO8Jx1XB/We7v4xGDhoFQ9emwuJZl5vTkwrAqSPEc+k3jTTT5U1Ill/d8LhwFgaTACbxDtSM92tuGBr4/ep/iS7w==", 
		"answer": "2+T4Z5//yFtqIB4th9O9apMH4n7ZyUrT", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH12Av548UzRh/mwPD6O3+QCnFRqnGAXbFmdXL3FJPKa636zIdlLxyGixtv+nOGtKTk8kFPm6lZ5YvfZiMRd458iNeb0uXjyGgBNdRLl8Bi6JscebRUw329eNXYJb5H2i6EIlX1aT2uRH961CXejzxRrYy3+iCiFNUxgAE6k8d5/809cJeL0a3T6UC3kwiWnHSXCK9lGFqftMKkpwOdroZ4ocWI8TPW++H3jrjc9p4cYxxXrcZra1qo16EauCg9WMazKAVC5ezUc1X6LmilNQEQud/r0zRo15cgW2wmyBF6jLdeZ4Bg05vrsjZwLNlrATa3pkpUh51vHxSZZq+903yk1F06NW4ydY8tsyt1swCfI0c+m22aSS9Fh8B/9tVZhQFxcGpBnn/siyuSwGqJPIfr7sD7l+flrr0vsrQvIEKIdV3eUIgfcaCAM293iu2eHbJUc5BhVzbuOJU5/S38MtaA3jsB1ZkQKmXq8Subnsi1K2q5uIG1zsdjF7dAN8KF+sq5tBzGbyehJm+ScM74FUjxQ3D3xE5ytgwg2mEE5yLeBIZotTkFjHGlTkwkhi/lYTysmaxZqoePbIc9yrX41TMe2P11j57l2Rg9RQi+zW1MsY+MAxxc2FfeXswUhAoiDa1BFZjVsn6elHrVC0gFdt22DK2GzT8IzuvwmiFpt5VOQo2aKQubnt8kxBLxCO45QX79oYX4MfAMSnck+759xfqkpYqye7OlPmArfFqgUPtRs4VUeg9+EAnRAGRdb7ulRaEQfe572nCKgw9BVXsJFk7N760FWAq+6s3bLmvScL5cDRHwcbYGB47MRkKPJv2m2DWJCbncgU+7H0gkQD7dILYL4ATkaczmLBbzhGl9udXtM0UbU4IDOTWzcme2srDDHw4ocDkiIMpTckKVTAIrgTDHZ9BpzaYSdRk+Ab+uDVhWl1FcizvXHhhWvEMOWuntV1IzL7sFJlce2iT1HK8NWVzbkzMJhVqFgjbkO/VeNkFjb2yWz0vylIdom7OplYaICdyiILga3J5DPL5aUNrCF15cjfLw6vOgBW07Cmg3J+uISvvBuUz3DsTt4sffwExO2/4hOB86NzyKmt/O+S5lb6QPaHVEqX8c7NnebRavlchO1ERtQhXq+U7zUicsuQN2LoDnZcrQM9ux+EJQAyPPF61Lnbx/zyPxO9udJA03DmA90QqVd9zZhyCLPLi71KUMRQ+jw5zZBZ5s7kR8jtWhg1hZuzJ2jnDuEjbJaubh5BFDJ246lPx4V6PR1LO5LW/uBFd4OA==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "2 only", 
		"option_d": "2 and 3 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040130", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddGIlCFnht64HOGoqnn9kocz6xe7J6aYmIXdophiMOZxe35w2J9PZQN2sBT9o4ab/1Bwn26cdjXM75v3GvAJknnZiCuRHRxkSHTmDxCoIK1tSm0Wpc20gE3hY5544grOduTypSduwT4xjKK2TuVTa1wGRSWs46pq1SZrI54scidtDzf57T2lLjH+NtLZg1Cq44/bF38g6AMuD05Rc2mKAZK8+jVXVrRLh+rLg0VucTllmBhw8IoX2Yi8V9VloJCZ8122Iz3/DsjcMx4EHO5rFZSwpdoAFWRDcwnOYyHajadh5a1Jx7D", 
		"answer": "2+b4Z5//yFtHIoXS+8L1n+t46019wTFK", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7FwPHzJivREWdRonOUU7pnMHXmUbfHfK3qwZZ/Z0+Zn1J19WX6rZH4/kBPhrsb4ICcfzARe4h7iOeM2+jkhHBPN4ZXipJ76p0MPPVSyX2ve8DTYO1h23yDIlawaD/9A2J7gT/SnX1CrZH3tSWuQJojyBAr1oZq6Ig6M8WS3KzT4UP4gg+E2n6DTbNwUUOYrN3o3EaQrJF4tN+I8TbJ/fj1n/yT+dAfbUhGt4M/ZEmzgqYNuD43EdqxaRFDsfDYZBT6ITymNU4J+Mnv0zgp0YogUWx05w9Ui41RcYByxJ2kuj0iMshuVSSypkoA0JVoWgXWcrG3x3uk7lQrYGgqaYZ0/Dk64RuULRRtj3maTS9U1IZ58d1ZlAojfH5VlXDlkH+/iGDPeJbz/4i8iu6wofl0968raU6SdU/IRIQSYvPEInd3xO2ITalSc4tvEmLiOMU69Hn2JtaA1zxNx9g0KmWn4CubnsjJN1m0gIb4mtF7EbEUdoOfqeqlpFnUaCLvYWqWasfnGQniSjz53xlkrgtlzCQV+GfKSJ139CNNkHG+BEV2hiLzZX2v1qlZ5o6dQ4AF2/z/nTsD2PV0jJS33RM/SBapiHxX8qWNW1lcxFXYXtoCyAU9TLUTEdbG92GahjbEQ30ZP9r3EeiOzThHmuL/zmBsqpkIUJ7OOBHanp4v21ekD/l8Ryf9uoPqLukHDyQY8rcx2v+kpNmuZ/bkI2NqexKyGfhY55BDKAt1UR/VAGROca2nUJgMAeZAwHbPhEdcT3oJElvY/rpISQvquM3bayrLc/EIBhuidLYJH4K4XUiPNOO9zSPAB7HcgkKyU1dlTTuTYbIIpRT4e4D+KwS2gShw8cDrcl9USs4WLjP2Z2K4q+OUDgo2bBArFIR0bkbBTh0hmiqDdKMnua8FMBwoUbyvWV8Q1hAPiDveAhhBtVwbUaG+AFwpar1NJRsVyCehGeAQWlzejj9KmVeIxzCsPftJPUwfdVCbhl+gkoEmnPD7kIuCHpTWJbhb1ogTPL4bS5yWHhsLn//or+XlAWk3An43IfaISurU8EvzEtz84szchUhDzP4fN0s+N3mfiJ3V9XpZJ6APeHFeuGFZuMvQbgPq0JsZwVhtEFnp40ToAWUkuh5kLoTjY97Uao+t9RBYBCvSWb0Dke84zi3wIM3QcB87R3Q8hQ/QYdPewibDCaT+gKkMAAinxdnfTY8t+0lty87y101Cpz45z2jqDjbeZ+L97QwUNnR9C6OaFlEdiwIxwXqz2xPsL4ami6MNzqROmKcW4A//4jV+ih6bTl7LcTG6HLyUzhGUQk5d7CRvKui5", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "2 only", 
		"option_d": "3 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040131", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddFL1nJmlpv92SGqquw9l1PjrpP7J2WcSxDaY5jxJCAxKT2yGZAKtUEj4524YhfbOZF3y64ZtHnLqwnji60L0CwcDipAWI0nT+WizxYp4329DWvUck+wRtygYJ04Yg1L5eR3L6W+g2tiAKHzjuBWrh3AkGLsPKmuArc4LYwsI2asCbe5rTwlLjSsMkObgQStpU/YlerlrEauD82Vc2mKAJZ9PfDdEboHCafKSYS7ovu13pwho0vHX088V9HgIxAZ4BgwpnwuT81Mdl5VTqp7EVSwtR/UAWEcb6sjyocNave73xiWPEpS6xtRHW4", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz3hfvtQQBK6FoVpzvW6f7i+bSuw8=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7Gzfi/ImrEBnBRqnHDU600cWP3UbTLb+O+3pJ9KxyAnht6/mHHuraw4l0Lirob+ZyaYzEWbI5TxuSB3ve3zWIBMMlWiIVx8No+buBF3zSsepTMJfJi3S6BNUCwcDyxCGM0gDnXnjxCqZP7/CmvW5o2zlUzh5Jx680ufMOX2LzT4V74kwiG2WnRWK9hAkeMp8vo30uZ4JIqsN6epCDetPv/2uzb9Z4cYxxXrcZ2bRuon61J+TstWM6xelJN/vbTZEetNCCmZxkc7c7xlmBmhpAgTmx04Q8GlotTItd22pTYsg4+DNlrATa3pkpUh8YmHyOecf2v0Xzh8hU2ezoqJYRismA0sxuZO11/lCuLSSBd1Il4vt4cgwFxPXpOmHPywi+ZhXacaYHm147IjeHj4LBwsqopKk6SJ1nbQs0yar2NJnVmz/qSDKgcJJprGzGmPMcrvC78LJqHny0F0c1gO3b3tCOXhsK1OGv6soPsh9JzBv8UPtDRqcKk8FLIdWP0L3mWdIvkSw3jXGnq1k5Rvx1l3yAE7XCYAYc/9G0DkXD9SFZwlzTpbXLhgbtQ5sKDap0lk/fpnSIFleR9m9v4wQl8SAL7mXdG8pOaQ1Bzw2jYLdkG0AwjCboVVMWLslmekDbHSmgIbY7/D+iGgztN1u+xh3I9vpwZVJWdbAzVjts0iAejBO5qQHXolIjNNfUGSm0/urt/yeKzpc+4YbOKI3Fqbha7Gfhc/5lCKANpFEvcFzBKc7GvWN0JROxDwTXkmAkFRm1dAEnF+qZISgGmpteIamWebb4IThbjdbZFBM/sS1WPIP+tzSKJFq2ZhlSrTUFnKcY3F+4kE9KH3zhkHlRVJg==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040132", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddDIkyMjE9+9jbRprHk/l0Iz6lV7c6bYjsKcIwvx9bJxev0z2IBMMdK2oNz8YkaPOBIyTDtYNubM+5ix3q8KRe5J3mbFn9ngHHXiWhfp4379ia1FNk21QY31pV37sMvfMOQmbuD5ESsugjRlTvRarRrBV2a9cip6FeTspF4tsyD8THa4ef82urc89UYIhxd/5Vvb1Koq6Y19h0wWMu8KB1NsfDYZBTsIie1Ik4O7cr303lsyJY6HWAnux5Uh8NVbdJh05vw43DxN/8uRqPj2uCKqAIE1r3i", 
		"answer": "2+T0KMO/kRjk88VzEA9Bvl9GGiGPvDasBnt40f0=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7AwO36NH/VByIGpmuXW61zMHDtUOfGfPT3x5AxKFrJn1R4+WWGoKT+t1AOmrteqZqXdS9DaoQv28CF3vDLykVJOtUEk5My55sTcPFEjDW0cMbaNPdhwC6XIkTkbzyvDX5z1Abej3IWv4Kv8DX7UdQjxQch1pNw6Ig/Ltac0rvT6UO8xhaNzn6CCLJiUUaWtsW7pwOVtMI9rd2MvzbItPXq2vHHsNgZZw1IupU/V1O1hOgM4Do5X9u9ZxwL8uXeIVfsNTumZxoV/Ivx2Xdi1cI9Uikn5BNPlr9YXs5AwpnwuT81MdkqR2n6hVZP1IA8XhSCfbK2kGvl7hU8dG84YMp/sy4+sk+IJxRtimeVWBBfoIhi7ZAQhkRicXxP3HXhjjOOhCWJbpzw/8DrgOnkqLxx+60gaXaIMFKYQYwIYKGAIXV3z/OeHuZVPd9zHyemPscv/zLqYJea23kd38slPDfo8mqLnc7+Kin6uoa5i8xmFbEEJZHE58/3s13JISDgNG6WJt/8XEjiQH/zwE5xuFg22C0Z/F7WNIdM4SwZm3O1R1AkwX2gTnWugrdfqoSPfJo+weas3jMe2Pd5iojylA8zRA+ozWtM8pePQ1Vb8VriFsQUhAA9TLcAGJrU9i2UnHncRHsEfM/6Qb+CwjhA3/H4gGY9j5wPW5idbBjVjp4nxh68APFqFWTspsbxOPAFSnAjurBjz+yq9860Yv3kPmopZAn3W/YZ551UYRA7AwTSETcPYbaqFp8LU/JAxXzEkEdJRGtAE1PY8q0bHyFwj6Pva5dildCym5VCs04=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "2 only", 
		"option_d": "1, 2, and 3", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040133", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddCKFWFzVhp93PW46zjt1JPm7FL7M6QdmIOf5h8iN2GweH6wX9VD8gW08Ay15UWcLRGwDK6NN3IYP8u2neQIgX/YXmwBWNn1DzZnHlbrY2vySnoHZp37BQ8kpR05Mw5L5eey63T6Q2snxaHnHSXCLBlAkfZuMG+7k6ZrpYEu/GDhjrS9/y5lf6T5NYOIglQsJB6I0iolrwM9S82Rdv0YQEE8PbVIV3jIyexNQse7ZShHOD/HkmTycP5nz4l/T5lFA==", 
		"answer": "25u3ZpSz3h+q440lEh/wyuv6d9zw1yvjvQfBR2mrD6vVc9Y=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7ByvTzdWjCBmcB43aQEqI0ZGjzUefNaK3zyIRiZ1GGm15293jSn6vD+FoDz6tJ7IuPMCsQPp9nzZCa2+vgiDFGIcdAj4F+pJ4Qa/pTwDK9cZTWL+hrw2uOMwX/YXmuC3l41DDYjjxEp4CwtQ6vFNMkgBYzg5R96Yg+JZeL0a3T7kKqhQPC033RT69lB12NrI6p5UfctIo99dqIuDXT4LT2nLjH+NtLbR5XrYpmalW716UI7C8qWMm4KCFE+OiQYkboJTjjJA8Tucnmlndo05EsWSk27V9HwpVXcMl2woGkszRwOcxpATyosAgAzpp/UwKSfbO/kHrl6Vs5dHYnKcp+siIirAqQPBg+m2WYDClQhpRj78UYngFwQWF8kkX0gyuOjWCBaNOxscDPiuH84L9v/bRnIFLANBzMT50ZJbzGZ2pz2frbAKlKNpJiGTbaM+Yh9TW5JpqbyHkEw5khb3ro5i/ZgMzlMGH6vp3vi9lzGqtAOdeF+sS+vBzGbyehM3KQbYvgUQn+D2/32gIltAogzTFQwXaYAZo/9iwYjXu0CUZ90jPoaTyyl7NZqoSPfJo+weas3CFQi/txk9v0xhg5V0j7j2pX8o2LD1VcjVXaDcJHxwg7H7EFVJTIsnmekDbDSmgYbc/iCKeJgyNOmvf5iyFusJkCFZuHOBGbnd8yzQXxMvJwWSfrpInuff8UBCQu//J1y+Omsti0YODkLmApbg+kXK9Q59VSaQw7AB7UBi9DefisQ48HAfNbwGDJgxJaQmwJBFTIu7oHXAC5lsr0YFnKYqUZAxvsd/NWSY7UT0nLJv2gzDXaRr6OkAe/H1A8Xj/dLrZN6Abjacz/KwW2nm1q7f3rHlBVQJAbNSP2Zyu4t6bDHw4/PyEqO54HaEbFQhRkgCfTIrloi+cNcQs+AaWoD1Ubkx9b3wraC0EFsV4bH6asVUAiLulHORsFxTL1ArUbWBnExjwLh1qJ0CesJvwLMAkwd2uDigCgmpxi3+vhh5fBCdXsbbQVxIIPPrMbSJvEGF5cm/7r+u/0Aiw2AC1kIfHEEqLDv0z9Toj1rMeawVlJ27cbdnM6Kz2YhZbd9SktLKRBL3JP/XAYudnXZkaowMhYlUZpQlzp4VikTmFhsBBwepz5eZGcI5Wm/EVbHyrAF7xCiuhwzDnlPtrCKFo3AmIjiEeCd9vEwTWPMeC7waMNRQ6t25rKS4NurE1r28ymykNOuHnZG0dAa/8cqaU4h6mPjv/K", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "2 only", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040134", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddCKFWFzVhp93PW46zjt1JPnKRU/s6PYi0Ae5h89N7bnqS3935IP4ZClo9lpJMMPPUAyjy+YNHJYO58wW2FNFawczG8CjBnmzjayn9ErYarySnoHZp37BQ8kpR05Mw5L5eey63T/EW9xgCDz2+UW6kkBU2JsI6n7QORoZEr9cCCpzfW8frtpvbv/ukDawta/4l5I0+0kugI+iUuVIinfBNf9OnVb0D+YCGwaA8P/Ivq2Hdm1JAsXn1rtiyXMRw9JyFxB+tbzv3piDo=", 
		"answer": "2+b4Z5//yFtHIoXS+8L1n+t46019wTFK", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7ByvTzdWjCBmcB43aQEqI0Y33sQ+fSfOL9zIRiG1K9hVJosn/V46b/5UEKjLwb2oGWfGIAbI5q2JCAxKT2hGdEId8EiYx989oPbvtDyS6+OJTaLvoux3rAJET+Jy28D3U0jTTXmG8Wp5H78DG+Wpo0xRsmg5Vx6Nt8OtiNmbua70OxgA+B3XWFCLBrB1GUsMC8q1eT4I07ttifjTzn+sftm+zW/dsFdkgA5cZMbFKw164F9z14WNv0aVJN8PfEZEatMDqsJAsO6ov33nVnhpEmVGV09w1Dh5NqbPR734uktSFwPsF5GnO5rFZSwpdoHySZfbH41mTr9xU2Zjomapho/D80sQaYaEB2m2XcXyNYmMBo7NUchUgjfGFE3H/0wjyKjiWCc4Xmq5PzjOSwobdnsrEoKkrAOkrdRM0dJaDIKHVmivmeH69TN99oEWLyNNgrwDfFLqWA3i0I3dwuOze0rmq1k8PxKmmzt5fqztVkEf8UPtSF78qkpFnUdWP1OG2WJsTyGQXxXG+43gFzshUgxjUs5lbQAZo//D5Nl3CzRlZ2lyT0LEipk6xZqoOces4+x/3pz3IEgeR9jNv40l0xRheozXJMpIGSSlJb3hTCFswThAg8CfQHFYXF93/WgX7RRTwBfsDyEqSOxylbmsX+nCF4p5EDRYCLYFnfj9w0wQTxB/F2QnStq4f3ffEaHGFs96dywq2nttmvcOHkOG0rYVq7WOFd4JlYbAdoLQXhCwBKYqqnRd0YTe9YwTXLhQIIRj9dHErJu6cOHQmrudeIY2XIZrwZAAqid7sEB47xXQfMPfC7yTPdA62Vj0K6H0Y8Di6VJPAf5Bf5fsz/KwW2nm1q7YHqNBFaBI4eJDPmZm75qqXDGAkzc2BlOoVEcQuVSh4g1DHXL/x1zaMFcgokUuiTEVUP1hBdmn7GF0hMs00SU7ztQ1IyOaxBYFkIjT+wELYGHA7LjzQMj1qQgi3+aelFPl4ufmiHwwzhlZYmi/fsm86CC9qiL7hbxIgRMfZfQYnCDU4fjvry6qO1rNtf0NDsQg48cRFhyxDI", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "3 only", 
		"option_c": "2 only", 
		"option_d": "2 and 3 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040135", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddCKFWFzVhp93PW46zjt1AOmrte7c6daWIXdo4vxMWLxe30xWVIPcEEm4Nm7ZURPPtGjC+sfdrMIepr3FKOdQywJwqyDXw0kj3ZnTxfu8O49DKoUd53wgxygo99rd85NdCXzeic7g2sjgPCz3SYRIFqQh3Z9eKp5UePrIs8sN7NsCDetPf4j+vW9J4Je0hGt4M/dF61kKAduCU+Edy8bVJY/u3cIVXjJGi3Lwtd9d7hxH1qx5YgU2509RxSi4xYIs91lorltTwnPtlvBw+0n0poyIM8UhaYbf231ijw6FB/dHgkc48trzk0tQqRLVpqiSuVX2NQhoUr994amhZxeGxUwzTC5vwn7dqKkMh33O3uGK4P", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7ByvTzdWjCBmcB43aQEqB1ZWLmUOfAd63qwZIxK0mLn1J482LPraKw9lAbhqdVqYGZMDACd4V4ycSMxdj58HlIIIZNicB76pkQbuZFzyntR9vSLL5t3GuFNwX5dHm+BWVnkTWWiGUWvIu+tSG0RtkygBo01oBq7N41KM7f2KaXqFmwg0aV2XKWQKkkHlLZocatq0yKpZA0rMSDtnLW9eD8iPHS/J45YwFcqIdrZkn8lKkHuCk3X9ymYRBe5eGQdVutMyeqK04e687mxjRr38IkXGI9+hgGlotTItN835SksT0iOo15GTqqs0FS3tg8XQKCNLSskGH3oFswYTo/bY8tsSw8r0+fKUFtn1eScCJigIF/+90cmxAjLjUAsHfuhiyHiWGKb9Pi+YW8hunls7xnsqE+aVWIMBzPU4QbbaeAKGEy3uGeTbVTOpMnFizifcEm+Xn1NZSG1joMxNAuKDfm9z6QncO1NmP6oZPwgMN3ALoSCt/x4cKk8FXUISLtMnLTb8X3VhriSn/skyJkuRw2xCgU7XGYCZt6tS4Mi221TQRmi2fhLGqghLdZ/pvOcIhx1fTvyT0Ci7g4lpX02Ag4Tgq8zWtLt8SISlVIxUCWEctH0AErTKcOHZqdsnmekDbDR3Mdeo75B+iTyykI1uL/ii09q5gLFY2DIwzVnp4pzlemAOl8RyfkpsbtNflVGWsl9v4xy+Ol996zcLO0PmA5ahS0XK9W9dVGbQNwUQfcHCFdc/inWN0KSeUPwXrDm0d6RnZHElvY/rpIXgWk6sfHYH7MarMJGhuid7xFH8/2SlTDPPWs23DLH/+Vm0SsWkU2RzSaYaQF4Efnf4X1LAfznG4k7cngckJUTY9XPSn3NGa4rqqNDEYudyllO4VOdgfYRAIh1C3PLul3iLUZMDAiVq2xHEJa1hhb3zfBTlZKpAwKV6DtT10rM+lGIU4CyHe6F+ATXRLOlTYDilOP/izQJ8lfMF0mdmGdmwyywdJVkPblwoiNBcOiJK5b0YwWO7NfBJjPX08Un7Pz6ujnGXh5CWs3OvDNHvHeuUPKDPz8q9CazE8LyrEaJFo4MXm4hpbVsDxhILIPZmMKvnIMv8/WIgSzmZxR0BBuX0fv8AHrRycmpBBlZ4fyKtzSLtux+FUfASHOULFX2PN+nTjsMJ/ech8tC3o8nwDQe9PewiaKPKC78qwACw+jw5zZBYls4gh6wdKm0UVCvi9wz2jtS2XVa+ut7hJbNTx6UvSSG1ZUiBBiwTK0nkDnNIPqiqkbi/BS1LwD8Qnlu202jUuYD0PaI3r5nviRoybStkJhxKtqUiagWmZ+y05ZETZzajcXOFP4KsMgdC3m", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040136", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddcJlLEgFp/9zbVt6D151YBhqZcqYGZMDEPcZtq25CK1uq3zX9CIcNFiYUy8JIaPOZJ3zbte9KbLP9gyn2MLkH1dAWzVjk01APTh3NAqY/7+iH7Wtsj1Qczmsdu6M85KNaL0KedqE65iEaL0niDTbx3FBSNvcvo+UqPq8I3s42BsDzf5/jwnv3AzNBYK0gSnYlraxuxlqZE9Ss8VIinfBdO4eHeaFrqYCelZx0R9tvmxTRoyIZpT2w5+wlHjsNZZIB914zxrjM8f9tvEjauolBJyJo8XBaYNLS203rh4UY6NW4jYMp/tT4+4QCaaFh/lG+PQCVVkZNX8OwXogxqfmcAk3CgljeOwGSNc4Xmq5PohPz1rbxt5rBnIFLPNE7dFo4Td6HFJHMtiK7ZnjpIIrQIufU9grtCpy8=", 
		"answer": "25S0ZNHn2Ryq9ocvRBuy1un+IW7dBmwFsD040wiK2oxt23hwtikfRLd+", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7fxPOyOGrUBiICt3qGQqZ6eX/kFKjELv7yxod0NByKjFU7+3jFsaDx5FZPm6BeqZyWYylDcY0vxNGH0/f7zXVEIPpKroh799oWb7RDwy+/cdfPYMlmy2DANEn/dzyuRHFmkXHFnnlTuIa18CP3FM4/xVU0mZV76IgzOpeYy6mF4Vmhxg+RnHyDTbxwFEbV9dmg4kCU4I85vsie8TvPtPn2iP2T/NcAZwRL/5J3Yk/8g6AMuDk0XtixKAVC/eiQZ1XkLGiXLwcOucLwlmNh38IgSSk9519Pj5NZcNRy2IykqD1wPttlHDf6oVFJy5B1URDWe7P4w3zh5UV/ZnYkdY9+gCMJrzyIKUB7l26SWGwDzsBZ+90WgwVvPWBG3HjhliqZgWnPapbk7pT9keH/rvlg861nIE+DJ1nZRYhccbvFZ3V72eLbAqAcP55pEzHqNNEr7wX3FJ6dzHkEw5khI2TotCmWgN/wOnH6hZf+i8B3ALYPOJHN7MenoxzTbmPyNXyRb8f9Qw2wXHD3wwt29xo8iCkf5GbRBo4/4SUI3m2/QEgkmymgfHCglbsc3YqLcc4n1vLpyTMEkft235LklA85SgutiHsP8pCXShxcwl3aXsQUhAQhHrFBGJ/a92GP1WLfC3kfcMrzQamJx2xc0uaxnW1yr5VOXJ/OIRbJj54qwRy0DeQ5QWitrofwMcAbNmof7rNlz+Ckud77JqnkDmo+Z1q6WOEU/pRVbUJoBQ7YFSFBabapFpIYAfND3WXPhEdJSXsJF1/B9L4JUUSlrITGb37LcbAQTgjnZLYREtrxQUmPNvCniDnHBa2ZlFS7H1AtS3qPKKMGpQj2OoDzKhegn2Fg/NLZPGVTTZBXNTSzdWeqquOABBQoei8xaL5PfwfWRB0mnTDCM/Bog+cPdlg5Sa20HBACgR4PmT/RGldXowwdXqvtU1ogJKBDKVgQwyO5COAWUh/YgzsZixaIyiesO/NYOgksfSSfjkLkiJ5vm/r6wGTUFN0NgPQLCm/2FEWVT8w=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "2 only", 
		"option_d": "All the above statements", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040137", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3idddJlKNnldy9nPV46bx+RMHjr5eqYqWYyMQaplg3cPJ1Ov513RQJsNKmYVh2JRNNbQA4DyjcMfXKfpr3S6DJkuwZSyvHTBinT3ai3tTu8/75yayWM022VU+n4l9/oR8M8Xfya2c+EG9ugjRlTvRZLxqFUeVvMqt+AOfoYx4t8jNsjPO5/H92vrKsNAKdh1Avoo/bEn8mqkHtSc5Vc30bhNI5evCcmjjHCaULwce8Yvs0DR9zodpXGs74hoGkZdXdsV+05bwr3I5LIJrBzb6oEtS1ZF/S0jU/OGSbI5erRgfvN4HVCTSqw==", 
		"answer": "2+T0KMO/kRjk88VzEA9Bvl9GGiGPvDasBnt40f0=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7exPP7JmfZB2cC43yCXON8cWfmFKPLfezt3YV+Mk/JjlR14XPXtqD+9FYcs6Z36ICbYy4Keo58iNOI2aT0xWRSNoZIlZNhpJUZPPhJyjjhNN3VKut8x2uTawXgdTatAWJgjXHSi3FXr4b3tSa1UJozyQYgg5ds5McyfMOQmbyB6UOrlgmQyHqFQbJqUVWXsY6r5E6RtYwxtsyZuD3VtPr8ju/c4tUYIjxaup8/YFqy16kF6yV4UsmhexcL9OrGaEbiLiWmKRoc9Yvn13lowYdlHXoh9xcGg5AWdcFn04qkrD08M9h+HDy040VOw9RvUB6aNLiq33vt71sDe0YlVp5sqCg4pAGIaAYk2kedQihCmIlv+8NZlgVtPW1Vjm+glDaHjGSIeYCvq5L9jOTnoaAj/qopLFLMdVPKFp0ZaqPMIlt85uiVCbVQOptiBGLlPNtu/izrOdaR0S0EwtxgOX7r+Cuel961Nnf6p53ugMc6VL4TdsbA5cf3sU+HcyzgJW7fJtn1UATnTmXrn05kuRxlxzUY7XCYAYd55yweimylSlBxgCKgWHSkj/5f64zOfoIi3LXuyCAJ2OR9kIv70VF8Sw2tiGxXvYeUAxxOw1CWEdkPwRtuDboIGZfd4VGYqXjjX30ZesPzD7zHkHYI9uL/inJxtpQLRsyNLRebiNtmyxakEvh9FWX06Ij4KekHC2hs9aAxx+yv+se6cfbkKmQpexWlStNX3ZRFfRB6HUvbBCdbb6q9FokWQPQP0XTE1wRJUmxMRVbN9awbUQ2ur9eIZ2Tdb6QYC17qZrITCo7qT07BM/ClxHyJA76OgU+vSkUuSynRYbED4UfmdYDxJR26kChh69T1JlhUSpBXESb9OWa4oabDDQc5ayM3O8pTckbBCxMlmn7AJux0iOcMcRYpUqSuHVUF1hhBnDLHCl0FtEkYULeoU0cmPqBKLhdRzji7ArQNSR/ejzUEwhadzCasJPNFOEckOb7DDckkqkoth5CJiXIgNdo=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "2 only", 
		"option_d": "1, 2, and 3", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040138", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddSL1mEhFh6/jbRpqTk/1YdhqZcqYeMMDYLe8ttycOA1KTn1n5CNtVX2oJrpI0XdfdIjDmoesHfIepnwWDAN1f/ZDy4AGNImmOfyjxmoJqo/CS6WJogxRQmnoJq5MY7fN6Mmbyb7Q2olAmB2WiCCLJiUVaLsM+j4k2b4Jco9d+CsjnItPbg2vXW89YKbAFRvoo/bl69mbs19nlxEYiWZwZDsefYZFnkIymvZw8T/Yvz3m16z4EoUSkj8R5SioZEa850lpn2uXI5Mt1lBye7rVAA14ZzXBKFZ7irkGfioFE6e28vZJ5ksyMJrzOSAFtp2madQjURm4Yr6tgc1QVhcnlF3GX0gyuOjWCBaICj4pOzhPr14LBt8aw1O0SDIQOagoKO0sQUSkHOtJoimK2zJA==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7RzfjyPGjRDyIGpn6XWqZmeX/kFK7RLvn2zNdzJk+Ajhtr4HnFprbjt1EWz79T4I2XMCYGcJ5rycSA2Oq31GNOMMNBnpNO6q4XdecAxS7tfdrYL+x8y22UZ2b4YjS0B3F41CbTi2herZGy+yD7Xcl31B031pdq4ss5L8Tf1q7T6l+9hw2L0nzRTLJzHxSLus2j+AOeucI7vciAuDHa+LT0n/nd45JLcR1Rt8Z+cBurlrwM6mZ4UMu9bAEHseXeZRT+ISS3Zz4V4Njq1XVlhpUsXH088Q1PjIQWa9MzwpDh/CIiMM5vBiD6rEIAxYZ5Xhyferr4xXik8lo8fmlrZ5MtsSg2qQ6SIVd/liuRSS1fh8wr7cUanURibi9Gjnnzln+Kg3GGc52vq5P9ifywt7xi5qsiO0iOMhCYV4MYJbbYIWh+w+iPBKlSc71oAyqmPt0r8TD6IZrU3jcJkMkoNmTu9yuV0trwOHGytoDwgNM2Fa0FdtjI+cSlpF3JdWPxM3KQY9jnXBuwQHq41wtrohwk3Cgf5l7WNIdM4SwZm3O1R1AkwH2gXHS4hbdf647OaIswx/3pzzsen7RxjNvj3Bh8Vxa0jnpQocSQSRxN31HXFcQJw0k7HPQTG5Xa4S2UjDbdTn8FfsD/AqmLgyFN2+3ism9Jt5kdFYWdbBrUmMwjywPxMfVgRm7uqYq5KvkUHmwp6Lt/za2opIqvffbkPHclbB+kSq9W9dVTegd6GgLTAmRacPi8WZ4VUqBNyzXHkgRARnFABlvAu6UNXAq55oTbe2nWI7APThjwbKARU8/7Wk7AO73p2zHFEv+LkEaqV0E3RzSabfAM6wOwf5T0Kx+6knxt9s/ZPG1Vd5cWKCL+cWWt5fDZSyQ1ayRlK4JCd07WShxklTDHZ+lvlLQJcxkhAb+iGEQekwNGkTmSD0pA8EUTT6q/VFIpPulVMlQSyCSmFLNfUxqKgj8Em1Kd1ivjJ8ZFBUEqaCSanAzhl4Fp3/zmkJyECcCiD7IP2s0AILNWTZnXExsdlPek/+n5AmU6B2E3Of3JSurUokb4BYj1sMaazFFbxqwcN1EvZSmZhpzc4yloPOVAaTBOuH0MqMvGawmkm1PHzmXGGq8N2zwbwX6o36c=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040139", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddCKFCcmVJ0/DbPsOXk/1ZPgqdI/c6PfzYGcJ8v39WIw+zy1nhPNIZUiI9x4YkMPP1OjDGkedHINPFgyy6SIkL5aDeuOH4m3XGWpWRfrIKv/Ci1FNMkgAE6k8d14tsofMeQza2d/A2vgweW1H6DQbNjUUSLus2t+FDcqYx4st+MvzvP8bTrn//a/9AYXgYB9sY/R16/mKUZ9zkxRcG7ZlJJ6KTfc1PsLiGgZw8e8M/wln16hpYhWCk5+wxSwpNZdsV9wtjzuTMkN8h4HD2941RSyJd5TATWfbP40WTooEc6cnMka5lRshE7iQCLaFl/lHLcQyoRgIhuvtEbmhJmPXxUnWLljzqFlHbPdYCs6pL5xev/sqtm8bd4a8oGuYgmmIui0biLewjgr5E=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz3hfvtQQBK6FoVpzvW6f7i+bSuw8=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7ByvHqIWLfDSIYsD+XWqY0fX7wQOfSYfn7x4MxMFmImVN+4H/IpOXg5VwMirtIqYeRMC4Kc4583N+H0qTlwXZIPMhXpo5G7JMMPP1TjD6iZsbeI+ou4meNIlbkaDe4RHln1DCWnmVGrcO082epW9k8gAE6l5M45Nt8OdaM0KSKqEmxlRWN0G2UTP1mCBSOtNqt+QOoqId4osyZtCCb4Pz4jrjA9dsbcUhGt5Rwdly016QA9S8rRce6bVJP+PfDblj7JTvjMwYYucji2ndg049pXmgm9hBIg5dTIsl9lozsuXIiMM5hWXO5olFTzpp7Hx6CNKm3kGr25VQ0NX4kcoQtiCU8sk+MOlt9n3iPDCVC1INq8twckURwcmNViH/vjH+chWSbdJbx4o77uebMrop387ciJESOIRyKDM0zfbrEJnN7xefbBLUcJ5diVy/pLsFu7DbtJZiAny4I0c0oKmXu+i3Zgt/6OmCpoNLwgJRxBr4OP8XAqdmyt1XIbzDdL0mbb9i0UBuwRnL73Bx3shsxiA4I4WbZHIBw+20EjT6kQUEkgjXvb3myhf5e88KZd4cy27XjxSsXnfo4nJT61hQyQhf7mnZXusSQW1RK3xTTEsgKwQc6H/QVG9bX/X+b1XjVXDwOcMPmDr2Jxz8I/fHwgGhputAHRsyPbA3CmttmxxHxE/J6Xif5oIftffUGSmoj7vJ0y/6ou9P7euutKGwwah73bedcs5pJYQZ6BQLSC2RAZvinRJIQAelBknLYlglBU3oJBlvCu6sJSBev6s3cLn7RI6MJHQquI7EQB47sRk7cdfi6iD7GEv+InUL+Uks2WnqNLqQI6xOwbYnzMBu2gWFq/oH1IF5YQZAEfC79NGyrpK2KHwN6bSkiIYVJaXvbdx4XgD/XIvRig7NAI0JtZa2kFl0GmQJGizfdABhHqQwRTaKsTlokaqhGKV8CjT6mUbQXWVzHiSkezkaT1ifiPbpcNEg3c2GBhkLn24J0kPzskZ3BA9qiLLEXkp8GL79USonqEW8Uk+Ck5vKgGGI6CX9lK/vcHsbUs0D7Esfnq9fTylILy6dIOU08JDeCit/Y8zNpPOVGfDBL/WcAvM+SbQDq2oBc2FlrUVms4kTlVW8kpBh9adP/YtzIapK2sFNeAzfCU/lBgbxs1SmkNNzYYAl/F3E6lRKTc9aKxS3DLaD6zrkaRRms09nKS4Ng7URqjui6yl8Auyl6jHnxGDbZY+mt6hsUK3FoRKaLG1NJxh4slSm+01aoL4qtjqkHnfwB2qAHoQXj4ihlz1CDWwraa3aq0/mNoybWsVMkx74jS2OiT3to3AUqQ7A74HZtRT4yCah6/Lf5IPHWm2amIZKrj9B6G7ypzJzOZpYa46kvRFk=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040140", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddFL1nJn1pv9zbJpeXz/1YChqta5c6IdSMXdo59wd6Ol+3khHBHNcNHjoV2pJgGPOBIyX2gfdreMv9ijm2PKlX/dDCpDX961D7QymhercOp+iSwaNRliVVyoo99rdo9KNLf1q7T60W9iw+B3XfRX7hlBVycp8em7AOVs8I5s8uIsibe8LT7g7jH+NtLcRxAqoVrdkm516cPuD4wVIimZxFAzeqDKBStFCCmZxwc7c6j2XIpxYosUGA39RMGlYZXdsh2xJHqu3I5LI1rEzW/oFBFw9R+RleCfLj402Tt7VQrcEYlWYRFszp1rA6SMRRxnCuIRCkRlYJk6NVZhhBiaWpNmXj0kX+CkyqObpaj4o7/ivripbp3reFsw2282LRhg6ZmrrzG/BqC", 
		"answer": "25u3ZpSz3h+q440lEh/wyuv6d9zw1yvjvQfBR2mrD6vVc9Y=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7Gzfi/J2rEBiIepT+AWqZ5eXLiWOfVa+zqwZJjLlKOzVJosnfApaDz41YLz6pCqZqXdWIOd4Vq2tGFl+f4yWFOIM9Qk498pJUZPOBIyX2/e9fQHPBaxmeTZ0zjJzqyFmJxlyWWvnRT6I6y+yKpVdZ3wxo/hohr5Nw1M9nf1q7T6Q2qiQWJnH+UXLh2HF2XsN3o40yL4Ic5psSBqHLS4LT6m/aT8ttLdQ1Tq456cV6416oQuCkwVMW9axNHsfTCblfoMzumNE479tmj02xoy5IlWCV0+BZLh5BCbc52lpH3/DcxLMRmDHOtpkVUz5FuWhPWdqT40Wvt5BUtdHMlJYhovywgsgrcIUA+mWSSWC1YmpMr/dEVlg12cC9DnWTijTGKlGDDPITr4oP0xeHj4Kps/rYlJUTAPFKYQYwIYKH8KVt8+f2aGaNRNpFzV3C8feEm+XnrIYKRnzYLkNooKnru9yuV0trwOHGytoDwgNM2HaxAN9fD7MijtViHYzqhNXWWJtjgSx3zW2nq1k5qsVgxwCRQ+m3bA7VxwSUEjT65WgRlnjTvLH+uhKxZ6ZbOS4Y0k+b4zycTjOFqmtv40l09Bxa0jnQDoIGZSk5cjUDZXtkPwUk5Da1BHZiR5WWfln6QX3QIP8P/D62VwiBbmuLjiyF8rYIPW4uLKFnphd0t21emCOlxFWatpIntffMTSmc++7F62a2guc77duGhOmwpagn3WP1cs5heegc7FArODChWIK+rV4kWRPJK1jXenwZGB21GBlHfu78BSQzqq4TbY2XRd7lcHQvwZbIGFvL2ckn8IfC9zT3MCKvcxh3+a0wgDiicNbVN6gGweYT3KRqwkmQk7sTkJlleVooZO2f6Zyu4o6WGCBI/e2wnMcpTckKVSBwtmT/XIsVpua8JY1gkUuimFUMZ1hJAjSzXDUwFhEQbH6ahSV4mPqwFIV0XyDShAuALVBmKlDseixaTxGLvIf9GOEoidySEik30k5d0lvHuwoePStWiI6gW0IgRaLldBI3XBkhcvPz2r+T4EGEpCmg7buzAW6LQvUDjDNy0rcWa111Cx7gJOlN7JDePyZfM/TNpJrFWL3FMu3YauNmSdg6vmYlU2kVmRBXj8wHzQHMkpFFyeJLiZtzeJp7l9l9NVjPCVq1Lne5x0yukAdfUJA46CnMwgwaEY8DPhzWPLqO7wasPABu2xNnfTY8t/klty5y9xQxDoz54hn/jBzbIZ+bu/BdbLG86qStPS1A/BdtVYz83qBQ1hA==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040141", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddSKE6Mnk90/HPV46Ti8hMfhq1Y7J3ffyRDbYRjwdTJxev0zzFVO8dQ2ohz8p9fbvFTxS65cdCbN/tv2maFNUz+YHmqDHl4kXHXhnAWvIu+tTSuRsg41Rs2n4l/rdozP9zf0amAqE+9gwjCy36QXLVhA1GdicD6ogPcg40qsN6Zvjze57T4iP2T/dEZZ0hRsItybFX8nqZJ/zg5X8GgbVJf+eXeIV3jYCSqKgsO7cTt00hnlctpHUo75hpVloxYZ9Mz14rh/D8/LcgqFjy3rktOh51yHwCXZrD0kH/h9BU8eXMmZJ5or20hqQ6SaF1w2miTQCgd1IR555AamQ1ufHtFj0ruvjGjj3LPcZLt8sDzg6jkqLwj86EoP0TAJkjZQogRYL3UNCd72aaaH6McMJB1BSflKYpsE7iTdZWScJaDbU9hsgip+Q==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7Ryu/6Jn/fDWcC436RV+NkeXTgUbSCYeu+2ph9LljJn1R4+TbSq6Tkt1sOma0b+4uMeTEXe48v39WIw+zy1nhPNIZTkol+4doecPgA2DWoNMfOMuxh22CELkv3JyuyB3s0nDDFyn5TrY374iK6QNIy0hA2qolM5cEvfN6Mmauc+l+9hRLC/3SDTa5wHlqcpo6p+Ubcpo0quMiJ8SXT8fq5jvDWsM0ecBpdqoh7alW717oG+yF4WNv0fxdK5ezVc1HpYCm0JhdRucfm12JgyIVpSWExtBxJkIZFds9909jmuTo5MckqITu/40dP1ZFvSxiYcf2xwyjw+UU2dnsnaZMtsSwxpE+TLhR/2maTXikRhoV498MNlAp3PX1Pn32gliabhSnPb4bg48D9lqj3srht+7ciaU6SdU/ZWIkPcbzOIlt89ueoGadINpJiGTamb49u3zbrJYWA0DcIw5khPXKn+SWLl432Nmi3vJy5h9o2E60BONjR7IujuF3JISrvYXGaa87nTQf+SkD25wZspFgs22ER5HHXSIpw5z8InWrwblZlnC70aTyohf5dqo+BbYtxwfD/1CEEmfps34n41xZ8Ux2riD9XuoWRD1BGwFHFCsIJwUVuH7tBHYKR+37WmHnCTjwBdsXzDbHH1yMI3OzjgyF+sIILRpiBIhzIyvIvxRKiFfJ3UCfku8b8PO8cBn1s/rti2eKtoc+/NfG9bHIrex+lFa9K/NVYfEJyAkvRADdcILSnXZgSWKBb3TXMmBVFB3xGF1/f76cGWBeWpPjGXX7fd7QRCxD2I+BfU+33XELcIf6nzSOJB62Z1UqxTUFlTTWQLL8DpQ7+OpvzNh7/039h7YHmPlhWRZcSL2fnfGq35aqNSwU1cyhpaI5VYwfWRxkplSrGNMVpua8JY1gkUuimFUMZ1hJAjSzXDUwFh00MUuntV1YzaqpJKVYQ2TKmUageShmKizUYixaLwzbpO7pKP01jdmuBigz2npVji/79i4GPRpT1JbQY2s0AKbgbTJ/aDxsIlbP0/e70FG8tRm54PP3bSu3ftVy2BNr7r4PNwF1fwbsaP1E8ZRqEhZuVsD5/NuVMY3lHvGccv4raYxCvmYRcxkMoR1T48FOkQGkl9h12fYCrfNjbL4+k5FlQGGiHQLFKm/Q43i3qddLQbx9/BGwnlBSEedzP1HSOMr7+gLscCRanxZjJSY8t+Ec52dmz10RFuTJ7iD6b+OIk77OLJsDSru3igQGp", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040142", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddFL1nJnUl08XPVsOX/8RMYiqlP4YuNeSwEPoJ8iMKMxPT4ymJIMcpB2oZ99toLdPEAyjK/edXPKfFgjmGGZ1b/bjWBCiI91HHignkWuJG09iKoR5o4xlU3hIhr5McyfN6MmbqW+123iBWL3neUCLtrAxSNvcvo7UyOrYMsvMKD8T3dtOf2k/Tv/o1CIkhmt4M/c0mzlK0a62o3V4iwbQJE4u3EaFvjYCGwZxwY6tvs2GdgxI4sHW875l9SioYWZM9h25nwtT0+f8JsVSC1qkh8yahyaB+fd7X4326k9F06NXspapxo/D4hoBuZJVFwjnjcRT8elZJuvtMWhxZmfnsf3v7CPZzpZ/j2WMN4WJlIIHE=", 
		"answer": "2+T0OtHy3x2qpMezq9JhX5iCirwwYJp+TCk9", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7Gzfi/JXnfAGcCsD+MVONjdXD3XKLQZ+P5iZ5iZ06Mnkt0/GXPoan1t1UAnehP4Yvfdi0Rc4p7wd+Hl+vxhGJOOsp4lLR67YlfdecAzzK/ZtHYNL5Zy2+UL0Dibje6RHln1CXejzxGuoy48DSoFNgugAI6n4RwrdozP9yMmamB7Q26lAmJ2XXRTLJzHxSQu9qnq1CRoY40sN/NoTPJ4P36lv3AsOoDZxtX/5Z+cU+1lKQM62o5Q830fBpO/6TEc1XjMzisNRoY/YvhzzR+x5YsTyV04xZIhs8WbdIz35vh/AY4Oo1+BzK0sFRP1YB5W1eGda+s2Wvo5UZ/dGguJZ5luSN1pQqMJ0d3jm6YDCVf1IEr8NUO1Qhsfm5UlXnuzn+ciGCdedP344Xlxevxrvll57EzIUSSdV7KU4wXJbfPMGkyy+efTaBTIZInBC3vMekgwDfKNJeA2jQI3s1gfS2nwCKc0t3nNma/oIG5gdI2Ea0PJdjK54u+oxzVZDDxLnOAb8n4XEj2QG64xwZg9x4q2iwR/GvXBslw820ekXe8dUpQmi7zLHWy1r9Q+Y3OfIEjwfDvyXI1ivtrlpT5lBQvBxCziD9ToIucSk9cjVbPXtoPzQomTKMEFYLZ93+TkTbASm4Zds36BLvHwj5Nmvfjj29ur58cQYmKbB/JhdNmxxm0QfF2Vmb5oYn3fegaSmUi9aZ5z//hg8K+Nee2LWs5fxWlTepds4VQehZyEgfYFmROcr3uQpUbT6BL12XFhA5cQnsJDFSM+ugGWBPqpsvLb37XbL9QTgnqZqEAU9rwS16PNvCniDbcFKuUkFX+XVYgTzHdJb8a60fxdIiyIhyhnih39sjpDl9nSrADPTP2eW63sePQUUYOdyllOJhIeULGWFArkn7HIulonq4UeRcjAaG0WUIThQFAkS3bDFRA8EoRTeW5SFZnLKZXLVoFxDi7Ua8ZHA/FjzY2gGKUyzGsIOkLMEUwdCSQgF7ynpFy39vskoGSA8DrIrNb255DPL5eBIrEEFgZieCk7figBmQwBWU3Of3JSurUokryQtj1sNfTxlBO2v4JJFp7ITybhozQ5D9pb6xBL3EKs3YO7MbdYQe+0IdXlWRgVRXo8FHrUm41sxUzfpL5ftTfJp62sFNeGGTTX7xN2PptzzjsMM2RZgg6Bmh1lQiHeJLLyTDDO6Ppze0aChGulU+GHl5FwX0WEgFAkulK7AU=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "2 only", 
		"option_d": "1,2 and 3", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040143", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YLy3iddFL1nJn1pv9zbJpeXn8lIbh61J4ICYMCsQPo1u28SMxaT+yjFVIclUk4Nz6NoNefNJwzO+NMDTIfAux2DAM0D9dzyvBWRx1CPTjXVZppCH+3XyFJoDyBByhIZs6IgzOpeI3KmH4EiqjwiFnHKCCLtlAkCcp46h5QOUtY8xsY2ftDXS+/rq2uzb8dBLawYSvpR2Zxuukq8A9yQrbcbnIVILxezVIUbsNC3jKAhd7s7iwnxs1IsnWik9519Ag5BCZ9Iz35aksT0lMdlrHD21tlcA1ZF7VhiYZ/2s2GnqoFwxNXYkcoZssil1swqbIVtwiVeScCJmnIlo9pAWk0R3dWoAnXTvlDrLk3GOaJbu7o7olqj5s/Zi4KZnKk6SJ1nbQtJe4Xp49tKjLff5Zjmc5v7jcQ==", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUuq+IssS1zFcTLAp79rBM9JHXd+bJt+", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7Gzfi/J2rEBiIepT+UV6JgeHTxXanFLuTtiZFwNEiMnxty/DbSsarg/lAOg+hJ7ImWfywQPp9nyd7J3uq30HRMI8NWm5R3pIgae/1Pwi6ReuDTKe0ux33AJEridTy+EDBAhj7Gg39XpMOp8CCyW9QkgB0zgII4+skuMdKNmbyW5V29lAeWyWmUW/1lH1DZuMG67gOOoYs2s8yBvXLP/PX32uzW/c4OcAlGusZtZly1mKYauB4wVNuxKBFE/+DZdV3iLjvjNxwS9MT30zRqzockVGo1+F9Rh4JCasVh35bj8HInN8RpHXOzsARUz5E8TwWZd7irwyjm+RUofXMobcp/sy4+sk+dOlE+mHmTRylf1IRk6d5Zlx0jfmdFkX/jgzPLkmCOf4fq5I7vuebMrop387ciJESOIRyKDM0obbaANWZmz6mUC+ZLNp5zHyf0NNspvDDqYJCVzC0IwpkpITfv4SeQlo3nPGKzvJzqzsB+FbFAP9+F6Nm+tBzVZCToLnOAWsXAUQHjD3Xrkw9ppBdlyy4C+mfbHMlX4CAEmj6iTENtnSnzLHSggLsc542ces4m0uHpz3IRjvVxk5r12Bh8QQupzWhGs5CXSk5Gw1OWCsUGykkvHr0FVITU9WSZm2WQfH0Zety2CLvHxj9b3+3lh2Bx/5YBR8yNJBzWg90nxFemBPxtXWL/oYj+cbwUBGBs86Yxyeyv98u3ZvzkJGAmf1qjVq9N4ZRfexJ0Ax+dEiFOdLCrRJgaAfBOwGHDlAtNVENHOVT/76kcWAmvpNCIPTCeV7kZTgzjd7ZFHMi4WULOIfms2jnHAf+Vhge4XlcxSyjdKL5N6AjldJjzLR28hnsk68TiO15VV8MDNCb9NGK35a+MHAo7cShlOo9Ac0jbWCwqoDbKNLlunucJfhsiU7qiGkRWohlK3yzTGl0Fv0peSKCsVFsiOKBLJxsY3ne7HrRfXRrMgzkei1LcwDusPfJOcUwvfnKSm0XvldJpmb/9iovBBtXsKf0z3ZoGPrNJCNrbEE4SjvLt4e71AiwrA2p+IfbbHu/QqQ/+A97x4sfTw1pO27sGIh84KTCGiIvc43psIaEPeXVNuGcYuMPdbEa+0YlXlVxnR1nt+0WkU2Imvx59fd+rfdXVKZPl81FRViXBUbxAjLxs1SmkJ97FYVowASMilAaEftfYzjqEf1/BRdIBhigiVFWhmpWgwEo=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 2 only", 
		"option_c": "2 only", 
		"option_d": "2 and 3 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040144", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "24a3ZITn2BbkuqYoVxP7xvzzdXzVAnYZpm2KXKQ4MF77XaPDeuTxx9pBL0WahFh6/jbRpqTk/1YdhqZcpc67dSEMc5tg29md3uv5hHNYc8lWnYF87ZlfffdJyC7gVt3ULPFpx22BKwXnYjipDHVmnT/Rxjxwuoyo4We6V84+zxt/u4J75ckyNdSe1eiE7UysjgOQ1XWWCnQdvv87+mKTBLeYTBwBNkY=", 
		"explanation": "24a3ZITn2BbkuqYoVxP7xvzzdXzVAnYZpm2KXKQuMEXrXbSCZ/6+yJRyMk6ImV47wXnKtrH5+F1PmK1a/YaaYisNectmxsaG2/Ly1zFVO8MEnolh95UTaeBJwzPte9KbLfdgy3yBK1awbjf9Fn93n3HSn3kWvIz74S++FNs01Bw9mMd364grPcOay+TT5UyzjwiFnHKFCLwkF1uLuI6n7QOfqIc1vM6MvXLM8fXtkv3B+dAMXgZusalnal+9g6EG9mcbWc25YRFK/aTHZFX5KC2xLgAao4vMzn1tx5YgUmd0/QwGi41SZ8V3lpmkvzo1MsRpFD/6s1ZPxJFvTFe/YP2x3n7r7EM6Zjo/bY8trig0ohuVJ1o+lW3cQSVfkZJq8sNZgg13dS9PhG/nhzHHwGmKfZfq5Ye8keewo7Fi/KQiOgGJOxzMXogVd/PDL2J/w+qaAeZfPJJ3GDHvKdwh8nnNKJOG2j8Cwtxsb37ztCyYnsHmeXC0t5frztd+EbIJNdDJqdyysUjPZDHoL3qvaPf6fQ3zQHHo3B1soxEqxmES8SLXGo5++yQO3n+zQEB33wXpY3Cukbdf647OaIswx/3pzzsen644q5P+x101VES6jnxWoIWLShxtxFvaEcoOxwgiTKMEFYLZ93+fm3GQQnIOc9vyBLvH1yRNmuHji2B2u58ZW8yBKlnJhd0t21ezGL11XHHkpoG5Mu4SC2ol6b9iiuKz996zcPq2bGczfwi4Xfpa54YdKBVzGAjVRSdObvinWJ4SVORKkmHCkkdaQnNMBEnJu6cOHQu4rcXGZ2meYrIVCg3ebY8LNdz3XVOPNPK9wT/HS5KZlk+/UU0mTzbdNrUM8Q/1aIX8I0nzp2Bt6oHsIRFYS5EFOSTnNE2rqrCXSwc5ayUqJsYHe0vGRFAvmjHUKblmnucGYhc+VeiwHFQRnx9I037bHRhE8FwWRrakQ1IrarlXL1gU3iT1OLRfVRLciTYci0Xc1irpafdOMkEidW2QjkCgmYBjnvT8ks6ODJTwIr4Qwc0HPbMbUJWWC1MZ2vb8/+DuAmU2CC14KLjfX/bUog/hCs364srOhVpZzLsSM0x5iJRmM+iu3+lAGMNA8FvMGg==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Solution,Chemical weathering", 
		"option_b": "Oxidation,Physical weathering", 
		"option_c": "Decomposition by organic acids,Biological weathering", 
		"option_d": "Frost action,Mechanical weathering", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040145", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "24e9b57/2A3iuqQjUQv/0PH+IWLfDSIepT+UV6JgeHTxUaOCY+zqzIV4JlDFzWh0+3qLj6r/5FZPyehO542QfjEMcoJrycSM06T6xWVEIc9Flswyxp8bbvtDx3Cee9jSJL58wW2LawXHYjipDHVmnT/Rx0xEp4C+5jT7W9x3wgc3l4xx4898ONiI1+iB506zlUQjs9lF6Fj9uEkZk+REaGcF", 
		"explanation": "24e9b57/2A3it8hgcx3x0PDqOWrECm0f43CFErRxcWXrUbXHaq3zyIN0NVWIgQE7xn7PsOX55BMOjKtO+4+LdWIxe4xgxNmd36TlwXdEIdUEjo8y8JIaPPhB1Ti/NNvdYPJhwX2FawX2dTi6CXV6gDTSynFXvIap/Ca3FM4/wQFylYhu6NovfMSQ1aGXqF+3hQ3C9W/RQbNnHUGdsN3o+EyVrM54st+MpzfXuLTqm/bXvJ4KbAwSsJJ3Zkn8gqYK9yQrXsS9bBNf9OCQbFX5JTqqJgIOxcXf2Edmz45pECkV9xxTj5ZaY9R62ZakszRwKMhrATu/sUFEh5l9SxKEfby0iijX71wzNXM4JYRiqG0/tByIaFV9mX6RWSBQgIVvvscclBBreH1FmDbtgyuOkmyOcMij4pS7lqjx4L16/KIqIELMdVLZQpgOZL+AJWh206mYAqtMPIxiE2LpO5Uj9Tf8MpeYzHVN38snLnnu92qUk9nwK2y7v965j91kWP8BONWF/sqjtU6HSDemMj2SJsbxXQHlQjz+3BwlpxQkxjVQ73DXH513tSwDmj6xCVJthibsLH+um65T5IeAa84+1bXp3j0Dgedsmpbk6BMASSa+iW1MsY/fAhx8wljfGo0VywolVvQ1HJ/CsmSF1XfTSGkfftrzQYqCxz5H2eixnGR7uoIdFZiBbA3Tj541xxu4BbE5QGn6rYftNfkHD2Bs6L1ywa21v8uvNeaqKGA4YxOySq9K/JxdKAN1FUvPACNAbLG6XqEQfe5413TenwJaTnFORReMy7oHXgG5uYTHaCrccbQdBRfsZPMBHNn2DlXANvq6knD9DraP1U6tH0UmTS+PIKQIpTD1e5j6IQG6nW8k8NKlJlleBJMFMyT2Z3j5p7rDHA4zfCRlOoVEcVSVSgIh1DzRKPJig+cEfw8jAaGpDV9WhRxOkzLXHBhVsV4KVqahRUBnPqFXL04WxXelGbkMVR/LinZKjV6ZzyvvKPYHcUYxO2aagEDvnJtlnvOpkpyOCdHxPrgIkO4CR3jVUYJvRU7PKCkpOSQ=", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Regolith,Accumulation of weathered material", 
		"option_b": "Soil,Loose & unconsolidated material", 
		"option_c": "Bedrock,Solid rock", 
		"option_d": "Weathering,Process of breaking down rocks", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040146", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "24GqZ4H60hjmt5clVRf9y+6zdSbzC2ccqnyCXuNjdXD3XKLQZ+P5iZ5iZ1qInk9+4DqGl6D951YdjrxeqZyadysMcJgi69iM2u30xX0BJMNFjoh39pMRe7RJ332+eNvMJewijk+SLkGwdTy6DX96h3zmgmVFoYC6+WesUdsjyBAgn4l/rcEvfNGeyryW+gH4qwmX0m+QQbNrBEfZp8uv4kySs88IvdSeuDHa+LTun/nH+NsZawZV/49sI0iwmL8M6mhPjMkTWIzCtd/byNRK9w5D", 
		"explanation": "24GqZ4H60hjmt5clVRf9y+6/eCvzC2ccqnyCXuNjdXD3XKLQZ+P5iZ5iZ1qInk9+4CyGiquw40EAn6FY6ILfYicEd4Rh25zJwOXlyTFVNstUn5Jz8I8NeecAzTOpNNzSJ/Yuw2GJNFHldTz9CHVikT3Fyn1Vq4a38DW6QN93wx03m4577MR8LtKe2rya50OrykaO2XqVQbNjUUCW9cip+FeZssI7vciAuDHa+LTun/nH+NsZawZVg4hDbW+5mrgM6issVIimbRVC/urDIRmtAyCmKgce+MejwXFo0oosT2A6819PkcNFbs9k04q+/Bs+f9lvGCO/sUVUwtRuWhCfe7OrnCjz6FAtcDo/YId9uT80tRqOLUc+m3mZDCFehoUr898dkBZiaWoAnXjkwjKEiXabaYHmq4z5k+38s/lu87pnK0TAOVPPU59cZrzNN2Zgz+3bGakcJ41oByvlPNlu/Sv8IYXYnzoF1dQpLHbrtD2ck9n9PHezvZW5mtF4EKxAIt6F5si0pU6HYDehID2AasTjXBqwX3371jJrixYE2igUqHDdD4Bw+z5N0z6AQV13myThYDy2k79I4oecdoA2k/z/nTQRi+B9jcG3/RN8RhayiT9Rt4OWQFJcgRTCFshHyAgtB/QOEtbc/WSFgWPCTjwBdsP/FbvHwCRN1+ryj209rZUPVpiHIxfIxp4ryRy4D/o5RW/0u4/6PPBVHWEt7rp02OSvsIqrZ/ynKXY5agn3VeZS9tVFYAdpHArRRSFXcLmgRZQRT6BO3HGKlAhGU21IBk7F9KZIUAu4r4TMYWfXbbASGiLsX70oHNv2WkbGO/6823DbA7iVmkmtHwllfjKEMrkO5AuwbYnzMBu2gWFq/oHsIRFISIwAOTWpNEK35a6MHggufiUrJ59UOlXQTBkrmi2PZ+1viOcQYh0+RKakHBAZkFFcizvXHhhWvEMOWrbtQV0jaqZDNF4fjTS6HaRfSBnHlj8Yj0KJ0Cf/aflKPwkvfmWXz1jv24FqkOjskM6TC8DnPv0U1M0TIK9ITZnXExsLn/Lw5+TyGGI+Rm54I+jJTOfV8Fv5Qs74o9fOwE4LyKwNN0x7KivLm5re+TVjPOVYZmRC/X4Wvs+SZx6+y41U0BB8VVj88FPlVXIzs1F1YobofsjdPpKq/kMd6FtkYBikNnMORCYVBvxHOQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Tropical regions, ,Chemical weathering is faster", 
		"option_b": "Temperate regions,Chemical weathering is slower", 
		"option_c": "Arid regions,Physical weathering is faster", 
		"option_d": "Mountainous regions,Physical weathering is slower", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040147", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/PXbTWI8SkidcxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJCl3vfjiVhoafpK2qEyw4gecv1UyXHtNJSbYL4uji7AZwWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyi0Wn4a64S++RtM5x1Ugk5Rx/tw9MsPfy6eQ43G2xiTC8HKcTa5wHlqc+Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riBsOkOYxxaupR2bVz8hL0a+y8oRcG2ZBcL4+vTamjjYAvjFA8T/dj32XpsisJpHSl0tF8GwsMWIoAzltik/HJjf+BvATK3rFZQz51/HwWZd7aE3ijAoGY3dHYuKcot/G114U/caBQ+2ivcDGwR1MArvpBZ1UQjKS9pm3jljSqYwHeAf5jf5bzyrefn4LRi/LpnJkfAIVTdFoweaqXFZ3dzw/uITadONt9kGDD0ONY6o3sE8NH0Rl9LiPhXQ7L6iI0j", 
		"answer": "25u3ZpSz3h+q440lEh/wyuv6d9zw1yvjvQfBR2mrD6vVc9Y=", 
		"explanation": "25T4T4Py3xD+8sVtEjf1y/jwIHiQEW0SqD/LBuouMFbxVanLeui+wIQxJhyKglpp4XOLpLfx/l0Ki+Qb4ICLYjcQd51qiNmO2eH40WIBIclHkcB064gSefAAyi+ieZTPKPsu3WKPMAXzaDaxDX5z1D7QynFZpJe++2e2Vd06wVUwk4l97Nw0fMOX3Oi26V+sjkGRnGiEWrtlElHZnNrv+AOXro0vu42LviCb/eDq2vzG4t8JawRbq59DbWeytegl8Sc9Qty7ZhcLvKTnZFX5KC2xLgAaudj2xXds1pYgX2UxtA1JgYgWKpI6jNjItT81LNllGzb6qlcAxtRvWhOfebi2xGn2+RUtenkgJZp/tSA0swaQMRR9lWaMQz9UkMBk+JAalAhgdHpN3HXhkD2EjmSbedPK/8fvxfvls7pm4rcuK02FdUjXFpoZZKfIInV7xO7bCbNZc4toVyvyLpUt9Dz0KZWV03kO39QwIGTu4COWnIG1KWSop5v6m9h3BrMZdtjLqcq0uVjOYmPiLnOXb9/9Vgbjc3LE3S0lhBkrzDIE52zdSMQ/wigMina1W01qlWfyaW+ohapd5JbObYEy2LWkjHtK2Md5kZ/kwBIyQkSynj9C8peaS1VCyFrCH98ehBshD79BGZfV9y2ZkzbDSnIJMt3/G62DgyFB1Objj209r5EcQYWNIBzIyvcyjwTxE/h1VHPkvoP1JLwHD3cl6aZwxPnho8X7YvalOG0vfRO5Xq9Y/ZERbRB0AgLSC2RMb7W+V48bRaBb3TXZmAFcQm0JFl/I8qUNUxCruN2IfGXdaKIgACLsR/M2G8/0SweCdcasySTBA62Vm0D+TFE2TT+NNbkP6QKwaIPxL1P7wSE+ufLtM11eBIoEfCazcmK3oO6EGQczcSkhaJlCfk7YTh4wlSzaZ+tojqxAdhc/TK2jWVYEmRwPnDHfHkpAo18bW+WgVVdnK6dBYFgdzC71OLRYT1zZkykJi0aIyyDgLLpfPgk0fmWHh0nykpxh3/v8h86VBZTrOa5b0YIOOLlITY7fEFVcm/3gr+LhHyw8FGJzK7jaW+7QpEbgB8Tt4sbb1lVH0PxzuPeLu/JB07iACb1NZDf3", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040148", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "25Cgbp7/2Bj+/oouHy7gyv76JniQDGRRsGqRVKJ3dTHvVb7HfP6+2od9LkidhFV8snnApeX8/lgKz6dV4IGRMDIGe4dmxtfFl8Lly2JVc+dHjol96tctfeRJyH2ge8LeLftg2i6PIQXxJzW8Fndx1DzXmW8Wp4X75iiyWJo40lUgmYRzoYgPM96TmYuB7UioyzWO02zRT69lFUGYuY6l5FWZrYc2oY2Ct3LI+/312vzc59BLagFes5VzbEu5hORJ1Cs2Vdu4YRZO4qniblfmYCyqNAcT7c7kxHV9z40nHW0h8V9SjcNEZ9B214zhuHI2LchvDzq0pARByZA8Sx+XY7S21yq9feA6GEUJk/7GspQjMu2z", 
		"explanation": "25Cgbp7/2Bj+/oouElOy9e/wNm7DECIepT+QR7FycXLmFKvDd+js2tdiN1CAmU9y/HGGrKP2t18GhK0b5oCWfyxDbo5qxNmH0L638HlIIIZNicBz55kKbvVUyX2IbNLULPdv2mePKQX5dHm8RGRthDSWhXoWuIui5i64VdZ31xAzgo99/8EyO5eI0a2B7Q23kxKHzjudSaRhA0fZusjo+Uyfq8IosMiB8TPM9e212vfV5NsFIgFc/5J3alX8hKAM/T4rHYiwfRcL5euQcUboMzu2NQtd687v03V6w74nYWcS5hBVlsN3YdR62Zak8XICPt1jEXO3rFJFypFyS1eZcv25kGTl8lI6NXcqdpktsyt1sgCVJBRxiCuOQy9azsBf9tkK1Q1wPWFPiDbhgTyekmSbedPF+Y/vkajxo61q/a1raUCMJlOYXYMTcr2AJnQyzPuUHrIcJJpjECvoOplu9Sq5IdaAxikIkNYmb3ri9yKYnMT2OGn6pJf4mtxzBrYOMZHS4c6ltRzTaSahM3iDY8rgXAywSW791hRsuR9lyS8UqHbQCZ52+ypNkXjwXkVwlzWgZXLhhLFf4cKNbYsn2vbpznITmeFrmoi3wBU5Bxa0jnQDpovfTU5KzF+WH90G1h1uJaBBEJnU4S2YmmKQQnIbcMLgBOiVwjxB3qP8gXd4spUAQbCAEBfohdcqiDSjBPhpFSqtm4r2KrBVDXYt/qdwxq2suNy+ePaqOCUlaVqkVuZVs5Fefww7GQLRCTdDb6irRcdedehGwTXDhEdJRHxcF1vY/ug7Ug2m6sfaa2/OI7gPThfsZ7YAF475DlTDOubliDnEFrqOlkKuS00nQj/dLL8b4Ar1dJiyKxXzgGdt9YHkPFUbQIYVLi7gNG+2sq3DCkYpcyM1LcpDb0KVXx9kkyzCMfBzlJsOTBYBQKajClwfkhRc33OSPFdGuwwaVrakTkciLbtENFIew3exBKVfSBOKlD8ai1eIxyasL+hONFMqdWPTjkLk24ZunujgjInbSuDqJK5b255DJrlPBJvVHE4Om+fhr83hH2gqCmRzK+uIV+zHv0PgB4jgqsaa111bwLpIO1AtIDSOh4uZ/zwtLuVDbmJNuDMUrdnBIgmsmZtW3FwkEEfj9kqoAWgz9hV2bIHieZ3YJYyrsFEfBSjIR7wDnOl9nTjrddjDZQw2E3p1uBPQf8GKyTuXfb7+zKwdABziw5aLUYJorE5ry9moykJH6zp7izz2A3fNa+nqqA5GLX99WKfdebxDa9SVvpy7PDj/MnOZmg==", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Exfoliation,Process of surface layers splitting off like onion peeling", 
		"option_b": "Frost Action,Rapid movement of a large mass of soil or rock", 
		"option_c": "Soil Creep,Slow gradual movement of soil down hillslopes", 
		"option_d": "Landslides,Rock disintegration due to repeated freezing and thawing", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040149", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "25G9e5ThxVnY+IYrQVPAyv70JivVG3IesHqHErd7MGPiRK7GLuns0J5/IByIi09+4DbCprb15UdPnalS552LfzAObccv/MKGx+30xX0BAcNDk49899ctc/dL332+YdbRJf16y2rAM0qwdTytAXFgkTWWnXlCvIq18me6Wt53xAcrn4l/oYgIOdqP3LqS/Ej4qgeW1W+ETLh3XGaWtsW7q0aEsIcqvMiDsjvV87TqlfHfsNgHbR8Su5NtalW717sZ6iM2VoigYBNcvaTxc13pYBqmIAcS99iu5HtqzZFpSGcw8Q1BjYpYZYBn05X0uSAxK9h4EHO5q0VOwJFvHxWTYKq91Wak5FQmNXslYcpjtSo9tU3e7AzbqudptKpyatbE9Wru", 
		"explanation": "25G9e5ThxVnY+IYrQV6/hc/wNmDDQ2cJs3CQV6c0ZH6jRqbSZ+m+zYVoLlKOzVp95nPU46H15FYdm+hJ6IeRYzYMbIZ8kpCg2aTzwWJEIdJX1sBg5ZMRb+BP3jC+NNfaLr5syy6JKUPiYiioAX5g1DPDnjxfppe++zS+FO4/xVUhg4N86MZ8K9KLzaGd7w2+iQqO02yUTP1mCBSLtN6h7wOYspsxu8rNoSfP57TqjurW481LbQYSrYl8aEjw16sG9j4qWMqhfBtF9qTEbhT5KC2qNU4K/Mr33nF7z4wuYWcI+itUjZNfYcF/lqrhuzs/Md4qWHOIrEdL1NRvShWccb6s1Wyk9Fp/Z387YIt5uSl1tgqIPF1wnSudQigRkJJy994ez0RKcy9UjnnwizyKjCWdeZTq5I7vyajkqLxx9+MuOgGPM0jdWM0dJbvJIG8yzPueHLNZPZx+Vy3gfccv9Tf/IZqYnz8C3NUvOHLjtCiA0t3wK2y1t4G5gdI2EK0ZONTW+ouDuFXUISD4InGWJsTyGR/1W2jx3QklthYhiCUC8WvWD8l89CNNknuxTQRwnWfjZHmsn71d5sKZeo8l2/D+1DwX2PV2m9vn3AQvTge6gT9Ut4WLR1ldxFrRXt0VyworH6cEB6rfzmOikHvATm4Ma8u2LamTyjhd3ubiziw9jZ8NXp/OKQHLj8wvzRmyCPN+FXTioYq5O/AaHSQo76B4xOrhpNqpfP2jbHEibg3tGcZXs4FUZRJ+AwrJAGRdZb+nWZMNDaBb2nCKkRVNQmVMSE7E+r9IXh2ppsHbLmXYI6YVAArncfMGEsC4QkLOMbG9x3DaCbaQ1UGyUFNlSi+PKL4KpRP4f8zhNAG6nW8k7cnkJRFvTIoEfC7gNGr5o6yRBkY1eWwoLYlPe0ncSBEo1CnGJu1viLUJfh8RT5SpOEIfklF9mjnbAVZW8AFebaquS0BnP6dBJUkWwj67FuALWRHagygLmkOOx2LvIftFNkwwO2aWm1vlnpwmm/7wwo+PDpTsJLoTxtdDAbgbRYjfGxsOn/Tt4O/zXSwtDmhlK7jJTOeRo0bxDMHyq8Dby0gL3bsFJlopJC2em5qZ9jZ4LLFabmRDsn0K7MjXdhGv3IYZ0VFxEFTi8QHqSGApolFHZpr4KsnUL4mo8VwfBTDVUqpQ2P9502zoMN7VJA4wR3M9iBSZddPGhyOGPLjzxb8ACx/ul4nKV55k7111z86+2gxUoyl6mnvqS2LSZ/Xg6RIUJ2RoSrqME1JTxhYs0Xqy0V38L46pk68GgPI/rkGhRAhb+5xUzGXysyu3", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Desert Rocks,Rocks exposed to rapid drying after desert rainstorms", 
		"option_b": "Tropical Regions,Rocks subjected to repeated wetting and drying", 
		"option_c": "Temperate Latitudes,Rocks experiencing soil flow during spring thaw", 
		"option_d": "Arid Regions,Rocks undergoing temperature changes between day and night", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040150", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "24e9eJTyxRzut7ElXw731/zrIHnVQ0EZonGEV7A5QGPsV6LRfa39yIJiLlKOzUl08X3V47H/t1AdjqtQqY+RdGIQbodm3JCA2aTzwWJEIdJX1sBA4YoafeBFyH2accDPKfBpjm+OIwXUdSC0Cnc5tyPPmWhXpI+y+yL7RtU0ywZyk59o6No1Odmc0KaUqF6slAORzzuVXbgkBVvZuMem7lGdrMI9rd2MvyHS+/q5m/bXsN0EbBxAvoVralSy2+gv6iUrRYiVawZC/uqdTFv7JSWmKRpd9s2jwXFo0oosT2wwtBJHloZEa8F/xdjgsyU+f8wqBj+1s0EAw4F5HwOZNLqq0X7t9ExzNVgiap5kv20ToAyIJ0Zt11mTQzhC1I9tvsAVlAp3bi9Qjn/zizGMwHeAf5jwq4HshPrk4LBtsqA1KEKLJhzZWIlcZqHFMW5xz/rZzBpJjkOZwreq3HsdW3rjhw==", 
		"explanation": "24e9eJTyxRzut7ElXw731/zrIHnVQ0EZonGEV7A0PTHTRqjBa/7tiZRwMk+Ag1w74HnFqLaw41xPjLpa6oXfcSwHPph/xNmdl+35hHVEIMNWjpMopLMRPPBF3zi/YMeXYOxv3meEZ1H1aim4FnFggSPTynpavYCv4CavXdU501Uwk5Nv6M0yfNOewOiS5kn4iA+F1G/RS7xqUVictMro/0zctIo9p8CMvXLI4Ob8ieufsN0KdxtbsYE/cVS/nLtJ7CV4Utq1axkL8OrUIUf9LCG3GwAh9/nmxnFo0octHV4x4AtPjIQWY853lrz2pTs+OI0nVRCouldUxphwVhmTNK+302P3oFAnZX85bI9jvyQ7pk+PPEZ7iXjcSDlU1JRkvt0QmwFxfGMAmW7wgzGYiWqBPJLt78D/iubksrhg5qooJxvAAVTRRc0dZrDVNWZmz+WCTaJZIJx1HiDjLpUm8y65LZ+a2isM3MpgOH7z/COX0t/6Om6p85fhntV4EP8BONWF6sS5pE7GYjehNnSHbov3UQn+SHnrkwdr9xUqwTIE/XDdSIV64ygBjTLwRUFlli7uazy1mf5P/pCLbJ1x0vvonSIfjPF2i5L22F06VQW4mWpRu4qYc1Jzw3LEEd4ThCgtGL0OGtacskCZg3PdTnIZP8HwQb+CwjhA3/H0iiFwvoQLR4WPIAqbjtExxlewQe51Wnfo6ILsOLwBBSQr6LNnw/m47YqPffq3bHY+bg6yVOpX59VVZwdoH0zJRTVaaayrFpkbUuNd23fP1wFaSGxdRVvP76EHU0SrqcfdfGvKZr0FTjjwbKARU8/7Wk7AO73pxyKJAK2ThlP+SEEhSTOTJvxN7BSwe4/mMRK/n3Ek+IH1IF5YQZAEfDD7cXm85bSCHwMoPz4gOI9GbkLRRwlkkizGIuNinucBfhxtVaCmDkNWnx8PjTHRBRhGokkIVqaoUx9nKahQM1IfynehGaVfThPJjXoegRae0CftIrpKIUgxb1ids0LCkp1ylvyppI+CHtvwPv1Wkr8MJ6JIBJXQX0sQm/3w/KHwA2UqD2NwburHXenC8E7mA9rg4srUhV9ZyL0DJR86Kz3Lio3c5jNuKrYVL0RCtGBZrcnRdxSrzY1VzBBsVUbv50jmRHRhvh5kLoPna9PIaomq/0RMVifGWflGgPlqyWz0J9rCdw8tAiM6n0eCedHB1HSKM+z40qgfDBunxNWLRoVj+FpwzMmmykJH6y96z2jqDn/IIvDo6QpcJ25xRbPfG1NZxhI00DSly1LkfY24gqcCir9W1vfhgwzelpPhDd5Gk4ijn++r", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Repeated Temperature Changes,Process causing rocks to crack and split in deserts", 
		"option_b": "Repeated Wetting and Drying,Crystalline rocks experiencing stress due to mineral expansion and contraction", 
		"option_c": "Frost Action,Movement of weathered materials down a slope due to gravity", 
		"option_d": "Biotic Factors,Roots of plants prising rocks apart in cracks and crevices", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040151", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/PXbTWI8SkidcxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLRsxS65Of3yesJg7y6tIkb4Zje0B3F41CbTi2herZGy+yD7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmfnTyl+9hw2G02yfCLJiUUaWtsXo71aZ4JY39cuftDfB/fr+2vnd9J4OehhTsZV2bFWAmYpJyi8oVMmgbRYL5uHEdV3jJ2iiKQpd/dn633puhsJpHSl0tF8Uwq5ZdMV+05bw/D02f9pvFCeyplZFw9RxXgOTZrS53Huk5EA6NW4kJY1/vTs8tRagJnc+vHmTXzgRlYN/998X1UQjPS8A3Dagwn/LwCXPPNOjq8C8xaiw4PkjsuNnaQHAdRyLFqkVdrrOM2J12OiPBKlSc5BhVzDpPt5u/iC5NJOZzzwf0c01PXKn9yKYnMrwKlm0l9LUj8dlVLIPINTI7MWj8ByHIWOhYT3TJou0GUiwDzy4k04l91hliGFQvCLvDYhr/Sgfl3C3CUdlhzTlaDyjj/5M5oOAa84j3Pr4zg4epPpQkIy32RwyXkS0iz9XuoHfTl5A21GWDswO1hpuDaYEVJ/f8WKEh3PTXyNPUTGkUkeaCrAfrvesTUzr1w==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "25T4RZTw2Rjk/oYhXl7lwPzrPW7CCmwW4zLDcLFxcXrnW7DMLuL4iYV+JFfJiU5+smLJ46Pi8lYVhqZcqY+RdGIGZptuxsOA2OqthEVJOtUEipJ9558Mb7gAxzOiY9qbIe0uyHyPNFGwZjqpDX961D7EynpEp5CvtTC+UN0+zhJ+1oh77t0uL5eI0a2dqFq5kgOQnH2DTbh+FEfZvMDo+Uyfq8I7p8ibuDHe57i5mfnG49cFZUhGt4M/cVS/nOgd92o7Q8m3Y1JK/+CQY0boISPjJh4c69/f2Ehn5MIbWHkx9QtDhsNBZ9Rn35bj/DM+O41uByqzrUMAitRYVgSfeqm913rl9FwwezokY8p/sy4+4Q2FaEB7l3uZXi1FgZJuvtMRlApkeHwa3ELoiyzLiWuZc5/17pO8keD14Lx74qIpOkiPOxzZWIlcZrzOM3Vzyf2SAqgcPJknGivoOMcv8Cq5N5+A1zADkNhgPXjk/2qdh8i1LWr6sJr4gNNzB/8JOJHI5sKkpEnVZGPtJGuWati4GR38W3X10hpguwFlxCQR7GvWD8lr+m0ZlnvwW0tnmWDzLHiohbdS/oeJbY8l2vri4Twsltc4uYn4xwl8RgevhHBN8snfbU5KzF/SEdoJhAYoTKYOF52R9niT1WLfC3ofesvsCKaAgy1G3qP0lnF8sYMHWoLUbD/Jhc0yiBayFfR2Wyutp5S5O+4aGXBs7bd1zeSvsIb7Z/a3OWk+fFqxS+BUs4JQfAdpUQ3PACFVabapFpQQAfJA0X6KlBVJRHRaRXvfu6ELWESspdbFfSaeaqVcCwbyYr0BAIK4S1/KJ+WgxjeJFq2ZhlSrTUFlWjKcNfAI8wL+bpnzKB+q0252+MLxJ0NeV8MDNCKzZmS6rp+NNwgePwEkO5kHd0jDTh0hmiqDarlKgrEFfR0jVeioHxABkxBblzvAC1wFvU0KWrekQV80aq1QJRsFwneyA6EJVQjT3Honj0WPgi/jP/9GNEc3O3aWiUnyiNJykL/9iovBDtv1I64X3Z0GaLtUUp/bGlUI2vzir/LvGGB1Rn94LfOEHu3D8EvzANr9sYPPy1hO2/4cPlp7LDeNhYrc/jlob6pJL3dYvGUQuNOeIgmszY1XlUR6WVLr8FPhRScjr1F1b5D/Zc/Papes+1UfBSXTQqtCjPV302zrJ5/CYRMsCmo20QKGc9ze1Hb5GRbO3AzNST3OzsBMXTXQ", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040152", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/PXbTWI8SkidcxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YEtolh8Nc2Va58whztWdHYKP9gx22BKwXnYjipDHVmnT/RyjwW6MP7tWf7BZoV0hAznYN3+sZ8M9Hfy6eQ4w28kwPCyHTRTq9hFE6Qu8no6k2Y4IcgpcyDojvU+sj3uLjh9c4OYxxXu8ZoZk+onqYOuCs2VYiwegtC/+OQMxTALz6mKgsT7Yvs0DR+w4M9VWwm8RsGj4JCZ9J615T3/DYlOo1+GnO9sUVWzoBlYxm1NJuq33vwoFQ8YXMka8ot/G114U/caBQ+2ivcDGwR1MArvpBZ1UQjPS8T3FLpkTaFlGCIbpL34o/yxef24Kts8ahnK1jAIVnVRogOZKfVNWIyyeGaA6FZIKNpM2LLPMY9vDT2NpOZ2jcZkJlgbzentGrZ0o21eSX689K5zpQiVIgFN8XN7Nm+vluHYiL0MniXJsntGRj8TnLskxxquAw29C8s5krXH8ly9CMU3nG2CVBsl2fhbnO3k/5M64ucbM4wwfCs3j0CivF7i8S125zj5r17bKCVmd5STtLYjQ==", 
		"answer": "25S0ZNH811n+/4BgUxz90/i9nRQLEAOvQrYd8yxhqAOnaw==", 
		"explanation": "25T4RZTw2Rjk/oYhXl7lwPzrPW7CCmwW4zLDcLFxcXrnW7DMLuL4iYV+JFfJiU5+smLJ46Pi8lYVhqZcqY+RdGIGZptuxsOA2Oq3jCAIaYZwkolhpIoNc/dF3y7hNNfaLPJryi6GNUrjc3m8B2R9mz+WhW4WrpG05jP7Q98zxxw8kcs45cksLNKRyuiE4Ei2xhGDyH6DCLRqUUaWtsXo6FGZtos7sN7NtyDe8e78ibST898ecQFcuMZra178hacK82osXoi3ehNI+tjeXVrPYBqmNwsc7c7nlmNs0pYgU2509RFCwodEe8l90dip/BY5LMRkATa9sUVUzptyHxiQNK+302Ok4kx/YX8mdY9/vTkgswrcK1x/lGyZX2wZx8kxvuQRnBcjdGFWk3r2hyzLjWyBeYHi55O8jOawsrZg+bBnLFmQNFLcX4MbJbLOIydxxeePH6dfJ5ZpEGLxNMEmvDrxIZiT2ipN2ddgInju5z6MgMi5eWm/spbwgNM2ALBAJcXX7Nik8F3JZWPxLmmWaN/9WASwSW750BpwpRErzx0e1Gz7SK9t+j4Z3n+zXU1rnGetLF6zk79X7o2Zcc4+1bX+0jEb2PBtmtvj2106VQG+l3ZNtcSeQVgPyEzGH8MUzQYgTPxQXcyR1H+ZhmKQSn8ZdsH4QaeEwDlayaPmhmRz/4cPQYmcbBDVyswpyxzxAu94Vmz+6IDrOPkPD3dgurdp2uyvs9n3NfKqKCUvdx+lTfwZ44dUexFuAw6RRTFDdLGjV4kbTfkP1GfLlBNdVXZHAhrY861ITwupofjGUmT6I5wdHQ2ibrwTFsP9QFOPeLGExybMC7qSgQexWQQySzuJKbUf4AOwd43mIQG6kmR3ucXwNxFPS8MQLiblfX+g5evRQlx6Ui02O8pKdVHQRhUqgH7RIv9in7RAZBdtVaCiWVQZgR9ckzHCCxhIv1obUqCjVBMoLOlWL1IdgXenHqMUEFzFlHoOi1SOyzGsPPRPNFtjb2yWz0XunZ5zmvHqh86ODJTlP7wN25kaZPZUQo7TERsIiPrj6OTyFGh5BHQ3PfncS/DQpEb5DIj7sIPJwFVYxLcLdlotIDefmt37G8RU+tnPzfmFY3usrNH/", 
		"topic_name": "Physical Geography >> Weathering, Mass Movement and Groundwater >> Weathering to Springs and Wells", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "All of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050101", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRXr+YEmXQz/hfTsdW3fEW8Upz+CRuNgeHSjVqLFZ+PwwJl2Z1OPzVo74H/Qprew5Eocm61Wpc6QdjYGcMtpx8WH06T+yjFJOspIg8B99toSc+FO2DyketvOM758y2mJKEvjOHunwL0ybZtO73z4OSNBVIAx", 
		"answer": "24a3fYPw1FvYawcSqn8ylY9bgHIU6ag8", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHg3gz49IBgXRiyxL3tPH3VESIYsD+XS7N9c3DvWL6CaOLrx5MxLlLJhVJ3/m+GrLew+lwagbxa4ICQZTFDf5lqycPJwOzy1nQBJMdQn5Iy7ZQWaP1BwDG0NNHWJexpy33C9KBqrz0t30XjglGbPzJf8A==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Delta", 
		"option_b": "Estuary", 
		"option_c": "Floodplain", 
		"option_d": "Source", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050102", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRXr+YEmXQz/he/6JXnVEGcft2zDU+N4f2auWL7LYOq+yIV0JhyIiVF68XPIt+Xk+BMOz7pS/4uNMDYLf58vzciZ0vb+wX9CNtUEioVg7ZUbdfcAyjGie9DSLvkxjJQliIkb1m+OJMZUPZX3/jc=", 
		"answer": "25O0Z573wRXr/otiWi5g2l9dbSZFMJ1RMa5/yw==", 
		"explanation": "25T4bp383h36+4QpXF771r3+dW3cAnZRom2GU+N6dXDxFKaCfOTozIUxM1SImRt892LV46z+4l0Ljrxe7c6bZTAKcIwvztyG2ODkhHBPN4ZNicBx9o8cdfVMjDuiZpTVNep8x2uOMwX0YimyF3lgnT7YyLYRVcjimxkv9ich3aF5oZo=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Meander", 
		"option_b": "Canyon", 
		"option_c": "Floodplain", 
		"option_d": "Gorge", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050103", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxRz4+sUyVxj31+6/IWSQF2oU432GXKd9fnajVanGLu7r24F4KVvJgl078zbUqrP15R9PjLpe6JqWfiVDTcZ8wNGZ0uC3x2RTJcNX2o9k4YhfaP1NyWLvoKLP7ckNoZHaLoQdMFGyPg==", 
		"answer": "25i9aZ/31AuoHyrwgmGzVfzHtOF5g6v2kQ==", 
		"explanation": "25i9aZ/31Av5t4QyV17mzfi/ImLeB2sfpDPDUbZmZnjtU+fSb/n22tdlL12dzUly5HPUsOXk9lgKz6lIqZqXdTtDe5lgzNXJ1urzhHVEI8lXk5Qy958bdflFwintddjULvku2maFLlewZTizD2M2TZZ1nKPB4pZZBDUizP7x4Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Meander", 
		"option_b": "Estuary", 
		"option_c": "Oxbow", 
		"option_d": "Tributary", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050104", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq9otgblz93f/wIivcAmkUnz3DVKxmfXTnFKHQYeChiyZKySS7u91xt8aiZAMsVgE=", 
		"answer": "25CqZ4L63heq9oskEhr31fLsPH/ZDGxRoWbDQKpidWPwFqIcH6o2vjXqmYk8O4B8T6s=", 
		"explanation": "25CqZ4L63heq9oskEhr31fLsPH/ZDGxRoWbDQKpidWPwFIjabOLpiZtwLFmazVpp9zbArLf98ldPmKBe586eMC8Gf4VrzcLJ2+v41DFIIIZHj5Qy65wZPPJSwzDtYNzeYPNvx2DAJE3xaTe4CDBwgTSWnnMWrZG05i60WpZ3xhogm4526og9fNSN3LuQ7UOsyxWK3WuUTP1oEF+c94qNHB4Wfm5hTODo2Gf+I0A=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Erosion by glaciers", 
		"option_b": "Volcanic activity", 
		"option_c": "Erosion and deposition by rivers", 
		"option_d": "Wind action", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050105", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ3v5YhgVhvhxu/2N27DQ2NRrX6RQKxjPDHnUaLSLvv/xZt0PhyehE9zsmXSpqDgt0AGi61Ipc6QdjYGcMtpx8KE0uC3xmgBMoZWk5Z39tocaeBUxTOqNMDTMvF7yWbANUDjbiqpBX5g1CPZiXcJ6pTi+BxlG9QK7YOduvQayPI=", 
		"answer": "25K3epb2k9SW8Z7kN4ePbMBoHS8y5EU=", 
		"explanation": "25T4b57h1hyq/pZgU178xO/tOnycQ2YUpm/DRKJ4fHT6FLDLeuW+2oN0IkzJnlJ/92WGoKTi4VYLz6pCqZyWZicRPo59x8OA2Oq7hH5HJ8NK2pR69pUKe/wA3ji+fcfPIfB6jnyPJE6wazikAWJn1mE6m80AEKFoQneW92NmrUs=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Meander", 
		"option_b": "Estuary", 
		"option_c": "Gorge", 
		"option_d": "Delta", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050106", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz3Rjk84MvQBOyyv78IHnDQ3UZpnHDU+NmeWfmRufEYuLp2td+MVmbzVo74WLDprWw80EAn+Qb5oiLdSxDbI583dyd3urwhHhPc8cEjYFm4YgZffhMk39K8Equ6Li30KVNP3mBP8y0", 
		"answer": "24K5fJTh1xjm+8dt3LCsY7sgyAEXwIcLf1EB", 
		"explanation": "24K5fJTh1xjm+5ZgUwz3hfvwJ2bVByIGq3qNEqI0Ynj1UbWCaOHx3oQxKEqMnxt6smXSpqDgt1cdgLgXqYGZZCcNPo96zZCd2KT2hHJJMshDn8B76toLdPEA2TOpccbXOfdgyS6SKEb7ICr9FnVnnSLCi3JVrcFNQPbrPwUNoXTuYQ6rbkNM", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Floodplain", 
		"option_b": "Estuary", 
		"option_c": "Delta", 
		"option_d": "Waterfall", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050107", 
		"question": "25T4a5D9yBbkt4wzEh36xO/+Nn/VEWsLpnvDULo0eWXwDufDJ63JwJN0axyPgVpvsnTJt7H/+hE2wUEk7g+kkVve4+AOx4KE", 
		"answer": "24P1e5nywRzut5UyXRj7yfi96IFVazQ83A1ErubZ48iQYQ==", 
		"explanation": "25a5Zoj83wqq9pclEh36xO/+Nn/VEWsLpnvDULo0ZHnmXbWCffn7zIc9Z2rEnlN64nPC47Xi+FUGg61Ipc6QdjYGcMtpx8KE0uC30HlTPNNDksBg7YwabrRF3jK+fdvVYoKV18/+mF+HBpEd4eDu5TM=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Wide, flat bottom", 
		"option_b": "Gradual slope", 
		"option_c": "V-shaped profile", 
		"option_d": "Absence of water", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050108", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ3v5YhgQBv0wO/sdX/fQ3YZpj+CQKZ1MGbrUbXHLuy+255nIk7JgF5+5mWGt631t0AKjuQb/ZePeSECcod2iNOB1vb2x2VEIc9en4Qy5oNffuZBzzakZ9ybN/96y3zAJkv0Jy20AHF41DzZnHlbrY2v5nj53ki3iV5OZlTSKZ6ydvlPeg==", 
		"answer": "25CrfITywwCo8P/8wQYJS3PMvXTMDKn1oA==", 
		"explanation": "25S2KJTgxQzr5ZxgWw2yxPO/NHnVAiIGq3qRV+N1MGPqQqLQLuD7zINiZ0iBiBto93eK47f15EYDm6FV7s6WfmIBbIpsw9ma36TgxWVEIYZAj4Uy8JVfcf1YxTOqNNvdYPh8y32IMETkYiv9BX5w1CLTi2tXvIapty+5hXqjLjjc86QfJFzkYms=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Meander", 
		"option_b": "Estuary", 
		"option_c": "Delta", 
		"option_d": "Gorge", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050109", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz3Rjk84MvQBOyzO6/NnnVAnYUpz+CRuNgeHSjWajXeuW+xpExJhybhE1+4DqGtK315VZPnK1f4IOafjZDd5gvzNWZ2Pf+0HRFc8dX2pR64doNdeJF3nq+NMLeLPFtx3qZZ0H1ZCu4BWNxh26UxwIbyxrbUNh1rwM17h9lOw==", 
		"answer": "25G9ZIXyk3nsGrIRqWdLXvF58po38s4=", 
		"explanation": "25T4bJT/xRiq/pZgVBHgyPj7dWrEQ3YZpj+OXbZgeDHsUufDLv/335JjZ0uBiEl+smXDp6z98l0bz6ta+5yWdSZDfJIv3NiMl/b+0nRTc89X2oR39JUMdeBFyH2pYdGbNPEuymuDNUDxdDCzAzBikT3ZiXVCscGqY8QPn0ZoHZSwKvbKjmxw", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Estuary", 
		"option_b": "Meander", 
		"option_c": "Gorge", 
		"option_d": "Delta", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050110", 
		"question": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7AzOv6JyvGAm4dpmaQEqJmdTHsUrPHYK3twZZhIljJj0I75n7D46Di+EAGgKZa5c6PYi0Ae5h8zcPJ2OK303BVNtQI2odg5Z4KffhM1X2re8bWKfBpjljNNE3xdzy5RGZ1mD3Tk28Wp5W+52eHWpojyRg31sdE4/soPcOa1K2d/A3q3Ea21H7RTrJ2HFWNvMGmq0ya4I89tMOJtCDItP3q2vmT4tsYdwRG/4l5I1r8haEf/Th/Qoi4aQZO4+XcIVH/LzuqKABd+MXnlnBs1o06VH09+xEGg49ZbMcz34z3/DE/Kt95EHP64wR8yadoXgOTebi2xCi3uhUKZ3gqa4N3vTk8rgHcKVhxlGzcXiVHkZJp/94ShkRgfGEAnXr0hy3LjmSbaYHi58D6ief/pKlv86opOgGBO1iYX4Mfd7bBNGIy3uGeTbRVIJQnGCSmO9kh8z3wLpHU1jdN0d0qLnTi+j7Zk9/wOHb68673vcB3ALoNM9/RqZ/t8GjPZGPiLnOActnhWhz5QHK43Aglsxko22Ef5iLKAZ965z5NnX++CUhhkyOgeHPhgrZZqoOCa4sj0uHl0jxQl/I4jJ7z3RA5SRD7mW1CvJePQE5bgRTBH9kC1kkoALsWWNbQ/GnW1UreC30cas/iCKvHxi9HyfrimmRwrNAKWpuAPw3Jj98riFeND85tVHPopYP3KbxAUCQf7qB0y+Dhp8OpdPC9bGopbA+lSq9O+5BfKA11FEvPDDJKcvitV40KVPJKwTXenwIIQXNGEhrD/egJUwu+osHaLnjXdbQOThz7I7YXHMrxQECPIfm7xyXODv+d1UO3SU0hS3bdLbUM4Q7+fczmK1OPnShn8cDrNVRIBIoZfCPhdWK3pKSGSxY7azggOoRUOMfytmkmb+0ogXwogicxb/8=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz4g3r44AtVxDmha+zdTicQ2Mfpz/WEqJmdTHgW7XQa+7qi9iMU6L21L6IgSLRNOx7lAY=", 
		"explanation": "24KwYZ32kQvj4YAyEgjzyfH6LHiQAnAU42yLU7NxdDHhTefWZui+zIV+NFWGg1p3smbUrKb15EAKnOhU786IcTYGbMcv3NiMl9K613lAI8NA2pZz6JYaZecAzS+oNMDCMPdtz2KMPgXxdCqyB3l1gDTSymtfvIv77CiuQNIx1RlyhI5u6NovcJee16zT5UKqg0aP3W+EWrgkA12PsNy7q0CdrsIwtNuI8TDJ+/X9n+qT5t8Hbg1LrMZDbW+0kugP9zg1UNy9ZxwL/uKQbFHsLiymNR1d8Nij1zR7w5E8UX10+xkGg8NEa9Z2xN/3/D4xK8h4FD/6plZP1J1zUVeZev2s2G2k70ArcGhrZ49juD51oAGYaFB7imSPRThYm44r8d5ZgQxmPWZOknPywj2OjmGcPK/t3pL+hOb5urh3+6wpaUCMOlLfFp8Vc7bSJWZ8wfrbDqdSc5ZpEyfjOZUv8C38Mtaa3i0Ywtgsb3Hr+yWdgsH0MGup85P3ipR/GrwSM9DW7IujuFmHcyryKj2cYIvyVQf/S3X21E4lixYSwCgc7SLcCYRstSkC3n+8XUF20jTlaHWsk7BIqpacfoAiw/r+yX5Qj/Vsmom30hEzUEj7jHFH8oWOWl1bxFeWG84I1xA9GLEMB9bV/XqYhmLCTn0AM47iCaGUgz9c2/f0g2Rzq9AHRsyAIw2bj8YlxAKiCOt8WX6tq4nrL/kWHiRsxrxC3v+ktsf7Zfq2LWYzLxO5T+BV5ZBCKA11FEvPDDJKcvitV40KVPJG3HKKgw9NB3lFCk2M9K5IXAqlvszNfCrMaqcZHF7gevMAAcH8R0nIdeWh2j/cAbfclAe6VlIsSj/RYbwI5AP5dIuyMBzzkGBl98bgIRFSSsMTLib6emq+oOOTChIuej4rO8iqsuYXo3TkpxnmQZHqkQ/n", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only Statement 1 and 2 are correct", 
		"option_b": "Only Statement 3 and 4 are correct", 
		"option_c": "Only Statement 2, 3, and 5 are correct", 
		"option_d": "All of the statements (1 to 5) are correct", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050111", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gZhb3hfrtNG/VByIBsXCFW69xMH7lFKaCfOTozIUxNVmZn15o93jSsOX15kYGg6FZ+4eKfWIBe594zdWHl+Hly2JIPMgEm452pJ4abPtTxSmke9qbHPBSwFyFJlb/aWP9MHhx1CPfnHlE6I66/CmvVdM501Uz1oV54ckyP9Lf262H/0i9iEaW1H7RTbNhA1OA9dyt+laVsoc89cuCo3Le5vvqk/fdsN8FZkhGt4M/cF64nqUM9j54Qt2keB5Ss5fUJ5CaRi4qMIrF5+QX5PE=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz0Ar58pc0WxH8hfzxMSvCBmMCrHHDU7FxMGXxQaKOLu/r3ddlL1nJn1564XnI46zjt0cHiuhY5pyNdSEXPo532NyI2eXjzX5Pc8lC2pR64doeb+dF3imke9qZj9k+rFN+T+kBkxZJVWE/rA==", 
		"explanation": "25T4b4Py1Rzut5UyXRj7yfi/OmjTFnAC42iLV600cTHxXbHHfK3/zZ1kNEiazVJv4TbBsaT0/lYBm+hP5s6NdSMAdstuxpCMxvH+yHhDIc9Rl8Bh8JsLebRXxDi/cZTPKPsuy2CFNULpJzirBXl4lTPajzxQp5H78DW0R9M4zlU3h5J54dt8KN+ambuW7ES1gwiWnGiEWK1oCBbImsTxPrHgS29K0fy9BURF", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both assertion and reason are true, but the reason is not the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both assertion and reason are true, but the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "Assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "Assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050112", 
		"question": "24GwbdHjwxbp8pYzEhH0hcLAClTvPF1RqnGVXa9idWKjQK/HLvr7yIV4KVvJjEx66zbJpeXi+FAEz6lV7c6MfysPPol2iMSB0qT2x2VIPMgElYYy4pYQa/1Oy326dcDeMrxWe49UQ1V9FNH+RJPgZew0", 
		"answer": "25CqZ4L63heojO2Xb8SLkyDEP66xwcV1bA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHjwxbp8pYzEhH0hfjtOnjZDGxRqnGVXa9idWKjQK/HLvr7yIV4KVvJjEx66zbJpeXi+FAEz6lV7c6MfysPPol2iMSB0qT2x2VIPMgElYYy4pYQa/1Oy326dcDeMr5L3GGTLkr+Jza+B2Vmh3HXmTxCoIb78yipV993zxNygo99rd89KNKNnrvT5UKugwuH0m/RTLR3HVudssu7qd7S2BHvhJpiIZN1zk3bnS0=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "er,os,io,n s,oil", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050113", 
		"question": "25T4epjl1Aut5MUpQV7mzfi/JWTZDXZRpW2MX+NjeHjgXOfLeq3x2552LlKImV5ovjbJpbH1+RMDgKta/YubMCsNPoNmxNyQl+vlhHxOJshQm4l8648MPOZFyzSieseZ8TIfvUhLX8U62ktXbBSH+g==", 
		"answer": "24a3fYPw1FvYawcSqn8ylY9bgHIU6ag8", 
		"explanation": "25T4epjl1Aut5MUzXQvgxvi/PHiQF2oU42+MW61gMHfxW6qCeeX3yp8xLkjJgkly9X/IorH15B9PgK5P7IDffC0Af59qzJCA2aT/zX1NKoZLiMB/648RaPVJwjK4Z5TJJflnwWCTZ2zkJzCuRGR8kXHFnn1EvIq18merW9M51FU9kMds5c18Lt6J3LrU+w2yiROQ0n6ICh9UAz61e2tuotMafy1M8WU=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "so,ur,ce,re", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050114", 
		"question": "24GwbdH13gvn9pEpXRCyyvu/NCvcAmkU43CAUbZmYzH0XKLMLuy+255nIk7Onht293fIp6Dit18AgLgb4J3fczcXPoRpzpCPxev6hGVJNoZJm4l8pJkXffpOyTHvzRqJOvkGvZ133ZaIKn1NOw==", 
		"answer": "25qgap7kk+gZ7VfjKkwe3dgTQuEz+zE=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH13gvn9pEpXRCyyvu/NCvfG2AetD+PU6hxMH7gV7LQfa3pwZJ/Z13Jn1Jt92SBsOX98lIBi61JqYKQfzJDd5gvy8Wdl+vxwjFHIclJ2pR64doSff1OjD6lddrVJfIu4XaCKFKwazi2AWM0lSPTyn9ErYKv8CP7Q9IyzlUz1op97MY4OcXf1aec+AH4ghOHnG+eCLJqFluQu8no7U+Tt8D1V7lx062EcAH4deE1zOPS", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Ox,bow,go,ne", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050115", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxRz4+sUpQV7n1vj7dW3fESIFq3rDW61gYnjgVbPHLun/x5R0Z16MmUx+93iGprf/5FoAgeha54rfdCcTcZhm3NmG2aT+yjFHPNRJk451pIgWavFSjDCoddrfJex9kSzaihC/Hu5cfmW3OTyR78l0", 
		"answer": "25O0fYf60BWq1YQsXhvmh4PK/Tb+dT1WOwFw33FgSIo=", 
		"explanation": "25O0fYf60BWq9YQsXhvmhfn6JmjCCmAUsD+XWqY0eX/3Rq7Bb/n7iZNwKV+MzVl+5mHDpquw8kEAnKFU586efiZDeo5/x8OAw+34yjFIPYZClZJ/7ZQYPOZJ2ji/NNneIfBqy3yTZWxTwH0zi9JHhVV+EtWrEeo=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Fluvial Ballet", 
		"option_b": "Sedimentary Waltz", 
		"option_c": "Meander Tango", 
		"option_d": "Hydraulic Waltz", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050116", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gYBfkwO+/IW7CEWMSpmzDU7FxMHfvVbOOLujyzIFwM1mNzUhu4HDHoKDjt1UAmqZfqY+TfywEPplm3tWbl/L2yH1EKtUEpo5O6qgafedPwmftQNzeOb5v3GvAIUriajy5RHRhkXHChTxVoIK18iKoFNM5gAE6k8dq5N45LpCMmaqS+0j4igOU2XfRS7xxAlGd9cyxq1eZo5Y3u8SO8SfL+P3/jrqXwBK7Rk4LTqENrQNRYjAT", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz0Ar58pc0WxH8hfzxMSvCBmMCrHHDU7FxMGXxQaKOLu/r3ddlL1nJn1564XnI46zjt0cHiuhY5pyNdSEXPo532NyI2eXjzX5Pc8lC2pR64doeb+dF3imke9qZj9k+rFN+T+kBkxZJVWE/rA==", 
		"explanation": "24exfpThkQ3v5ZchURvhhfztMCvZDWYUpnvDVK91ZD2jUavHeOzqzJMxNEmbi1p492WGoqn/+VRPnaFN7JzfZiMPco5225C93+HkwTFVNtRWm4N399oebvEAyjK/edHfYPp7yy6UKAXzbzizA3Vn1DjYymhercOp/DG+Rp0kgBczhYI44c0qOdvTmaeV/Ei2xgWDyWiUTP1mCBSNsM285E2Vo8ItpcGEtyabyPq5u+uT5NYOIhpbqYNtI1+zgKYK7T4rEcG6fB0L+PDDIVLhLyenNwIc8MWvlnJm1I8sTyky+BBJhpNaY8l9lpThqjc8LI1rBzb6r0FG09R9S1eefbqw1Xqk5Vk6Y3s/bIVjr2F1oh2ZKUB3lGzcWCRUh4Ur6tULhwVgeHwC4Z5kDP2JYrniKwxjOLu3QA==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both assertion and reason are true, but the reason is not the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both assertion and reason are true, but the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "Assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "Assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050117", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gYQrgwPzydXvZEWMSuj+AU600YnTwQavWLuTwiYN5IhyIgU9+4HfSqqr+t1wJz7pS/4uNMCEMa5l8zcPJ6+rLykNEMtVLlNoyy5QaPOZJ2ji/NNfaMOp73GuTZ1H4Ynm7CH9j1D7Qyn1Yp5ez8DX7RtMhxQdylJ446NozON6R3uiH4F+3kwGKnHrRX7xwFEaKvcusq0eVtos8sI9Ez/mWgCfMKlXbgdiZ+ATj", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz0Ar58pc0WxH8hfzxMSvCBmMCrHHDU7FxMGXxQaKOLu/r3ddlL1nJn1564XnI46zjt0cHiuhY5pyNdSEXPo532NyI2eXjzX5Pc8lC2pR64doeb+dF3imke9qZj9k+rFN+T+kBkxZJVWE/rA==", 
		"explanation": "24asepTy3Fn6/pchUQeyyv78IHnDQ3UZpnHDU+NmeWfmRufHfOL6zIQxM1Sbgk58+jbH47Lx41YdnKBe7c6beTQKeo4vyd6Nl+D+0nRTJ9UEk5RhpJwTc+MA2DLtd9XLNOt8yy6UL0CwYyu8DX51kzSWhXoWqY204S++RpolyQM3hMdM5cEvfNaTza2B6VmxiQjC033RWrRyFEbZtsG9+VCZs8I7tMPNmDzf8fH92urW48sHdkhbscZDbRu/n6kH/y8rEcG6KB5K/+DDYlX9JWilIg8J7NnmxTZ8o2I0f4J9tLl8nbbNjyk4", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both assertion and reason are true, but the reason is not the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both assertion and reason are true, but the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "Assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "Assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050118", 
		"question": "24GwbdHjwxbp8pYzEhH0hfD6NGXUBnAYrXjDW7A0YGPqWabQZ+HniZNjLkqMgxt56yyEhe3FMiJWXXVKxlz6eaZ83w==", 
		"answer": "25m5fJTh0BWq8pcvQRf9y78fwRjNw70V/JuPPqHSLZ1X", 
		"explanation": "25i9aZ/31Avj+YJgXR3x0O/sdW/FBiIFrD+XWqY0Y3jnUbDDd/6+zIV+NFWGgxt09DbH47f54VYdw+hY+4ueZCsNects3cKf0ve3xX9Fc8RBlIRhpJMRPOBIyX2/fcLeMr5txm+OKUD8JQ/Y0NR+AqcfaoAVUeosAuI=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "High water velocity", 
		"option_b": "Vertical erosion", 
		"option_c": "Lateral erosion", 
		"option_d": "Glacier movement", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050119", 
		"question": "25S2KJ7r0xb9t4khWRuyzO6/M2TCDmcV42iLV60uMjo1308R199HpYr1/wwCQUQ=", 
		"answer": "25T4ZZTy3x3v5cUsXRHihfTsdWjFFyIepXnDVLF7fTH3XKKCY+z3x9dyL12Hg153sJScOP9kRgYW8cWOVQqS+Yw=", 
		"explanation": "25qgap7kkRXr/IAzEhj91/C/ImPVDSIQ43KGU61wdWOjWKjNfq38zJR+KlmazVJo/XrHt6D0t1UdgKUb/YaaMC8Cd4Uv2tmf0va3x3lAPchBlsK+XUfqQn2lqVs7by/KdLeg", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "A river flows over a waterfall", 
		"option_b": "A river erodes its banks laterally", 
		"option_c": "A river cuts through resistant rock layers", 
		"option_d": "A meander loop is cut off from the main channel", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050120", 
		"question": "24GwbdHFnAri9pUlVl7kxPHzMHLDQ2QesXKGVuN2aTHxXbHHfP6+yIV0Z0ybhFZ64H/KuuX04lZPm6cBq7DyFDU6R/H8gROL/vC6Pc8=", 
		"answer": "25m5fJTh0BWq8pcvQRf9y739LCvEC2dRsXaVV7E2ZoJOnNz82Pvi8Knf131G7A==", 
		"explanation": "24P1e5nywRzut5MhXhL33O6/NHnVQ2QesXKGVuN2aTH3XKKCfOTozIU2NByFjE9+4HfK46Di+EAGgKYb6J3feTZDfZ5725CA2fD4hGVJNoZXk4R399oQerRUxDjtYtXXLPt3jFzbCmophs0ja4hfOAz6sRQ=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Wind erosion", 
		"option_b": "Glacial activity", 
		"option_c": "Lateral erosion by the river", 
		"option_d": "Chemical weathering", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050121", 
		"question": "25T4f5Dn1Avs9oksEgz30e/6NH/DQ3cBsGuRV6J5MH71UbWCeuTzzNd1MlnJmVQhsGRB9Ez8xUXwmyilx/wPA38=", 
		"answer": "24O9eoX60hjmt4AyXQ37yvO/NH+QCnYC432CQaY2ksNWXXrE1EXXO668i2aiwQ==", 
		"explanation": "24K5fJTh1xjm+5ZgQBvm1/j+ISvFE3EFsXqCX+N1YzH3XKKCbOztzNd4NByMn1R/93KGobyw/0oLnalO5YecMCMAaoJgxpCI2eC3xXNTMtVNlY4+pJkeaedJwjrtYNzeYOlv2muSIUT8a3mpCzB5nTbEi2hT6IG69iysVcgzgrk0jORZgbR5KO3PNRqe41g=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "The river's increasing discharge", 
		"option_b": "Vertical erosion at its base", 
		"option_c": "The river's meandering course", 
		"option_d": "Glacial movement", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050122", 
		"question": "25T4bJT/xRiq/pZgXxHh0b3zPGDVD3tRt3DDVKxmfTH0XKLMLuy+255nIk7JgF5+5mWGouXy+FcWz6dds8xfnIa8am2E3X7yPcSkHPco", 
		"answer": "25q7bZD9k/cz573iWqEgiWZpcWQ82O8=", 
		"explanation": "25G9ZIXywln+7pUpUR/+yeS/M2TCDiIQtz+XWqY0fX72QK+CYeu+yNdjLkqMnxts+nPUpuX54xMCiq1P+s6eMCAMepIvx9bJxOX70GZAJ8NW1sBh8ZkXPPVTjCmlcZTUI/tvwCzuQV90KedjSRC5ThCMXwm6", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Freshwater lake", 
		"option_b": "Ocean", 
		"option_c": "Glacier", 
		"option_d": "Underground aquifer", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050123", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEgr31/C/M2TCQ3YZpj+CUbc0f3ejUK7Ua//qwJl2Z0uImV5psnDUrKiw9hMdhr5e+86Lf2IKbJlmz9Gd0qTxzXRNN9UElZIy9IgQav1EyX26dcDeMr5owXzAJEr+dCywFGR9mz+JyP7DILkajj3afp6ACzgl3hU=", 
		"answer": "24exfpThkR3j4YAyQRf9y7+AqQX4tEORMaMNoZaKTX/M", 
		"explanation": "24exfpThkR3j4YAyQRf9y732O33fD3QUsD+RV6d9YnTgQK7Maa3pyIN0NRyPn1R2sneGsazm8kFPm6cb5IuaZGIVf5lmx8Wal+ziyXBPc8hBn4RhqNoMafdIjDy+NN3JMvdpz3qJKEuwaCv9E3FgkSOWmWlGuI+it52EN0GfFpKNWgPCctj5Ebs=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "River meandering", 
		"option_b": "Erosion", 
		"option_c": "Waterfall formation", 
		"option_d": "River diversion", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050124", 
		"question": "25T4b57h1hyq/pZgURbz1/z8IW7CCngUpz+BS+N9ZGK5FovEqScVdfhB4m5XLRNbDbI=", 
		"answer": "25u5eoP8xlWq84AlQl7kxPHzMHKSkbIzNGccKobWANR+OxTP/A==", 
		"explanation": "25T4b57h1hyq/pZgU178xO/tOnyQAmwV43uGV7M0ZnDvWKLbLuL43ZJ/Z1qGn1Z+9jbEuuXi/kUKnehe+4GMeS0NPp9n2t+c0Oy31nRSOtVQm45mpIgQf/8AwDy0ccbIYr8yu2v5IftsUXZKsbCsp2s=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Gradual slopes", 
		"option_b": "Flat bottom", 
		"option_c": "Narrow, deep valley", 
		"option_d": "V-shaped profile", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050125", 
		"question": "24G9eoPy0hz5t4wuEgz70/jtdX3RD24UumzDU7FxMHfsRqrHaq363JIxM1PTz01GOtPqNkCMrB0gvMekEWo=", 
		"answer": "25G3f5/wxA3+/osnEhH0hen3MCvCCnQUsT3xksxIEA6DW5Hiqh8GMayc", 
		"explanation": "24G9eoPy0hz5t4wuEgz70/jtdX3RD24UumzDUaJ6MHPmFKHNfOD7zdd1MlnJmVQ75n7D47f54VYdyLsb5Y+LdTACcstq2t+a3uv5iDFCIcNFjol849oZcPVUgH2oeNHNIepryi6TMlf2Zjq4FzJGxEAKwR347r5NJUTHFtH7", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Downcutting of the river", 
		"option_b": "Deposition of sediment", 
		"option_c": "Lateral erosion by the river", 
		"option_d": "Glacial activity", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050126", 
		"question": "25T4ZJTl1Byq/pZgU178xOnqJ2rcQ2QUomuWQKY0ZHniQOfEYf/z2tdwK1OHihtv+nOGpqH38kBPgK4b6M6NeTQGbMtr3dXJw+uthld/ZbRpywwfdbj57nmUZ3E=", 
		"answer": "24exfpThkR3v54ozWwr7yvO/MX7CCmwW43mPXaxwYzMKSG97sSAY+jXurBy6avOW", 
		"explanation": "25m9fpT2wlnr5YBgVBHgyPj7dWrDQ3EUp3aOV61gMHjwFKPHfuLtwIN0IxyIgVR19TbSq6Cw8lcIirsb5ojfcWIRd51q2pCNwvb+ynYBNcpLlYQy4YwacuBTgH2vYd3XJPdgyS6VNwXkbzz9BnF6nyKUJHOMX0qyfMgd8YolFbpjnQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "River deposition during floods", 
		"option_b": "Vertical erosion", 
		"option_c": "Glacier movement", 
		"option_d": "Wind action", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050127", 
		"question": "24GwbdHjwxbp8pYzEhH0hfn6OX/RECICqnGIW61zMHX2UefWYa3qwZIxJl+KmFZu/nfSqqr+t1wJz7te7YeSdSwXPophzJCawubkzXVEPcVB2olhpJERc+NOjDy+LpbY5RLkE5s6qN66/t2Ft+R4", 
		"answer": "25G9ZIXy2Bqq5JAiQRf2wPP8MCkYHew6z3fkFHCogQL9BCCO", 
		"explanation": "25SrKIL21RDn8os0Eh/xxujyIGfRF2cC436NVuN3f3zzVaTWfaG+2ph8IhyNiFdv82WGrqTpt1YXn61J4IuRcydDbYJhw9mH0KT41jFSJsRXk4R36pkaMLRMyTypfdrcYOphjmKPMEDiJzyxAWZ1gDjZhD5jR0Y3XmsGRtskn9M8yQS2", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Erosion", 
		"option_b": "Glaciation", 
		"option_c": "Delta formation", 
		"option_d": "Deltaic subsidence", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050128", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRXr+YEmXQz/hfTsdWjYAnAQoGuGQKpudXWjVr6Cb63swIF0NRyKhVp1/HPK47H49kdPhrsb7YuaYCcRPp9nyd7J3vDkhGJUIdRLj4527ZQYPOJBwDGobZTdLPFh3DHCJ7UHV+UZwWZKpyQuC1+8eA==", 
		"answer": "25a5Zoj831tHjFms7v39mqeh5kG5oWUf", 
		"explanation": "25T4a5D9yBbkt4wzEh36xO/+Nn/VEWsLpnvDULo0cTHxXbHHfK39wZZ/KVmFzU9z82KGqraw81YKn61JqZqXcSxDaoNqiMOcxfb40X9FOshD2pZz6JYaZbgAwzu5cdqbJvF8w2uEZ1H4dTaoA3g0kSPZmXVZpsGwzNoUk/ZYjbaH9pFi77EB", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Floodplain", 
		"option_b": "Canyon", 
		"option_c": "Terrace", 
		"option_d": "Levee", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050129", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEgr31/C/M2TCQ3YZpj+TQKx3dWLwFKXbLvr2wJR5Z06Am15p4TbCprX/5Fobz7te7YeSdSwXPoJhiNHJ0eX5iWJJMtZBnsBi5Y4LeeZOjDy+NMDTJecuyGKPMAX2dTawREx61DzZn3JCqYq15mevW5oxzBQm1oZq6MkvY5WCQMM7B8DYGZZ3hdvuOhDC", 
		"answer": "25S0ZITl2Bjmt4MhXF70yu/yNH/ZDGxTjFUncBbu4pqPTaYYhJ4MxQ==", 
		"explanation": "25S0ZITl2Bjmt4MhXA2yxO/6dW3fEW8Upz+CQeNmeWfmRrSCaujuxoR4MxyaiF9y/3PIt+X5+RMOz65a58OMeCMTe48v2NGdw+HlyjFWO8NK2oZ+640WcvMAyi+ieZTWL+tg2m+JKUrldHm8FnV1h3HChTxQpIKv4SKpFM4y0gczn4k6HpuNsvMGTkx5FMTwb2ZdNw==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Canyon formation", 
		"option_b": "Levee building", 
		"option_c": "Delta formation", 
		"option_d": "Alluvial fan formation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050130", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEgr31/C/M2TCQ3YZpj+NU7dhYnDvWL6CaOLsxJJ1Z0uImV5p8XnTsbb15BMbh6lPqY2QfiwGfZ8v2tmf0vbkhGVOc8pFiId39todc/BJyS7te9KbN/96y3zMZ1blZDH9BWM0mzLTi3JF6L+1tSipFMkywQZt1J7L/gFV/5kz96PiOHjUZVg=", 
		"answer": "25CrfITywxDv5MeQYt6RRGaFqSegDKvb1LUA", 
		"explanation": "25CrfITywxDv5MUhQBuyy/zrIHnRDyIGomuGQKB7ZWPwUbSCaOLsxJJ1Z0uBiEl+smTPtaDi5BMCiq1PqYKeYiUGbMttx9SA0ve3y3cBIMdIjpdz8J8NMLRT2T6lNNXIYPFty2+ONAX/dXmuAXFn1nu3tLXKphcjYamtI0pAink=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Deltas", 
		"option_b": "Estuaries", 
		"option_c": "Canyons", 
		"option_d": "Floodplains", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050131", 
		"question": "24exfpThkQ/r+4klSw2y0fX+ISvYAnQU42yXV6ZkMGLqUKLRLuzwzddwZ1KIn0l05TqGp6D15xMfnadd4IKaMCMRe8tgzsSM2aTlwXdEIdRBnsBm69oeb7ZeXMdqUjXCZIhQOnfa790x", 
		"answer": "25K3epb2wlu7Y0zvSRKbOx8dtDjmYrxn", 
		"explanation": "24exfpThkQ/r+4klSw2y0fX+ISvYAnQU42yXV6ZkMGLqUKLRLuzwzddwZ1KIn0l05TqGp6D15xMfnadd4IKaMCMRe8tgzsSM2aTlwXdEIdRBnsBm69oeb7RHwy+qcceZT/irw2XaK82/WhVW/YAtQw==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Go,rg,es,as,oi", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050132", 
		"question": "25T4epjl1Aut5MUpQV770e6/OWTHBnEF42+MW61gMH7lFKLQYf73xpk9Z0iQnVJ483rKuuXn/1YdiuhS/c6SdScXbctuiNyIxePy1jFDPMJd2o90pI0eaPFSjqUpkW0V1UxDO01Z5DCmPqo=", 
		"answer": "25e5e5Sz3Rz88oli7vhdbw1LB4LlkzNYH+5GtA==", 
		"explanation": "25T4epjl1Aut5MUiUw33hfH6I27cQ2sC43aXQeN4f2bmR7OCfuL3x4MxKFrJiEl04X/Jremw40ofhqta5YKGMDULe5lqiNmdl+nywWVSc8cEloFg458NPPZPyCTte9KbN/96y3zABUTjYnmxAWZxmHHSj2hTuo6y+yKoFM4/xVU+n4px+YgoM5eI0aGQ4A25xhSLyn6DCL5lHxScp8Gs7gOVtJF4t8iJ8+90DyykvW7Klvsljrao0p4=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Bas,e l,ev,el,hi,gh", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050133", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUMWw3mhay/ImLECyI9qmyXEvE2TCxPeoofWDpCjEeFkQPDEA==", 
		"answer": "25i9aZ/31AuqusUGXQz/xOn2OmWQDGRRoj+AR7FidXWjRKbWZq363JIxM1PJn1Jt92SGprf/5FoAgeha54rfdCcTcZhm3NmG2ajTxXwBEMlKiZRg8ZkLdftOjHDtVdjPJexv2mePKQX/YXmvDWZxhnHQhnNB6IK18We+V9Uk2QYmk4o46d05fMOQmaCG5Uy2xg+MyH6DXrhqBV2Wu4KL6k2Fr4x4+I2uozfa4P32lLjc9p4KIj0frI5+c164174I9CY9SIigYABE5OPYIUDlJWimNQEO8MTtlntvhpAsTmAn4B5IlsNEbcN4lpTlpTciLIFMGTy1p1RMxp1yH1rWULiu1WTr8Fg6e25raowtvW0zrQ6IaFVsn2rcQilQhsBqvsIQgwFxPXtInWKghyebhXeGeZ3g7pO8le3iqbZn+6BnL02POljRWIpSJ8JIEqaGNSAi98l1LppQvXg=", 
		"explanation": "25T4ZZTy3x3v5cUpQV7+zPb6dWqQF3UYsGuaErN1ZHmjQK/Deq3/iYV4MVmbzVZ6+XPV46Tjt1obz65X5pmMMB4NX8tsyd6Q2Oq3zWIBMoZGk4cy8psTcPFZjCqkYNybM+pry37ANEz0Yir9LWQzh3HQhW5brYf74i++WpojyBByhI5u6Np8P8KLyuiH4F+3kwGKnHOQWrkkA1uavt3o5FWZssI59cGCvzWb4P30n7jv/ukDZwYSr4Nwc1e516oc8SY8Ecn0bBNGseveIVWtMiG1IhxRucL3lndoyMIqVWg68xoGioxBItR709j2tSQ1LY1sGTytsARkxplvHxSXev253HvroFQ5c38occp5tCh1sQOdJkBt1iudQiVclYx4spAYmwAjam5UmWSgkyqKjGybZdPq5cDoje2wsrB197FnFU+hdVrUWYIYdb/BLmkyw/rbAa9XNt9mVyDvOplu+jX4NNaVzTwMkNclN2On4CXZk43nMHO/odLKgdlzALYNM8KJqd+/tRzVaDXkMz2ccM7mXwT/WG+40gBh9xsq3iQC+yLMAIBstSwfm3/wXk1wmmf3bWikhP5d5IbOcps1kYYtEPv818QH9SKjPGmjeHE=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Meander,Formation of a curved path due to river erosion and deposition", 
		"option_b": "Dam Construction,Alteration of river flow and ecosystem due to human intervention", 
		"option_c": "Canyon,Creation of a U-shaped valley through the erosion of resistant rock layers", 
		"option_d": "Floodplain,Development of a flat area near a river that experiences periodic flooding", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050134", 
		"question": "24GwbdHj2Rzk+IglXBH8hfL5dVeSCmwSqmyGVuN5dXDtUKLQfdG8iYV0IVmbnhtv/SyERQgVmJFCHhdChj9NqAnVeg==", 
		"answer": "25i9aZ/31Av5t5EoUwqyxO/6dW7CDGYUpz+KXLd7MGLsWK7GLv/xypwz73kk1ICBRiXuaf076Wvtrw==", 
		"explanation": "25i9aZ/31Av5t5EoUwqyxO/6dW7CDGYUpz+KXLd7MGLsWK7GLv/xypwxDlKKhEh+9jbLpqT+81YdnOha+4vffScCcI9q2sPJw+z20DFJMtBB2oR34YoTZbRD2SntfdrPL756xmvANEr8bj39Fn93n3HZjDxX6JGy4yKpE8l3wx0zmIl94YR8M9GL3KbT61+9hxKL0nzRSf1gA1WUtNqh6AOQoYw8ps6MoTeZz1DvtwXUT1FFqmntW6DyfQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Meanders that are eroded into solid rock", 
		"option_b": "Meanders that form during periods of low discharge", 
		"option_c": "Meanders that are artificially straightened by \n human intervention", 
		"option_d": "Meanders that have reversed their direction due to \n tectonic activity", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050135", 
		"question": "24GwbdHPkx749oElVl7i1/L5PGfVPyBRrHnDU+NmeWfmRufQa+v724QxM1PTzzfFqwxi+xPvh5AaZsGAMBs=", 
		"answer": "25T4epjl1Aut5MUlQwv7yfT9J2LFDiICt36XV+NjeHTxUefHfOLtwJh/Z1mYmFp34TbCprX/5FobhqdVq1Va15hosR51zE6XR/4Si08=", 
		"explanation": "25T4b4Py1Rzut5UyXRj7yfi/OmjTFnAC42iLV600cTHxXbHHfKrtiZBjJliAiFVvsnfCqbDj40BPm6cb5I+WfjYCd4UvyZCL1uj2ynJEc8RBjpd34ZRfaPxFjC+sYNGbL/guy3yPNEz/aXm8CnQ0gDnTynhTuIyo/DOyW9R3zxNyhYJ85MU5MsPdA4mA9z9FKTCdS4c/K4CEyA==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "A river's meandering path through a floodplain", 
		"option_b": "A river's equilibrium state where erosion equals deposition", 
		"option_c": "The varying discharge of a river throughout the \n year", 
		"option_d": "The accumulation of sediment along a river's banks", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050136", 
		"question": "24GwbdHj2Rzk+IglXBH8hfL5dVeSAmwFpnyGVqZ6ZDHnRqbLYOz5zKszZ1OKjk5p4TbRq6D+rRGQFGmm2Y0WaoHcGJSBqvgw", 
		"answer": "25T4epjl1Aut5MUzXQvgxvi/PHiQD20SomuGVuNhYHnqWKuAySnROCYFigiYuhO0rGMd3Q==", 
		"explanation": "25S2fJTw1B3v+ZFgVgzzzPP+Mm6QEWcXpm2QErd7MHCjRq7Ua/++3Z9wMxyEjFJ15nfPrbaw/kccz6tU/JyMdWICfZlg28PJ1qT7xX9FIMVFioUy8JIeaLRVwjmoZtPUJe0u2muDM0r+bjr9EWB4nTfCxjxErZCu+TOyWt13yRtygo99rdo1KtKNmauG/FmxiAHCyHODR6hjGRSLvN2h5UTctIcqp8yEv3BhvorNRmxcguDhrhPoykYh", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "A river meanders across a floodplain", 
		"option_b": "A river cuts a gorge through resistant rock", 
		"option_c": "A river's source is located uphill", 
		"option_d": "A river undergoes delta formation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050137", 
		"question": "24GwbdHPkxv49owkVxqy1untMGrdPyBRs36XRqZmfjHqWufQZ/v729dyL12Hg1534TbPsOXz/1IdjqtP7JyWaicHPol2kpKhwChDnE5MjB2dJzZTJAlS", 
		"answer": "25T4a57+wRXv78UuVwrlyu/0dWTWQ2sft3qRUax6fnTgQKLGLu72yJl/IlCaz1RNDf6PpXlx3KST7wfLGSs=", 
		"explanation": "25T4aoPy2B3v88UzRgz3xPC/JWrEF2cDrT+KQeN3eHDxVaTWa//305J1Z16QzVo74H/Qprew9FsOgaZe5c6LeCMXPo9m3tmN0ve3zX9VPIZJj4xm7YoTebRTwTyheNHJYP1mz2COIknjK3myAmRxmnHSn3kWvIz74S++FN4y0Bohn5Nx4sZ8M9Hfyq2X4UC9iBLC3XWVCLtoBFeNoM+84kySs8Ixu42JuCHY/PXrnf2R3paHOODPmhrHj4DmjCReMg==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "A single, meandering river channel", 
		"option_b": "A complex network of interconnected channels", 
		"option_c": "A river that flows through steep-sided valleys", 
		"option_d": "A river that forms a deep, narrow gorge", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050138", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Qzn9otgUx3mzOv2IXKQAGMf43KMVqpyaTH3XKKCbeLr24R0Z1OPzUly5HPUsOXy7hMOg7xe+4eRd2IXdo4vztyGwKT2ynUBN89XjpJ75o8LdftOjDKrNMPaNPt8kSyyM45rDRUI91OTfqxA5WP2", 
		"answer": "24CqapD92APr44wvXFz0ufs2lN4zIRswXNYPI9cU", 
		"explanation": "24CqapD92APr44wvXF7xxPO/NGfEBnBRsXaVV7E0c372RrTHfa380NdyL12HilJ19TbRorH15RMJg6dMqZ6eZDYGbIV8iMSBxeviw3kBJ85B2oN96okLbuFD2DSiepTUJr5s22eMI0z+YCrxRGJ7lTXFxjxXpof7+jOzUch30wEgg4Rs+No5L5Ud8tsdgQYoJgSGgNpJcSRh", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Deforestation", 
		"option_b": "Urbanization", 
		"option_c": "Wind erosion", 
		"option_d": "Delta formation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050139", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Qzn9otgUx3mzOv2IXKQAGMf436AUaZ4dWPiQKKCfeL3xdd0NVOahFR1vjbKpqT0/l0Iz7xUqZ2adCsOe4V7hdyI0+H5hGZAJ8NWicB36o4abv1Oy32/fcLeMu0xjCTYz4jP1JwkdlPTKHZxmEg=", 
		"answer": "25S/epjwxBX+4pclELhhajlvbII7RBTP2nYLueE=", 
		"explanation": "25S/epjwxBX+4pclEh3zy73+NmjVD2cDomuGErB7eX2jUbXNfeTxx9sxK1mIiVJ19TbSrOXj8lcGgq1V/cOTcSYGcMt4ycSMxfe3wX9VNtRNlIcy9pMJeeZTjklG+CUFnPa5CFZe16zv8I8=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Urbanization", 
		"option_b": "Agriculture", 
		"option_c": "Deforestation", 
		"option_d": "Dam Construction", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050140", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzwQvl9IAzQV77y+vwOX3VECIerXrDQKpidWOjVavWa//3x5AxLkiazVh052TVpuXk+BMFgKFVqY+RfzYLe5ko25CK3+X5ynRNf4ZClZJ/7ZQYPPUAzzKjctjOJfBtyzHCDVFf70NP1G0FAiA6ZnkOpQ==", 
		"answer": "24exfpThkTrl+YMsRxv8xvi9224spmn6ddLSufW5DSOS2w==", 
		"explanation": "24exfpThkRrl+YMsRxv8xvi/OmjTFnAC42iLV600f3/mFLXLeOjsiZZ9M1mbnhty5mWGoKrl5UAKz7xUqYSQeSxDf4Vg3NiMxaPkhHJJMshKn4w+pJwQbvlJwjrtdZTYL/BownuFKUb1JYZ7rCMIN06UGnFb5TtKXvM=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "River Divergence", 
		"option_b": "Stream Migration", 
		"option_c": "River Fusion", 
		"option_d": "River Confluence", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050141", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7gyv76JniQAXtRtHeKUas0cTHxXbHHfK3725h1Ik/JmVN+snnTt6Dit1EKgawb5ojfcWIOe4phzNWbl+j4y2EecR0Ff4ix0loMEPHMPHU+waI=", 
		"answer": "25y2ZpThkTTv9oskVwyy4O/wJmLfDSDh6TUGihz0+lpHvyHDdGPm", 
		"explanation": "25T4epjl1Auq8pcvVhvhhen3MCvfFnYUsT+BV61wMH7lFKaCY+j/x5N0NRyFglRrsmLOsarl8FtPhqZV7JzffScCcI9q2pCMxevkzX5PcXk7sDxUELYGlKJAP5xH4UU=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Inner Meander Erosion", 
		"option_b": "Oxbow Lake Formation", 
		"option_c": "Meander Cutoff", 
		"option_d": "Point Bar Development", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050142", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxRz4+sUkVw3x1/T9MHiQF2oU42+RXaBxY2KjVr6CeeX3yp8xNFmNhFZ+/GKGqraw80EAn7he7c6QYmIPe417iNKM3+35wDFDKoZJlZZ76p1fa/VUyS/yNowvMkgDcuBRICAINNpElkY=", 
		"answer": "25G9eJ7g2A3j+Iti2iJuxuNdrPdzeP1IZsxsvA==", 
		"explanation": "25G9eJ7g2A3j+ItgWw2y0fX6dXvCDGEUsGzDULo0Z3nqV6+Cfej6wJp0KUjJhEg79mTJs7X18xMAnehX7IiLMCAGdoJhzJCLzqT6y2dIPcEEjYFm4YhdXPAXxWZt6xgHV+am6YOmdA==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Erosion", 
		"option_b": "Transportation", 
		"option_c": "Sedimentation", 
		"option_d": "Deposition", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050143", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUMWw3mhay/ImLECyI9qmyXAOE92rEc2WeEAh74U8aiBEYv", 
		"answer": "24CqapD92APr44wvXF6/hd73NGXXBnFRqnHDQKpidWOjUqvNea3/x5MxIl+GnkJo5nPLsOX04lZPm6cb4ZuScSxDbY573NyM2uH50DFAPcIEm4Nm7YwWaP1F33HtR8DJJf9jjl6JNUTzfnnwRFF4gDTEi2hfp437+iH7RtMhxQdylYht/9s5fNaMmaed7Q2qjxCHzjuSSa1wBEacpo6840bcpo43oo2Ct3La+vvtkv3BvJ4vYwUSnIlxcE+ugqsd8SU2EYX0SgdC/eDZb1OtLy7jNBoP7Mj3w2Zs1cI9VWggtBxOg41RZ4Bh347hrnI2M8J9VTK0pwRBwZJ5XAPWdayt0Xzt4xUzfHwuKcpAuSw7pQqOaHJxiGadWCVemsAmvvYWhwliaWZPkjbvhH+KwGaaboXm78DshPz44LBtsrcvLAGSPErdRMoPJbDPMnVhz6mfGKMcJ5AnEjDpLtwh8nn4LpLU2zwd38opO37o+mjNqPLj3glBmgfEUX1Nwa5I", 
		"explanation": "24CqapD92APr44wvXF7gwPv6J3iQF21Rq2qOU600Y3T3QKvHY+jw3ddwKVjJjFhv+2DPt6z15BMGgehY4JqWdTFDV58vy9GHl+361HBCJ4ZWk5Z39olffu0AzzWsetPSLvku2maFLlewYTWyEzBklSXCj25Yu8O6+yP7Udk40wwhgoJ1/oh8ANmszbqW6UD4lg+Q3XiICLR3UUORsMDo5E2Z4JAxo8if8THa5ODsiP3AsMoDZ0hUs4loI1S616kH9z4wVNr0ehtd9PaQVVzkM2irJh4N/MXwlmNhw4xpXCkm/QlDkMNTcM9304ukqDoiMNhtHXO740BJ0Z14WleCfLyskHvh8FQtdG4udsp5qyJ1swaKLUY+iXKPWClch8BX8PIMnAhndGFH3HLhjyzLg22OcpTm+MDoje2wt7h6srEuP0SSJhzeWoILJZfBKnQy2f2UH6McJJ5zEjCmPNsqvCv8LJOVzDxN2c1gJnmn9yWXht/6NWm/t9L4g9tjGqsTepHE782ys0jObyShNXWWJtn9Tw3iCG+43Q9xogokxGEW5G3PSJl+4TkIjHCjCQQkrinNaX2vkrtO+cKPbYtx0OD+yzcD2P1235q3xhQqQhb8nj9Ts5CXD2hHyE2WGMIVyUk5BLEPVJeR4GSAkGSQTm4Ce8vlQbyPxmxHz/f0nCF/vp4FFYOIbBibics03hLxAPN9FWPouInqNOgGSncp/rt8z+O198W1NeesKSUjYRSyS69b8ptaKk0zbSWxbH99CS9UvHptpIQ=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Urbanization,Changes in river flow and ecosystems due to human settlement and activities", 
		"option_b": "Stream Piracy,Alteration of river course as one river captures the flow of another", 
		"option_c": "Dam Construction,Building of structures that change river flow and affect aquatic life", 
		"option_d": "Meander Formation,Formation of a curved path in the river's course due to erosion and deposition", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050144", 
		"question": "27SqbdH13Rj+u8UlXhvkxOn6MSvDFnAXonyGQeN1fH7tU+fDLv/335JjZ0qIgVd+6zqGrKPk8l1PiadJ5IubMCYWe8t7x5CK3+X5w3RSc89K2pR64doNdeJF3nq+NNbaM/suwmuWIkmysGpzmanAPx9wwhwYP9IBhg==", 
		"answer": "24exfpThkQ3v5ZchURvhhz7XgGvQPZduiOISsSqlfe4=", 
		"explanation": "24exfpThkQ3v5ZchURvhhfztMCvWD2MF7z+GXqZicWXmUOfRe//4yJR0NByIgVR19TbH47f54VYdz75a5YKaaW5DcY17zd7J0evlyXRFc8JRn8Bm69ocdPVOyzi+NN3VYOpmyy6SLlP1dX6uRHJ1hzSWhnlArY/7wS++R9931BAghIZ76Nt8PcWambqW5UO5iBKRnHSXCLtrA1mcp46u50yTpJI0tMSDonAkShjna4Fc29uP5iTklgue", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Ri,ve,r t,er,ra,ces,up", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050145", 
		"question": "24GwbdHjwxbp8pYzEhH0hf7+JX/FEWsfpD+XWqY0dn3sQ+fNaK3/x5hlL1mbzUly5HPU46zjt1gBgL9VqY+MMjzWHReE7m/2oJBMxiXU1sI=", 
		"answer": "24asepTy3Fn6/pchUQew3x5nHRtSyIjKc7HB41dSJA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHjwxbp8pYzEhH0hf7+JX/FEWsfpD+XWqY0dn3sQ+fNaK3/x5hlL1mbzUly5HPU46zjt1gBgL9VqY+MMDEXbI5uxZCZ3vb2x2gBANJWn4F/pIoWbvVD1X2id9fOMu0u2WaFKQX/aTz9FnlikSORmTxerYK/4iapUJoy0hohn4h2r35XUl9qTZ9rv76uBmkE7hY=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "St,rea,m p,ir,acy,yi", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050146", 
		"question": "24GwbdHn1Avn5YAmVwzhhenwdX/YBiIXr36XEqJmdXCjWqLDfK3/iYV4MVmbzU9z82KGpr3g8kEGiqZY7J3fYCcRd4RrwdPJ0ej4y3VIPcEGdOxxmliycgl915DxrC7SSg==", 
		"answer": "25O0Z573wRXr/otiWi5g2l9dbSZFMJ1RMa5/yw==", 
		"explanation": "25O0Z573wRXr/oszEh/gwL32OHvfEXYQrWvDU7FxcWKjUqjQLuz5255yMlCdmEl+snfIp+X+9kcanalXqYaecisXf58jiNGal/D/wWgBIcNHn4lk4doRaeBSxTijYJnJKf1mjn2FI0z9YjepRHRhhjjYjTxQpIy08TT5qDope/uM7Hf31GucEprrFQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Fl,oo,dp,la,in,mo,un,ta,in", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050147", 
		"question": "252tZZD9kRjp44w2Wwr7wO6/Jn7TCyIQsD+HU640c37tR7PQe+7qwJh/Z12HiRtu4HTHrazq9kcGgKYb6o+RMDEKeYVmztmK1urjyGgBOstUm4NmpJtfbv1WyS/qZ5TkH8FR8VG/Z0T+Y3m4B39njSLCj3EUZBLUntYQXhO9MzFyn9njcw==", 
		"answer": "252hbIP83Rbt7sdA0Ebzy61PWKiiEkCXA/lH", 
		"explanation": "252hbIP83Rbt7sUyVxj31+6/IWSQF2oU42yXR6dtMH7lFLDDeujsiZN4NEibhFlu5n/Jremw+lwZiqVe55rTMCMNest/2t+Z0vbjzXRSf4ZFlIQy7I8SffoAxTO5ccbNJfB6x2GONAXzZjf9BXxgkSOWmHVArZH78yu0Q5onwQEmk5V2/oR8K9aL3LrT+Vi5ig+WxTfRSbNgUVWIoM+84kDcqIM6vNmMpSGZ8EymrT2c/3Y8BcTxQxMJkw==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Hy,dro,lo,gy,ge", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050148", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gYBfkwO+/MW7cF2MC436RV+NieWXiWOfEYf++2oJhN1ObmVJ19TbCqrP15UAKz61Y5p2GYzYGc5gv9N612dbyxWJOPZwEvoV+8JsMPORSwyukcNGbJvt82meMIgXjaDCxRHF6kHHei35fvIKvtSOuUZojz1UmnoI46c0sM8SWzaGc5g23gEaMyW+DQbhqBRmLvM2gq1CZpIs1sMOZ8wioZWWx1UypQD7fEMM7+rg=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz0Ar58pc0WxH8hfzxMSvCBmMCrHHDU7FxMGXxQaKOLuzwzddlL1nJn1564XnI46zjt0cHiuhn542QYjAGfZ8vzciZ2+X5xWVIPMgElYYy8JIaPPVT3zi/YN3ULrxOnbVdqco6fGWhmXcTcKJY", 
		"explanation": "24exfpThkR3v+5EhQV7z1/i/PGXUBmcV43aOQqxmZHDtQOfEYf++2oJhN1ObmVJ19TbCqrP15UAKz61Y5p2GYzYGc5gvzMWMl/D4hGVJNoZAn5B995MLdftOjDKrNNrONOxny2CUalf5ZDH9F3VwnTzThGga6JSz/CSzFNklxRQmk5Q4680uKN6T3OiA50S0xgeM2DuBWrJyGFCcpo6g6kGVtIMspo2LviCb4vXrk/fG454Ycg1RtoNsIekp41U6hgoazX5+qlBM8S0=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both assertion and reason are true, but the reason is not the correct explanation \n of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both assertion and reason are true, but the reason is \n not the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "Assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "Assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050149", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gZwzwxPP2L2rECm0f43yCXONxaHDgUbXAb/n7iYV4MVmbzV13/XnCqqv3t28Bz5RV24ueYy0NJMta2tKI2aT21nRAIIZTk5R6pJMSbPFSwTisdtjeYO173GiBJEDjJyu4AGV3kXHCgnkWpIK18WCoFNs1yRk7gp44+cd8PdWM1rqRqF+5jwiE3XedBP1oFFWdvMCvq1eT4Is2tt+IsCHe8LS5pvaT48sZZAlRusZtdlWzka5J+SQ8EcC9bxpO46TWbVviJGixLh0W6ollMYPqkbBiiUw4WSfGmpv2", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz0Ar58pc0WxH8hfzxMSvCBmMCrHHDU7FxMGXxQaKOLu/r3ddlL1nJn1564XnI46zjt0cHiuhY5pyNdSEXPo532NyI2eXjzX5Pc8lC2pR64doeb+dF3imke9qZj9k+rFN+T+kBkxZJVWE/rA==", 
		"explanation": "24KwbZ+zxAvo9otgUwz3xO6/MHPAAmwV7z+XWqZtMGPmRKvDbei+x5ZlMk6IgRtt93HDt6Tk/lwBz6lV7c6MfysPPpxm3NjJxev2wGINc8RRk4x27ZQYb7gAzTOpNNvPKPt8jmeNN0DicTCyEWM0hyTEjH1VrZD7wS++R9930wAgkIZ76Nt8LMWaz62d/A2qhw+My3qFTa8kF0aWuI675EKXqYw/9cSDpT2b4Pz82v/B/8sFZkQSg4g/YFqphKEH/2oxRYigZ1JN/evHIUX4KSuoKxdd9t3mxDR9zodpTnwm8h5Fh8NiaslglpvlsnI/Kch4GTy7pwRSzoJ5TQTWY7Ss2Cjh+FY6Zmlrcot5uT954QOZKVB3lGzcWCMRmY95+5AfhwFyaGpOiDbhjDvLk2CZeYHmq4bwiuf0qbdksChli1sKaaezlQLzs3vsvg4=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both assertion and reason are true, but the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both assertion and reason are true, but the reason is not the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "Assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "Assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050150", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gdBL9yvnvOWrZDXFRom2GErBhY3LmRLPLbOH7iYN+Z0yMn1J09n/F46z+4l0LjrxS5oDfTCw/cLlqycOG2b634n1OPMJUloF76olffeZFjDy/cdXIYP9qxG+DIkvkJy2yRGJ9gjTEmTxCoIKvtTW+V98+1hByhYJ85MU5MsPf3a2D516xkhXC2G6DQbNjUVKVusGs+AGCldMz+OsxV8tMQXYjDcLM", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz0Ar58pc0WxH8hfzxMSvCBmMCrHHDU7FxMGXxQaKOLu/r3ddlL1nJn1564XnI46zjt0cHiuhY5pyNdSEXPo532NyI2eXjzX5Pc8lC2pR64doeb+dF3imke9qZj9k+rFN+T+kBkxZJVWE/rA==", 
		"explanation": "25O0Z573wRXr/oszEh/gwL32O2/VBmZRr3CUH69teX/kFKbQa+ztiZZ1LV2KiFVvsmLJ47f54VYdnOhP4Y+LMCMRe8tp2tWYwuH50H1Yc89Kj4525Y4aeLRE2S+ketObJvJhwWqTawX/YS24CjBwgTSWnnMWvIu+tSO+RNUkyQE7mYk44s58L9Kb0KWW5ln4hQeQznKUTP1mCBSNvcvo+UqKpZB4sdifuDzctPL1lffXsNsdZwZGrMQU5MmvbEObXcb4mIdkNrxh", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms Made by Running Water  >> The Development of River system \n to The Human aspects of Rivers", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both assertion and reason are true, but the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both assertion and reason are true, but the reason is not the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "Assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "Assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060101", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEhvh0fTyNH/VByIQsXqCEqB7ZnTxUaOCbPS+wJR0Z1icn1J19TbSq6Cwx18KhrtP5o2afidDbo59wd+NiKZD94CbS5/YlzTWxQ2WalsB", 
		"answer": "2+TqKJz63RXj+ItgQQ/nxO/6dWbZD2cC4ehKUiuRUbEaxOD67P5CMNs=", 
		"explanation": "24W0bZjgxRbp8oslEjfxwL3cOn3VEWMWpiXDZqtxMEHvUa7ReuL9zJl0Z0yMn1J09jqGrKPk8l1Pna1d7JyNdSZDaoQvycPJw+zyhE0DGsVB2qF14dYjPrRMzS65cdCbJuxhwy6BJUrlc3nvUjB5nT3ag3NY6Jq+9DWoFNswz1UmmccpvIRrbIffwK2S+l74hwGNnF+EWrRqFhSNvce7q1eVrYd09ciVpTfV5/3vn7jU/N8IawlGtolxI1S/lL0b6i88HYi3ZwRO4+3eZhTsMDixKBYU9Mr303hwhtF5GCk78l9SioYWR8FhwpCjr3I8PsNuVTKopkUA0J1oV1efd7j45GDt8xU2e3kncI5ouG04oByPIUJ72mKfSWxCnIVu6sNZmhJmby9Dk3j0izGOjnGcPJLt78DviOn8rLxxsqQrKEKJME7LFoQSJb7PMmlmy+CVArNPc41iECvpM8Zsa5++2XZDVM+ANNFv1dGSTw==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "8 million square miles", 
		"option_b": "12 million square miles", 
		"option_c": "16 million square miles", 
		"option_d": "20 million square miles", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060102", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRrl+ZEpXBv80b33NHiQF2oU43OCQKRxY2WjXaTHLu7/2ddlKFiIlAQ5cZchk8kSb0rWbpNOJ1lEgw==", 
		"answer": "25S2fJDh0g3j9IRiIio72n9axbIAdckUYG2SUw==", 
		"explanation": "25a3ZoX63xzk48U3Wwr6hen3MCv8AnAWpmyXEop3dTHAVbeYLszw3ZZjJEiAjlo3smLOpuXj+EYbh61J54OQYzZDfYRh3NmH0urjiDFJPMpAicBm7J9fcPVSyzi+YJTSI/suzW+QZ1H/YzikRFlg1DLZhGhXoY2otSa5W88jgExi08d364goNNLfzqeB5En/lUaL337dCL5rHESLvN2h5UTcoYx4sN6ZuD/a4PH92u7c/MsGZ0hducZtbE67n6QQuHhvEcW9ZB5C/uqQYkHvKSvjLAcR9sbmwnF71cIdVWx0/RxDwoxYIuF9wpn2vyY5PMwqHCD6qkpD1ZF4VhWabf2s2GHn6xl/YnM/bcp+syAw4Q6OLVVt2m6ETylUkIll+ZBN2VQzLS9NmWLlkCzLiWvPeJbz/4i+H3SnAnqeU2muwsaRvTBtNg==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Africa", 
		"option_b": "Antarctica", 
		"option_c": "Asia", 
		"option_d": "Australia", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060103", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEgr31/C/M2TCQ3YZpj+EQKJ6ZX3iRufRe+/t3ZZ/JFnJi1Rp/3PC46Pi+F5Pna1d+4GFdSxDbYVg35CG2aT2hGJPPNFCk4V+4MVd46xL1b2zDqoidWTcAFsU1w==", 
		"answer": "25aqcYLn0BXm/oslEPuPHz9wzu+qUapZpwqtpR8=", 
		"explanation": "25Oxep+z9xb4+oQ0WxH8n73ZPHneQ2sC42uLV+NkYn7nQaTWLuL4iZh/IFOAg1w74XjJtOXx9FAagr1X6JqWfyxPPohgxcCI1PD+y38Nc8dKnsBi5YgLdfVMjDCoeMDSLvkuwWDAJgXjaTaqAnlxmDWWq28Wu5a49iKoR9MhxVU+l559/9t8M9Hfyqac/w25hQWX0W6dSalhXRSNvcuxq1aSpIcqssLNoSDU9/Hqif3AsNENIgtdspZtZkivnqcHuCs2VYigehNF4uLfc1nsNCGsKUJd/tni0mFoyo4wHX0h5hFPjIQWa85n2djitSA+f+R+VSG/s1ZF1JFySwTWdbP42Wbw5UcycH4iZJ5o/D4hoAiZaF1w2n+USWxFhoFl7dkNnAttPWlSk3ugjjCEk2DPb53s/MDoiqjjr7Vq9uMgJUCDPF3UFoQfYPFyDBXPSSkph67k7qApN1Vs", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Neve", 
		"option_b": "Firn", 
		"option_c": "Granule", 
		"option_d": "Crystalline", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060104", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRXr+YEmXQz/hfTsdWjYAnAQoGuGQKpudXWjVr6Cb63t3ZJ0NxDJhVRp4XOLsK3/8h4ch6lL7IrfciMQd4Uvzt+b2uHzhHNYc8FIm4N75ZZfeeZP3zSieouZdxUWTtFXodoD56SuNwSYJQ==", 
		"answer": "25axeoDm1FvyZS2YsEoP5FMbbTr0f6ra", 
		"explanation": "25axeoDm1FnG9oskVBHgyKe/FCvTCnAAtnrPEqJ4Y36jX6nNeeO+yIQxJhyKgklp+3OK46zjt1JPi6FI/YeRczZDcophzNaGxem3x2NEMtJBnsBw/doYcPVDxTyhNNHJL+1nwWDADlGwbir9B3h1hjDVnnlEoZm+8We5TZo2gAYmk4JooYg9MceX0Lyb7UysgxTPz3OQWLhgUVaYpsemq1SVtIp4tI2etD/S9/3rme3f8cxLbRoSt4ltcF6vn6cMtSYxWs30Zwdf/e3eZBTOKTqyMgsOucrx0zR935IgXmg4+AYGhIxDbMQz35aksT0lMdlrHD21tlcA1ZF7VhiYZ/253myk81AtY39rZJktqCUw4Q2VOkB2imedTylC1I9tvtcVlAdqeH1T3v1zuCD1U9jS0UWUOo9bR7I=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Arete", 
		"option_b": "Cirque", 
		"option_c": "Bergschrund", 
		"option_d": "Moraine", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060105", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxRz4+sUpQV7n1vj7dW3fESIFq3rDQat1YmGuUaPFa+m+2551IFmazV104HvDp+Xn/1YBz7xM5s6cfzARd458iNOcw6T1xXJKc8lK2o9i9JUMdeBFjC6kcNHIYPFojm/AKkrlaS28DX4r1ofXgUCnlCyMWsSDUoQdBns=", 
		"answer": "25SqbYX2wluZ1sz+Y3uG5tCXudbJxG89", 
		"explanation": "25SqbYX2wkOq1pclRhvhhfztMCvDC2MDszPDXKJmYn70FLXLaur72tdlL12dzV104HuGtK31+RMbmKcb6oeNYTcGbctq2t+N0qT1xXJKftJL14Jz55Ffc/oAwy29e8fSNPsu3WeEIlawaD/9BTB5myTYnn1fpsOP/SKoUZoxxRQmg5V9/og9LtLf2OiH7V6shwuH0m/RXLIkBVyc9d6n/EaOppc09cifviHS4vG5nPfB89sYIgdU/4FzYli1kroauAsqVNyxe1JE9/DVbxTlIT6mZx0J/M7zlmdlyZIsTik1+hsGj4JPItBh04vhsiZwPMVrGT+/rUNF1NRoUFebe6i2xGnt7lA6Z2lrYZ9o/Dk64RuULV1s2nmJSytUkMB/+8ILlA1tP5VVlHTXL4G8lSsWoDAfgJk=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Aretes", 
		"option_b": "Cirques", 
		"option_c": "Bergschrunds", 
		"option_d": "Tarns", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060106", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxQD68sUvVF7kxPHzMHKQEWcCtnOXQeNyYn7uFKDOb+73yJsxIk6GnlJ0/DqGoK3x5VIMm61J4JSadGIBZ8tuiMeA0+G7hHdNMtIEnIx964hfffpEjC65cdHLYO1nymuTeAfu48g7Lr2uvM0bF/3sBdw7", 
		"answer": "24D1e5nywRzut7MhXhL33L+aDGFy37VL3sDgTEMRYVx7", 
		"explanation": "24D1e5nywRzut7MhXhL33O6/fUzcAmEYonPDZrF7ZXbrR+6YLtiz2p9wN1mNzU16/nrDura8t1IDnKcb4oCQZyxDf5gvz9yI1O32yDFVIclRnYhhqNoNeedVwCntcsbULb5r1nqFKVb5cTz9A3x1lzjXhjxTuoyo/Ci1FO4/xQxyhohr/s0vL5eI0KyWpA2+igeWnH2dR7J2AhSYu8ro+FeZpZJ09cWEtjqW5/39n/yT598HbhsSi452cBu4nrsd8SQ7RcGibVJY+eXAZBTkM2iiZx4P9s/21WApyYRpSWExtBhUi41Sa850lpnquHIjPMJ/Bzq0pARBxIB1UBnWe7v412Tl41w6Z2lrZJktqCUwuE+RJ0J72n+UXiNEk4gr6tgc1Qhic2tTn3fwh31zjfEJWbS8xhHMxhhkWaAs", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "V-shaped Valley", 
		"option_b": "U-shaped Valley", 
		"option_c": "W-shaped Valley", 
		"option_d": "X-shaped Valley", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060107", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEgr31/C/M2TCQ3YZpj+HV7N7Y3j3FKjELv/xypwxIU6IilZ+/GLV46n18UdPja1T4ICbMCAaPoovz9yI1O3y1jFWO8NK2olmpJcacOBTk3/sz12vkMw68Ypo/cEDegmu", 
		"answer": "24GxZJ2xQXHTf85yJ43vLYbLX9qHwA==", 
		"explanation": "25i3epD63xyq04AwXQ370e6ldUbfEWMYrXqQEqJmdTHiV6TXY/jyyIN4KFKazVR9smTJoK6w8UEOiKVe55qMPGIQcYJjhJCI2eC3y2VJNtQEnoVw9pMMPPhFyintdtHTKfBqjmyZZ0SwdTypFnV1gDjYjTxRpIK4/CKpFO4/xQxylYh16Ig1Mpeb0K6V7V+9iBLC2nSDRa4oUV2XtsK970qSp8IssN+AuDza+LT0lerS+dAOcUhFt498axuxlroCuD4wVIizZBNI+OHCJketJimxMwYY6t+j13B/x4wqWCV09RFCwo9XdsVh15SksT0iPsRkECD6tExJxJw8TQKYNLy032bjoFwrZjo4bI5or20Yrh2dIVp7iSudXikRl5J+/dkYmURqc2tJn3f0jS2YwGqJPIPi+JS8guTxo7Bi/uMmKlWJI1XMT8/1l5pNHx5dwHbINVaE1Fig", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Boulder Clay", 
		"option_b": "Till", 
		"option_c": "Drift", 
		"option_d": "Ground Moraine", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060108", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq9sUSXR36wL3SOn7EDGwfpnrcEKN0bO7gv4aSwkM/sxLLv14=", 
		"answer": "24e9e5jgxRjk48UyXR35hfXqOGbfAGlT/A2HdxxNxF1jGUlbY0F2tw==", 
		"explanation": "24e3a5n2kTTl4pEvXBD3wKe/FCviDGEZpj+uXbZgf3/tUaKCZ/6+yNdkKVWYmF479XrHoKzx+xMDjqZf74GNfWIqastm25CIl/f6y35VO8pd2pJ98ZQbefAA3jKuf5TTKfJijmGSZ07+aDWxRGR8lSWWiHlXupD74S++FNc20h4h1oh+rc8wPdSW2KTT7V+3lQ+N0ju+RrgkAl2dsI6n7QOIqId4h8KOuTeb2fvsjvfd/tsOIgBTrMZ+I1y5mbwF/WZ4QsW7ZwZD9OCQcljiMC3jIQ8e8MXklmBhw8ItVHsx9wtPjY0WbcYz0ZTlvzs1LY1nGiW/rkFO09g8SB+feLj4xGDhoFovZXU4bJ5o/D48pQrcIUc+jnKMRS9QmIxyvsMNkAFzPW5OmDbqgziMhWHNd00auHGJo2TBHdxqghN+iw==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Resistant rock hummock", 
		"option_b": "Smoothed downstream side", 
		"option_c": "Roughened upstream side", 
		"option_d": "Ice movement", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060109", 
		"question": "24KwbYP2kRD5t5EoV17RxO7rOW6QMW0SqD+MVONRdHjtVrLQaeW+xZhyJkiMiQQ5vSTlbpbT1oYXgb66v1BOIg==", 
		"answer": "24a7Z4X/0BfutVopuub7fTCCuB4dNEKcGuw=", 
		"explanation": "25a5e4X/1FnY+IYrEhH0hdj7PGXSFnAWqyXDZqtxMFLiR7POa63MxpR6Z1OPzX5/+3jEtrf3/xMGnOhaqZ6Nfy8KcI5h3JCf2Oj0xX9IMIZWlYN5pJwQbvlB2DSiepTXL/1v2muEZ0z+Jy21ATB8kTDEnjxZrsOe8S61Vs8lxx1+1rR74twwPdmbmYGHqESrxhKK2TuXR6hqFVWNvMGmq1aMr4x4osWEsjqb0fDwlPrG4tkDIitTrJJzZhf8lqZJ8CMrRcemYREL9+vCdUboMzvvZwcOucn233h9hrYhWCkX9QxSjoYWUM9w3djsvSFwL8FrDDa+40UAxJFySwWXeP2q32ThoFwxNW4jYMputTks5hzcIF1tjmSOVWxQmoQr98NZlAojdGJQk2T0gzGfwGaacIf2+YHwxeTxrr1u87Esa0bxgkh/abjH5lOpzjs1BGM=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "England", 
		"option_b": "Scotland", 
		"option_c": "Wales", 
		"option_d": "Ireland", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060110", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEh39yO3wJmLECm0f43CFEoF7ZX3nUbWCTeH/0Nd+NRyugVp4+3fK45H5+19QzYQUHu4CQ0Fi0b+wJWEtVtQ=", 
		"answer": "25OxZpSzwxbp/MUmXhHn17/gzBpV1pdqo4EooduLGAla", 
		"explanation": "25e3fZ331Auq1IkhS179173YOWrTCmMd40uKXq80U37uRKjRZ/n3xpkrZ36GmFd/92SGgKnx7h9PjqRI5s6Ufi0UcMtu25Cu2+X0zXBNc/JNlow+pJMMPPdPwS2iZ9HfYPFojm+OZ1D+dDavEHVw1DzfkmhDuob7+iH7WdsjxQc7l4trreEofN6R2qSG7EirxgWO3WLdCK5tHUDV9d2p5UfQ4IM2sY2bsCDS++Hq1+va6tsPIhpdvI1sI0+0lrxJ7y8qVIikYRFA9OCQdEStISanZxoP+MXwxnt70octHWsttBhKg4BfZ9JglqzsuXIzMMB6GiCzt01PydRzWVeUe6i01G32oFYzdGNrZotj/Ds0sxbcP116n2eFDChUhIVl+tkXkkRscy9UlHOghTqEjGqIdZDi58DxhOP1takj/aVnPUmFdUjdRJ8dbL2ALnMyxfuSCq9SMotiE2LgL9ojvoSS5IhHtUYVtdrElcyD5Bk=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Boulders and stones", 
		"option_b": "Sticky clay", 
		"option_c": "Fine rock flour", 
		"option_d": "Mounds and hills", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060111", 
		"question": "2523f9Hywxyq0pcyUwr7xu6/IHjVBXcd43aNErZ6dHTxR7PDYOn3x5AxIFCIjlJ6/jbLrLP1+lYBm/cZAoR3j8T/PsVAZLXob2PpjA==", 
		"answer": "24GwbYizwxz88oQsEgr6wL32Nm6QDm0HpnKGXLczYzHnXbXHbfn3xpkzhUG6wWJBA8ehYeqbWWYcPA==", 
		"explanation": "25CqepDn2Br5t4QuVl7Vyfz8PGrcQ08etXqOV61gKjHGRrXDeuT92tdwNVnJgVpp9XOGoarl+1cKnbsb/YaeZGIUe5lqiMSb1urk1H5TJ8NA2oF84NobeeRP3zS5cdCbIucuyWKBJEz1dSr9AnFm1DfEhXEWvIu+/DX7W8g+xxw8l4s4/scpLtSamZyb7VT4hxSHnG6CTbtxHRSQu4695UeZspEstMOJuDzctPP1m/va8dJLbwdEuot6bU/8la0K+T8rVIigYBdC46TTbln9LzuqMwcS94vi2HApyo0qXH09+xEGgYJYItBh2Y7tuDdwPMF/ECD6okZP0oA8Sx+TNLmxwm3n9Fwwezoqa44tuTUhpAGIaFt42nudXzgRk4xq/dkYgQ1scy9ihTbzliqPmWyBe9Pm+ZL9keHzs/Uj4aAuLE+UPE/MRc0fZL2ANWJxxeeIGbRJMIsnAyrjfdMi8y65MJeAyzwf3spgIHGn9SSam8j7LSW9v5P6h9FkB/3s8ItaDDiqPxvxMsGV+Q7M", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "They provide a timeline of glaciation", 
		"option_b": "They indicate temperature changes", 
		"option_c": "They show the age of the rocks", 
		"option_d": "They reveal the ice movement's direction", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060112", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq9sUjWh/gxP7rMHnZEHYYoD+FV6JgZWPmFKjELsns3Jp9LlKa0hnNBhUOeJj6Fc1ZsNXJ3zB5", 
		"answer": "25axepLm3Rj4t5YoUw73h59g1PJGQiFQ5mdDlS+jo+k=", 
		"explanation": "25GqfZz/2Beq1I0hQB/x0fjtPHjECmEC+T+nQLZ5fHjtR+fDfOi+zJt+KVuImV5/vjbVrqr/41sDluhJ5puRdCcHPoNmxNyal+L41nxEN4ZCiI9/pJ0TffdJzTHtYN3XLL5axmuZZ03xcTz9BTB3nDDEi39CrZGy5jOyV5ojxRQgkpV3/YgzLpeW176W+lm9gkaRzHSeRv13GVWJsILo/EqIqMI59cqIvybX8bTqlvfD9Z4EbEhGt4M/dkuvg7oM+Sd4QsGwbVJK/+CQYBT+NC2mNwsPtYvu2WZshoMrT3wk4F9VjoxGZ4B82NjwtDdwO8J9GyCusUFBytRvVhOTNJmqxWXo6VssNXs5YMp5pT08og6QJE0+nGSJQigRnY4r/8IclBcjaWdBiDb3hy2OwGqBf5aj6I/qgPr1pPlh6+MuKkTAJlTdU5kPJ0RmTuCC+l1+bvEReYFArzs=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Circular shape", 
		"option_b": "Oval shape", 
		"option_c": "Pyramid shape", 
		"option_d": "Rectangular shape", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060113", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Brl+YotWx2y1vT4O2LWCmEQrXyGEqd7MFTwX6LQfa32yIF0eB4ulaJPA1V9VYLAtq/v9+tX", 
		"answer": "24WqZ4f61Ryq+YQ0Rwzzyb3tMHjVEXQeqm2QECJLfwFJWrIXL/uDq36ZmSI=", 
		"explanation": "25CrY5Thwlnr+YFgdx39y/LyPGiQMGsWrXaFW6B1fnLmDufnfeb724QxJk6MzVd0/HGK47L5+VcGga8b+4ebdycQPohgxcCGxOHzhH5Hc9VFlIQy5ZQbPPNSzSuoeJTPKP96jnmFNUCwYzytC2N9gDTSyn5P6JCv5yK6Wcl3xhk9gY526ogrNcOX0KbT51/4hAOM2XqFQP1lUVOVtM2h7lHclIo9rI2Mozeb8ff2lPfe+d0KbgRL/5V2ZFW1kaEK+SQsEcqxaxNe4uGQdVzoOWisIRoY94vg2Xp9x4snHX81+ApHgI9TIsR2xpf3tSYjf8JsVSC7rUAAxpp4HxCEdau93CSk9102dnJrZJho/CgmsgqSPF1/liuaQz4Rl49l7cQLgAd3dGBO3HvhljqZiWSDb9PG+Iv5l/uwoatmsrcvPFLAJEnZRJ8VYLeAIWhgiv2TCLVZc41iBC3zL9Yr73W5MISbyTAJ2dcnb3bptC+ancP6NGy585D8gNFwHatAIt6F6sS6vUnJaDfoJG7TaM71S0jkR3n1kZADn8wG77qpfND1FnqQENs=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Source of hydroelectric power", 
		"option_b": "Provide natural reservoirs", 
		"option_c": "Provide sand and gravel", 
		"option_d": "Support heavy cropping", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060114", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gYBHxzfi/GGTFF20frXqGEqpnMHCjRqLRZ/7qyJllZ06GjlA7+mPLrqrz/BMJgLpW7IrfcjtDeYduy9mI26T2x2VIPMgEpo5O6qgafedPwmftXcDIYOt+3XqSIkT9Jyq0AHU0nSKWmXFZp5ez8CP7VsN3wRcgl5Rx4sZ8PdmbmaGH+w28iRGMz2+DTbxpUUeQscvo4lDcso0tssWIvzfftPbg2ujf5d0AawZV/T8T9QItO9y3i9CzWdWJ/1c=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiITtmvDYON9YzHtW7OCeuX7iZR+NU6Mjk87927Wr6T+9kcGgKYb5ojfUWD+EWo9SHvOp9e7QgxzX71L", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gcRHg1/j8ISvxQ1AeoHeGEo57ZWXsWqnHa6332tdwZ06MnlJo5nfIt+Xi+FAEz6BO5IOQcylDbYNu2NWNl+buhHZNMsVNm4wy5ZkLdftOjBS5NMDCMPdtz2KMPgX4Zir9BTBnmT7ZnnRTrMOu5TSvRt82zVUhn4N9rYAwOdLfyqGX7QT4hwiGnHrRWrJxFlycu8usq0eTt4wrod+IsD+b5/39n7ib48oEcRsSrI97ZhL8k70MuD43Ecy9bhRO4+3eZhToMiewLgETudvx2Xds1ZEsTlU6yBF0h4JFbc4plrvrriA1PNkqITu/41ZFxodzUVeGZrKu2Wzh8xU+ezoqZol4riwhpE+ZMERym2WdWCVemsBt8cJZgQxmPWxInWThgSuOkmycaJrgq4b5hPzlsrxwsqwhaUDAB1PbXohcSLzVM2h8xOyeQeZPJo93GDDyNNspvC3xJdaVzCoIws0pIHmlzJttVSBQA0LE3aXR5EZ/0g==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060115", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gcQzzwr3+O2+QN2MYrz+KQeN1MH3iWqPEYf/ziYB4M1TJjBt282XV46r2twBPnadY4s6PYi0Xe4h7wd6Ol/D/wTFNNsNTm5J2pIkWePEAyi+ieZTeMvF9x2GOZ3n+WzePAXFnmz+MykhercOY9DSvWN938hoxncd364gZON6R272B70X4jxXC3TuSRLx3Al2a9cuw6k6MrId4usvNkiDa87T4lPyTxN8Cbkqu6k9nRclu7FTfOcU8tqX9", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiIQrXvDYON9YzH3XKKCbeLs25JyMxyMlUt383jHt6z/+RMJgLobyMzhe6ddeFdnLLMGFYjfRT4E", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gcRHg1/j8ISvxQ0EDonjDU61wMEXiXauCZ/6+yNd9JlKNi1Rp/zbRq6Di8hMOz6Va+p3ffyRDLct9x9OCl/f/zXRNN9UEjoh3pJYaeeNB3jntZ93fJb5o3GGNZ0DiaCq0C3441DLEj31CoY28tSb7UNMk1Bw8lZM4/sA9LNKj15Sd2ki5lQmMhjuyR692FFeN9fqg7gO/oZEsucjNgz3Y/7T2nLj29NcFYB1AuI4zI0y0nqsBuCMrEcn0ax5K4vfZYhToOCmuNwIYucTllnUp5ZAoWik1+hsGtoJfbowz0p3pszwjK99rATap41BIzoc8UxaYcLu3wmWk8FAtc38ocYZ0/Bk9pE/PaEZxmWDcQyoRgIhuvtMYhhBveC9Bn2Lzwj6YwHGHedPfqYPuhO/M4vlz4KwzLEKUPFLfFpkUYPP8ZXNzw+WnT+ZeNpduGSamNMFu+iv2LdaRzTYe2dYubR5PD6ITojgR20HXd5J/3Bk=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060116", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gdw35wO/sdWrCBiIdrHGEHuN6cWPxW7CCfOT6zpJiZ1+GgEt04XPC46r2t0AOgawb6ICbMCURf51qxJC12dj59nRAIMlKwMBG7J8GPPlB3jbtYNzeYPhh3GOFNQXjbi24FzB7knHFn34br4+69i66WJo6xRkm25B5+c0ufMSLy62S5V76cA9oTjCm6UIxtebjOgg/WA==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiIQrXvDYON9YzH3XKKCbeLs25JyMxyMlUt383jHt6z/+RMJgLobyMzhe6ddeFdnLLMGFYjfRT4E", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gcRHg1/j8ISv1EGkUsWzDU7FxMH3sWqCOLuP/24V+MBybhF9892WGoKr951wciqwb5ojfYyMNestuxtTJ0Pb20nRNc/JMn5ky5YgaPPJP3jCocJTZOb56xmvAI0DgaCq0EHl7mnHZjDxbqZe+5y66WJo0wQcgn4J8rcolfMSK2+WU5Ey7jweOnHaURKkpBlWNsNzo+FeOpYM1po2Yvzbe5rT42v/f8d0CZxpusbpxUV69hKcHomobXtqmbRFfsdDYZBT/JSmwKABd+sTxxHFq0o4wHWws5BNHi41FItR709jrrjs3NsMqGjX6pldLwoZvE1eFYLys2WbjoEE3dG5rcYJopW04oB2XaEB2nyuaQz5ckZIr/d8Mhxdmbi9Pmjbzlz3Gh2mOf5ri58DxgOTk7a5i5qY1aVKUJ1nZW55cUbvJNCdh3/mLArRIIN9zHyemPMY9+SvtKZmancRECT7svfn/UFtPmlzUSew=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060117", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gdRLzxvT6J3iQAGMf43yRV6JgdTHWGbTKb/37zddnJlCFiEJosn/I46358FsDjqZfqZyadysMcJhTxuyH5eH2135PaYZjloFx7Z8Nb7RF3jKpcZTNIfJiy3eTZ0fpJzuyEHg0hD3DiXdfpoT79Cm/FNs10hQhn4h2rdguM9SayruW+w9exUzGl2TCuMLUQyWYfNcu", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiIQrXvDYON9YzH3XKKCbeLs25JyMxyMlUt383jHt6z/+RMJgLobyMzhe6ddeFdnLLMGFYjfRT4E", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gcRHg1/j8ISv3D2MSqnqRQeN1YnSjXanGa+j6iZRwN12LgV47/XCGprf/81oBiOhN6IKTdTsQPoJhiNiA0Oz7xX9Fc9RBnYl96olTPPdSyTy5fdrcYPpn3XqJKUbkbi+4REU5hznXmnlS6JW6+Su+Tcl3xAA31pN3rdw0OZec1qWR4UO9gkaSznSSTa53FEfZusjo+0+Jo4kxu8rNsDzftPX7iPnA+dEFXgZusbR6YkizmfJJ2yUqQ823fFJ/+eGQc1HsMyetZx4P9t3q0nF6hoMnHWg39wpUg5dTIsR2xZv2tSIkNsJkVTy840xP0NR7UxaVfbiqwyj36FQvcDo9ZIZhuTQm4RuUOltrnWPcTiNFnMB78sUang1tei8IiH7lwjOChnGGcpSj5Ia8l+fzq/ll4KIgJESOIU+RFowSYfPBJXVz2eCUA+YUJ5diVyX0NNsq9Tf+YJea23ke09Y1PX7p82qWlI3hMWD6pZP1gtFvVLkMOd7Xqcq5tBzUaCfkMjTRTl9qCAOD3pnKcMpPIoenGg==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060118", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9geh/8wvTxMivGAm4dpmaQEqJmdTHsUrPHYK3/2oR+JFWImV5/smHPt62w4FIbirpd6IKTY2IKcMtoxNGK3uXjwXUBP8dKnpNx5Yoab8hO8DOfcdXIL/A0jlqSLkflczivHTBilT3aj2VF6Iu6+yD7Vdg41hBym4Zx44gqPduT3LGAqE+9hQeXz37RXLVhUVmYvMDo/UKQrIch9cqBsDHS8ebq2v3B/9oOIgVdrYM/cVqsnqwF4Wi+N4eoC1TIw2zsqOSAFmDX", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiIQrXvDYON9YzH3XKKCbeLs25JyMxyMlUt383jHt6z/+RMJgLobyMzhe6ddeFdnLLMGFYjfRT4E", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gcRHg1/j8ISv4AmwWqnGEErV1fH3mTbSCb//7iZh3M1mHzVpo4XnFqqTk8ldPmKFP4c6IcTYGbI1uxNyal+35hHZNMsVNm5R34NoTffpE3z6sZNHIYMpmy3fAJlf1JzyxAWZ1gDTSymhEoYGu4SapTZohwRk+k55rrdw0PcPf0KaH7V+rgwWWnGyYXLUkBVyc9cOp4k3ctoM0uciUjTzn+sb8m+vc/oRLQQdArYN8dxuIn61J6i85Qse6KBNI8vHCYEDoLDHjIhYN9crq2Gcp0YowHWE1+hhPjIQWdMF/2p39r3I1J8R5AX/6sFBB051yWFeCfLyskHzs5Ux/fXslYspsviIjpE+IIFE+l2qVQmxHlYxn+8kK1QB2eC9Ukzb0ijrLjWSGctP16ozwgPGwp7Vi8aoiO1LAME7XUoQSYvPNKHV3ivuaHa9YP4YnIyrvLpU96SnpL4SAzHkZ2NxgLmT08TiNm8L7e7ckG5yNKLoKASwowdLcoqk=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060119", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gdxD2hfDwJ2rZDWcC436RV+Nyf2PuUaOCbPS+zptwJFWMn0g75X7DreXk/1YWz7pe6I2XMDYLe8t8zdG12dj59nRAIMlKwMBb558deeZH332uddqbIfJ9wS6EIlX/dDCpRH17hjDfhHVV6I664SKpXds7gAI6k4k4+cA5JZeS3KSHqES2xhKK2TuCTbwmmoj0uxkbpHblTAPcdRW95A==", 
		"answer": "25T4YYKz1xjm5IBgUAvmhc+/PHiQF3AEpj1H3esm/O0e/DyDhrhK09GF", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gexDxyu/tMGjEQ0cfpz+OXbF1eX/mR+fDfOi+z5hjKlmNzVlisnHKoqb58kEcw+hZ/Jrffi0XPpxnzd7Jw+zy3TFTNsdHksBm7J9fb/FBjAmlcc2bIexrjm2SIkTkYj39E3hxmnHRhn1VoYap5meoQNUngBQ2gIZ27sEyO5ee16zT6ki/jwjCyHTRWrhwA1GYoYLo50adtos2so2PtDrS+vC5m7jB+doMZ0hducZ7Zlmunrs19hY2Y821ex1Fq6Tzbkb/JSu3Zyce/MnmxHN6hoEoUyk39Q1Um8NbbdJy35btv3I9PtlvBzq7rwRXz5FyHwOecaT402no9lB/c2gkaMpqsCw2qAqOOxg+mH6IDDhZkZkr+t9Zmwt3PWtFjHnziyvLiXHPa5vm5cDoje3p4LRm/rdnIE/AIVTdFp4ZZPPpKXRmz+ifQeZIO5p+VzDjMdAv7zy5NJ6Rnz0I0sspPDfu+j6W0tn9PCW1sJf4gJYfM3xkSrXsKfXGKS67jJHS", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060120", 
		"question": "25K0aZL60BWq8pcvQRf9y732JivAEWscom2KXro0c3D2R6LGLu/niYNmKByZn1R492XVpraqt2wwsJdk1rGgTx1Df4VriNGLxeXkzX5PcXdWSl8b+7564DybVxs+Gck=", 
		"answer": "26W0fZL42BfttclfJj8668khktftF628cCw=", 
		"explanation": "25K0aZL60BWq8pcvQRf9y732JivdAmsfr2bDVrF9ZnTtFKXbLv3y3JR6LlKOzVp19jbHobfx5FoAgehr5ZuceysNectgy9Ocxfe303lEPYZQkoUy45Yef/1F3n2rZtHeOvt9jnqPZ1H4YnmoCnRxhj3Pg3JR6JG09iz3FM4ywQch1oht+Yg1MtOWz6GX/Uy0xgSO03iaW/EkEFqd9cq66kSP4JYwsMDNsCXa7bTNkvHAsM4ZbQtXrJU/c1e9jrtJ+WorWM+6YRRC8uXedRT/LySmZwcTudjr12RgyIVpWmU19xZHloZSIsxy2Jz3vzMgOt4o4j8UmBzaMZnBFsDQqYBxvw==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "pl,uc,ki,ng", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060121", 
		"question": "2525Zpb63x6q4YQsXhvr1r3+J26QBW0DrnqHErR8dX+ja5j9UdLB9qhOGByfjFd392/V46Di+FcKz6VU+4vfYy4MaYd2iMSB1uq30HlEc8tFk44y8psTcPFZ338CyMj6r+bEnJ/M6KVKLnkY", 
		"answer": "26GqYZPmxRj47seLYCG8FPWBtgIYKSZ/iA0J", 
		"explanation": "2525Zpb63x6q4YQsXhvr1r3tMHjFD3ZRpW2MX+NgeHSjUK7EaOjszJllLl2FzV5p/WXPrKuw5VIbirsb64uLZycGcMtiydmHl/L2yH1EKtUEm452pI4NdfZV2Dy/bZTNIfJiy3eTZ2jxbjf9EnF4mDTPmTAWv4qv/We3VcgwxQdykYt57sE5LsTTma2B50m9xguNzn7RWrx0GFCVrILo6EKJs4s2so2ZuTeb4ObwmO3H8cwSIh5Ts4p6ekj8g6dJxGgwUMazVFAL8Obfd1GtISanZwEb7c7tlnd7w4M9WCkj9QtDkIVXbsxglEiwkQzabydlc4m+1CGCbRo=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "tr,ib,ut,a,ry", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060122", 
		"question": "25K0aZL60BWq45cvRxn61r33NH3VQ2NRp3aQRqp6c2XqQqKCW6DtwZZhIhDJjlN64HfFt6Di/kkKi+hZ8M6eMDUKeo4jiNaF1vC3wn1OPNQEm452pKUgQ8t/8wKSS+ubM/dqy33C21uNznSg6wlippE6BOU1zQ==", 
		"answer": "26asbZTjk4+Gf8ouV4gmpPaUONhA6sE=", 
		"explanation": "25K0aZL60BWq45cvRxn61r3+J26QCGwetHHDVKxmMGXrUa7QLtiz2p9wN1mNzVZ04GbOrKn/8EpDz79S/YbfcWIFcop7iMaI2+jy3TFHP8lLiMBz6p5fb+BFyS3tZ93fJe0u+maJNAXjbzitATB9h3HXym5Tu5a34We0UpowzBQxn4Z0rc0uM8SW1qbT6UO8xgKHzHSCQaltHlrZsdu64k2b4JYwsI2ksjeb1fP8ibqxlN8+HY3X3s3m6bONzhRT", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "ste,ep,sh,eep", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060123", 
		"question": "25i3epD63xz5t4QyV17xyvDvOnjVByIepT+RXaB/MHfxVaDPa+Pq2tdlL12dzVpp9zbDrqf181cKi+hS586YfCMAd45925CI2eC3wHRRPNVNjoV2pI0XefoA2DWoNNPXIf1ny3zAGHrPWAaCO09Lq3MyyS1cUTXRp7EPlEg513Df", 
		"answer": "27i9ZIXgk0o6jSW55iu3GFlFwSMS2Fs=", 
		"explanation": "25i3epD63xz5t4QyV170yu/yMG+QBXAerj+RXaB/MHfxVaDPa+Pq2tdmLkiBhFU79XrHoKz15UBPjqZfqY+NdWIHe5tg29md0uC303lEPYZQkoUy45Yef/1F3n2gcdjPM75axmuTIgX3azi+DXF41DXTmnNFoZeotTe3VcN3wVUxhJJ75MkwfMWQ1a3T4UP4lQ6DzHKfT/1wGVHZuc+m71CfoZI9po2Ct3Lc+PX6k/nH9dpLcA1VtolxcBlPt7IthlZjADCvX5++taZe", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "me,lts,fre,eze", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060124", 
		"question": "25T4Wp7w2Ryq2oo1RhH8y/j6dWLDQ2EZom2CUbdxYnj5UaOCbPS+yNdiKlOGmVM752bVt7f19l5PnKFf7MLfYzYRd4p7zdTJxPHlwnBCNooEm452pJtfbvtVyzWoetHfYMFR8VG/GHrPWAb9F3lwkXNyU+V/iqL81ZzGI+QWKcAp", 
		"answer": "27G3f5/gxQvv9ohiXfOuh3QIT/N+YoEdX0HKOQ==", 
		"explanation": "24e3a5n2kTTl4pEvXBD3wLG/JmPRE2cV432aEqR4cXLqVauCb+7qwIF4M0XFzVN64TbH47b9+Fwbh61fqZuPYzYRe4piiMOA0+G3wGREc9JL2oFw9psMdftOjDyjcJTaYOxh22mIIkv1Y3X9F2RxkSHTmDxSp5S15jOpUds6gAY7koI47Nt8PZeN3LuG5Fn4iQDCzHeES7ZtH1PZgMCs7lGPtIM2scSDtnLS4Oe5nP3S5MsZZxsSt4Nzc0j8nqwM9j4xV9H0fBpOseHWZ1HuNDvjKAhd/sfi1X1o0osmUyuPS/VI1kuDpEuEdBshOkoE", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "do,wn,st,re,am", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060125", 
		"question": "25aqaZaz0Bfut7EhWxKyw/LtOGrECm0fsD+AXa1neWL3FKjELuy+mtdjKF+CzVhp83GGs7f/41YMm6FV7s6eMCUGcJ9jzcLFl+Hly3VEN4Z7pb9N26UgQ8t/jC6kcNGbJuxhwy6HK0TzbjixRGdxlSOUC7JogvjuXsZod/H1bSKIcg==", 
		"answer": "27m9bYbywx2oce8OiTQ1DnGaW+KpJCRr7Q==", 
		"explanation": "25y2KLLh0B6q9oskEirzzPG/M2TCDmMFqnCNQe80ZHnmFKTQb+q+wIQxJhybiEhy4WLHrbGw+lIcnOhU786NfyEIPpxm3NjJ1qTk0HREI4oEj5Bh8IgaffkA3zSpcZibMOxh2muDM0z+YHmpDHU0hz7QnnlE6I++8DC6Rt530xw2k8d+/8cxfNKHza2d+0Sug0aF0HqSQbxoUVGLut2h5E3clIoxpo2Oozfa4PHq2vmT9NcYdgFcvJJ2dV78m6kH/Dk7UNixKBRO8PDFc1Gvo4i+3KhE6hu2lH2Xk6sBlw==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "le,ew,a,rd", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060126", 
		"question": "25e3fZ331Auq9IkhS1KyxPHsOivbDW0GrT+CQeNzfHDgXabOLvn3xZs9Z1WazVp1smPIsKri41YLz6xe+YGMeTZDcY0v3tGb3uvi1zFEIclAn4Qy6ZsLeeZJzTG+OJTSLv1i22qJKUKwZTaoCHRxhiKayn9aqZr3tSa1UJolzxY51oF04t0ucJeMybqW6Un4iROWnHKfCK5sFFGNpo6p6FGTs5F4ivKyjg3ky8vGpbjD/N8CbBsQFEYEsFdGLPdnyHyV+6YgiA==", 
		"answer": "27K9ZoX/yFn/+YE1Xh/mzPP4d5aBmH9orDjubokq6YtDP7w=", 
		"explanation": "25e3fZ331Auq9IkhS1791734OWrTCmMd42uKXq80dn7xWbSCaejw3ZtoZ0mHiU5382LPraKw518OhqZIqbqXdTEGPo9q2N+a3vDkhGdAId8Ek44y4p8NaP1MxSm0NNDeMPtgymeOIAX/aXmpDHV9hnHVhXFGp5Cy4S60WpZ3zRQ5n4l/rdw0OdrfyqGU5kS+jwWD0m/RTrJ2UVWep8er/k+ItZA99cyDtXLX9fr92u3A9Z4CbEhVs4d8alqokqxJ6i8/WMe6e1A20XrdUSleObXb0XWg6LY5", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "ge,nt,l,y un,dul,at,ing", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060127", 
		"question": "25CqepDn2Br5t4QyV17wyujzMW7CECIFsX6NQbN7YmXmUOfAd633ypIxJlKNzVd+9GKGsLHi9l0Liqwb4IDfYicEd4Rh25Ce3+HlwTFVO8Nd2oFg4docc/lQwy6ocJTUJr5jz3qFNUzxayr9AHlykjTEj3JC6IWp+ir7QNIygBk9lYZ0rc85M9uQ3rHT3EW9n0aDzn7RXa5hF0GV9cin+QOIsoM7vMOK8SbT8bTGpcfsz+E0XTdt/4l5I1K/kugE9zw9XM26fFDsTC3YwxaycewqHXxfR4sj", 
		"answer": "26a3fYPw1Fnr+YFgVhfgwP7rPGTeQUbKxcCqKmaB0cmJQ+pM4wU=", 
		"explanation": "25CqepDn2Br5u8UkRxuy0fK/IWPVCnBRtnGKQ7ZxMHLsWbfNfeTqwJh/axyBiFdrsmLUoqb1t0cHiuhI5puNcydDf4VriNSAxeH00HhOPYZLnMB7559fcftWyTCoesCbJOt8x2CHZ0L8Zjq0BWR9mz+WvnRTu4b79yiuWN4y0gZyhZN548x8M8KLmaGdqEG5iAKR33qBTa4oUUSLutih70qSp8IutMGYsDDX8bTwlP7c4tMKdgFdscZ+YVSpg+gd8C94QcmnfFJK8vDZblr+YCelZwkR+Mjq02Z6hGAFqg6rnLmWmVjRYKu/1Xs=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "so,ur,ce a,nd d,ir,ec,ti,on", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060128", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fQa+r/25N4KVvJv1R4+nOGjqrl41wBga1eqYeMMCsNfYR92tWKw7u3+H8Qc+9Q2pJ3958SfvhF332sNMfTJft+3WWJKQXnbj79C353kXHBhW5Y6Iq1tQ6vVdYugCk8xMdR+dt8KceMzbqW6UD4lQ+G2TuYW/13HFuWocbo71aZ4JY39cyPozPI/fv32sTdo54idk9B/4VwblazmaQQuCw3RMawKB1F/f2QaFqtLCe0Kw8T/Yvk2nVqz4M9WG105hpBi4xYcYLynxyMWPcPEFYBGGGlRbV7", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUqq+IssS1wji07jg50EhYK2o3/aFidB", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7by/7wJ3nVAHZRkXCAWqY0XX72QKjMYOj7iZN+Ik/Jg1RvsmTDsKD99V8Kz6kb+oaadTIQdYJhiMeA0KT4ynJEc9FLiI4y7ZRfVeBBwCTtXcCcM75vjmmMJkb5ZjX9CHF6kDfZmHEWq4u65ya4QN8lyQ83ksd69Ig9fMSS1qeH4EGhxhSNyXWVTbkkA1uavo6g4k+Q4I0q9caDvj7XuLTqkvnD9dpLYBESuIp+YFK9m+gM6iUrWMe6VBx3/9fEYEDoLS2tM05Po4vA2WZ7w4E9HV088V9TkpBCcMVy29j3tTY1f8JsVTL6kUtDz5E8chiDYLK23m3hoFwsNWkmaoV5tG0xtArcPFs+m2mOTT9Ym44rytgQhkRwdGtF3HDhgTqYwHGHedPn4pL5hvz5r7cj/aVnLk2BNlXdRM0RaqXFKmJ83qmaA6IcOownBCrnLdAqvDvgYIKc2nke08shP37p82qYkdn8Nmv6vJS5mtxzVLgMN9LM7NmLvmDJUjfgNXieY8XgGVuqD1X20AF3pR0m3GEi52HQDclS+jgZkXC+TEF30iThYjyjk/5a5ZeAe8443bXu0iYY2Ph3iJf22hl8Rgq/zWpTvoWRSxxIwVXVF8wTwQ1uHrEGHZnf4S2inXPJC30feo74DrzH0SlbzvH4jXV4u9AaWsyCIw7Xi9AiiBajBPxqGSfspoK5Pv0bSmYpuqJjz/6kud77fP3kOmQ4ZhWiSq9N6oVUe0J0F0vJADZdYbGgFKFgda56r6LxjTz2/GQmyXQ=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "3 only", 
		"option_d": "1, 2, and 4 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060129", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRj48sU0WhuyxvX+J2rTF2cDqmyXW6BnMH7lFILQfOzqwJRieBy1gwo7xn7DuuXn8kEKz7xJ6ICMYC0Rao5riNKQl/P+ynUBD8gW2rR64YNffeZFjDuiYdrfYPdgjnyFIEz/aSr9AHlykjTEj3JC6IWp+ir7QNIyyQdymZVx6sEyPdvf2qee+EKrjxKL03XRdLM3UWCRsNfo6lGZ4JY9p8CItXLL8eb6kv3XsNwHbQtZrMZ2ZRu6mL0H/GoxX4ikehdI8PbZbkH+YDisNAcJ8MTtxTZhIRI5aDV3CrprdBai0xaF", 
		"answer": "2+f4aZ/3kUqq+IssS1z5CJjjQYToCkb2LtWsGmEU", 
		"explanation": "24GwbYiz0Avvt4MvRxD2hfTxdXnVBGserWzDVqpydnTxUanWLuvsxpoxM1SMhEk7/WTPpKz+9l9PjKdW+YGMeTYKcYUv7cKb1vD+x2IBMtRB2oxz9p0aPOZPzza+NNvJYPxh22KEIlfjJy21BWQ0gzTEjzxCuoK15je0Rs4yxFUzmIM46c0sM8SWza2XqE+hxgGO3XiYTa93XRSWs9qt5QOaoZB4s9+CvHLP/PHwiLjA/8sZYQ1usbpxV1O5jugI6i94Rc2mZRdPsfTVc1flJSzjJQIS+sDwln1vhoQmSGcwtBZIwpNEZ8NyxJHrqSFwL8J5HCezrEpTh6R5TRSecbn40mTr414sNXs5YMporj80tQafOxRqkmqIDC1DkcBt8cUXkURqcy9QjnPjgy2Cj3CcPJzxq4XwgP7xtLxnsrMoOkiUPFPWRcFcdqbDLydz2amZDKpdPZxiE2LpM5U69Dy5NJmEzHkC1pkvO3/i5mqLnc7+KiW1odL6gt1wEqw8OO3L2t+2pFnKZC31YSzTb9i0UAbzQG7q1g1x9z032iAE4WHLSIht8G0djHe9SFZtnj6geG6gmK1M5ZCaeopx0eys2j4Rm/19jYi7lBMzU0S5lD9Uu4qbDcVd66AWtMBZj/fLsM/YMzc=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "3 only", 
		"option_d": "2 and 3 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060130", 
		"question": "25a3ZpL2wxfj+YJgdgznyPH2O3icQ2sVpnGXW6VtMGXrUefLYO7x24V0JEjJnk965nPLpqvk5AlPs6YKqbqXdTtDf5lqiN2I0+G30WEBPMAEiYF84NoecvAAyy+sYtHXYMJgnC60L0DpJzivATBxmD7YjX1CrYf7/Cn7QNIygBE7hIJ7+cEzMpeQ3+iH4Ej4kQ+M2DuXRLJzUWiX5o6c40aF4Io5o8jNsHLntvb4ifPW5J4EZEhXuIFsXxn8g6cZ9y0qUNi8cVAvimtmqFN/axVDe3C5ltef", 
		"answer": "2+b4Z5//yFtHIoXS+8L1n+t46019wTFK", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7W1+jyOWLeECIQsXrDVKxmfXTnFLDKa+O+zptwJFWMn0g74XXUorX1t1IBi+hL/J2XMDYLe8t6xtSMxejuzX9Gc9VBnol/4ZQLPMBIyX2+cdDSLftg2i6JNAX0YimyF3lgkTWWg3IWpIy18mv7W8w2zFghnoZo6Mx8NN6T1bvT/EW5kkaDzn7RSbFtFlqcsY646lGdrI49uY2ZvnLP/PG5nvHB9d0fawdc/4l5I0+0kugO9Cs7WM2mKBRH/vOQVVzoYC+vJg0U/Nmjwn1lysI9VWggtBJHiYZFItVjlpz2qT88NsN5VTqp40UAyp1kSwKEcf231ij271Y0OTo4ZIRp8G00rwvcK1h/g1eScCJigIF/+90cmxAjLzUAuGT1jzOCjnbPfYHmq47zkaj2r6tu96dnK1jAIlXWUs0obbbZZ2Zgz6mdArRRNpsnFTumOtkv/zD8MoXU6zEIkM4pIXOn9yuX0sD6L2D6oJf9h9lzGqtMdtPQ/Yu+pBzEYC3vLmnTZdnxWBz1D2jw1k5puBYihGEf/mPURZp39D0Imj64QEhogWf0ZH211r9O78KNd48j0vb42CAZi+BxnNv40l04VRG2gXZNobiRc1J82VXCG8ACyh1uX+5BIJ7UslHUl3fDQHkZP8HwQa2AxD90mKPlgXFyuIIPRYSXbBDIyt9m3A6hBL12Uyfgp5T4NPIQSkkj6LN4xOiy98upcLO2JWEtagn3VukZ9JlQawt6HUvZACZdaavuQpUfVaBOwHCKkwJYSGxAEV/Iu6oRHQOmq8fBa3jNI4UUCweiYLILU8b5WEKPNLG/ySLAA6uF1Ui4H1ctTyqYMvxN7Anzdpn2LR2003xs/IHZcFNaV4gSKGf8ciu8oqSQN0R6ayM1J41Ve1fdUlAQnDuDG7tljLQLdQxtTq7nHFcRhS0N3yrdHldCok0OV7ztSUBnLKZXLV4VjSC9FK5fXVzNijsJh1OOgi/pJe5YcUgtfySHh0mgn5dkjfb6woeSStDnPbII25kGLPZSStrXX0kdlPfr4qHwEHgtA395bA6qgF6UG8UJQBcWmbeAKQw=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "3 only", 
		"option_d": "2, and 3 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060131", 
		"question": "25CrY5Thwlnr5YBgWxr3y+n2M2LVByITuj+UWqp3eDHsUufWZui+z5h9K1OehFV8smLUoqzk5AxPs6YKqbqXdTtDc4p9w5Cd3+G313hVNtUElYYy948dMfNMzT6kddibLfti2iOXJlH1dXmuEGJxlTzFykBY+sOP/SKiFNslxVU/l4N9rcc6fNWQzKSX7V/4hQqDxTutRu4kJVycrI6l6lrcro0s9d6YoSLU5uC5l/nd6Z4fcA1XrMZ7dl78g6dJ7CI9WNr0ax1G4evDaEDkLybhiyMqPIrdovapupGohFSRZA==", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUuq+IssS1zFcTLAp79rBM9JHXd+bJt+", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0Eh/81ur6JyvZECJA436NVuMmMFTwX6LQfa3/25IxK1OHihc74X/Itqrl5BMdhqxc7J3ffyRDbYphzJCI2eC3w2NAJcNI2pR65Y5ffeZFjDmoZNvIKepryi6CPgXjcju6CHF3nTDaynFTpJes9DO+Rpok1Ac3l4prrfw0Oc7f2LqWqFmhlg+B3XedUf1iHkGXsY6h5QOdsoc5po2ZuTPPtOP8iP2T/9AIZ0hRsJB6cV6416oQuC00UMu9bQBYscHDalH/M2iiNQtd9Mrn0zRmwMI6XGcwtB5IhsNRcMFl05So/CU4Ns5iVTKopgROyIA8XBiYcKi72X7hoEEwNW45YI8tuz86thuUFFpClF+USWxCgIF/+90cmxAjLi9JjzbpjDyEkneKf4ejzpP3gPrj4Lpi/OM0PFGQOk7MFpkOYLbTaydw3/3bGa5ZKt9qFjumM9o6vDv8YJeHnz0I3solb3b0tCyWgMjmLXb6p5r4mpRxBrAXdt7LqcSjuFnVITf4MXiAJsTyGRv/RnC6JD3dZ8K7WmZsxmcqfmf8jg==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 2 only", 
		"option_c": "2 and 3 only", 
		"option_d": "1 and 3 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060132", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2BT69oY0Ehr9wO6/MmfRAGsQt3aMXON8cWfmFKjMLuXrxJZ/Z12KmVJt+2LPpravt28B3uh85Y+ceSMPPo99wdadxKT+yjFXMspIn5lhpIkKbORP3intcdLdJf16x3iFZ0T3dTC+EXxggSPTykBY+sOP/SL7WNUy0wZyhot55MYvfNaN3Oia5ku9lBKL0H7RSbNgUVqWoY67/kqIoYA0sI2LviCb8vXrl/Hd9543bFsSi456I3yukqkduAY5Ws2nKBRE4+nVZRTvOWikKw8e8Mr333tnho8oVmx08QdFh49aZ85nlo/lqDciKMxzBnF8rFjLnP2CfCp6MiNPXTiq", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUqq+IssS1wji07jg50EhYK2o3/aFidB", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0Eh/81ur6JyvZECJA436NVuMnMFbvVaTLb+G+zYV4IUiazVJ1smDHr6n17kBPjKlVqYyaMDQGbJIvztWbw+37wT0BMtUEjoh3/doebvEAzzKgZNvIJfouwWjANUzzb3muC3l41CXei2gWoIKotSW+UdR3xBAimZRx+c04fNWGma+f6U6xgxSRnE+ZTf1DA1GYoY6E6kiZs8I+ut+AtDab9u25nfTS89cKdgFdscZ+cV78lqQa92o9ScuxZB5O//CQdlX5JTq0JhcOtYvixTR9zocwHXkm+wlPhoYWY4Bk14GkqD1wK99rGyCqrFZUh5NzUBOFNLy21Cj05VoveX8Xa7ZjiCUw4RyIKUB7l26SWGwD1Il4vtkXlgtxb2pDiDbMjTqYkyWfcJLq5ZO8hPr14Lhg5rYmJU2ZdUrdRJRcY7bSM25+z6XbDKhYc551EmLpO8Er8nnsM5OQnz8CwpkmLmXq/SSe0uH6PHap85vqztU2A7YOMpzH5cSgvhzUZCfoLHidcovgUQnkD3XrkxxstBBlwS9Q5nfMGoB6+zke3OR5QxZ5D/e5UPoPXQNfQZc=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "3 only", 
		"option_d": "2, and 3 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060133", 
		"question": "24e9b5Dh1RDk8MU0Whuy1e/6Jm7eAGdRrHnDV7FmcWXqV7SCb+P6iYN5IlWbzV599HPFt+X/+RMHmqVa586eczYKaIJ7wdWam6TgzHhCO4ZXjoFm4ZcacuBTjDy/cZTSLv1h3HyFJFGvJwWzVTBAnDTPyn1ErcO6tS+yWt4lwRsxk8ds4og6PcWS0KaUqEmtg0aW0zuFQLhtAxSVtNyv7gOPqZg9po2xv2CbwPz8g7jW/tYKbAtX/5J3ZhuphK1J9yx4V8mmZRtF9qTdYFflKSamNE4h95ij+3t7x4snVGp08BpWjZBfdtMz1Znq/DYxMo1lB3O8rFZNh5h9VBKFNKqw2WvsoFY+ezoia4lisjswrwaZJld72m2dXiFYmocpbmoxxLcv1dhcGSuA6vq9jA==", 
		"answer": "2+T4Z5//yFtqIB4th9O9apMH4n7ZyUrT", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0Eh/81ur6JyvZECJD436NVuMnMFTxRqbWZ+7tiZZjIhyFjEl89zbErLD881YdnOhP4Y+LMCoCaI4vytWM2aTj1nBPINZLiJR34NodZbRHwDyufdHJM75axmuZZ0bxaXm/ATB11DnfhHhEqY248GevW5oxwQc/n4l/oYg9L5eL0a2KqE65iEaG3XaQT7gkEkaWpd3o6k2Y4I85tsWEvzfJ7bTUlerS+dACYUhWupZwcFKohOgI6i94UMu3fR9e/eXEaFvjM2isIU4a9crg33VlhoYsX3s9519SioJCIsNy2NjlsCE/f8lrGHO1sQRGyIZxHxuXf7irkFzs5UY6NXYqbo9+/C40r0+VJldxlH2ZQiVUmoNuvtYYhwlqc2gM3HfzwiuDhXzPf5Ltq4bwiuf04L9q968jOgGBO1iYW4wXYPPJMychiv2UTadfMJp0BGLyNdAjwDfFLqKc2nkexNg0Knri+j7Zw438KiWzvZH2nMZzF6tAE8PX6N++s0+HYiLvYXyQct71VQTpD379kwxguR0jwSIZ6W6YHIY/8ywfk3e+TggkkzSgeHSkj/5f64zOb5w+xfzo2HIejeBqlp75wA58Uwv7mXdG8peQRlAP5VvBG9sC1kVuGLwEDdbS82PWlHrDRDwPeo73QaCOzSha2+3yiy09voNOWImAOBDUhNsiiBazDut8F/bu0E12RifC9tWlPHWjl6w=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "3 only", 
		"option_d": "All of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060134", 
		"question": "25K0aZL60A3v88UsUxD21v7+JW7DQ3IDrGmKVqY0Z3nqV6+CbOjwzJF4M0/WzWd1ozbyq6Dpt1IdiuhaqZ2QZTAAe8tpx8LJ3/3z1n5EP8NHjpJ759oPc+NF3n2pYdGbNPEu2W+UIlf2ZjWxFzByhj7byntaqYCy9DO+UJoi0BkzmINrrfQybper0a2KqEm9kgOQnG+eXa9tAkCK9cq97gOIr8IsvciEo3LJ4fP+n/yT8c4bZwlAvoh8ZhuAmftJzCI9Ec+4aRFC8PDVZRTgLz2tMw8U99ijxWFqzsIoTikg/BoGo49GcYBywoz2vTEkf8N/GDaorFFTh4BzSgWfZ6mrkGnq7kA+eXYyJ+7JlidRty94Ddmun3oWSAg=", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUqq+IssS1wji07jg50EhYK2o3/aFidB", 
		"explanation": "24GwbYiz0Avvt4RgQRHn1/76dW3fESIZunuRXaZ4dXL3Rq7BLv3x3pJjZ1iciBtv/TbRorH15VUOg6RIqYiNfy9DeYduy9mIw+HzhGRRP8dKnpMy0JIWb7RJ332sNNfUMuxrzXrANFHxczywAX5g1Bbai39frZGotSS6Wpok1Bogk8d5rcQzKJeQ3+iE6Vm9lErCy3OYS7UkElWX9cytq1GZrIc5psiJ8SbT5vvsnfCT598fZxpUvopzcBu9maxJ/Cs1QoigZ1JM9OrVc1X5JWirPgoP9s7v03d91IsqHXk74xpUvo1qbPR704GkuDckOt8qATyvsU1T04c8WwKTNKm3kHzs5VwtNWg+Yo1ouG00sR+ZKUZ/lGiZDBhZnZMr98NZlAojdGFDk2TyhzyfwHabfYfm5oXykajXrLhg+6IzLEXAOFPNWJkdbL3Taydh3+qTTadPc4tvEmLHMcU9sHn4MpPU3joZxdgsI26n9WqUk8f6KyWuvIfrh8diVLsFJcXM58qjuVPJIRPkLm2fY4v1Sw2wTmjswQ9mox0hiDUfqHbQDclt4CoKm3rwS0FlhzP5LHOn1qpU75GLP4M+xvv43Dsei7R5kZ+3wBU5BwurnXBRppGRRkhGyEeWGMIVhAY7GLAOG4SR826CnGDZX3UIbIK2Er2Ey2xJyaPihWh0sZdCFYSHJxDVjZJmyRm1QfB2QGn5qY/3OPkHA2orxrxNxNmpsoq8efKnJWQ+ah73VOBM/YFQYQxoURjIBiwPYavuQpUbAcFDwmaKlhNcVX5KERrC7qUNTwu/uYTcYX/MaqIIHV7jbb0QEsL0Vwf7Pfi6iDnaRr7clkisTUEmWnqONbEZ4Ar1dJiyEBu200lo6dKlM0NeBIwZOWf8ciutrabDBgkpa2w1J5pSdkbHCwQrgSzKNO0niaITZBEjQLyuFl4F1hhB3yraCxhSv14SW+WASV8rI6ZLMxsey3elFK8PUBmKkDMZh0Lc1irpadtHIVpjfmWQhwz5npN03+vmwouPANv7bakT180QK7NVQYjPUxsIkvak4PT0FWM2FC12LezBSOvFuUrlToj1rMea0VROib0dOksuNziHyZ7N5ChsLLFGYH5Z/61G1TmDQzWRH330VTKndrk=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "3 only", 
		"option_d": "All of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060135", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRom2GEqp6c37xRqLBeq3/y5hkMxyAjl47/3fVsKDjt1canaFV7s6LeCdDTodqwcOd2OfyynQBI8NWk492u6YRLbRpzzjtd9vNJexryi6PMUDiJ2jvRH19mD3fhXIWu5Ku9DW+FNc+zBAh1sc4rYh8fJej1/rTwU69xhWK2X6FW/1zFEac9d664k6dsos0rI2Ev3Lo++Htkrjy/dsZawtT/8Y/Ixv81+g19nl4eMuxahdZ9veQZ1v/LWi0LwsTucLg0zR6zocsSXp09g1Dg4gWa85n2djtsjY5KcRuADK240ZMyJd3TFfWNP34kCik3FtrNV05YI9jsCw7pU+LKUc+nHmZSWxXho9mvtkakERwdWpFiGWibdtGHtKjuOXc1fy42G4PaA==", 
		"answer": "2+f4aZ/3kU2q+IssS1wP7+wKvWvmjKcIFO7Rf1Wq", 
		"explanation": "25y7bdHw3g/v5YAkEhHkwO+/ZDmQDmsdr3aMXONnYWTiRqKCY+TyzIQxE1SAnhty4TbH46b/5UEKjLwb+pqeZCcOe4V7iPScxe35wzFVO8MEqox37YkLc/dFwjjtZNHJKfFqgi6JJECwZDarAWJxkHHZnHlE6NLptSqyWNY+zxtyhZZt7No5fNqW1a2AqEK+xhKK2Tu0Sa9wGROK9d29+UWdo4d4gcWEonLS57T4lLjS4tsKIgRTrYF6cRuon6kHuD4wVIiBZhtf9OCQUkDsNC2wZw8T/YvO02xgxY1pXmY59hZIh4dqbPx9/5vh/CE4Osh+BnOtplZFh4RuVhqXZrS0ySjt7hUMem8/bcpMsSgnqAydaGB2k3jcRT8RlY4r994amhZxeGxU3GX0gyuOjWCBaNPK6IW8luD1pa1wsrQiO0TAJU7RW4wObL/ZZ258iseUH7JUc75qEjDvPtRu/Tf9YLOBzTge2dhgK2L1/SSe0tn9PCWKv5fwncB5F7oOM5HV7Nm+v1iHVSvkM3jTcc7mXEjxQ2/3kwdmslg2wCQV/HGYAYc/0j8Im3C8SEpg0ibuaDyAmKpd+IGado0w7/vQ0xsTnfZ9jZzklBszVQn7mndGvMSWTFkP3lzTG9kUhAs8CbUKVJ/f5mLWnHjUQmoEe9v3DeiFzyNL0fCxuml0rNAHRsyPbBrUmMwjywPxEul4QWLgrYjtfdUWD2Yp6LViiuuupcf7YvuhIiUmbgiwXK9J+pBSbRE7Hg2dDCdKILq8U5wVAe9J1DXMhQhFB3ZKABrf860NSRfqpdaIaWbfYLgZHA3ebY8LNNz9S0nDNP+tiCfIFf+ah0K7H0I3QTfdKLMIpRT4f4nmN1OHm2F3ucj2clBVBIoZPyjhZm66seOQHwcueiEgJp4HXVXQTh4olTDHZ+5mnucDfw4oU62jWVIP1hBB3zfRCxhWuEkbS+WpVUEuJK4FNFMUjQe5FKkMSBPJgzQPzkaZ0CvjLbp/OUxjcmeWz1/onpdy3/bnwqmTD9HsIbwV1s0KO/ZIUJPaExsMiPb36u/0UXg2AmxuYrjJUOaRuVu2C9u0tsvfhU9OyrEGMh83JCuMjIzNsDNuKuVcZ3VPqTMQoorGagPqzodL2VQqS2Sz/uVMALjfI6pBRDabsw==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 2 only", 
		"option_c": "2 and 3 only", 
		"option_d": "2 and 4 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060136", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt5EoV170wPzrIHnVECIepT+EXqJ3eXD3XajMLuLwiZ94IFSFjFV/4Sn6rfSw1FwdnaFeqYGNMCEKbJp6zeyd6+qlhFhCNoZXkoV+8p8MPPFY2DijcN3VJ75nwHqPZ1X/azivRGd1gDTEmUBClI3otRL2R9I20BA21oB07Ms1Pdvfzbqc/UqwuhK+0i/RYLxqFl2Xso6+6k+QpZsr92ynjd9a/SWmOIqlo+ZVzBg=", 
		"answer": "2+T0KMK/kRjk88V0EhH8yeS9YrzQbhOj1IyZPI4XrKnsLA==", 
		"explanation": "25a3eoP61Fnl5cUjWwzj0PjDO16dEGoQs3qHEqR4cXLqVauCev/x3JB5G1KhjFV8+3jB47Px+18Klrtn57KRRCoGbY4vztWIw/HlwWIBMtRB2oF+6NoZc+ZNyTntds2bNPZrjmuSKFb5aDf9C3Y0kz3XiXVTupD71iipRtMy01UzhII478crMJqM0amD7Un4ggOSzn6CW7RrH0fZocap/wOdsod4s8KfvDfftPbg2uzb9Z4DZwlWqIdtZxu5haca8SU2EceyKBVH8OfZZEb+YB3uNAYc6c7nlnNlx4EgXGV04A1Jl4RecYByxJ2kqjM8M8hzBnOuq0VUh5x9SRLWdri93ijn4UcpcH5rap95/C8s4QiQKVd3n3mPDARQmodi8NdZgwVvcWpZjzbhkDrLlmSDcJb6+MDojenk4Lhx9+MrJkKBIVncFoweaqXFZ2Yyx+iSA+ZKMpNrEjumPNsqvDjrJdaH2ikMwtg0KnOn8jiWn438LSW4qtL4zsdiEboQdtLJ4M2x8rFe+zektL9ClnMwrnaup3Y=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1, 2, and 3 only", 
		"option_b": "1, 3, and 4 only", 
		"option_c": "2, 3, and 4 only", 
		"option_d": "1 and 4 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060137", 
		"question": "2523f9H+0Bfzt4omEgr6wL35OmfcDHUYrXjDQbd1ZHTuUanWfa2+yphjNVmKmVdisnLDsKbi/lEKnOhP4YvfYDAMfY5825CI2eC3yX5XNstBlJQy65xffbRHwDyufdHJf8Jgny6nK0TzbjyvFzBymD7BynpXu5e+52e6QJojyBByk4N/6Nt8KN+e1+iQ7UOsgxTCnDvRCP0kUWiX546P50KfqYcq8t7Ntz7U47TwibjU4tsKdg1Bq8Z2bRuon61J9SM8VcSxKFILsaSQIRTRLnvjBgIRuczv13dgw5A6HW84+wgGg5cWY84z147hrjM3Oo1lE3Ouq1ZFwtR6WhKCNK29wijg4Ux/NTprJcot/BE79U+7JFV9k26OX2xUho9v+5APlAhveHZT3HT5wi+HlWaEdZ3kq4Hygajxoqti4aooJwMil5Pfyt0jD1Ze7SaP8co1", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "25K0aZL61Av5t4MsXQmyw/zsIW7CQ2MF42uLV+NxdHbmR+fWZuzwiZR0KUiMnxtP+n/V46zjt1IBz6FV6oGNYicAast83NGd0unyymUBFMpFmYl39olfevhP232rdcfPJewuz3rAM031Jzq4CmRxhnHCgn1Y6IKvtTOzUZoyxBI3hcdM5cEvfN6MmaqW60ytlQPCyHOUCLRnFBSYoY6840bcpYY/sN7NuCGb4PzwmfPW4p4KbAwSsoltZhuukrsA6z45X9z0fB0L9+jfdmjjHCaEKw8e8M7xkWcpwI4mSik9519BkIZXdsVgwtjtsnIkN8gqGDq+p0hFh6B0VgTWfa740Sjn70ctcHk/JZl5vTkwrAqSPBRKkm7cSyBQl4lu7JcK1QJvcngAlWWghS2OgXGKb4ej4o68keD14LRq9qcrLAGCMF/ZQ54ZJafILnQyw/rbGq5ZIZonAyrjfdwt+XnwM9aA1zAD3twzOzfm+i7Zn8LmLSW8v4fwiuh4KLEhOt2F7se2s1XCczChJ3GccYv1TUjkR3m40hhgpRkizWEf7iLMAJt68G0Lm3ukCVRhgGfkbWXhorZV+cKHbM4w3bXl0zEfiuZ9nI+3xwk9UwG2iHFX8rCXShxc3VHTGo0IwkkpALUCHZPDsmuammGQXX0fdsvlQayC0ylG3ur/iSFysdAaXYnOPxDBj54pzlelCfg5Umvsq4/8L7BVHmwpuqF9xf2k98W9NeesKSU+agilWOZXv9VQZgY7BQPYRSVCb62gQt0RR6Bc3HrdkQZESz96ClfJu68EXAejr9bbLmnfbfEaAhH1I7IWU8j5XVOPNOLpmWCZRrmZkFP+T0E3Dj6cOPxN8g/5domyKwe7lnp3ucLkPBFdSIwAfCbgNHi1qrTDChV6fmwjLZ0Hc0nWQxU31C7GNbl+iKYSTBYRT4+rGFMfkwNc3zvAAVxA8FofU6moWUBnKLAFMFcEzjy8H6dfXRLOxjsInFePyy3iac5DOFpjcnfTjgzjlIB0mvz9wp2VC8DnILgVxs0kJLdYTZ/EDBsZiPzg6qH2EGA1A3RkbvrRHvLdpUz9C8bz7oPNzVVIwf4BJR8vLTzLmY3W8z9+POVAaTBGtHUNpcTVIgek3cha1EJ6SVzi8gH2TmQqpVFyYJeredjYI5ag/kQTViXJU/lCmu55ziXrO5ORcxI2BGt1mBTQYtrPhySRMq/+075JCh7i0IvCS45k4k853NOxyF8AqjVxz2/nD3/XZ+n5qB9TI3V2WKDfDlVYxgEj2Ta0xxPuMYClleRRppIfGn8T/T7eRlMs3n0f", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060138", 
		"question": "25a3ZpL2wxfj+YJgRhb3hdzzMH/DAGpRhHOCUapxYj2jXaPHYPn3z44xM1SMzU9p53OGsLHx41YCiqZP+tSjfnNDUoRsycSM06T+yjFVO8MEuIVg6p8MebRvzji/eNXVJL5hyC6zMEzkfTyvCHF6kA3CtnIE6LCz+jWvUch31B0zmMds5c18O9ue2qGW+l74iQDCyHOUCJxoAUelofKmuAO1tMIxpo2ZuTeb+Pv3nf3A5J4MbglRtoNtI1Ky140c6iUoVPSgVBwfscnVYEf4Mi2wZwEL/NmjhyQ5ho8gUWwntBZIwo9TbMdn3tqJt1I5PXYYjAZjDvpm4xDq", 
		"answer": "2+f4aZ/3kU2q+IssS1wP7+wKvWvmjKcIFO7Rf1Wq", 
		"explanation": "25m3a5Dn1B2q/otgRhb3hd/6J2XVEGdRjH2GQK91fnWjW6GCXfr33Y10NVCIg187xn7PsOX55BMOz7xJ/IvfYzYCao5izd6dl9D/wTFgP8NQiYN6pL0TffdJyS/tfcebLPFtz3qFIwX5aXmpDHU0tjTEhHlFrcOU9yKpWNs5xFU9kMdL+sEoJtKN1amd7HG2ugix1HSDXLh2UUCRtMDo/0uZ4IU0tM6EtCDItPv/2uzb9Z4qbhhB/7J3akj8nrtJ+SR4WMa3ZwBZ9OfEIUf5ITymKgsT7YvX3nEp544sSXo3/F9hjoJVa8VhlpH3/CY4Oo1mGj29pldUh5NwXhSfca/42Wak9F06NVsndZlRshE7iBvcIUc+jmOZDCBemodu7cRZkghifmZFjjbpjH+ulXeAbJaj34j1lqj5s/lisrc1PETAJkjZQogRYL3UZ1N6z6m6AaNIIJxvVwXqPNYn+Su5KYXUyzEIkNUvIXDi5z7ZlcH0Omy/odLwgJRTAa0PJtT55/e5nVnGcjbzJG7Tad3xS0ihHyy43gdpsgtlwS9Q5GfWD513tRkFl23wQFckkymgZXKimaxO74GaP50l0uHp0DcejLRMl5639RE5Uxe4hT9kvoWcRlldjVnTH94S1gw9TLUDG4PFsj/F1XvZR3keP4alVuiMzmUI0+2xgmRzuIQGF6WeulrfWQdCQVr6mI+ot4o=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "3 only", 
		"option_d": "2 and 4 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060139", 
		"question": "2523f9H+0Bfzt4omEgr6wL35OmfcDHUYrXjDQbd1ZHTuUanWfa36zIRyNVWLiEg7+nnR46L89lAGirpIqYeSYCMAast7wNWAxaTk0WNTPNNKnol849oTffpE3z6sZNGEHPA/jkmMJkb5YiuuRH96mCiWj25ZrIb79Cm/FNQy1hAg1oN9/ccvNcPf1KmH7V+xhwqRnDvRCP0kURSlu5zozE+do4s9p97NoT7a7bTrlfTW454EZEhXrYlsalSy2+gd6is2Qti7egZK5e3fbxitISanZwoY6cTw32BgyYxpHSl0tF8Gwr9YMYBU2pnntTMkOskqEz+1rFZTh5t6SxKYNK6w33+k5UM2cX8lZo8tsyt1shuOIVVqk2SSDGwR1MArvpAlm1AjWmNBn3/lkCzLkHeGcZLx4ozlxe7/srQj+61nJU6XOV3WUs0dd7bBNCXGKg0O5gqSJfwZCGolvOB3", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxEhfhhfTxNmTCEWcStz+BV6B1ZWLmFKDOb+73zIViZ1+Igxt6/mXJ46H151wchrwb5I+LdTAKf4d8iOeB0uq3xTFGP8dHk4VgpJcacOBTgH2kYJTXJf94y33AJUD4bje5RHE0gjDEg3lCscO082e2Vc4y0hwzmpQ0rcEyP9uK3aGd7w2qiQWJzzfRW7xqFRjZtMCsq0SOoZQ9uY25uTfI8bT0m+zW4tcKbhsSvIdxI1m516wM6CUrWNyxbFJC/6TdbkbsKSamNEJd7sPq1Xwpx5AsHXs98BhDkcNZZIB02pnntTM8f8lvFyGzsHhO+5pPSxaCcbC93nyktBU2ZjoqaZli/CQ7ogCOOlF9jiueSS9QgZNuvtcVlAdqeH1T3HXhjH+Nj3eCPJrtq4G8k+niqbx36+MoLwGBJ1nZRcFcbL3DK3J2w+ecTatTJpFzFivoLplu6jj1LJONzHVN0dckb2fr9T6ck9jmeUK2spHwi8ZlVL4SM5HI5tij8FDOaibtOD2HaYvyVhr9D3X2kw93shk2iDYY7XDdSJ138G0ekHGnWUVnmWfpfzylk7tMqoeAcJs227Xt0zZQjPx934/y2Q05VQWvmG1GocSeXVkPzlvaGo0CygY7C7xBEpnDsnmekDbDRXMaP9r5QamEwDlFz+/wmmQ9vp4KFYKBOFnWj9Iy9BmND85tVHPopYP3KbxHUCQL9rNyw+izpIqrefK9bHclYx+kGeBfs5BDZxFyHgWRRTBdYba9RpIMVeFb23rE20dJSXsJAV/c9LsBSQ2lpITvYmvdarQOHV7jcbZFEsn9QFPcdf6viDXbCayVmknyH1A3TzSOMb8f8Qbkc4P8aFOynWwk/cT1PUJSUIoYMmfHfG6g5aaRBAI/PzgtLcpLe0nRWBMlhDuDJeAnnasVcxMkT6/nGF4S1hBNjT/BB1dL/AwKV6C0AEc1K6dWMFQD2Xe4ELQaThXLiilKjE/cwSP+O+NCP05jb2yWggzhl51omL/9iovBCNv2ObIWkoIFaKJTQdrRE1ofk/b2r+7yUW4gRn5iPejNUObYvki2FsDxr4PTyxxfwbtIIV4vICvLnZfY5HprI6pYfDBFq3YL7N7aZ0at1Yla3FV6HBXt+0WkVW8kr1F3a4PkedTIapak5FVNHyXLRPlBgbx8yCH0PNHWJA43Am51kBPQYtrPhzGNOez0xu0dDR3i0JXKRoNo/gh23Jyw2gxErit6nHX2AnjdIvPl7RMUK3I4RruNG1RTgwQe2wa/7UfpKYqngqgdzuMbmJIf4A/+ozVzix6KQ0XBcWCq0fCKsmiGrU8u3upmSm+nXn1uy0wrQrA45mtnQTkoRq80j6LnJbDQl26hbpWrjZgF4BZHRbXLO76zuMa8JK3Bb6L+1o+VKmGh5ZtoELWuN9tFLHPLcH0Qqv7gaoGEfhyBOmqH1/uXFGuPZTJU7XIulXDORx1oJG22Rd0dHC8ShIpzY7QessvptURxPGXGWrAo3q0ImFJcHhBqXu7omWVEF/YiMJ3cd0lk+1MSCupVZWv3fUJzJ9lU1HC9TCnv/yG9l/ppCNbonBFrO0uZxirIenTJ++42eN+WuNSehwL3djjdl29V5g==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060140", 
		"question": "25a3ZpL2wxfj+YJgRhb3hfv6NH/FEWcC43mMQK5xdDHhTefFYuz9wJJjNBDJmlNy8X6GrKOw41sKz65U5YKQZysNectu2tXJw/biwTFAMclRjsBz9p8LeecAzTOpNMTCMv9jx2qBKwXgYji2Fy9ImmCWq25TvIaotSapUZoxzwc/k4M479F8KN+amaWW7VmxiAHC033RXKprUVOVtM2h7lGP4MJ49Y3N8XLn+qa5u+rW5NsYIhpXrJNzdxu6hacEuD4vXoi3ZwBZ+OHDIVf4NDyqKQld+8rg3TRmyMImTXk75xZSh8NFa8R2xdjrunIxf8BlAD2uok1Oh9Q8H1fWNP2E3juk0EwtdHciYYth/D0woASPaFJxiGbcWyRUmsB/6d9Zlgtxb2ZFjzbthzqfwCXPPNOjq8DAi7ywkKBx864uLUCMdUzdV4YPJbXPNWoyzvyeTbJTc4tvEmL0ONYr7yrwL5jU0D9NxNEyKnKn+zjZn8LnPCW5uoDom9FlVpqY8hW7d7ynq1eYBC5FXng=", 
		"answer": "2+f4aZ/3kU2q+IssS1wP7+wKvWvmjKcIFO7Rf1Wq", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0Eg3mxOn6OG7eF3FRom2GEvE0cX/nFPP+YN7qyIN0KlmHmRspqDbnsaDk8kBPjrpeqYiQYi8Gestt0ZCd3+G3yXREJ89KncB94toLa/sAzzS/ZcHeM75Pjm2JNVTlYnm0FzB11DPZnXAbu4u65SK/FN4y0Ac3hZRx4sZ8KN+ezeia+w2+iRSP2X/RSqQkBVyc9cat6keLoZA89cifviHS+/q5lf6T8Z4MbglRtoNtI2y0kqZJ7D03Ecu9egNe9PeQbFHoNGTjMwYYucLtwnF70IcnVGcztA1PhoRTIsJ21ZfpuSFwPsMqFCG/t0F8yadoXgOTebi2xCiwuhUPbGgqaINpvSF1sQqdI0c+nGSOQWxVgYUr6t9ZgQxmPX1Fn3PzkTaEjiWAetP345L5gKj/svlu/bEiaUKJJ03NU55cRKCAM293iuqSH7dJNownEjDpOdBivC3xJY/U0zwMxtxgLXLv/SSd0sy1KmCoupfqzttwVLQOP9fApM6zt1nDITHoJXqWdYvAUQ3jSjzq2gpisgtlyyAeqGfODYdr4CwBkmfwREF2lSKgeHPhkLFO58KPP54owfTh1DYRlLRompr86BMASTCziD9MpoyaXRxc2VXCG8ACyh09TLUTEdbY/G6Zh2TVSGgxcf3iALyCzilGzqOg1CFcrZUaUJ/OLQveytAp3Fe3Du90UGOtqp+5KfQQSmkp/6Z4xOrhuMz7YeSrbGImbhm+XP1Ks7JdaQFyFBnORSdObvirRJIaRKBOwHDekhQEB31cERrY860RHQCl6srHeirdcbQdGhuid7sAHvL2fVPOIfSkzT7dRuzG1XenTUUoRz6cLfAd4Ab7acz2K1O9nHwk/873PxFMTIYZfDPkeyu6qrGRAgMpPyEgLZ4HSl7HSh0tkD/PZ+lijKwTMB4iU6XnDlgTmFFblyzXCxhKogwTULeoAFAuOLhQJUhRyCW6FaVfSBTPxjYLgFKPwSP8LLhbVdZuzlvc7UyGF/6tdYHT", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "2 and 4 only", 
		"option_d": "1, 2, and 4 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060141", 
		"question": "2523f9H+0Bfzt4omEgr6wL35OmfcDHUYrXjDQbd1ZHTuUanWfa2+yJV+MkjJmVN+sl/FpuXR8FZPhrsb4ICcfzARe4h7l5C12bW362dEIYYVyMB/7ZYTdftOjC68YdXJJb5jx2KFNAX/YXmpDHU0mj7EnnRTuo37/SK2XcknyBAgk8dv6No5fNSQz62B7Un4hB/C1XiUCIFqQxSxtMKuq0ya4JYwsI2Esjeb9/vvn+rS99tLdQlB/49xI36phacZ/WoEX5v0TwBO9OrcYFrpYDysIw8EucPixTRoyMIgXmx09x5WwoBZdMVh35bj/D0mOt8qQHO3qkhMzptyHwSHYbyq1Sjp6Vk6ZjoXa94tiCUw4QafLRR9m3vcRSIRuYF599VZtx1xeS9snXjkzn+qjnGObpD34oP9xf/xs/lu/bEiaVWINFKYB9lQNeOQZ2F3z/3bGa5VMJQlUc/KBSVgWwnX5pAYWLymTw==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH63xrl5ZclUQqy1un+IW7dBmwFsD+CQKY0ITHiWqOCPNHw+oNwM1mEiFVvsiec44rm8kFP3Pob5IeTfCsMcMt82cWIxeG3yXhNNtUElYYy8JIaPPpP3imlccbVYPZrw2eTN031dTz9E3VmkXHVhWpTuoa/tSWiFNM0xVU2g5Vx4898KN+amYGQ7Q2ZgQPOnHWeXP01QxSUvMKk4kyS4JEpoMyftHLW/fj8icTdw8oKdg1fuohrIwnm14cH9DN4UMq7fQYL/urVLEDlKTqnZwEbud/r0zRgxYdpXmYi8Q1HhYYWZtVh35bj/CY4Oo1DFjb6gkNFh4N9TFefev2dxXrr8FB/QXIuJZhorzl1tg6PaF1w2kWTXjhZ1KFm+8IQlgUvPU5TlXeswj6FhCW8c4b348DdiO3iqbpizq0bJ3WIMBzXQoUZd/PTM2Zmz+SeA7JPc551EmLlMsc8+TrtHJinyzgZ1dQlIWOnp3DZtd/wPGu2spz9zsB5EL4ZdtnE+ou2vhzOYiahInyDJsj7Tw3iRnL/kwFzsgplnmEd4W7UAYZxtT4ci3+iTARpmyvlf0Cvpapd/oeDeoAlk6G2nQYYnbRxnJ631xwsBw21zVJCoI2aD35W31CWMswJwEVuLboVFYTS5mSVlDbHSm9NcsHkBOiTyy1GmrKlwjEt79AIUImabA3Tg90tilJz0lX9nXGBL03bH4yZ2+Y=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060142", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rz59JcpUBvhhen3MCvXD2MSqnqRQeNwZWPqWqCCeuX7ib5yIhyoil4kskrI8uXE/1YWz7xe+4OWfiMXe8tmxpCZxeH0zWFIJ8lRicBx6JMZeucA8DP/NP3YJfxr3GmTZ0TiYnm7C2J5kTWWnXRTpsOy9iL7R9IyxQEh1oVq6Mk3fN6RzafT4UO8jxCL2G6QRP1mHVuavt3o103P4K02udTNvjzeufrwlOzbsNENIglc/498Zlm5ha9O62o1UNunKBtYsfLZcl3vLC3jJgwS786jwnxshpEsXC4ntAxTkIVXYcUz6paw/BU8Ps5jECGp41NF1ZE8Wg+VeKir2X7hoEEwNV05YI9jsCw7pU+dJlA+u2WITT5SgIlo/5LDFOi8RkHz5y5VW1Rl9Eo7", 
		"answer": "2+f4aZ/3kUqoTRikMfo2huO6iLkTw9A3OA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0Eg3mxOn6OG7eF3FRom2GEvE0cX/nFPT+YN7qyIN0KlmHmRspqDbvoKDy8kEInOha+4vfdi0Rc45riMeB0uq3zXJEc9VMn4Vm99oQbrRHwDyufdHJM75s3GuBLAX5aS2yRHl6kDjAg3hDqY/79yu0V9Ek/BsBgoZs6MU5MsPfivLTx0O0n0aD3nSEXP1rH1HUu8em/0vcr4R4tMPNuDHe9vHrnb/AsNMKcRsStpU/dVKvnqoF/Wo5U8eibVJf+eGQclHsZzvjNBsP/8rg0zRdzodpT2wn4F9JhMNCasUz35vhvjciOI1jBnOvrUBF1YN9SxKESLOE3lzs5RUwYXIud8p+qCwhpAKZJkBt2mqOSWxYmoNk7MIclhBfc1xUnWLljzqFlCXeJtPE54H/jO3is/ln/eMpJlXANFDPV5QPJafFNWp7xOiPCOZVPd93BSflNMUn6DbsM9aX0zAL1spgG3/i7Wqak8O1OGmpvNLti8Z7HbEBItSF4MX3sRzRYDHoJGmKJsTyGQfkR3nqkxlkrgtpiDIF62qYCZo//CNNnz68SE9h0ijyLH2v1rFf74OAQ4ACx/T42D8VluA4y8G38xE9RA2+n2wDt5yWXEhKyRTfEI0KxQc3TKQABoLCsmKQ1WLYTjwacNz6BeiD1j5B1OSxmml4/7kNUMyvKxyXytAp3Fe7FO5tFW7j6KHrOPkbBmUi/vJwxOnhlsSvdOGnOGwpbli+ECsvAOB6g9tveuiLEqjP", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1, 2, and 4", 
		"option_b": "2 and 3", 
		"option_c": "1, 2, and 3", 
		"option_d": "2, 3, and 4", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060143", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRqmzDRrFhdTHiVqjXeq3tx5hmIVWMgV9orTb6rfSww1sKluha+4vfYzcQaopmxtWNl+buhHlEMtBd2pd76o4abrRTwjK6ctXXLL5SwDzAE031fnmwAXxg1DTYnnVErY+itSOuRtM5x1Uhg4p16Np8ANnMmZyb7VT4gAmQ0TuGQLhqUUeXutno6kCftY8tucyZtCGb/fq5ifDW/MoOcA1W/4dtZlqv164b9yd4Qt26ZBtM+fCQYFrpYD+qKQpdxcW3lkdnyZUvVGw48AwGg5FTIsVr1ZTxrzsmOo1+GnOqrEhB1dRuWhCfe7OrkjesPv4YuaSanLYH0KU4apA=", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUqq+IssS1wji07jg50EhYK2o3/aFidB", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0Eg3mxOn6OG7eF3FRom2GEvI0cX/nFPT+YN7qyIN0KlmHmRsqqDb1rarn8VoKg6xIqY+NdWIQa5h7ydmH0uC3xmgBO8NFjJky85MRaPFSjC6je8PdIfJijlqIIgXjaTaqRGR8lSWWjH1apJD7/Cn7QNIygAI7mJN9/4g4M9KMmaac/A21gwqWnHieRa1oFECcudfo4k3ctIo99d6YvD/e5ri5m/bXsNcfIgpHtop7cBuph+gG7i8qEdy9ZRcL5euQZ1v/LWiiZx0T9tzl33Flwr4nbn014BpLh41CIpMplqvqsyU2NshmESD6pUtSytRrVxKYNK6233+k4VY8YHc+aYt5uT51qAHcO1x7ln+ZXilV1IF5+9EK1QJxcmIAj2PujjaMiHHPfZ3nq5f1i+ywk7ds5aUuLE2EJhzZRIhcaLzTMyd+w+KeAb8cJ5AnES30MJUn8nn4MpOVzHka2NwyKjfz/C/ZhsjnK2SzvdLwnZRmBrAUM9LR7M/3tk7IbGP1KXjTdd76GQn+Szzv2gBhixYZxhUY7SLXHIF6520ein+kTElhnDPzLH2zk/5V5IGBbZw00OHQ0wEEmeB9kp75wF1uHUSIg3BUtI2aQ1hcjVDZXsMI0EkjCbgVVJPf5mSEkHrJC3gYbcf4BuiU1iFF3/GxvW5wutABU8yaJBybmdAp31e8AOQ5WGLhvMq5P+kBSnAk//JixOK2scO+effkO2wmY1qkTeZV/9VDbQ96GAXhCxdbYayrW5gQVaAbiDX5mQhfQXZMCV7fu6sJU0SspdbFLmPQI7BcGB/warYRCo73SAffOfCqzSOFRrGTgQe0SlcxDjOTYaAC6QbiOp73Ixq8nXskzcngKxFYRY1XOijheSuwq+OOBBM0ay0sJpkLOk/cTBhkhDLCM/xmmLRMMBkjReiiD1UY1hhB3y3dA10FoE0MS7btT1VnPqFAYFYYyXq5ELQWSAnOgylIcOYHO39AJ03XaIHyka/47Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 2 only", 
		"option_c": "2 and 3 only", 
		"option_d": "1 and 3 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060144", 
		"question": "2523f9H33lnt+4QjWxvg1r36J2TUBiIHonOPV7pnLzHfWvaCWuXsxoJ2LxyZgU54+X/IpOXM+QFPrbEb74eTfCsNect7wNWEl/P+0HkBJMdQn5Iy2JRMPMBI3jK4c9ybIfx8z32JKEuwWzfpRFJt1CPXg29fpoT74S++FMw2zBk3j8d+4cczLpVNW4W0KAsZK0UP3PE1VcS6", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUqol5tyMTgvamx+yDS5tdxxbQ==", 
		"explanation": "24W0fZL42Bftt4wzEgr6wL3vJ2TTBnEC43CFErF7c3rwFKbMaq3tzJN4KlmHmRt593/IpOX8/lUbiqwb6ICbMCECbJlmzdTJ1vP23TFDKoZQkoUy45Yef/1F3n2ZfN3IYPZv3n6FKVawcDG4CjBgnDSWjXBXq4q+52e9Rt8y2hAh1oh2+cd8KN+ambqc60arxgeM2DuCTbltHFGXoYLo6k2Y4JYwsMPNpTretPP1m/va9cxLbwdEupUzI0upm6QA9i14RcCxKABE8u/DIVXjJGiwIgoU9M7twjR+z5YhHWAgyBFngJFXccl82Njtr3IkN8gqBSG1oEFT1NRzWVeEe76zwyjl7lF/Zn8vbIdosjl1owqVJlM+nXmTWSJV1IF8/8lZlx0jaWdF3HHsgzyChXfPfYCj4pS8iOfmpaoj/bUiOwGUPVmYUZ8TcL3EZ1N6w/rbBadMI5ppBGLxNdAgvC3xJdaT0zgO2dwyb3P19S2K0t/6Om6p85P3ipRlEbsJO9TL/Yu2vFPJZmP1KXjTYdn7TAb0Azzr0BxkpxErz2ER5maYD5t2+ykEkHnwSFNli2f0ZHnhhatO7IONerI/7/vL0TMTkfFqjNvz210ySBD7iG1MtoHfWV1DwVHPDY0F3UkoBbgNHZjWsnmekHuQXHUZd47hALyC0WxHyKPjj2hutp4JFZiGKVnNi9IqzQ7xB/F2WnWvxnN3BCiXExqi6lhnpFV/iA==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "1 and 2", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3", 
		"option_c": "2 and 4", 
		"option_d": "3 and 4", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060145", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt5EoV17xzfztNGjEBnAYsGuKUbA0f3ejU6vDbeT/3ZJ1Z1SAilN383jCsPqwy11ez5hJ7J2afiEGPoRpiMKG1O+3xnBSOshX2rx8tto6ZP1T2Dijd9GbL/guyGKBMwX2azayFmM0qD+FylpZuo6y+yD7W9x3yBQ8kY526ogqPduT3LGAqHG20kau3XiaCLJiUVmWp8+h5UaP4lx57DpzYCNVupef9qAgkdU=", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUqol5tyMTgvamx+yDS5tdxxbQ==", 
		"explanation": "24WqbYL23xrvt4omEgz9xva/N2rDCmwC+T+xXaB/MHPiR67Mfa3/25IxI1mZn15o4X/Jrbaw41sOm+ha+4vfdi0Rc45riNKQl/D/wTFEIclXk498pJUZPPNMzT6kccbIHPBIwXyNJlH5aDf9C3Y0nDDYjXVYr8Ot9Cu3UcMkmlUal4l/5MY7fMGe1aSW8V74hxSHnG2QRLFhCEfZocap/wOdsod4ucKOsCbe8LT4mPfF9Z4KIgVTtog/dVqwm60QuCs2VYi1ehcL4uHAYEbsNC2nZwgP9saj32ApxJtpXCkn4BpDksNVbsl10KTqkDMzNI1lE3O8r0VUh5JwUBiEZ+f492Tl41w+YX8vJYJkuyU5oAGYOxR6lSuSQzgRnIF9+5AfmQV3PWlMk3nykX+/iGDPapLv54Xllqjxsrwj5ro3IEKBOVDBFrhRdrvBN2J2hqmMBa9fO99qEiPoLpU69DjtYIKc2iBN0cslb2Du8C+L0szheXGyttLtgcQ2ALcBOJHR4c6u8F3VZGPgNT2Hbs60WwfkW3P17wBWuFgxwCRQ6WzLH4xttSQe3i/wSEpg0nTcYkCvorZZqpKcep003fbpnT0W2Pl3jZr+2hgvBw2ozX4DsYyeXV1M2VHEF94TzQpuA7JBE5rQ8WSXgXPUC3ACaML3D6yUj2xG1fexiW18vJkPQYmKbBHSjdYqyRm1Er1UWnXsoYj8LrwUGGFs6Lt1zeiy98W9NfSoLWYjbhb3Xepb4ZxCKBZzEB+dBDZKILyrRpINSPRK1jXIjkdPS35KDF/e6Og8VQGz6sXaayrQbKVcCBH3bbdFGsC4SUvONvio3DXNRreVkk+yXkohXXqfJLMM8BT1Opj6IVO0n2ln8MT3IRFaVoZXKCj8NHitoKaTSxI1Py8kOpheOkrASBhkkDvBNfB0z6mnwfMgOq3mHPr8QziWElY=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1, 2, and 3", 
		"option_b": "1, 3, and 4", 
		"option_c": "2, 3, and 4", 
		"option_d": "1 and 3", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060146", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Rj654AuQV7lzfjxdX/HDCISrG2RW6ZnMHL2QOfAb+71iZh/Z1OZnVRo+2LD47b581Ycz6ddqY/ffS0WcJ9uwd7Wl9j5lTF1O8Nd2oZ99pdffbRUzS+jNOjVcr5axmuZZ0biYjipATB11Dbai39frZH7ySnoFO4/xQxykIhq4Ig3Mt6Z3OWW7Eq9gkaQ1X+WTa4kElWVucusq0KOpZY9po2xv2abwPz8g7jX9dsbZwYSq456I1+5h7oM6zkxXsb0YRxf/qTRIVfkMjm2IkxGQ34LbfRVvWMN+E8Fa87r", 
		"answer": "2+b4Z5//yFtHIoXS+8L1n+t46019wTFK", 
		"explanation": "24KwbZ+zxQ7lt4YvQAz7wO6/Nn7EQ2AQoHTDXa00f2HzW7TLeui+2p51Ik/Jgl078zbLrLD+41IGgeQb/YaaaWIFcZliiNHJ3Or+wnQMNsJDn4Qy9pMbe/EAzzyheNHfYP9gjm+SIlH1JwqyRGR8kXHXhG9BrZH7/DT7B+Y5/BsT1oR3/9o1OZeWyuiSqE+3kQrPz3OQWLhgUVCcpdyt+FCVr4x4ocWMpXLS57T/lere9dpLYBESq456I1O5lqwe+Tg8Ec2mZwFC/uqQblKtIWikKw8e8M7xlkNhw4xpSX47tBxJkJFfZ9Mz1Y3w/DAxPMYqGj36rFRQyId1SxLWZ7S81Xuk71N/dDomap9jqCw8r0PcPFx72mKSWClDgoVl994e1RZqeWhF3HTlgTCGhXbPfZ2j6pL5ke3MroVt0+MzKFOOdVXLFoxcdr7BK2syxuiQCOZIO55zVyv1fdMh7jT8JNad0XkMkNovPWXu8Wq+nsz2MGCooNL9gZR4G6tANcPA6N+y8FvLYCDoJG+AJub7Swn5QXnrkw93slg3wSUX7XGYB48/8iEMnXexRQRglyXyZW/hgrZd/sKPbYtx1/D80iEZjPF835nulBowRgeyiG1Q8rCXSkUPzEbTXsMI0EkoA6YMEZKR5WWTmzbEXHNNfMHkE6GC0GxLz/exjGB+tNABW8yBPAnUmdcyzVeiCPl8Rifirsb4ffEaH2o4+7t/iKxc2XVoVwXyfWNXJzWkac4=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "3 only", 
		"option_d": "2 and 4 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060147", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt5EoV170wPzrIHnVECIXrG2OV6c0cmijU6vDbeT724QxLlLJgVRs/nfIp7avt28B3uhv4YuGMCERe4p7zZCb2Of8hHNAIM9KicBO6shfSPxF1X2/ccfOLOoux2DAKkriZjCzAWM0qD+FykherZr7+SK6UJojz1UmnoI468cuMdaL0KedqEK+xhSN33OUCLBrBECWu8Ct7gOgrtZ4gcWIqHLe7Pf1j+va5tsHe0hXrYl7Zhuon61J9Cs2Vdu3aQJOs6tKWJHpTRQCnWyBvm1KdlQ=", 
		"answer": "2+f0O9Hy3x2qo8dmrWEHpJcs4tKMsPG24sAJ", 
		"explanation": "25K0aZL61Av5t4wuEhL90vH+O2/DQ2EQrT+FXbF5MHCjQqbQZ+jq0Nd+IRyPiFpv52TDsOmw/l0Mg71f4ICYKh4NQoVCx8KI3ury1ysBHslWm4l84YlffeZFjC+kcNPeM75hyC6HK0TzbjixRHRxliPfmTxCoIKvtSapUZozxQU9hY5s6Mx8Ps7f3qSS60S9lBW+0kmeS7YkE1WKvMC7sQOur4Ez9c+MojvV57T4iP2T9NsbcA1BrI9wbUj8g6AI7Go5Q830bh1Z/OHUIVb0YDyrIk4Y68Tw33tnho0vHW449RxPh5FFXs5B2ZvsuXI9MNh+Gj20pkEah6ZzXB+TNLC3xXzr7ls6cDoqd48tqywjpEKQIV972m2ZTThEhoV4vsQRlBAjfH1F3HDvkDKOhCWNZdP344W8hOrioapq/a1nJkfAMlDZVYQZd6D8KUhn3v6aHq4cI5NmHiz1Z5UB6S3uIYWcnykB0dAuPDfm5i/ZlMH0LSW7oZf4nZR5Ev8TM9XM5M65pBzTaSL1YXyBY4vwXBj/XHXs1goltQFlxSQc/HXZHIxttSsfkXPwTkhlkS7lfm+dmIpV5o7UP7o43/ms1CFQmbRshovylBI6Bxe+iXZOt4qLD0hHzECWF95HwAw+A6cIAJPVsm+P1XHcSn8EetzlPaa0zGxc0uaxj29uqJUcFYWdbEuXyo1qiBa/Bb0taWnRpqH1PP8cD3Y/urZ+iuOuo4q+bfCoOXYjeR+7QK9c4ZpVbUJvGQ6dCSVBZKutV40bAdRH12yKlAZGB35FFlWM/60YUhejvoTFb37bcbgdAg2uI6AQEMa4T1SPOP67yTnHA6zclEm6H0swWi2cMrhN9Qvxc4LhZp9i4NX5cfqdWi+GUhjlebU=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1 and 2", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3", 
		"option_c": "2 and 3", 
		"option_d": "2,3 and 4", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060148", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "25a3eoP61Fnr+YFgURfg1Oj6dWTCQ2EGrjKnV7NmdWLwXajMLvr2zIV0Z1KMm14783XFtqjl+1IbirsXyJyaZCcQPophzJCZzvb2yXhFMsoEioVz74lSWvtSwTipNNbCYOxrzWuTNEz/aXmyAjBgnCPTjzxZusO2+jW+FNk+0gQnk5Q0z80uO8Sc0bqG5kn1ogOHzDuHTa9wGFeYuY6r+UKfq8I5oY2ZuTeb/PH4nrjc9p4KIg9evoV2Zknwu9Ea8CsoVMz0bx5K8u3RbRT5Mie2IAZQzIbw3nV5w4ZpS2g4+BpfwoVZcM120tjmpXI3M8xpHDao5FcAw5trUQCXZrn42mfx8ls6bDhebQx6AkAnYlcsnAPo5TK1", 
		"explanation": "25a3eoP61FWq1IwyQwv3ib3wJyvzFG9Ln3GnV7NmdWLwXajMLvr2zIV0Z1KMm14783XFtqjl+1Ibirtn56/fcy0RbIJqhJCI2/f4hHpPPNFK2oFhpJtff/1S3SioNNvJYP15wyLALlawZnm6CHF3nTDaynBXpoe9+jW2FNk/wQczlZN9/8EmOdPf27HT6Q2rkgOHzDaGSbFoFFDV9c+l+0uVtIo9tNmIo3/X/f/82vDc/NIEdUhTq8Zra178n60I/Go3V4i1KARK/ejVeBT6KC2xIk4O98T0lnVnwsIgXmx09RxFl45DbsFn09jNqHI5LI1+HTb6qkpJ0519U1eFYLy/1Sjt7hUrfX9rY4V/sSwhqACSaFt42mrcSyBQl4lu7OwXqQpCb2pUmWWggzGPwFWWbpLu4oT9iajApbho4fkbJ2ePJ1HdUs0efPPSImR32fqSAqgcPJknAyr0ONBu8yu5LZmG2nkO2csxOnL0yCS4gMjhPHb6soD8zsd+Fa0QepHL6Nmlv0uHcyrlJniAJt/8WBywSXPq3k5yvx0riCYc6WHRDZtstSgfkXq1CUtq0iXveHThhbdY75HOcIhx0rXh0icejPVxkde32Bg9UQ21ij9C8peXTk5fjUbfGsoChAsrGKMEEZiR5mWT1XfUQX0OesDiQauO0T1d3/CxuWl4sdADQICaJQnXj54lwQWgFPhqFWL/p4L8ff1VGW0i/b50iuCuosSvdPqqYCUje1q0WOEZ/5BQbEJvHkvJDSEPZre8W5wKSO9BknrM1xdRVX5EDF7N9+gYWAWhufjGUmT8ZqMbHR3qcaYLF5TEQGPKMOHp3jXbEraflEv+XFYkTTHdIKRN8Q/1OoT3JRfznG4k+IHiPlBYTYYFACnSNGm8t6SQCA4oaiIhaINUOkaVSAIhgj/QNPwngrVAdB0oUeikC1EVnVFblz/GTl5KokENH6S5AEcvL+lQMEsU33ewH6RfUxqKh3oNglefyyf+ZbpYNFkiaWWHhkLn24Zumr/kjZiIBNOiJL4ekosRJ7sbUJLTX0gIm/Tq7u/0UWU6Ay14KLjcVueRuUzzBMn4roPbx1NdzIIGClEXaCqDiI/c9HpKI6RMZnFG/UcLo9/ValyW170UxlhpQFDotVflTWskr1F1YYHmb9mcKILl5FhaViPLVrpKne4/zmzgOsjfcxstAyM/nhKCeNfT+zqifav3wa4ABBTiw4vEUI1loAh4ws+9g0dOpCx7z33xS3eaV6r+4B9EJ3g4XbWTFlhEylcrxnq30UHlOIvqhb9JmrhEmLAB7h/+rS93gx6NTF7HbH2q0fDetibBskYiwK9xHGewG3p5jgErUvU4sn1hVyMpQK14/IL9KfHDkmCsJ5mqjZsE4VNaVefLIbn7udD5NabLPOX40YXDP2DkvJZxDea7LNACYECAdzUetLvwIpLFYQWWJSfE0amdEz+HKycb7zlqk3GaXRZvOSCGBtpVHyZXlMJmMbYXrcLh8GNjPH7IH/F+2K0FnkIZDVxKRbzpmWINGbh2K4eeZ0ts7U9cDuMUaWSyewY2bsgG2GK6AyGg+ST8grQuKJr4nRVpLUkYilk41u/jn6RsXVuEUEa4", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Corrie and cirque or cwm,Depression where neve accumulates", 
		"option_b": "L’shaped glacial trough,U-shaped valley formed by glacier's downward journey", 
		"option_c": "Aretes and pyramidal peaks,Formed by recession of three or more cirques", 
		"option_d": "Bergschrund,Deep vertical crack at the head of a glacier", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060149", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "25i3epD63xz5urUpVx331r3wMyvCDGEa42yLU7dgdWPmUOfAd63425hiMxyIjk9y/XiKi6T+8FoBiOhN6IKTdTsQM799wdKcw+Xl3TFXMspIn5ky5ZgQavEA2DWoNNnaKfAu2G+MK0DpKwuyB3s0ljDFg3JF5bG+5jK3QJox0ho/1pJ26NkpPdvf3LCQ6Vu5kg+N0juTUf1jHVWavMu6p3OVpYY1usOZ8TXX9ffwn+qe1cYfZwZBtpB6I1K/kugE+TkrEcmgKBRE/vCQblKtLSe2KRoc8MXwlCqGUNf7Cxcc08THFr/icSw=", 
		"explanation": "25i3epD63xz5rbkuYhf3xvjsdWTWQ3AeoHTDQat1ZGXmRqLGLu/niZFjKE+dzVp45n/JrZn+2lwdjqFV7J3fcTAGPopsy8WEwuj20HhOPdUElYYy9pUcd7REyT+/fcebIfBqjn2FI0z9YjepRGR8lSWWgn1ArcO58CK1FM4lwRshhohq+c04fNaR3eiX7V23lQ+W2X/RSqQkEBSeuc+r4kaO4LE3uMjNvD3J9f33n+uT8cwOIg5drYt6Zxu6hacEuDg3UsOnKBBZ/u/VbxT4MGihPk4b68TwwjRoxZYgUmd09RFCwpdeZ84z1Zn2rjs1O41oDHOuq0EAwJh9XB6TZv25wyjt9BUyemwudrZjgCMdoAGbIVp52l2dQCBUjZMxwt4thw1haHtBjm+glD6HjGCWPJLh5Jb5xfz4pflu86opaVeBOVDdT7ESTbLOIG58zamNDKpQNoZ0VyP0OJUr8DzvIYKR23ke2d0lb2Hm+Caci961LW27p9LwgMBzBqwFNcWF/sKjuBzTaSahLHyaaIviWAT8SmW45wZgrlgk2iRQ/HvIAYp++SEU3ni/XEpg0i7uLHutl71V65aLe8490vvozjERiPFr09vg3BguQkSogH5PvoGND1tDzFffG98UhAAgTKATHZTE5myEjDbGSnABetflQayOx2xG1fexi3Nyu5VOVJ/OKBzemtI/iBaiQelxUCfgqY/3feoUBmgp4/J2xuyivs+pSf2YIlclbBH3e+5K+ptCMj51Iw7OEChbIL68WZBeVO5Kw2DLm0dNX3xIE1vY8qcGHQaz6tDAayrZb7AfBxvwX703HM3zDkXOJvin23DIFLrckUKuTUE2XTOSL6NN6hWwcoP+KBykgCht94HnN1VJS4AcfCThcWqtoKfDCR96ayQgaI5OfEHQWRUqgDfCK7lin6gTeRcjAampHRATjhJOiT/GB1dL8EMYH6TtR18mKaBAMhslxTKsUaMeUlzehzEPzlmSgjTtO/NEJFpjaGySn0nz19JpmevsjM6EEtzrL7QP24MEaL9JVp/RClcdiPrw5uTzUWU3Rnl/K/HaHuTeokL3FsH7rP/U+VJ7wLsMO1A1MXmshZ7a+T9/dZlBSmheuH0KpdzXIg+p3MhU1EN7EFT4tVXsRCcnuR5nLpztKtDTP5Wx8VlRBRjJdvlTkfl80CPqIZ/WaBs8DmYn0Q6DNtOK0y2TOOz0xu0OCRmh3pzZBZ5l7Vw5yNOgzl8AvDNwgTztBXOabfWt5RFGJzxuSriTH0QdgRsj1jO0zECoLp+ji6pJgaVVmLod9QO3o2Fmg1+FQQrBcTP42/qfo2/Qu0s4iaxvXXLjT3Z/3A0tSrAq5jl6SChhT657qPb6KvHF3mygO5KszIUDpURVSKDPb4mzuJX1JqaFIqT/ysCQP2Dk8Jd6RPq6MZ4ELnKNZzwR5LzxIpXRZB2WfG6cxr6WASKYIGBS4DlviGePFk08r4sVZLharUk7zODd3kM=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Moraines,Pieces of rock shattered by frost action", 
		"option_b": "Hanging valleys,Tributary valley above the main valley", 
		"option_c": "Rock basins,Result from unequal excavation by glacier", 
		"option_d": "Piedmont glacier,Extensive ice mass at foot of mountains", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060150", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "25y7bZP2wx6n1YkvURWyx+/wPm7eQ2QDrHLDW6BxMGLrUavUa/6yiaR/KEuFhFV+v1PKprPx41oAgeha64GJdWIUdoJswJCa2evghGNEPsdNlJM+xZYaaOdDxH2KeNXYKft8g0mMJkb5Yiv9DX40pybfnmZTuo+6+yP3eds7wQYin4l5re8wPdSW3Lre2ES9gguN0m/RT7FlEl2cp46h5QO9rIMrvszPwr75i22qEZcTClJaVmTiBg==", 
		"explanation": "25y7bZP2wx6wy4sCXhHxzr39J2TbBmxRpW2MX+N9c3SjR6/HYvv72qt/BlLJhFh+8HPUpOX55BMOz6Ra+4maMDIKe4hqiN+Pl+30wTFVO8dQ2ohz99odbvtLyTPte9LdYPh8wWPAJgX3azi+DXVm1D7EynVVrcOo/SK3Upo2zhFyn5Q468QzPcOW16/T4UP4iRaH0juGSalhAxStvcuxq0CdrsIout6I8Tra7vXrnuuT5NFLcQBbr5U/YlW416kb/Wo3V9yxZlJY9OHeIV3jYDisKw8Pudnm0X1myJEVU1U6xxFJlY9fbMUp6pbBsDcmPtljGj36okZP0ZE8SB+fd7X4w2br9xUtcHcqbIR+gCMBqQrcO1pxjWeVQikRnZMr6tgc1QFveHlBiH/vjH+EkiWOcIfq/5X4gKj/rvlisq4oPE+UNFXWFoIOJaDMKHd3iuiZArBZc4hvHiHufcYg8y65IZiQnzAO1ZkyKnrm/STZi8j0KyiovIf3ipRfAP8SM8HX7NiyvkjUITfpJD2HdMr6SgHkRnP2kwxgow8gzS9Q6XDdCZo/+itNjXuxWktqkyugf3Kugf5f5ZSLbc4w3fGszTcCnfp2lpr7lBQ/QkS6g3sDu5ffRlJJwUHTEM4CwEksFfQHFZXF/X+F1XrZQHlNa8v7Ea2VwjhdyOaxj295/4AcUI+HPBDPi8ovxxmND8F3dGvovJX6NbwyBmUv87djkNGvkMa6dvqhPiUjYVqETuZN6ZBDZAN1FTfTMSxKIJmiU4kNQugP9XnLlA5NVT9AFhrY861IUQW4rcHbeirZb7AfBxvwI7oLU9rwSwfuOeG6hHDFCbydgUK6H00rDi6VJPAv4BX+f5/3ZDK/g3sk9selAUZSUJkSLivyem/5jLfEGEY7Pz8sL4ROfE7WSh4w1DDCM+x1jKtAfBkjRaWmC1tWlx9L3zfBTkhEolheUKPtVFsiaoNQLlwX3zagXIETWQjZhTJHrF+Z1jHvIfJEI0djTkq2vG/P26VpjfPtwqaEGN32LLoekp4KPLNnSqbYMloQm+D05u/hUUs1B25+K+qSYuzhuUryD8f6toPdyV1IwLsadlY1ZRiHiIzS8QZjG61KL11LsXIKvMPcY0aN1Yla3FV6EFz/tU7qRCcusFFnZparZtzOLZ625BBPHyHDWrZNjLx/0S3nPNrDd1o2CSMhmQLQYd3YyzDPfaD0w6wdABzi3peLVoV4+EB8z8+mxl5O6xp5jm/pCjqaV9TMqDdAYm9oWbGeHk4diQI2lTWn20GoPM+8hrUdzrFT3bRT4Bi3tilzz1iDQF6ObHWqyv6b91XHt0k1iY9vVWewG15i2wIwRfkl4TlvTilhQLI0t7j6O7+EmG69bpWs3swE6FtRSLTPb66yp9C8JK3Bb7b4zI6NJnzmsZRlBfamJNJFLHfDYC4cpa7xIORD8amBdhUe3zmhWtk2w4A=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Iceberg,Block broken from ice shelves", 
		"option_b": "Snowline,Elevation above which snow remains", 
		"option_c": "Aletsch Glacier,Glacier in Switzerland", 
		"option_d": "Malaspina Glacier,Piedmont glacier in Alaska", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060151", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/PXbTWI8SkiYsxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxMjhrtPpKe2Kh4NQoVOiPeb0uH5yHBPN4ZY2sAypMtfX/tWyS++NNnUMvsu2maBKQWlJzS0CHx9mz+WmW1DqZG+tSqyWN8k/BsQ1qZ2+ckuP8OW2qnT9A34xkbQnFieXrh2AhSYu46p+Uad4I0+9Zrf4X6LpKS5ienG8cwOIgVbs4NsX1Wf14sA6jstVIioKFILsaSQIRStc2iCKx0SucDt2WNnhoM6HWh09xBUkIpTIsl9lqvnsyY8PsNuKT2e42NMxpd1WgWFNKH4kCikoBVrNVcqfMpgszsw4QCSJE0+myuaSTsRnY5o9tUK1QUjeW5Z3H/uwh6FlGSdf4fq6IHAi9T+iLZ0sq4mJ1jAOlqYQoUZJbLCLnF3ivmaBLRPc551EmLlMsc8+Trtf9Tf1C/perl834LTFsGvPe57", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxRH48oBihNe0hfegvQArXU1qVizr0A==", 
		"explanation": "25T4T4P21Bfm9oskEgKylL3cOn3VEXFRrnCRV+NgeHDtFPKCY+TyxZ5+KRyanE564HOGrqz88kAzgY9J7IuRfCMNestm25Cd3+G3035TP8IDicB+5YgYeedUjDS+eNXVJL5vwGrAJErmYiuuRHF61DDEj30Wp4X79CW0Qc53mEZk2tcovYgvLcKey63T5US0gxXC73TRXLVhUUeNtNqt5kaStMIxpo2OviDJ8fftpvbv/vxLQwZGvpR8d1K/lugVuHh4cseibQBYseXeIVX/JSnjKAhdrpmzmiQ5lsI6THw15hoGj4paZ9NP2LnqqDMiPNljFjL6qlcA05x5HwCZZrG8l3uk7FQtcn84ccpkvyh1sgeZLUA+m2WYDC9egoV57ZAYm0Rib2pB3Hnmwj6Jj3CbPMa3q431ieT5r7cj4bIyKFOFdVHRWogPJYDPZ3N6z6mIGadINpJiGTamNMZu9Tf6L4SG2joZ7NccIVSn1yOLg9jweXn64NLYgsd5VLQOOcbLqcqk8F2HYizzM3SWJsL6GTvzQGj00gBhixYEiCIZ+nPNDcl25m0M3ny/XkgpgS/hfHml1rpZ+pCLbJ043PusyToRjLRxjNvx2w8xQgD7j2YDpoyaD1RKzFDBH98DhAw8A6cIG5iR/WvWlDbXR30OdsvkQYGTgyVbmuL9nW49tJ4BQoLOLQqbi54lxwWjCPg5XGmtm4X2KfAUBGBsyb0x3uWk99mvdOehIWAke1q+Sq9a/IdDbQFvLQXhCwAPR7SvVZQbU/MPzjWe1ypJXj9ECkzJu6cGUR3qq4TOa32ear8fBhvxI7JFF8/hDk7BddCn3DHbBauVlkaCUWMpTzmUJKIepQTxdMz/KwW202lwucXsNFdeVoYZKGfgZG68obDPSwI/bykrLINJfQfaRVAwnDuDM+B3iOcPdlgqTamkEFUE1hBBm37GBl0FpEkMTaSkThMzIqhRYFIFjT6mUa0QShXEgXoFmFOOggviadtFJUgxeHCajE2s25Vqnvzgh5ySStfjI/0W3ZsGaLlVSIOWHhsan+Sk5u/jGWkqRmw3KvnRHtHe8Fv+B4jntsLOwFFOx6pIP0x7JjaZm5ra5AZjE6t7Z3VYuHUWvs+eIhKi3JpclVF6VRW/tULrU3UktQUzfpLieM6eiDZ2sqabr1RmbZIB/suJ7Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060152", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/PXbTWI8SkiYsxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc6zeTEXM6JGkuyH6+rWhFBTNtJBicBupNpfPLQAjH3tNJSbYL4uji7AdgXWaCuwAXQ0liiWnnRErYb7+jX7WdUlxVUxn5Vp+M0vANm9mZiK+ky1jwKD0DuhTbxvAhSF9ZzowE2Vpod1sMmKtDab5v39nf3AzNAoIjpdvI0/QVqvnqYauDZ4EYj0KFILsbeQR13hLC2nZwwEucfi3XF6hosnHX088V9Qg49aZ9kzworrqTU4A8NOVR61sUVJyZFvHwvWNP34kCikoBV/NTprMcpAvSkw4RqMaFt42nuVSS9Uh8Bk+JALmgdoPXxInWL0hy2OhCWNZdPl+Y/vkajxo61q/a0bJ32OHVPPFoAda6qAKGEy3uGeTadeOoliVzLnNMc9vDjrJdaX0Csf1do0cDVvxgeu0WQCNL7Mg7RTL67I", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "25T4SYP2xRz5t5lgA17Uyu/yMG+QAXtRt3eRV6Y0f2OjWajQa639wIVgMlmasVVa4HPSpraw9kEKz65U+4OadGIBZ8t7wNXJ2uHy0HhPNIZLnMBm85Vff/1S3SioZ5ToL756xmvANFHxczywAX5g1DjFynVYq4yp5yK4QOY5/BsQ1rdh/8kxNdOe1eij7UyzlUaenCnRY7NtF1HUsMqv7kfcsos8ssiejTzr7eb4l/HX8dJLcg1TtJU/Ykm5164G6ic9VYi2cVJf+eGQc1HuJTuwLgETucTllmBh1IcsHWYmtBJJkIYWYclhx43hr3IEN8gqBTa7qFcAxoZ5HxGZZrC91Cjm+RUrfX9rd49gvSQ7qAGbaEZxmWDcWCRQgMBi7ZAVkAJ3PW1FlH/uhn+KhnGKbtP344W8huHisaxm4eMvKFeFdVnKWYkZYfPUL2Iy2fyJH6lJPZtuGSWmMdQg+Cr6IYaRnwoCkM0oKjf04CuNl8DwN3H6uoG5jdtkBroDIu3L1cWU8G7IYiihA3yAb8XnGRSwHDze2gJpshxlyjhQ5GPTDZo//CNNina1CVJlnivldTy1hLFJ7Yqycbw+0P6s3zMDkfpr35rl0V04QhSpiGxQu4uRXBxbxVXCXswVwUkoA6YMEZKR8HTWgX7VC3kfcN3/DqbHzCoI3e/wjWh4rYNOYYSLNVnYi9BmyhLxB/R1WWLp6ITgffAUAWE/tvJz3/nho8K+bLOlPmBqYRWjGe5V5JRIe0J9GAfRACAPU7fuQpUbAfNb02HPmgJGUz9AFhrF9asHTxavqdD0YFbQR/ExAQzjar0AAI7kDhOPGPCtzXDcFv+TkweuVkEmSyndLrZN9wjzcczhLBKnh212/MWlMEgbQpEYLzOzdWitrKyNNwgXcD4kIYRCaQfUWRVkhjfHIPx0zagGMB8hQKuuGFxWkhRNjTfBTkxNsVheXreoAFciOqZWKU8UyXe3COAYUB3Jjz8YnRaoyiesLf9JI0AwO2eSgQzintJrnvvswpuRStvkba8U0YYQZPZIRZTSUxsdlPek6PPhB2k1RkRjbvvJUKLQvFz5Qsrx4s7bwVkL3K5IOVl7NTCOiprKsDVrb7dAbHsKqXsYuIraYxCvmYpc0F4oQ13t4VXhU2Il9hNqLpX5Zc7Iapqm5FlQGGT0WPlXkPk4zjjlIdrcYRQrR2om0QSfZMDPxCC/M5D19KUMFx2k2IvOCcp55E1ry5yz0UkA+Xt2gG7wDnXOIvfs4QxHYC3jonHHUJ7CnfTh8leWw2M=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060153", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/PXbTWI8SkiYsxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPqdm28TE/s2t+H99PecEvYxz55MeaPFEjBWkc9zXIfBqjnLAZxSwSji0Cnxt1DXTmnNFoZey+im6WJoxxRQmg5V9/vQyHpe41amQ4UysgwLC8HSGRLxqFUfZqY76q2WZoZYtp8ie8T7S//G5mfHB4csOcUhTsYI/Ykm5g60axCQbEe+4aRFC9PaQbFv7JSWmKRpd5Yujlicp4IM6SWwmtBZIwpdeZ4B+35zgsDcMMekqNzaopFdDz4ZpURPWaP34kCikoBV/NTprJd4tmCgwsU+KLUZqk2idQGxShoFo9ZAYgUR3dWoAlHPhhn+EhiWOPJTv6oP1gPrMroVt2qwwaUyBO0WYWYtccbvFZ2Zww/+eTbZdOo10VyP0OJUt8yvrJZWAgHtIIY9nBklWqfrCU45JCiC/", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "25T4T53y0hDr44AkEjb7wvXzNGXUQ35R8j+uU6p6fGijUKLSYf733Z5+KV2FzV1+82LTsaDjy10og6lY4IuNY2IKcMtnwdeB2+X5wGIBMtRB2o1z7ZQTZbRF3jK+fdvVIfIijmOFJkv5aT79EHh1gHHCgnlP6Iap+iO+FM4/xVU+l4l8/ss9LNLf7aCW8Q28iUaM02/RTLh0HkeQoY6l/kCU4I85ocifuDPXtMf22uzb9Z4YdglGuot6bU/8nrtJ8SQ7XtqmbRFfzersb3atBySiJAcc7c7nllhm0Y4oU20ntAMG0MNwZ8Fnw4rhr3I8NsZvVTCzsVVVwoc8XhmSNLyq1Xzh82kxUnYqZoNorj51qAHcJFtplmqSSD8Rl4FlvtYWhwkjfC9WnWTphyuSwGqJPJXm6pTpl+3j7Plq/KArPEWJO1uYVYQOdKbFNCsyy/ueGaNPf99mGSamMNo8/TD3JYXU7DZNxNElb2Tz9T6cn8j7LSWzoNL6gcZkEbwUCt/55+j3l1DGYirkMz2ead3xVA3+Wzzkk10lkRk23CQCqGvWSJ138G0Al3q0RUFYnADsbX+ok6xPqo+BaYtx1fT/yTcC2PVs34//0V0+SBCvgnIDpoyeQRxO2RTCFshH0AY+TIAJHYWR+37Wl3PTSmkeeo7iCa3HwSNczuz8zm57/4QGUMyJIBjYg9s0iB6iQfR3FWTippL4PuhVHW048vJlwujhsNi0YP2gYCU9ZxO0Ua9J4ZpHYQZ+AkvQCjZKIL68X54KSO9BkkbF1xNAQj9aEVvY/qUNUxDqo9eIZ2TdbKMOCx32X705Heq4bELdMuKqwCLcCLvciQfqH2AgSyrdN7Uf8Q7ze4CyJwGykGMk+NWlJlleBIsSPSOze235pOOEBwc5dik3FIRmOkXQWRc3lzbRMvdjza4TMBltRa2iCRAAkwNblj3TAhhGok0dVOW5SFIzaq9KMlYCjTahUbQXWVzCgzsOzlmagiOsLvZKMkAmaSS6mwzpiNJgkO3kh4rBHdznI/0P2ohDL7paR5PTDRsMj//o/KHhBm0gRmtlIfWISurU8E3zBtr7ocia9lML3bYNdkwvJC2OhJrX5HpkPOVMYGJYuHANkMTubDKi3Jpc0196VRms4UnhU2JhtwN2LsGradLOOJ6m5BBPFy3VRPsnNBkaVORQX+C5pC1D2wAA", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060154", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "24e3a5n2kTTl4pEvXBD3wLDNMHjVDmAdpmzDU+NneHTmRLTJZ+O+3p52Z1OHjl475XnUreX5+RMpnalV6ovTUzACectuxtTJ4+X+yDxiMtVQloUy1pUcd7RPyn2IcN3VIut8yWbMBUrlaz24FjB3mDDPx19Zppe6/CmoFNg41Rk2k5VrrckyOJee16+G5EyqxhWW03WUW/FBA0aYocer+A6/r48out6ItXLU8rT0m+zW4tcKbhsSu495ZV6ukqYduCwqXsX0fBpO+PaQckH/Mie2KQoU98yjxHFuz40nTitdyPbHhbRqaabBFY7RgOf2", 
		"explanation": "24e3a5n2kRTl4pEvXBD3wL32JivRQ3UQtXrOXqp/dTHlUabWe//7iYN5JkjJhEg79HnUrqD0t1EWz7xT7M6ecjACbYJgxpCG0aTwyHBCOsNWicBb8NoWb7ROzTCocJTaJupr3C6UL0CwQSu4CnN81CbZmHgWroyptRv5R9IyxQUhnY52rd81O+vdmaqW60ytlQPC1W/RWrh3FFmbucu7q1eUpcItu8ibtDyb5+HrnPnQ9Z4EZEhT/5V3Zl6shKMA9movWM+IZi5F0vbRZhTsLizjMw8U9YvqxTRoho4oU20y+w1LwpdeY9Qz34ukuj0iMshuVTGj41BIwtR5TRiFfbK2kGfioFR/cnYqZoNorm0ctU+fJ1ptk3iIX2xeksBqvsMNkAFzMHxJmHPkwjyZgWLPNJDv4ob6zKjxrr0j8+MrJk+HeRzfU4MIabaAM2Z7xqmvBaMcMI1mEGLvLpUo8yv0JZLU3SBNxNElb3/i9S6Ok9/xeWCovIHwgdo2G7lAItnAqcy7sV/OZDGtYXydYovgUQ2wW33x305spFgjxzMd7WaYCpA/4SUI3nq1WUt3mzPpY3Lhmbgc7Y6PfIcw37Xo2DACkedEkaf59hIpSwC+nz9AvoWGD1VcjVWWCtQXwUkhCvQGGJfS+2ya1XLVW3Medtq2FaCG12xByaPygWxtsIMLUcyBKlnZhcsqzBKjErE5VGnqvYr4L7wGHmsi/6E9iv61vsmwbLOnIGQzI1q2V+sZ9ZxfbUJpHgjWRSJDb628FqkWRKBN3WDGkwJaVD9IC16M6LwHUwG56sXaayrdYqMOBxvmI7EcU9rwSwfIOfCqwTXbRr6SkQe6WlQqXTOJJLRN8g/1dMzmLBbzlGRl+sjgIBFWQY8DL2fHfG75treKCA0jPy8pKZMHe0nRCxYtmjuDNfZkhucGfBc4U+imC1VWlx1ckH7WC0hKo0UKWqHtQkpnPqFAYFwdzDS8FLIjUiDEoygYj0KVwTGsKOhOcUssbmiXil7z24Zunuupg5yEStLtOLMfkoQNaLcbVp/RFlQS2ufs7vWgGH95AmRxKP3aW+zF8EnkDcW0tsvfhVFK3bsaP143ZS2DiIuZ5DJoNuVOfXUKsHIdqYrdZEaPy5pYwVlrQxXt50SkVXUguAJjYYH/b9mcKILl91xeFS3CRaoDmfJ8nSjhJdDCbQ46AyMimQKeNsbCwnSEMa34yagbRRWn243YBwvX2sqRwf9QLvuwco6GVDI=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Roche Moutonnee,Resembles a sheepskin wig once worn in France", 
		"option_b": "Crag and Tail,Castle Rock of Edinburgh", 
		"option_c": "Boulder clay,Contains boulders and angular stones", 
		"option_d": "Erratics,Composed of materials different from their surrounding regions", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060155", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "25GqfZz/2Bf5urclQRv/x/H6dSzSAnEapmvDXaU0dXbkR+CCeuLuxpBjJkyBlBde4X3Dsba921wBiOgdqc6RcTARcZwv2tmN0OHkhHJOPtZLiYV2pJUZPOdBwjntddrfYPl8z3iFKwnEYiuwDX51mHHbhW5XoY2+5mqYW9sl0xBykoJ6/8EvfNOayaeA4Vm9gkaDyDuFQLgkFFCesI6n7QOIqId4vM6I/CHT8fHt1tfG5MkKcQASr4p+alWv2osG9j45WMb0fBdZ4+XTZEetISanZwoY9d/i33cpwoc5Uno94AwGjYUWb8V/wtXzvSY1LY15ASG/oklThWq2aSd9e4N3CcuXtiyghHA=", 
		"explanation": "25GqfZz/2Bf5t4QyV173yfLxMmrEBmZRq3aPXrA0ZHniQOfDfOi+2p9wN1mNzVdy+XOGn+f5+UUKnbxe7c6adyUQQskv/NiMzqT21nQBNclWl4V2pJgGPOBIyX2pccTUM/d6x2GOZ0r2Jz6xBXN9lT2WnnVapM/74i+yV9J3yQZyl8d15NAoKcWamaeVqF65iALOnHyDSathHRjZtMCsq0CQoZt4gcWI8SbS+Pi5k+uT9NsbbRtbq4N7I1ml17wB/Wo/Xcm3YRdZseXDIV35YCWsMQsOucT102Yp0oosHW4m+wpIhr9YXs5WxZPhriFwPt9vVT+1rUMMh5p9TQWZY/2q2Wzj5UZ/YXIqccpsrih1ogCROFttn2/cQyoRh4Fl+pAYmwAjen1BinPswguDhXzPfYHmq4bzl+X1pPlh6+MzIUTAMVnIWZ4VcbrPKSd9zKmcAadfOp5rVy/jMcE5/S38Mtag1zxN3dwsO2Dm4C+L0s70K3eztoG5mtxzVKwBONWF6MWz8FvVYDXkLTHTZ8XwGRz4SnK41wt1uAss3DJQ4XaYH4F6+20ZlnvwXkVwlzWgf3Cuga0c7o2Zcc4+wbX/yT0Ai8h2o5XD0Q8xTgq6gT9OvZaeRlJK3hTXDMhH1gAqC7ESVJnXsmqalHXZSnBNe8v0E6GUgzhA2/exj3N4/5QLRYOdJQ3ejp4n3FelCfg5UGPqrcb2O7wBAmFs87F0iv6pss+vNcesKXxqbgiyGelW4ZhUbEJsGQ7TRTBHZfipWpwdSOVdkmbemBdbB3JGE1PC/OgJUwDqvszNLm7bYaMVHV7rcPMJFsjsDkXKPfinzAzHMrqOmE6wXkhlQzWPILkD4BSwfYDzJxqynyho+M/hNF5JSawHOSngNGK35aLDBQMtPzssJo5IbXvbdx4LgSrUJupvzbcMcREjUuimC1VWkB1Oi37THF1EowwRWeW+RVcuJ6xLNBsFxTahUaENWVzOgyoFnV+IxyasK+MLPEwvb3OSm0ny24Fyjfroj53BPtznbbAe3pkUKaJeVtrFC0kZm/73r+LhA34gRnl/K7jbW+bYvUr4FoS0o83ehUhDzLBIMlorKiqCnd/Q5Hp6J6BBL2RCuDMOrd7XcEa51YdOxhBsX0LitU72AXQ1uQFgLrz+fsrdOZPl4FxeHyrUF7pClrx70iLwNNbfJA46FXE0kgKDNtPEw3SHOKDvwaQKRRynx5bYTJ5+rv4Tcejp39eNNLuOwEZoqXA=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Drumlins,Resemble 'basket of eggs' topography", 
		"option_b": "Eskers,Long &  narrow ridges composed of sand and gravel", 
		"option_c": "Terminal moraines,Coarse debris deposited at the edge of the ice-sheet", 
		"option_d": "Outwash plains,Contain terraces and deltaic deposits of melt-water streams", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060156", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHbxBTr+cUBQQ73xunsdWTWQ0UdonyKU7dxdDHPVanGaOLsxIQ8DlKPgU5+/HXD46r+t1sagqlVqY+cZCsVd59mzcPJ1urzhH1APcJClZJ/99Y9c+FMyDi/NNfXIecu3mKBLkvjKh+4FmR9mDSWi3tEoYCu+TOuRts7gAU+l452/oQZLsWezaGQ+wCXhBWWzm6SXP1iEEaUvMCvq0eJpcIsuo2ZuTfS5rTqk+LWvPkZZwlG/6p+aF6v16cPuAQ3Q9y8KDNG9PbZYlWgBiexKk4Y4cjm2nhsyJZpSmgg8Q1Rg5pFINyEhiRYaju122+KJbzbPro=", 
		"explanation": "25K0aZL60A3v88UsUxD2w/LtOHiQC2MHpj+CErB9d3/qUq7Bb+PqiZ58N12KmRt0/DbOtqjx+RMOjLxS/4eLeScQPophzJCd3+G3wX9XOtRLlI136o5fSPxF1X2uddqbMOxh2GeEIgX2YiupDXxx1DDRmHVVvY+v4DW6WJo7wRs22sd379soLsKczeiV6V+1jwiFkDuQRrkkF1uLuI6t80CZrI49u9nNpjPP8ebum+HAzNA3bCpdqop7Zkn8lKQI4WooXcm9ZgEL8PbVIVLiMiWmI04f4Iv33nEpwoc5Uno94BZJjMNZZIB02pnntTM8f9ljGT/6l0xFh4B1UxvWfa740Sjp6U0rYGguJYVr/D40rwvQaFNsm32ZQGARlY5vvtMVlB0jaWdBiDbpkX+PhXWAb5r37oS8h/GwtLFmsqQrKEKJME6YV55cbKeAKmhkz/rbArBZId9zHyemOsch6Tf9YLSbyjUJ1ctgLHvm7WqJnsz8N3b6sJP3ztZzVKkFJMiF786lpFXLZGPgJm+aZd74TR3iTnC43w9rs1gnzSIR/XHdSJ138G0Zl3K8CUdrnDPhZXKy1rBJ/pCHeoAlwLX41TME2OR0npXjx10yQgG/zWtM8oONQEtzw2jYO98VxR0nD6dBFYTUsm+ZgHrUTm4eP9r+ALzHwj5NmuX+m295/5kAFY3OPhzcg9EoiAO5AOk5XHStrI//O/kHD2o4urRjxeDho8K+Nf6lOGA4Zhu7GftR8oERfAp+CEvcFyEPbbmqU90RR6BqwGfLgw5LVD9IF1+M77oJUxe6pdbca26eYahcCRLjYLoAAd24T0nLdfWs2D/aD6uZkQepV0ErDi6VJPAK6Qbzc4ngZB62n3x3ueT3IFBPTYAEfCTyeiu2p7CXGRM5a2wjKZhKc0nSCxIhlz/WNPwnma8FaVguQKbnG1VWmhBdmDuSD1ZB8B9eS6rtUlYqJb9AHFUtwwO9FOA4ThnLknomj12Z0WLjL7plPls3cySygknykpFn3/77h86ASsf7Pqke380MLvZdTYzTX1cdiPThr+3hGmkqRnl/L+yISefDtQ/wDdr5p8eax0ULzrIJNVY+NyrLvZfcsDZsJKBcL3FYuDMYoorbbxaly5xY20QoQ1r550LhAWgn9gZyepb5KtvTONuh4llRHS3JUPUDke5q1CvlIdbealZ/Bm0x0ROCd9zZ1zuRKa3vyaIHRSyq0oCLRJhorEl13dPywgxQpCtgg33wS2LVd/Xk+woUJnlrX72RG0lUiRlgVatRZGKxVVdbhPFQZBIQMQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms,Influence on human activities and landforms", 
		"option_b": "Boulder clay plains,Fertile agricultural plains", 
		"option_c": "Erratics,Obstruct farming due to their size", 
		"option_d": "Great Lakes of North America,Form excellent waterways", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060157", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "24GqaZ/g2Qzn9osjV1PTy/TyNGedDmsWsX6XW6x6MGX6RKKCYeu+z5ZjKlWHihc73WPStKTj/xMfg6lS553SUy0NaopmxpCMxO/y1mIBMshA2otz6Z8MPPJP3n2+ddrfYP9gyi6HNUTmYjX9AWhghjDVnnVZps+c+Sa4XdsjxRFym4ht49w9NdmMlImH/F+5hRLCyHSEWrR3BUfZs8G6q1CXqYs2so2Mvzab+fvslOzS+dBLYQRbsoR2bVzwsKQI+yM5XYi4aRlOsebVZUegEz2zNwEP7Yvr03V/38IqT2Yk5BZIhcNXZNR2xNjovTk1LI1rBzb6pkhJyp1yXgOTcP/cJAR/SAX6YXOjer7z3mdV", 
		"explanation": "24GqaZ/g2Qzn9osjV1771r3+dX/JE2dRrHnDU619fXDvFK/Xfe//x5NjPhyAgxts+n/Fq+X8/kUKnLxU6oXfcTAGPoZg3tWNl+Lly3wBPMhB2odg5YAWcvMAzS+odZTPL75vwGGUL0DiJzi+B39mkDjYjTxCp8Ov/SL7R9820xo8hcdM5cEvfN6MmaeV/Ei2xgKN0n7RQbMkHFuMu9qp4k2TtZF4p8iKuD3V57i5jfDW4ttLdgBX/4dxala9m7tJ+ys2EcqxKB9E5+HUIUDiYCCqIAYY64vi2mBg0pctWHp0/REGlotTItNm25XhrnIxMckqATz6r0tXwoY8XhuCfamt1G33oFwxNW4jYMp6tSMhpB2gJmhwtX6IWy1CnMB78tEQmxcjfH1F3HDsgyvLgXeKfYCj5Ia8lu30qbRm/LdnPUmBIRzZRIhcYbbQKHR73uyfTaRFc5JiGzbxPMEr7nnqNISR3jQekO0oKm6n9yuX0s76N3G7upy5i8d9Ea0TdtDL7Yu8sVHCcm+hNnWaZcO0WBr1D27x1wlgpFgqzmED6WzcSIhx8W0KjH+mTEgkhi/heDyghLsc646dcM433Ofh2DZQmu04kp77wAo9UwGpzVpQuYGNXBxOw1CWFcwKwRpuD7UPVJTUsniFkHKQTXMfP933D6zHwiJMmuTjj3d4s9ALTZicLRrPg9EohFemCfR6XSfku8b4feoUBnEt+L50iv+kpMWuZ/ChbGMlfVq0VuFK54dEaxZyHgXhCxhBR7SvVZQfVeVLknjFgglcRnZHFhrN6a1IXES6pdTdYmvMI7UZHQrrbbIRGsH2DkHAJ7G9xyXbD6yIhgv+SEwqDjmSLLVN8Qiwf4L4Kwrzkmtw8NfsJlheV8MEKST7NGqq5bCIAg80eGBlJYVSdFPUQh5klzLKKvtug6BMMBkjReivEFsfmBYPqzbXTlVKpUIKXqyjUxMoLK9AMhsC2SK7H6kRW1zZhT8Ei0SFgiPiLbpIOUgvd2GdiEXunNJymu37g4ePNtreI5oX044KKbobSJvdGhsen/f3r+LhHywqE31nIercHurUsVnvQsvmrdPKzFJMib8OIlopZS2DjN/V8TFoPOVOfXUKuH8QocPcYxKv3cht3VUoQ1Do/EzhT3NhohlyetP8a86cLp61/0NWAiHDF7ta2Ohw2GzjOd7SbR8tR2A0n0eSc5Lcwiaafar+0rkACR3ul5jFQcp55E05wt25xl8AqDp7z2zwBGDTZuKt6V5HLWlqSLHfFVsdkRY20Cjx2Fz6fYa4la8Oj6RI17tRTLAf7Ch/bCJ4AnaK6i8kOA==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Transhumance,Animal-migration type of farming", 
		"option_b": "Outwash plains,Contain eskers and kames for sand and gravel extraction", 
		"option_c": "Glaciated mountains,Attract tourists for skiing and mountain climbing", 
		"option_d": "Glacial lake beds,Support heavy cropping after lakes are eliminated", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060158", 
		"question": "25q2KIX71Fn6+4QuVwqywPztIWOcQ28esGvDXaU0ZHnmFKHQa/723pZlIk7JiENy4WLV46Tjt1oMiuhY6J6MMCMNestoxNGK3uHl1zFuJtIElYYy8JIaPOZFwTyket3VJ75o3GuTL1LxczyvSDBgnDSWhn1Er4ao4WerRtUnzwcmn4h2rfNubIbMlPmuqk9T7A6++OoEKKtaE60Ramc=", 
		"answer": "27CgYYLnwlnr5MUnQBHny/noNH/VESCClVojcGvl+T7e+dqyl5rW", 
		"explanation": "24KwYZ32kRiq5IwnXBf0zP7+O3+QE20Dt3aMXON7djHGVbXWZqrtiZFjIk+Bmlpv92SGqraw5EcAna1fqYeRMCsAe8tsycCal+X5wDFGP8dHk4Vg99Zfc/IA2DWoNMbeLf9nwGeOIAX2dTyuDGd1gDTExjxRuoyu+yOsVc4y0lUgk5dq6Ns5MsOMmanT5Vi7jkaO3WmWTa8kAUaWpcG6/0qTrsIsvcyD8SbT8bTum+zW4p4NbR1cu8Z2bRuunr4M6jl0Edu7YR4L/OvZckD4Mi3vZwEPud/r0zRo0o8mTnk88Q1DzMNxcM9m2JzzvSY1LY1jBnOuq0EA0JVoWgXWYLW5xCji6VkzZjo/bY8trz00ogqPaFVwniufXi1Sn5Mr995ZgApneH1Hjnn1jDvLk2qGcNPi5YS8l+fzq/lv87oiO1LOdXXMEZ5cZPPDNXJxw+iXTbVTJo1kEmLgMsdu+CvwLp2d0T5Nx9g0KmWn9SSd0sTnK2y9sobwgdo4VJYOdtLK59+lsU/TLWPzKGuWdNi4GRz4QGn/205zvgssyi0JqHLKB4R2+ygDijLwQUtolmfvYnC41r8c+Y+Pc4Jx1eft3iYZl/o4kJ23wBU5BxO0n3NH9ZffSU5K3lzBH9kC1ksSA2SHgQdcuf3HSroJ6yC7", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Landforms of Glaciation >> The lce Age and Types of lce Masses to The Human Aspects of Glaciated Landforms", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "is found in atmosphere as moisture and clouds", 
		"option_b": "is found in freshwater lakes and rivers", 
		"option_c": "exists as groundwater", 
		"option_d": "exists as soil moisture", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070101", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/2CUuOvgNdVIk+Mn09osnfUpuX9+EAbg7Eb74GKfiZDcI5u2pCd3+G3wWBUMtJLiMBO6shWPNxBwTypdZTSM75vjn2BKUHpJz24F3VmgHHqhC8f6LSy+yP7Ucg40xw9mMdx/ogxM8Wama2V7kS7jwOMyDuYRv1lA12d9dyt7EqTrpF4ocWMv3LS+rTxj/Xa9J4ZZw9bsIhsI2eyw+FJwSsqVcm6bwEL8PbVIVziMiG5KAAJ+MejxHtqzcI6SXsh9wtTkIZFXs5P2LDrq3I9PsNzVTy841BIwtR9XRiAcf2rxGnw5Vg6e244JYt/uW02rh2OLVdqxSmEHbR7bSZaaKjZ8IuW3IEe", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0Eg3mxOn6OG7eF3FRom2GCJ96R3jtUOfHfOLtwJh/Z1WazVZ04HOGpqP2/lAGiqZPqYeRMCMRd48v2tWO3uv51zFVO8dK2ol8pJIKcf1EjC+oc93ULu1SwFeBNUHxaT6uRHFmkXHehW5fsoy14Sa3FMg4wx5yhZNq+MsoKcWaypSd1EOMjgPC02+ZTa8kAkCYocul7k2Is8I5p8jNuDzY++brn/vHzNA3bCxXrINtd0j8lroMuCQ3RYi5ZwFf/f2QZ1v4LizjKQsc64v33nEpw5M8XH075l9vjMNQY8NnmtjpsyEkf8lvBjaot1cAxoZ5HxGZYbO8kGHqoEE3cDombI5psCh1rQ6IIUBrnm6PAGxTkZR8+9UX1VczPW5OmDa20n+PhWKdeZbwq47zl/z44LZxsrAoPFWIdVPeFpkUYPPFNnJz3uaJMah0MpJmEyOmNMZu8jbtYJfUzDgD1MBgK3L08TiN0uX0NGS+stLwnZR3VKsZJtSF5s33tFnUZDH1YWmbZ9+0UBuwTHT5wQ9mox03wTsV7CLaEcl99D8I3my/Sk8kuzOgZW/hkLFJ5IbOdoBx0ufp3CFQj/x9jZ63wBU5Bxa0jnQDu5ffW1NAjQeWCsJHxgxuCaYOEJPVsm+P1WHZRXhNcNy2FqmTxj501NrwnGV8sZcdFY2cKVnVhcpmwBijCOd2W3PspMbrMv8eSnc46Kdy3vizstn7TPK2KGQkaAn3WP1cs4JYZgY2AgjICTRbZbzuRJIdSqBJ3WfHlhNBSHFaRU7E+rxIXBav6tDRfmPdYr0QF17nb7wLFM/sS0OPNP+tiDjIELrclAepXlIgAzaUKrVN5Bfgf43gJR2wlihQ8cT8clBJQcMZMzOzfGSrrLmMBRI7c25H55AP4dYJDZ+VR2KH/xJK", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070102", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/2CUuOvgNdLIkmOiFU783jC45zx5VcOga9IqYyQZCpDdop5zZCB2Pb+3n5PJ8dI2pNm9psLfbR8wm/kNPWbDft9zy6JNAXxJyqpAXVk2SLfjnlS6Iuy+Sv7aNRkiVUbmJR94co5LtDf0LvT6UP4jxWN0HqFTbkkGV2VuY6/4leU4IN4p8KYvzbe8LTtleiTzNBfK0h2uoBzYk+1mKZJ6i8rRMSge1JC/6TEaVGtMimqNAcT/ovs0DR9zodpUWg68F9Vl5FQY8N2lqTqgDwHN8RpHXO1pQRUz5E8XhWZYrj4w3zl9FAycHQ/dspsrih1qAGfJ0Zsn2iIE25N5DQ2dWUZ45YWNX4wsHY4", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kU2q+IssS1zVbDoKf3IKA2NImUSncxP/", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH63xrl5ZclUQqy1un+IW7dBmwFsD+CQKYuTH/ZUbLFa+PtiZZ/IxywjEl/83jBsOXy+EcHz6Ba/4vfeC0Rd5FgxsSI26Tk0GNAJ8cEoIVn458Rb7RB3jjtY93VJLN9zXuMN1H1Y3mvC3N/1DfZmHFXvIq0+zT7QNI21FUzhII4+dEsNdSe1aSKqEi0iQiF3W+UTP1lH1DZvc++7gOd4JU5o8jAvTvQ8bT4iujW8cwKbAtX/7J3ZkL8lroMuCw3Q8WxbFJJ6KTEaVGtISqxJh0U9sWj2XIp0YsnWSQ2+BBRjMNFY853lqHlrjYxMcp5VTKopgRBy4dzHwCfern1w2vx7EUrcH5rd4Vut20zrh2RKUB3lWWPAGxTgZQr6tgcjERib2oAiG/wizyKjGmWPJ7s+YW8jPripb52/qI1aUiOdU/QV50ZJYfIIn4yy/ueTaBTIZJiE2LkJJU69Dy5JJOS0zgZ2dYub3jhtD2QnMm4O2m1pJy5ndV4EP8uM9jR4c6l8GbCdCTkL27TaMTmGTHxXXj53Ql29xAk3iRQ4G3KAZNw+zkMkj6jXVZlhibcYlikkLJd/ouBcc4j1ub50SYD2P1234//0V0uRg2ohHFE8ouZD0hHyBTaH8MDhBo7HrIAF5OR1miQmXfEQnMDP8flQbyPxmxa3+7+mGBx/58IFYCBIwreytMn3BKjCPx1GSf+vYXxff0GSnct9LYxy+Ol986uZufobGczLw2+V+sZx51Ye0J4EAWdFyFcdbS6FpQQAfRH1zXGmBBNVXZHAhrD/egcVQHqpsXGairNdqMaDx3nX702HI7sRkKPNP+63zXbRraP1Rb+XkohDm6hL4wD0Q/1Oo/9NgG2kHwk6tXkJlRWQY0DL2fyZm7jma2iSws/bC1lIZkHewfGXxUhhHPQLv1iiecIeRQhAYWiClEF1hBdmn7GF0hMs00SU7ztRlw1J6xBYFkIjSO9FOAaThPZjzUEzlmagiOsOfZKJUwibiSnh0n525pnifqpg86HBtX2bakUws0CJrIbV47TGktcifrg6vLcH0U3FWh7LP3aWaLYow/3DIj9sczWxEhOzf4AP1M3ZS6CnZeZ8Xp/ILBBa3VO/WcWvIr7bBWv1Ypcx1d7EFT+8AHwWHcotRB/YoqrbNLOJ56hsFJGVjDPUvlGivNr1CPqddDXJBt/FHYngwiFeNbDyTPDMa31xL4KBAinl63DQJMt7Vp8jtO010lO6zZ0i3miBHCacOL+4Q1AI3JsC6aQGVYdkh8jwXq4zRPlMp2vx7QMnblSzLQd9UzjrWFznVGfRkXAI2fi3/jeo27D/lQ027hsSWinUn1qjh4rR/tplrxHe+uuga9wroIF2xvCUw==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "3 only", 
		"option_c": "2 and 3 only", 
		"option_d": "1 and 4 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070103", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/2CUuOvgNdFL1nJvVpy/GLDp+XU8kAKnbwb5ojfUTAKZIRhyZCAxKT2hGVYI8MElYYyxpsbcPVOyH2ReoaSYN9iwi6EIlb1dS2uRHFmkXHUi25ErY37ySnoHZoW1AEgn5Nx4sZ8NcTfzaCWqF2qiQWHz2jRX7VhA1HZosem7w6er5A2sI2dsCDP/ff1n+uT59sKcEhXvoV3I1Son60buCsvUNH0VBwfuKT9bkf5YCymNAsP7dij12ZshoEmUW0I+iNIqoxBIs1y2IGkszRwK8VvVTK4rFJFh4doXgOTebi2xHuk4Uc6NXkkd5hovzlq49pVCli/kvXv3ZztoBrpcs0=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0Eg3mxOn6OG7eF3FRom2GCJ96TH/CQLPQZ/n3xpkxLk/JmVN+smbUrKb15EBPmKBe+4vfZysNesZtx8KH0qTnxWNVOsVIn5My858ebrRFzT6lNNvPKPt8jm+XJlzMaQ21ATBElTjYnnlS6Ke+5iKpQJo4xlUThI5i4sY9fN6MmanT/FSog0aN2juTSbloEFqdicCb5AOIqId4tMOepjfJtP3q2qrv/uIFTAdG/4dzbxu4krsM6j4rEcmmbVJJ8PbCZFqtEyeuIk4Z/NjmxGB6isI6SGo8tB5VwpdeZ4Bd15XtvnIUOt5vByf6qkoA5pJuVhSXOP2w0X7hoFR/Z3MobcpptTswsxyVPE0+lW3cXCBQmpR4vtEXkURic2ZNnXrzwhKEk3HPeJbw7pLolqjxsrwj/KwzaUKPOViYf4NcY7LDMysyx+iVFOZYNoxiBTb1fdQ8+XnxL4LU3jcJkN0yNjfT/C/Zocz9OHe787b8ndFkAPNAMN7Xqc6vsVHXbSatYXWSdYv1V0jxWXnq0glg9wwgxTEV+mPMHZt6tSIL3ibgCUBhlTXlaW/hsL9U+IeAd4s4x7cbBkRbu6TWQQvE3Nenyf5B", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070104", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/2CUuOvgNdGIl2dhV5p+3jB46zjt0cHiuhX7I+MZGIGeI1qy8SAweG3wnBCJ8lW2ol8pIgaeOFDxTOqNMbUI/V9jnqPZ1bxaT39DX40lSPfjjxErYSy+imoFOY5klxyoo99rck/KN6Q1+ic7g2vjwiGzzuYRv1gFEecp9q7q0qP4IoxssWBqHLJ8eftiPna/tsPIjRc7M8/VV6yg6EP+SksQoi1ehcL4eHSY1joM2ilJg0Y7c7nlnZwhpUoSWwmtBpUjZBfbc5P2KTqlD0nf8BrGyr6rEIA05x5HxaUe6u9kHvw4UE6eH8lcZktvT8w4QaSK1tsiG6fWHMTHewW0rRHJbXfGJ6j5GFRGQ==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHgxRj+8oglXArhhay/NGXUQzFRom2GEqp6c37xRqLBetHw9ZlGIl2dhV5p+3jB46zjt0cHiuhL+4GcdTEQPol2iMeB3uf/hGNOMM1X2oFg4dodbvtLyTPtcNvMLr5nwHqPZ1b9ZjWxAWI0hDjTiXlF6Lez/DT7V9s5gBc31oN34818Ps7fyaCK+0S7hwrCzGmeS7h3AlGK+Y67/kCU4IMr9cufviHPtOP8nv/a/tlHIgdA/4V3Zla1lKkFuDoqXsuxewFO4qiQckHuKGiiNE4S4cLn12BgyYxpamw14BdDkIpYZYB6xdjl/CQ1LdQqHD6qrFZUxppoHweEe769w3uk6Vt/dGgiYcp/uSo8rgGPZBR/iSuVWGxYh8B/9tVZkw1xbnsAj2Llkn+CjiWbdJaj7Y/uiOnkqbZtsqwhaVKBO1jkWLsZa6fJIWZx3vrbDLRZc49iFSDqOMZu6DH4NNac3i8IkNslKnmn8iual9nwPSW4qtLuh9pyVLoSOcLM5sX3hFTCeGPgM3jTctLkUAvxQ3DhkwhqohYhiCgeqGbdG4xt4T5B3mm4TFZh0jPoaTy2n7BYqoGPcc4z3/r7nSERlvA4npXzlBkpVBD7nX5Rpo2cQ1lcjVXCXsUOwwFuH6QEEZLCslmekDbDSnIJP973E7yOwCBNyaPyj289vpIcVIiLbA3Tj542zRWzDfhqGSfqoZDwM/tVHmwp9/Jwiv6suMWvfb/kKmQpag6yXa9K5odXaQF+LQXhCxBHZfi9QpwKRO1K3GGKxUdBVD9KCkje/qscHTCir4TJbX7XbL9cARiidLoLF924R0mPMfS6zSLdFf+VhgewUFBlRjOaKbwUpRX1aZjgJRq9lmwk0M+lNFBYUM9XKC/2NHywq6fDAhV6cCIgaIVBOlPdTlApmy3XZ+lomqISdg0hAamgHF4ChVFAmX7XHFdWuUMQH6yjAFciOaxXNEhR+T+wUbcWUhiKhTsEzlWd0DD1aelKP01jemqXz0j1iIYmj/77loeCBtHxbbwPkoUKL74bV4rTGl8P1rPz5+jjGSw6B2M3K+rHWueRokD1Cdu0o83ehVNfwbsadkwuNz+KiprKsl5mBa3i0O6OQl0+C7dfhkI=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070105", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/2CUuOvgNdFL1nJqlR5+zbiprb15UdPhrsb6M6LYi0Td4huxJCB2PC3wHRSNtRQ2rx8ttNfT/VIzS+sNPDeM/t82i6JKUb8cj24FzBclTzXjn0WrY/73Si2Rtt3/Bth38dM5c18F9aT2KCS+kT4ogOR2WmFCLR3UVKWoMCsq0qS4JYwsI24ghObyPqt07jq8cwPYwZVrMZ+cV78g7EZ8Sk5XcStKBRE5OrUIV3jYDyrIk487crg13lohqYsTmwm4CNIvo1haslw3tjrunIkN8gqFDG1tUEA1IB9SxKbcbOswyjl8lB/dnU5d49uqHJ3bxsuK4PUUW10N7tD4Y+w6Q==", 
		"answer": "2+f4aZ/3kU2q+IssS1wP7+wKvWvmjKcIFO7Rf1Wq", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0Eg3mxOn6OG7eF3FRom2GCJ96Q3DrVbXDLsn72pJjMxyAg1h353LDsOXY9l4Oi6kb7ILfWC0ObIpTxumIxeD2ynZSc8dWn8Bm/YoWf/VMwCTtctvOLvoux2DAM031JxipBXN1mTCWrnlFrZGvySmIW5ojyBByl4lr+s0ufN6MmfrT6UO8xlK+0keffLVhUVuNvcu6q1CIoZY9uMiDpSGb9eb82vHd89EZcA1Rq7pxX1WIn61J3yU6WIiQbQFO4/CQaEetIWigKAIZuc/mxXF70sIASSk9519KjYBXdsV3lpHq/CY4Oo1JED2usUVMh7VvVhaYNK6s1Xj05UZzNXslYcpkqG09oBzcKVo+m32ZXi1WkcB/+90JkBZiaXpSmTbvhH/G0TXPeJbk+YX5lqjTpbVw+7Y0aUiOdUjQU80LbL3UInUyy+efTfQMc5tiEDDjOMZu3zz1M5+BzHkE3pk0J3Kn5z+Un8jnBWuOu5e5pdV6FbcBJNiFzc6ktU7TISryYXucc8XwGQH+D0/3xhptsgoriAAW+mvbCclW4W0EjT6kQUEknibya3mygv5Y75GLbZpx2vus/DQCkfd509v22hl8ThD7jnBVt5aMD11BjVXEG8xHyw9uDbYOAYKRqz3G2SaAGzwebtv3E63HyCVE1e70mmRvrNJS1CbUzczBMMFIdXhKkTT1", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1 and 2 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "2 and 3 only", 
		"option_d": "2 and 4 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070106", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/2CUuOvgNdDKF+ClBt/92XDsbHjt1Idiuha5Z2QMCkNcZxhiNGal9bywzF9PZQN2ql8pLYWfu1BjDyjcJT+J+d+2iLANFH/aSD9AHVnkSPCmTxXuob79ia3WN8zgCY3hI5qrfQyb57f/LqUqESrxgfC2H6CTa9wUVuf9cuw/0aSs4susI2euTfe4Oe5lf6T8dAMdwRTrcZvZlm+m60auBY2BYH0ShNP/eXeZUetNy2xIk4b8NnwwjR9w5AkWG10/REGo4VEa8Ny6pbYsho/KI1nFD2j40tGh4B0WleXdrKu1Sj39FQrcHcua55+/CwnpE+VJldxiHmZTzgO1saYpl9IUOi3Tsj4Qmy9+wc=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxCF7Ayv70LCvUBnEUsWuQEqJmdTHiWLTNLubwxoB/Z12azWl+9UrIkarz/EpPi61I7JyLY2ICbI4vydya2KT8yn5WPYZFicBa5ZceePUA/jiqNN3IYP8u2neQIgX/YXm5AWNxhiWWnnRXvMOy5me4XNslwRYmk5Vx9804fNWGmaGH+w26hxSHnGmeS7YkAkGLs8+r7gO1tMIxpo2LvifV8LTwlLjS4tsKcUhFt4NtZhuon61J6iU7Woi9e1Jf/uuQMhT5L2ihIk4Y68Tn03ApxJtpSmA68F9JkMNBY9R2xKTqgDwDK8x+ED6/rVAAk848fRaSeLy21Huk91AtcDotbJh+qG0hpB2RLVA+k2XcbSpDnYNqwt4tnQEjaWpSkTbcwD2KhGmOcpfw18K8kunj4L9q4LAzaVSTMFiYX4NccbvFZ1J8w/2eCeZvJ55zEjGmKdpu+DzqI4Sd3TxNxNElb3vm+i6KkczlPCW1tdLthtE2Nr4EOtDL7dj3nl3TaCzvIHHTVsrmUkj5QTzL3Btxv1gBySof/GOYPIF6tTkIjHPwQFcknCj3LGmyk7oc/o3Oe4si0Ofl3zdQmfph35f22hkvRAWriD9XuoWLD1VcjVfeH98Gxx0rHr0bEZKR8HTWhmLVTmxNbML5Ea2Uj2xM3+bhznN8qZkAUJ/CbBjVjp4j0Ae+Evh9FXXiq43FM8AbPmwpurF+2P+ktN77ZuelOGAnahSjSq9Y4ZALVAxIBQrJAClKbqzuBMdeaO4P/nzIjgYIRnFNRX/L4rgcEUS5vsvGdyraZqIZHArxI7IXFo77T0vDMPXp+zXbD62gm3S7TU03DjOOYbFN8R7gf8z9IlO3lnth69WlJllaUMMeL2fwfGqrpKCXDhQzZSkhaIheOk7BWFAhjCrGKepum6JAYxAoRLy0WV8Q1hBBmCveD0oFoEkcXamoUxMOPulMMxsXwiK7FeAWUlzLlD8LnRaLyif+LLpfOUxja2GRjUDliNJnjfqploGOStjjP7oekpkMaLReBJjaEEwS2vH9r/XoFCwuD2NzEvb0UNHFsVvzD836toOJnxxu27lIP0x7JHmPjIzc4i4tIKMPamheuH0KpdzXIhWi3I1NxhBnVhX/9E/gfWkEpBYzZ4Cra53IM4ugsF9ZViDCRLxRjLxs1S3wddbCJBk3BnE0khOVZNvQwjDDP7W7ybkaRR26w5zFVoN76Qhqxtm3118ApD01nH3sDzbzdqfk+15SLWl2T/SWFB1clBIjxnqm1lb6OM++j6Mbi/BIy/USoQD4tmF5iR6fTkTKI3Lk2raKv2OGqU4vzepqTyawT2FiwAtkQf4k535mADkuCax7qrO1OLnB3nKuIJj4zJ4C8FhQBDPo176qLexYa9S+ulEk9dE=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070107", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/2CUuOvgNdQK1DJiV5o92TSsOX8/lZPja1P/ouafmJSK1sv3N/JhLQnhGFAIcdIloV+99oQerRMzSmkYMHfJb5SwDzJZ3bxbzivBTBQkSLTmGgWoIKotSW0QNJ3zRonmJN55MZ8Pdmbmbqc60ahxgqD0n+CS7x0FEfZicD7ogO9opA5psSCv3LS+uL2lu7W454fag0Ss495d1KykOgI9i54U8S7fxtF9qTRdlX0YCelZwIS9tjmlnlo0oc7VGg45yNIvo1haslw3tjrunIkN8gqFDG1tUEA1IB9SxKbcbOswyjl8lB/dnU5d49uqHJ3Y5UFzSPB2mIg/Z4qtPc7Dg==", 
		"answer": "2+f4Z5//yFuwo8gtRcpR5VdHb9SvxQyG", 
		"explanation": "25q2ZIizwg3r44AtVxDmha+/PHiQAG0DsXqARp96TH/QQKbWa+D7x4MxdgbJo1RvsnfKr+X08kAKnbxIqYKWdWIBe594zdWHl7WiFDFVPIYXylAy9JsNffhMyTG+NNvdYPJv2meUMkH1Jw21AWJx1DDEjzxSrZC+5zOoFNw41Rs21o52rccoNNKNmbiS+lmrxgmEnG+ZTf1zHkaVsYLo+FafqMI5po2ZuTeb1eb6jvHQsNoOcQ1Aq8o/d1O514kH7CsqUty9a1JP9PfVc0ChYCmtI04J8c6j92BoxYMkXCkQ8QxDkJdqbPNn14zhsTc+K404T3OOq0EA9JV0XgWXNJm9w2329BU2Zjo/bY8tsCwnpgqPPBR2lX/cSClCkZJ/vtkX1RBreC9Xk2Tshn+ilCWGb9Pv5IP9ke304LBtso0oO1WIdX3eRIQfZPPBKWMyyeaNCLRPc55pVyP0ONRu8z+5IZSbyi1NiZktJnvr/SWX0t7kLGSottLyh9h5GboUM8PWqf+/tRz0YCvgM3zTQs7nXBrkD3T5wE5k9w4k2igV/HuYB48/+SwDmm2zSFRhgWugZXKimqtY44yJP4M+xvv43Dsei7g4jZT03wR8Vwi6mXpCp5fTD11ByRTFH8MDhA07ArESKJji5myCkHvVRWhNLJS2IKqVwj9B1e2xh3I9q5gLFZycIxremc1myg7xFvVwVm+tuon6Nu9VC3YpuqV+2OPhtt26bLOmNSU9ZhSzGeBLs4JQfAdpUSLJRS1BdreiQJgNAfRH1zXYggVKTnFORVXKu6QHUhev6snJem/MarAQHV7jZLIMHd3sDkLONvnpxyTBA63cpkjyH0UnXDuOKL8DpQP/f5+yKhyn02Fq787pJFQbSIoRKC79cyu4q6fDCQo1aCUrL8pGbUbMCx8i1DLMKOpizaoBZB0/SKmrChLKGFrGBEeOS2M5pcUeDfTY", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "2 only", 
		"option_c": "2 and 3 only", 
		"option_d": "1 and 3 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070108", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/2CUuOvgNdVIk+Mn09osnnA47b/4kcHwr9e+prfRREiPop9zZCK2OjzhHVEIMNWjpMy2JRNNbR03iioNNDeM/t82n3AJlf1Jy21C2Nx1CXei2gWqZG+tSa5R9U71QE3mp4478kuLtKRmZSduwT4ogOR2WmFW/1oGFHZvMDo/0uZ4JI3ucyf8SDe8/32lOuTzNBfK0hmt4M/dFKyk+gB+Tl4X8f0eh1H9KTZbxTpJTumNRpd/NnsxX1myL4nYWcc+wgGj4JYe4B80NjwtDdwPs9lAzb6sFBB05FxWhmCZ/25wm2k41otZ38ocdUve6QT297+v0I1BpVWO6Z9SA==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz3hfvtQQBK6FoVpzvW6f7i+bSuw8=", 
		"explanation": "25q2ZIizwg3r44AtVxDmhay/PHiQAG0DsXqARp96TH/QQKbWa+D7x4MxdgbJuVN+snLDsKDi40BPgK4b+oGKZCoUe5h7iOW69qT21nQBMMlInsB24YkabuBTjAmlcc2bIexrjmKPJETkYj39DX40gDnTyltErYKvtQW6R9M5gDE3hYJq+YR8K9+W2qDT4V74h0aK1XyZBbxoBV2NoMqtq0eZs4cqoY25uTeb9eL8iPnU9Z4fZwVCupR+d06ukugA9mosWc30TwBO8PCQQ1X+KSbjAwsO/Nn3ln16hoMrUnwgtE4WwodTZdJ204uknzc8LMR/Bn/6okpEh51oHxSXev2/1Xyk4UZ/dnUnYcpsr21481/cLFF5iG6ZX2xykYx498UK1Q1tPXtImTb3izGfhXezcq/t2JT9ke39pbd3svF9aXWSIFmYUogPYKHUNCdz2OzbA6lIc4tvGDHjfcEm/S25IYSRnzgPw9YsOmPi+DPZkMznK2C086bxi8ZzVL4SM5HI6MWu8EzLYC31Mj2SaM+0WAb5Qn30wE5xvxkxiC0Z/meYAYc/8Sgem2ykWgRQmiKgQXOrl6hZqqaLbIsjx7ms2z0C2PFgnpbn2BhwBw2ozXdMv4HfW1MPzBTAH98OwR03TLsHVIbd82OChjqQWGkOd473EuitzD9Az+KxmnN4uoNOVIKKbBrJj9E1xwO0Qf9sRm/ou8q5PPIRSmUi879wxv7t99mudvvkLXZqbBWuVvtc4NVQZgY7GgrTAiVdb7fuRJwKUtxB7nv5gwZcQnJMC06MqPJIeQG5r9bcfSrabPESAQqib7oAU8f2DlPHMLG5xzzIFP+OkEC3UEo2Dg6VJPAd6gvxaMzgIRS6nGZ3ucD3NxFPS4xXPyj/cCu4q6fDDxQjPzgqaIhCOkTaRQMtkDvRIv0niaITdQo5UuiTEVVWtwNMizfRTlxAo0kMS+WkUxMzIqwFI1QdyTKmBeAbWQ/PlC5Kh1jc1irpae1EI0UnNySSgUigkoYml/76wo+PStX0KK8a1YhDPLNWVJ/EHk8JiPak4OegEG42E3k3Y6uYHubUt13zB9u0gcbW1lVe2oIGClEIMTifjJLc/i4te/8PW3hP/WQQos6SaxXq2MhU1FpnQhXt8kTqVScusFF2fJz4Y9LSapKrsFRaBSHVQ6oDrPR9nTvtO9uRZxsxR2A0gxWJNsHLyTDDPKL/gKkcFgzix5jZUYNu4E1qjt2mg0RJrDM1nGznDnLJLqf64BdXKjx7SrrfH09SghJixzWy1UCoPIGux6kdhrVTmKYG8wr2oSRlzSJ8aj9169C42MANGwoNxc8=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070109", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/2CUuOvgNdVIlqFjE9y/XiGq6r8+1wYnOha+4vfdi0Rc45riNKQl/P+ynVSc/pKyMky0JIaPNJBxSS4eZT/Je58y32TLkr+JzW0AWM0lTPZnHkWu4a6tSu+Qt87gCk8xc44z8kuP9+e17vT6V+9xguN03XcW7VlAVGd9cq95UaP4L424YTNgjfS8ue5m+rWsM0DbRpG/4dxZxu+hacI/Go8RMaxey5FzernaV3uKGisIU4J8c6j13Zm0IdpTn014BpLh41CcYByxJ2ktTwzMN94EDCu/AaG+Tp4mj+JqpZcUd1l6Mgu", 
		"answer": "2+f4aZ/3kU2q+IssS1wP7+wKvWvmjKcIFO7Rf1Wq", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHgxRj+8oglXArhha+/NGXUQzZRom2GEqp6c37xRqLBetHw+oNwM1mEiFVvsiSc45H48hMpjqFC/IPfVCcTbI5829mG2aT+1zFAc8RFiYl8pJYQf/VUyTntfdqbBfl33nrADlGwbir9BnV4myaWmXlX6I++4yK3GJo21FUzmMd94c0qPcOW1qbT50v4hwSNyW/RHOgkHFGNsNy7q0GZrI0v9d6IsHLX8eL8lsTdw8oKdg1fuohrIw/m15sM8SwrEcmmbVJH/urXIVXjJGitJhwP9tyj0mFnw5FpaWEx7V9HkIYWZM9h253g/DApf9pjGzep41BIxoA8XRuZY/2x3ijloFYwe2k/ZIR5/Ck8swqfPF1xlFeScCJlnIUr/d8LhwFgaS9TiHf0hzKOjnGcPJLx7trAi9vkoa1m/6YpPQHRbxz8U4sQZKfJKGkywuaXAalLIN9mBSemO9o88Tz9YJSNny4E3t0zb0Pv8TPZk9/weWG/o4D8ncd/G7ETdsXN6N/3sU7CISXuM3CWYovjUQ3+D2jw1k5yvhYhiCMc53XLSIho9DRNina1CUhrnTTlLG+gmLoc64yKP50+2vnQ0wEEmeB9kp75wF1vHUSZjG1AuoWRXBxO31GWHd8C1worAqBMB57Q4miS1XLFRXkeP/r+BLHHwj5NmuX+nGx4u9AMTMyZJRffmZ4ywBalQf91WnCtoYi5PLwGA2or9rcxzuSzssmvfPyqbhuj0T55eVP3F6FtvvwTBW0=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "3 only", 
		"option_c": "2 and 3 only", 
		"option_d": "2 and 4 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070110", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/2CUuOvgNdVMk+dzV1p/XuGt631t2AOh6lJ6M67dTEGbJ8v29+E0vD+yXRSc8BFloxhpJMRPMdXxSm3ccbXIfBqjlKOdQywQyyzAWM0lSPTym9CqZey9me6Wt531RsxnoZ26sEyO5ej1/vaqGG3gxWRnHKCCLwkFkacsMDkq02Trs8out+CpCGb+fXtn+ra8dJLXgYG9sZLa178lqYH7Ss0EdimbRFC4e3EYEDkLybjLgBd/c7w02Z91cIgTikh5wpHjo9PIpIjm8u0/Ds+PMVvBg+0n0poyIM8UhaYbf231ijw6FB/dHgkc48trzk0tQqRLVpqiSudXikRnY5o8cILkAd3Ii34K+gOcztvSrA8Amwz3s+U", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxRH48oBihNe0hfegvQArXU1qVizr0A==", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk45ZgUxz90Om/MX7DFyIXsXCOErd8dTHQVa/DfOy+7ZJiIk6dwRt/53jDsOmw+1wKnLsXqY+RdGICcIV6ydzJx/byx3hROtJFjol96toWcrREyS6oZsDIesJg8mCzM0TkYjS4CmQ0xWuWqXNEuoa44WefQckjgBMgmYo4+cA5fOSe0amB6Q2cgxWHzm/RS7xqUUCLtNit5wOQr4w/9cmEoiba+vf8ibST9cgObEhHr8ZrbBuon61J2SYoQoi9ZlJ45u3Ee1H/LCmtI04p8cLwln16hoAsXmgh5xoGlotTItd62JykvzM+f85rByGj41BIwtR4SgSCNK25wnzt41k6Zjokc49//CE6rwjcLF1tjmqSTylCqI5Y6tENkAlmc3sAziygqzGIj3edeZD3q6Tpi+3j4Lhx9+MpJlXAJkjZQoQfJbLOIydnxOqTDKhbOpFgVxbuOMxu/Sv8YJWb0SoZ0dc0I26n+SWPm8PydSW7oNLthtE2A7YOMpHH5cSgoxzTaSahMnydYovkWBrkRn/01h0ltgoq3S8U1GzrHIhr8CAIkGrwGh4kuynjY26zk71Iqq6Bep0ik/z/nTNQgfF0k5Tg3Q40CgapgmhN/sSRQFICzlveG94O0gxiTKMIGpKc8GGZgniQT3kdcN3/Feiu12xByaP/gXU9uIILUIKyIirPi8ojxRK/Fb0tDyfEpoX2L+4QCXBszrp0iuyvud+6ebO0PmApZgq+Te5N+ppfKAt1UQ/YFiFddKvuX45eVflf23bLmwtRB3NMFkmM76AJU0T7+oTBYGnWZqJe0DwVHORfJ5bOr9mb1w9k/g==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070111", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRom2GEqdxYH7wXbPLYeP/xdd3Il2dmEl+4SmGn6uhvhMrmqZe+s6jfnBKPrxuzNmal9j5lzgBEcdOm4RzpKYRKL0A/DipfdneLuosxILbYnUPV2/uxWdGLrqqDQ==", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUqq+IssS1wji07jg50EhYK2o3/aFidB", 
		"explanation": "25GtZpTgi1nO4oslQV7z1/i/MW7ADHEYt3aMXKJ4MHfmVbPXfOjtiaN5IkXJjEl+snDJsaj18xMYh61VqZmWfiYBcoR4xpCa1urzhHBCMNNJj4xz8J8MPP1OjD6oZsDaKfAu3m+UM0DiaSqBCkd1kDjF0DxhqYey5me6Rt93xAcr1pVx+80uPtKbyuin4EihxgeQ2TufR6kkFVGJut2h/0qTroM09cuIsCbO5vHq1rjR5cpLdgBXpsZ8YlX8la1J8Sx4RcCxehcL+PeQYBThLzzjKAhd68rq2HJoyo5pXGcwtAtOh8NBY8R6lp7tsD4jf9pjATv6tEVUwoZAUTWXfry80TKkwRU9dHAqYYsttT51oE+bLVpqlnLcXyBehIll+ZAJmQVqcy9UlHf0wjaYwGOAbp7m78D+nKjkqLwj9qY3JlKJIVXXWM0TY/PTImN7x+yVGeZaIZBqVyOmMNo78i34KZjUzTgD19xgBmOn/TnZk43xPHW1oJvth9t4FbNAMNTE/d6ltWDJUSblKHCWaN+uGSmwX3n82gNguQxlwTJQ6SLLBIZv/CMK3m2lW0JlkSKgeHSggv5V+cKIcJw81vGs3ytQjPx9357l2w41SAr7gnkDsIGbXVNMxhTUB40V0QcgBboGVIHQ5miE1V/EC3UeP8D5FeiGgyhNyuzih3V0sJ4PWcyIKRjPn8wj9BmFCfhrUGHiuoO1fegdDyQv9aBjz+6199mvdOehIWAkewn3WP1cs8QRaQx/UVifHkcovkKaXK/7//uznpuBPQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "3 only", 
		"option_c": "2 and 3 only", 
		"option_d": "1 and 3 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070112", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV17h0fzrMGbVDXYC+T+/XPI9MEXrUefqeezwztpZKByLjEhy/DbOoraw80Ycm+hf7J6QYysXbctp2t+El/D/wTFmPMRN2qR3958NaLR8wm/kNODTJb5ox2CFNFGwYyyuEDBghjDAj3BF6JCz+jWvFN4+0wEzmIR9/ogAMoTWmZyb7Q2flAODyDu1Xa5wUXaWosLo/EKP4IEqsMyZtDab8OH82uzcsMgOZQ1GvpJ2bFX8kLoG7z4wEfS6PFsLxezVIWfsKCmxJk45/NjmxGAu1cI6XGcwtBZVwo1TdMVhlprosyU+f9llVTyuq0FSh4Z5WB6Zeq6E3lTq1102dnJraowtqCUw4Q6eJ0J72niITThUmYVl6sNZlBZmPWxPjmTlgSvUwmgRxaSyhhArQuN7ickTDXw=", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUuq+IssS1zFcTLAp79rBM9JHXd+bJt+", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk45ZgUxz90Om/IWPVQ0oGonGEH4t7MHPiR67MIq363IRlaxyIg1875n7D44Li8lIbz4xO+prfUi0UctFTxuyH5PD20HRMNshQ2tEopLkQbuZFzyntQNzeYNZ5z2CHam3/Jzu8F3l61DjFynBZq4Kv8CP7XdR34x07mIY47MY4fN6MmaOd51q2xgCNzjuYXK4kF0acpNut5VfcpJcroY2epT3J+ee5rvDW49tLZh1Bq8Zsd1SumrtJ+Tg9Ecu1fQFO9aTSeBT5KC3jMAcT/Yvh2nt+z4wuHW0h5wsGhJFZb4Bn3p2kmz0yNo1OECC/sVB8yadoXgOTebi2xCi2uhUcemg5YIl5/Bk9pE+aIVp7iX/cSDlCgMB7/8INnAdveHwAnWTlwiuDhSWDdZTr/4Xvkajxrr0j8aIpaUOFdV/ZRJ8VYLeAJX4y3uGeTbFVPZsnES30fcEm+Xn1L5iT2ioZkN0pPGPm+imcgfH7CnG7p5f0i9piVOxadvjL6sSlolnEdWPVKXjTQdnxWBywa2nrx05HuA8piDYR+yLbGox+4SgJ3nqlTARwnWf0ZHnhhLtR5ZSPc84+1bX62DUVjPVslpT5lBsuSAn7mXdG8oieQVgP+VzTXsEGxwJuA7JBApPW93mXgX/fRTwMc8L5Fq2DgzhA36Pmh295/4QBFY6CIw6bntYjiAO+Ee52XGutqZH4JLBVCXYp+6Z4xOrhs9+oYbO3OGo4YgmLV9xN8oFUZQd1BUuJX2RmbruhRI8bQvQP5n3P1zRJT35bBBro/rsNTxDtuYTbb2TaI7gPTh3tbaAREsDsQl6PN/SgxjeJBLOTgkn+S0tlQS6VJKJN9wL3c4P8N1/zmmZn9dThO19cBJcfOWfecW+wsaaRGQc0ei0raLlCewfURRRkgDbGZ9pmn64Cch0sT+iUHFEqmCVHmizXCFdXtQBeS62oAFAoOLtAI09R3iO0BaUSWRLelXoLnFPck26se7iUrNlUpJqaCpwpkVPaZXUi", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 2 only", 
		"option_c": "2 and 3 only", 
		"option_d": "1 and 3 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070113", 
		"question": "24e9b5Dh1RDk8MUMXRvh1rG/NmTeEGsVpm3DRqtxMHfsWKvNeeTwzs0xG1LYxBtS5jHV46P/4l0Lz6dV5ZffeSxDXYNmxtHJ6+qljTFoJ4ZNicBr4ZYTc+MAzTOpNMTUMvF73S68KRa5JxCpRHh1h3HXynhTuJeztSi9FNs1zwAm1tYooJpsfNGa3LzT4UP4pQ6L0nrRdLMwWBSwoY6n+UqbqYw5ocie8TTJ+/m5m7jF+dIHYw9X/49xI32ulqYK/RY2bcaDYBtI+aTfZxT5KC3jJgwS786jxWBo0ockWGcg519HkIYWa85w2Yr2uTEkYI9q9TBhbEayBciN5Uy1sJI4", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kU2q+IssS1zVbDoKf3IKA2NImUSncxP/", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk45ZgUxz90Om/OWTVEHFLn3G/XJBgcWXmWaLMeq2vk9dYKV+Gn0l+8WKGj6r15EBPhrsb74GKfiZDd4UvxdGHzqTnxWNVIIZLnMBm7J9fa/tSwDnhNN3VI/J7ymeOIAXTbzCzBTw0gDnTyklYoZe+8WeIQNsjxQZ+1oZ26YgOKcSM0Kmv5n6shxKH0X6fXP02SxS6uty67kCI4K43sN6e8TvItPW5g/3f/NEcaxta8oRtbEyy2+gH9yR1Use8bQFC5+GcIUPkLizuJQIS7sWj0nF5yZEgSSkd4F9PkcNGbdJ8w4uo/D81PsNjGzT6t0xB09R1S1eXeLG3x3uk91QrcGhrcYUtrCwmsk+IIEZxj2yUDCVF1IVq7dkVjDhtTntBiHPthzGfwDbVPLDs+ZL5hvywlLFmsqciOVWIdVPeFoETYKDTZ258isqTBKhdc5xmGWL0ONQt9HnsMNaA0HlfgIlgKXLi4BaXodn0LWC3tpztzoAsVJYONd7X+860pBzrbibyMj2cdMLzUAbxW3nrkwh3uBVl3CkVqGbdG4xt4T5NkXjwaFdtk2ugYnO11rhO5Y/Ofs4n2vng3DUV2P12373l1RM/QkZM/G+Uf2FlXUgCJjtKsl7E", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1 and 2 only", 
		"option_b": "2 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_d": "1 and 4 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070114", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRp2qNV7A0cWPmFLTKb/37zddzPhyIzUt64GLPoLD89kFPn7pe/4+WfCsNect4wd6Nl+D+1nRCJ89LlN8y2JRONbRizS+ufNXVYMJgnCfAFED5YSr9OH4n3XHmk25XpYq/9Cv7aNRjiVUal45q/cEyfgKPDxWIuteP+71RySLl4Yo=", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUuq+IssS1zFcTLAp79rBM9JHXd+bJt+", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk45ZgUxz90Om/MX7eBnFLn3G/XIF1YnLrVamYLsy+y5ZjJFSIgxty4TbH46bi8kAMiqZPpJ2XcTIGestr3d6Ml/D/xWUBOtUEiYhz9J8bPPZZjDztZMbeNv9nwmeOIAXnbje5RHR9hjTVnnVZpr+1xiKyUoB34VUhk45+rcEvfNbf1aed7wH4iAeQznSGCLlxH1HZocap/wOVs8IrvcydtDab9u25m7jD4tsdYwFetoh4I0y1maxJ/CMqVMugYR1FzergeEbsLSGnJgJHueqjxm17x48gWWg4tBtTjIYWa9Mz19jgqTw1f9liFCf6qlcA1Jx9TxKSNLGx222k4RUvbGgqaINpgCMdoAaOOF1wwCu9DCRQnZJ7995ZkRFteC9JjzbhwjuejmDPaJvi/8D1lqjjqLhz96dnJUiLMBzZFoUdbKHQLmlOxN2TCOZfPI11EiHyfcY6/S38LZOayypN0cslbyan9SSd0p+3PV4GorcZ+y5v37weqBXLRA==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "1 and 2 only", 
		"option_b": "2 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_d": "2 and 4 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070115", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0hjkt4clEg3zzPm/NGnfFnZRt3eGEpBxeXfwC+f+YLy3iaN5IkXJjEl+smXOrLfkt1IBi+hd6JrfdDcNe5gv9N7bnqTDzHRIIYZKm413pJcaffpTjHqge9vVZ75SwD3JZ3H4YiD9BWJx1DfZn3JS6Iq1tTOzUZoAxQYm1qZt/twuPduW2KbTzEirgxSWnEefHPQkJVycrI6k4kbcsIcqpciDtTvY4fj4iLjH/54fag0SqI9xZxu4nroM+z4xXsaIZi5FxuzZYlytLy7jMwYYucrh2WJshpE9XH0x+RpIlpAWY9J2lpvrriA1PNk1V7BXJ1EibY7sE6PI9WBFHYA=", 
		"answer": "2+T0KMOz0Bfut9ZgXRD+3L8T1sGM18o74gXtN0NaapQz", 
		"explanation": "24GwbYiz0Avvt5YoXQzmhfzxMSvWAnZRp2qNV7BIfkXrXbSCffn/3ZJ8IlKdzVJosnjJt+Xz+EEdiqtPqb2aeSRDep5hzcPJ1vbyhGVYI89Hm4x+/doTc/pHgH2jdcbJL+kijm+OIwXzdTyuB3V6gHzFgn1GrYf3tSi9QN85gAc3kIJq/804fMOQmamAqHH6lQeM2DuCTbx3LRbZutzo1wGPoYw89d+EtTXe58i72szb9cdLYxpX/4hwdxuvn6cb7Go5X8z0bhNfzersb2DlJSGxZwAc9M6j23FoyJFpGmQ7+xEBvo1iaslglovwvSY1MshkAXOzsARDyIZuWhSCNImw1Sjw5UcyNUZpVo9kuhF34QyTJVFt2m2OQyERlY4r38IYlw1gPXhPjnKgjzqKjmyBe9PfqZPrivr0nPsj/bFnFQOCOV3cU8EgJ/PBKWMyw/3bBLUcJoxiE2LyMpUq+Sr6Mp+W2nkZ2NxgPH/m5C/Zncu1LW2/oJe5isF4EaxMdsbN4Mi/8E7CcibsI3GWJt/8XEjzWm7u1goltRQkzCRQ52SYCcls4iIfmj6ZXQRgnSLzLHKugv5R74OAP7Jz3vrj0w5SpPpEka//0QR8Rha+zXlMp4qbD1VBjUDeG40wwRo6TJUUB4LD82GflHiQb3keetziPaazyyVbmvDlj3V4spUAQcyHP1nVhcpmyRSyFO94QWKtm4PwO7wRH2op6fJw2OjhucWvNee9PGwpbha7QK9Y4IZeawt6BQ7ZRTNGdLDuQpUbAddKwWGKthJbU21ICVPN9egsWBevuNCIWmLbevEdHBuibrwXFo77QUrCOv+l0XDPCaqSkQe3UQQkXDOZYbED4Uf0f5/3NgfzgW1j8M7rIRFSSsMBPTX6e36q5bOCGRIpPyMjaJ5PfwfCRAIokHKDNOxkhecBY1g5Sa3nKlEelwNO3xrXHV1XpAwXUeWDT0EzIulkJkkYzjaJH5wRaBTPn3oGh1Pc0if+Of9FNUAgbmiSnQz0lNJyl/qplYePDpTmJK8e0ZkKJ7hnSq7eFkhciefl++TtFGItRmRkbvvHTPDUs1u2Mc39pIPe0FJO2v4JJFp7KiuCjJHN9T4tP6RdbnxGuH9ZuMWSdg6vmZhL0EZpWVnl+0akVm4vslF3Z4HuacnVJZXlxFhaD2TPVq9G2P040SPqMpORZwg6FHc5mAmVNsbCxiDDL7n10+0ZBAqj25XOScp54whtxtny1EVOr3c1mHX2AzbOauKt6xFaIX1uTvSME1lYxhEj1jO/2RP8NYrqkK8HivBA1rFT9QTy4iJ5gUiJVwrdanfvnvCftG/IuQcg3qt6HGCxVH4t2gQhBOci/H0sNrff8aj+ouaPm/Hw8fBcFA==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1 and 2 only", 
		"option_b": "1, 2 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_d": "2 and 4 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070116", 
		"question": "24KwbZ+z0hbk5IwkVwz7y/q/MW7DBnAF422CW61ycX3vDpvMP6S++5Z4KVqIgVc7+2WGsaD34l8OnehS586bdTEGbJ98iOyHha235TFHNtEEk45x7J8MPPtGjC+sfdqbI/9gjm2PKkCwcDCpDHl61DnZn25F6Ieu5y61U5ojyAA8koJq/twzLtqMmZSduwT4tAeL0n2QRLEkGFrZscu77lGIs8Ixpo2MvSXa7ee5kv3S5sdLXgYG9sZLa06yk60b6z43Q8WnKBNZ9KTRIUbsMi3jKA0e7Nnx03pqw8IgUykw8QxDkJdFXs5P2LDrq3I9PsNzVTy841BIwtR9XRiAcf2rxGnw5Vg6e244JYt/uW08rwyTOkZ7mX/DDg7zpX0IhxnJsZpMKMLMPdk=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxRH48oBihNe0hfegvQArXU1qVizr0A==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbYP2kRj48sVzEhf8xvLtJ27TFyICt36XV65xfmXwaKnxeuzqzJp0KUjJ3AE7wHfPraPx+19Phrsb54GLMDAGeZ5jycLJ3uq3wHRSNtRQicBb8NocffoAzjjteN3cKOouwXzAdAmwZSypRHlg1DjFynNQvIa1tTG+RsN3yRs0hIJp+M0yKOuR6ryS/Ei1gwiWnCjLCI9lGFqftMKkq0qS4IY9psifpSGb/ee5lPfHsN8HdQlLrMZ3Zlqqjugg7Go7UMb0ahcL/e3XaUCtLzrjdDITyt/iwnFkw4w9HT1utCtOl41SZ9Jgwpf2sSFwPt9vVT21twRBh4Z9TRLWe767xXr25Vs8cDoia8ppuT4wsxuPaGB2n3LcTT5U1IFo6sUYmQh6PX5VlWLlwjyEjWiAct+j7pPsgOv5obVv6+MuJwGUPVmYRZgRaLbSZ2p9xP2THppSD5FIGS7/fcY6/S38LZOay3lfkNAzb3To5jickdm1GCW8toW5h9p1HLoTdt7Dqdm2uVKHYiLvYX6ca860TgHkR3X2kwZqogo2iCUF+mvWD8lr/TgDmnuiWlBrgCrzLHWv1rpZ+Yeca51x5/3lznITmfo4k5720F0oSES9gX5QusSZQ1NAyV3YGYFH0wEnD7xBF5ffsm+T1XLRRXsIbcHjEuqiNVRBvLadI/eyhpWY14a6", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070117", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDbOLr3dd1IlqFjE9y/XiGq6r8+1wYnPJn59/fRysNepgvy9GHl+flwXBVNoZAn5Bg4YkMdftO332vbZTZLPF5x2CHZ0TnZiD9CXFgkSPfi3BF6MP7tWf7FJoLzkdyoo99re49Nc6K1Oi37V2qgxWR1XSfCLR3UQXK5Y6u7kaI4IA9ucKa8SHe9bT1n+7W/J5LIkgS/8Y/X1Xv14wM/iY5RcG7ZlJD/ujcbkP+YCmxIk4c9dziz2cpx4AmS2x05xpHwo9TdMV/ltik/HJwf41WG2f6l0xF3tR9TRLWZK+x3Wn26VkmNXwkd4douG0xtArcPFs+jWqIST4RkZJk7dkWmzhtQWF3lH/jin+EhiWbdJaj6oLzk+2ws61i5qYqLE+UJhzZRIhcZrzSNWJx3rbZdhtuu0fvbODN+4oKnAKwfw==", 
		"answer": "2+T4Z5//yFtqIB4th9O9apMH4n7ZyUrT", 
		"explanation": "24KxZpXgkRrr+cUjQBvz0fi/MW7AEWcCsHaMXLA0cmijVqvNeeTwztdwMF2QzVZ65nPUqqT85G8Bu6BS+s6MZCMXe4ZqxsTJ3ve3x35TIcNHjsBW4ZwTfeBJwzPtfNvXLPF53S6BNUCwYzytFnVnhzjZhG8WoY374S++FP820gE60ZQ4/t0uOtac3OiQ+ki5kgOGnHmICKlsFBSLsMOn/UKQ4I0+9cGCviHetPn4jv3B+d8HcUQSrJN8axu9hOga+SQ8Ecm6bFJY+OjELRTvOWi0LgAZucrgwn1myMIeVGcwtBpUjZBfbc4z1Znq/D41PskqATz6t0xFh5JzTRqXYLS33ijr5hUrfX84YMppuT0npByPIVtwiVeScCJlnIUr2NEQjBFuPUtFjGTlkSyCj2vPdYCjutOsxe71pa0j8KYrJlbAJlnZFoEZc7bMG2lGwuCITbVIMotiGifoKZUn73n3L4LU3joOxcshO3KnwCKc0uv0MHyvvtLdi8RkEawTP97LpYu7v1/GdSblYXSdJu7zQBjkAzzxwE5suRwgzSVQ6SLUB54y+TQEkHnwS0V3mymsLH60gv5V/sKHbM4/3OGsjGFA2PJ9mo+31hgwSBP7nnpC8oiaWVlDjX3CXsQUhBonC7oIEp/S82OCmW+QT3kIb8vkQamJx2xE0+bizmN4s58ZFZ+LLVnXj8gjxFezGL1qUHHouof1ffEQHmE+6f4xxOK198CuZufkfTZ6LxyyXPtl/alfTAd9HQrJDCtBILChWpERVvMP02fP1wZEUH5QFhrN+aceWES5r8WIYm/IZr0gACrqaqBFANr5WkLCMP+9iDnaRrGTgQe9UFY3SzmJYZQI4wvxboX9KlO7nGRo9tb2clJaSsMVOWfxe3+x5aKBBBA/Py0rLMpFf0vaXFA3kT+DK/xxiKtMMBwoUa2pHVkYkVFAkX7GBl1MogwSUKasVFooJOlELl9RyjK6Ha8YVR/LinoJgViIxzr4ac5DNFBjenaWz0Lvj9J0muz9kIeCHtHmbakUko8GIbhcBJvUEE0Z2uDh7qHsFHo8ClF5Evb8VufI8E7kB4jksMrXxE5CxadIMFApKDyPyZvM9Xp5IOVYbmRPrzMcvsXBawmk5YZt3Vl7EEb49FXhTGIvolF6fdPlZcmcK5im5UJeAiGHc7xFlP1s1CPqddfeaBYwEHB1kBWVNsLYzjmCL6X32e0PCgqv0p2LQZ9orFx2jsu7zUgAril6nHXtBTqabOj5qAlVNnlqC7GNFU5UiRli4jul20GoOJ2llK8GgPBVwaUa4g37rjg2hlCaQEbYZmCqyv6b92fFqk4ux+psWialV3x6xwIjBOcq5nx8DG0yXKJ8/LfmbKPNiGS9Pdy338we8URRR6rZY/2stdzwIOPBKqPg2JSKIHyh+ZxlCPq4Np4XJWXYaClfoqz7b8TQZQzTLm6J3a2ZHmuBI2BX4XZ9nyKDVQxpP2myR9odHC8ShIpzY7gTts/3uVxgPGvDDrhn1+EGnRtOBV5dCJ1cWm1LR6IFT0n3Nc3qDjo=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "2 and 3 only", 
		"option_c": "1 and 3 only", 
		"option_d": "2 and 4 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070118", 
		"question": "2523f9H33lnu4oslQV70yu/ydWreByIcqniRU7dxMHjtFKPHfejs3YQuG1LYzX9u/HPV46Ti8hMcm6lP4I3fcSwHPo9giN6Gw6T6zXZTMtJB2sAypNpfPLR8wm/tUMHVJe0uz3yFZ1b4Zim4ADB2jXHCgnkWpYyt8Cq+Ws53zxNygY526dt8fJffmejTqHG21Uag3WmSQLxqAhSYsdip5UCZ4IA9s8KftHLM/fr9ibjV4tEGIgkSr5R6dVq1m6EH/2o8WNqxawZC/uqQIRStYGjjZzITrYvHw3ps1cIoT2x0+R5PjI9PIsZ8xJXhuHIyJo19FCe/sQRBxJdpUgKadamx32bY7mkxXXU8JYdssjR1rgncPFx72mqeQzpU1JN//8QcmAFtaXwAnWTlwjyEkneKf4e8qYMcVvXGNUUN6jkxXJMwR8g=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxRH48oBihNe0hfegvQArXU1qVizr0A==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbYP2kRj48sVzEh391+/6Nn+QEHYQt3qOV61gY03taKnxeuzqzJp0KUjJ3wE71mPIpraw9kEKz7tT6J6adGIBZ8t7wNXJ2uvhwXxEPdIElYYy85MReOcA+DWoNMPSLvou3meDLFawcin9F3F6kHHXhHgWq4Kp5y6+R5o+1FUzmoh26oR8OtiN1KGd7w28kwiHzzulQLgkAlyYpcvo5EXctIo99cmYvzeb8PHpn/bX454EbEhGt4M/Z1Kukqsd8SU2Ecm6bFJY4eHVZRTiJmi3Lwtd7sLt0khn9ZYoSWw58RFSwtAMIuJyxJvsvTwjf8xuAzK0oEEAxZF6UAWTNKqx3mz3oFMtendrZMp9rigjoAaQIVp52m+VXilSgIlk8JA7lBZgdW5OjzbhkDrLg3eKb5Dm5ZSxluDxsLxnsqcyJ0STdUjQV5lcZKHFZ2F92OSeCeZeKt9wHiziLpU69DjtYJSY0C5N2ddgLjf0/SSensi1PWyotpHth9t4VIsIM5HS4MWz8F7LbjTyYWmbY4vnWAb0D3rq3AMloxAgiDUZ+HGYB48/4SUI3nqlR0Ekhij3bW6lhf5I4ofOfIs/x/D+kXITmeFrlpXwlAk0QkS/mHFG8pCQD1FA21GWGMIV0wg8CIgPJ4LQ5mibkHjECyhXP+rjD62Ugy1a36P8j2hzs4lOU4OcIRzfytw/iAC4D/k5VGTuvYvsMf0BA2siuoZ5z622vsS/NeOtL245Lw+nGfxY/ZERaQx/UQjcFzZGZavuX4leQOxA3HKG1wNNV3BaDE7F9a9IVBDqo8qIb3jbYqJcGRbncbZFB8b9DlDGO/Xp2yDMA7vckUK9TUEkXT+OYYQF7BSweY38ZBChlmlw/IHhJ19eV8MYOmfldXmwqraQSxUyfjwgO8pGdEOVWBk+kS3/KcVpoqkMaVg+VamzHF0TmAUPzn7bHRhMvk8RTbeoQ0dnDrxLJUhRzCWwUa4QSFzZkjseh1Xcwyzoaf5EcUQqfHaSm0mgr5pjhr/okIvBCdvsPqka3JkPMfZWS4zfEVxQ2vL3r/XoFCwuD2NzbvrEUfXC8Fv+B4jno83ehUxK26oBNVM+NnmKm5DM/j4vbvzhRZZErtEz4gYcqFzoUQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070119", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt5YvXxuyxvX+J2rTF2cDqmyXW6BnMH7lFKvNa/7tlqt/dhygmRty4Tbfpqn8+ERPjqZfqZiaYjtDeI593NmF0qS3hDEBc4YEpo4gpLMLPP1TjDCsfdrXOb5owXuOIwX5aXmpDHU0pzDei25X6Ke+5iKpQJp3gFVy1sc40cZvfPuQ3LuAqESrxg+PzH6DRbhlE1ic9dqnq1SdtIcq9Y3N8XKbtLTFlKyTxNYOIiBFvoh4LnOz16oI6yM2EcC1e1JKsejRc1PoYCymNwEO8N+j2XIpyo0sTnoI+iNIqoxBIs1y2IGkszRwK8VvVTK4rFJFh4doXgOTebi2xHuk4Uc6NXkkd5hovzlq45VzwmR8EeaJDS1q6S+mMRk=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz3hfvtQQBK6FoVpzvW6f7i+bSuw8=", 
		"explanation": "25q2ZIizwg3r44AtVxDmhay/PHiQAG0DsXqARvlIflj3FK7RLvT7xZt+MByIg1875HPUuuX28kEbhqRe1YCjfhYLe8tg3NiMxaTk0HBVNstBlJRhpJsNebRJwj6iZsbeI+o08mCpMwX5dHmwBXl6mCiWjHNDpof7/Cn7QNIygCYznoZq7IgYOcSay7yv5nmwjxXCz2+QXLhpFFqN9ce7q0qSo40qp8iOpXL3+/Hqibja454KYRxHvopzehu6mL0H/GoxX4iiaQBC/vHDIUTsMjywZwEbud/r0zR+yZAlWSV0/RFFjpZSa850lorhuzs/Md4qHD36gExJyZUwHzKDZrKo1SSk4Vs7NVQkd55l/Aw4pB2VK1Uy2mmJWGxYgMBi7ZAXmhAjcG5Jknr5wjmElWuLPJrtq5T0gKjDobFi4KJnDUSTME7MaoMga5/PInRhiuCITa9RI5p1GifnP9krvC32YIGVyzwf7NcUJ370tDmNk9nwNGC0p9LwnZR/GrwPJMPA6t/3nFPCcjChKG7TZ8jgTAn8Q2W4whtsox1l2C4C53fLSIhx8W0MknK/XlckhSb0aW7hgrEc+oOdbM4l2+fjyDUY2P1so5XL2ik0QkSTmn5Ntcm3QBxNzEffEI0PxRpuDfQNFYTW9y2SkGbfWHUZP8HwQaSIxj9b5u3Fhmhu/4MaVJiLIRzVnp4v21eyDu9rUGT56LLxOLw9HWUi/f9Zxa3pjs+3efyzbFcjeR+lEK9b8oZYZkJyH0v+DS1BYfinRd0VT+9Y3DXMmBUITmtaRV/U760GTg28r4TMa3rRcLgIHV7tZfMJHMvrXQWTBZGPp46rHHf/rTptn8Tf", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070120", 
		"question": "2523f9Hywxyq4IQkWw2yzPO/MW7DBnAFsD+FXbF5dXW8aKmTLtr/zZ5iZ12biBt6/mHHuraw8VoDg61fqZmWZCpDaYp7zcLJl6S3hDEBc/pKyMBF5Z4Wb7RB3jjtcNHeMPtgy2rAJVywcTyvEHl3lT2WiXNEuoKo/Ci1FN4i0hw8kcd74ccpONWKy7uH+w34xkbCnDvRdLM3UWCRsNfo6lGZ4IYqrI2LviCb+fvqjrjc9p4fag0Sq49yZhv81+hJuGp4bcbgKCVK9e3DIVX/JWilKBwQ/M+jxmZgy4M7VGUttBtTh8NCbYBy2JHpvT5wPs5+HCWzt01F1KhyYxm+e6r43Wnq+RUwczo/bY8tvS86twrcO0B/jm6RSSJFh8Bq7NVZlgtxb2pDiCmiMR5g5RsqxZBPebVToK2xJg==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0Eg3mxOn6OG7eF3FRom2GCJ96R3DnXbSCb//7iZN0IkyMg15/snTf47P15UcGjKlXqY2QYjACbYJgxpCNwvb+ynYBMMpLj4Rw8YgMaOd8wgmlfcebM+pv2muNIkvkJzCuRHN7hiPTiWgWn4K//DT7VcgygBo0goJ2rc4zLtqa3eic+g28gwOS2XWUTP1mCBSNvcvo7lGTs4susI2MsibS+/q5lf6T9t8YdkVUs4loalW7178I7C8qEcyhehtF9qTYZFX7OWixJgcTucTxlndlyZctX3wm5wtVvo1qbPR704GkvSA1f8l4DHO8rFYAyptvS1eZcv2s2G2k9FwycEYlUYJkr20mtQ6ILVl7lH/cRT8Rl4957NUagURUfGtJjzbhkDrLlHyfdZDi54zlxeziufll/bFnPUmFdVHZXIIObKfZZ2h0iv2TCOZFNp51W2LnM9Fu6DH8Odab0TUUkNEhOXKn4yuNl9+1P2m1pJv3iZRyAa0JONaF+c6luVPDcmPuJz2bY8riQEjiTnX21Q9puyQr9C8k4GeYAYd8+j8fm32kCVdwkzPlYXmvgq0c65CLJbI/5PTo1CFQmeZ935r7wxwlVES9hHNPt4DfWFVbxRTBH9kC1jUgOLwIB9bC5myCkHvVRWhNdt22CKaEzD5a3+DlzkBu/50LW5iHIxfejpJm3xa1CO45VHXo6JLgLfUWC2gg4/J12PThscWpNf6rP3FqYBz3Tedcs4xUaRBHHzfTMiVLaavuV48bAeZAwHjPk0dYVXZEBEjF97FIWRGv6tDHLmvQarwdAl7jYKcMBcfsR0LcCf+dwDnaRqyIlFO7UkErWnqUMvAE6wT/aJ73JwfzpGlg8NKlM0NeBJMFNSryZmK1vOOFBBQ3eihlKYRDOlTdSgAhkH7BPrlzhaJAdQoiUqGxHBAXlQVGkDCSAV4Fp00KWrfhAEMmOL1MI04dzCW5COAbSQ7DiD1KnlOOyy3oOrpENwkrfmWFlgzymptomf7ljs61AtH7bbwJ180NJ6IbVIjfEloOk//9r+fvA2E8Ai11N7jJUOvcsUO2A8vgq9XT0VVO2vwhZoIBPpxMNCHplGp3Tk84", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070121", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/PXbTWI8SkidcxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDUoJ83J2g/r7LylABAcND2o9gpIkLc/pZjDmoZ9HJNLIuny6nNUr/cTyuRHF6kHHehXBap5SotSapUZo01QFyn4k4/8c/N5eMzLqV6U69lTqM/jurTahjFFrV9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riBsP9LcQ1T/4l5I0i9maw19gl4dNqzKB1ZsffRb1D0YCymNAsP7YejhTRKyY85Unox8F9JhMNXbMdm2pn2/CI1Pc9mECD6okpEh5NuXgGTeK6E3kyk0lo8fjo7YI5orzk0rRzQaBQ+2ivcDGwF1LRq/Nwc2AhqdmoAkHfuhn+GgXacQJ3f5ajzkqj9obd6sqwhaVWIMBzZVIQKYPPQJm5g2amaH6McMJB1BSflKYps/ruerkhIIEmPRqaNW49A2g==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz3hfvtQQBK6FoVpzvW6f7i+bSuw8=", 
		"explanation": "24e9b9H8w1n544ouS172wO76J3+KQ0NRsXqEEqpnMHCjUKLRa//qiYN5JkjJhEg78XnLs6rj8ldPgK4b6ICYZS4CbMt/zdKL2+HkhHBPN4ZDiIFk4ZYMPN1UjDS+NNLUMvNryi6CPgXkbzz9E3V1gDnTmHVYr8O6+yP7Ucg40xw9mMd364guM9SUypSd0kitgQPChjuwCKdhBFOcu46h+AOd4JYhpcjNvjSb8PHqn+rHsNIKbAxUsJRyI0+0lrxJ8Tl4UsC1ehNI5eHCaE7oJGihPk4a68TswHF6hoMnWSk8+xNKjZRFItR714ykvSA1f85/AXOzrVBPh4B0WleEe76zkHvx8lM+dn9rUYJopW00swrcLltsl26YDC5I1JRj+5AOnApnPW1Mk2HpjDjLk2SBeNPi5YS8gf3jtPli9aIuJ1KUdUjQU80OarDLZ3Rn2O+aDqNgPbp1EGLpL5U9/Tf9OdaQ2ioIws16b1bptC+LlY38KiW785b8ndFkAP8UPtDRqcKk8F/IbDPuMniXJsTyGRvxQXi4+holvgtlzi4C5WfcSItmtTkFmz6nQEpg0iXsY2uomLkc+YOAe841xvvpzg4eqvt7lNvn0Rk5VBC6gWwZ8raQTFcP3VHSG94TxQU9TLUTEdbY4WKalGLVTzwfcM39Qa6I0SFJzur+gHI9q5gPQcyPPhybmcs22BijFfh9FWX06Ie5M/0HGGs7urBw2ejhg8K+bLOlPmBqaRWlVOpds5dIKBZzFEvKACVbaL28X5MZAeFB1jXPhQhbTnBHRVXKu7oHXg+56ABfrNgx2TvaomzL41KOfaI=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070122", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/PXbTWI8SkidcxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4Zok5NmqbM2JshO7X2PddDXIfBq3SLAZwWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4vIgUNdCXma2F6V23lAeW1XSfCK9lBVHZtMCsq1eZrZI9p8yZpCDe57T4jP3B8dkCbA8S59GvRWeytegk/SkwUMa9ex8L/uKQQEbkJGiGNQEO8MTtmjQ7hqogUWUntBpUjYdTZoBxz9j2vTs+LNllBz6p401O05s8WAKaeLS9w1TqwxUXdHcqYYstsz91swCfI00+nm6PST5F2MArvpBZ1UQwPVxUmXPwzyyChGCLMNPs7ZT5i6j0sqAj5KIrJUSZJmDWcs0rZLfJNCsyiqnbTeYcc98nV2KmfZVuvHm5YNbUn3lNkJlgbzentGrZ0pm1HH2qvIH8ipRkG7wLJZHR4cSlv0nAaS/4YW6eacTgUQ30D37hkxptslgywS8U1GzkBqFw4m0An3CpCUti0jPoaTyglLdK78KefocjwLXtzzdQkfp7kInl0R4oGEbF5tFsrYGFIEBvmzMv9EPN", 
		"answer": "25S0ZNH811n+/4BgUxz90/i9nRQLEAOvQrYd8yxhqAOnaw==", 
		"explanation": "25e5bJ3y3x35rcUCUxr+xPP7JivREWdRonHDU7FxcTHsUufHfOL6zJMxL1WFgUg783jC47fx4VoBirsb3YaaaWICbI4vzt+b2uHzhHNYc9JMn8Bl4ZsLdPFSxTOqNNXVJL5r3GGTLkr+Jza7RGN7kiWWmHNVo5D3tTSuV9J3wQZym5J8/twzMtLf2KaXqF6whwqH4HW8Tb5sEFqQpsPo5EXcgZAxsY2ooz3I/fv3wLjn+NtLbw1Rt4dxakix16cPuCsqWMz0bQBE4u3fbxTkM2i3Lwtd6dns1XF61cIrRCkj/BZFisNEbcN4xdjlsjZwLMJjGXO7sUEAwoZzWxKSNLS2kGz2+RU+Z38qdspEqG08sk+fKUFtn2/cTjURgIhuvscQmwAvPXhBiHPyzn+KjmHPdZDm147UhOXxpLgj/bFnO06DPkWYUogPYKHUfSdTiuGaAKdYMt9uBGLnfdEr7zzrNNaA1zgZkNAzb3To+TqWgcjxeWq885D4nNE2BrADPZHs/Yu+oxzBbjHsJHnTZNK0TQD1D2v90hptsgosxiZQ6WzcSIxt+j4EkXDwRkIkgCjjZ2+dmIld7ovUP69xxPTo1HIZi7R535/lzV0uThK+n31GtsS2WxxG3hTQEd8KwQ1uDq1BAJ7UsmuammGQRHpNaM/iBLrHxzla0+32zmA9uZwBWojMBtLoY41uOJHC6J7PyXB+Vg==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "All of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070123", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/PXbTWI8SkidcxZxzJzRs7sjaGj6zj4x4mpvJn56/fVCcFcop7wd+Hm6S3lT8BAclHkZMy95IebPFEjD+0NMPSLvouz2ySJlb5aDf9FnVnkTzUhnVYr8OZ5yahXdZ3zgAmhbt2z4gKOdmL0K6S61mrykbQkjumTbx2GFqe9c+/6lrcr4R4p8KOunLI4eb/m/vW454Je0hFtoh7I1i9hboQ8SQ/Edu1ZhYL4eXCdV3uLC2wGwA+uerhxHV6z40nESl0tEwIwq9fZNR62J+kvTw0f89mGiSzrUMAxoN9RleZcv2032f35RUydG4ud4NssD51px2TJRRqkm7cSz5egY5vwt491T1ib2tBknHzzn/L1CvPL9Px5IP3lqjjpali4KIzLEXAN0WYVYIOd7rEKHVhiu2OCOZIPN9wHizifdQs7jjqKZma4zcx3vEvODfq9SSA0sLzeXGyttL4jN1gEf8QN9jX+ou2olmHaC3iLm+BY8jgBkpl0voniQHp7nKHQ2P3TG8v", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "25G9bp3yxRDl+d9gdhv0yfzrPGTeQ2sC42uLV+NkYn7gUbTRLuL4iYB4KVjJj1d05X/IpOXx4FIWz6RU5p2aMC8Cao59wdGFxKTx1n5Mc9JMn8B19pUKcvAA5SntfcebMvt93mGONEzyazz9An9m1CXejzxQp5G29DOyW9R3zxNykoJ+4ckoNdiRmaCc5EG3kRXOnGyZQb5sUVWLsI6s7lOOpZErvMKDonLS+rTtkv2T98wEdwZW/5J3Yk/8lroMuCk5RNuxbFJJ6KTEaVGtMi2uKBgc9Yvs0DR6x4wtHWg68F9Cl5BCXs5P2K7hsiY5OcxpASDg43JFyYB1WRaVYK740XrhoEcwdnE4JZ5lvTl1qQ6KLRR8n26SDD9ZlZBu+pAbjER0dGFE3HfikD6YiWqBPKfr7pm8hPr14K164qokKE2MLBzLW4ITcbuAJml2ivmUAa9PO5pjVy3ofcEm+XnqKZKRny0F0c1gKXbk8TnZhsXweXKzvZa1ztV4EP8UPtTcqcSxpFnJISvgN3jTZ4vkUBzkSni43BwlvxcrzTgT52/aDY0/9D0dm3+iSEpnlxvuUHKAlKxd+YuBcdRx8vf+3CEZl/o4loi3wBU5BxSpgnxGoZffQFoP2l3YGoAFyAY5AvQSFZjVsn2Xh2LZSHAIbI7hBKmVyiJPmuLmj3g9rZ8NXsydOQvdi90j21eYFb1wRif/rZXpMvIGA2Yg//J3xf/ho8K+NfWrPmgrexO4V69W9dVcaQxiUQ/UAyJKcr2gQt0KWPBKwTXFkUdMQmxMF06M96kGWQKluMnbIirXbbIQGxrrbbRFBcv2Wk7JNPK923yJH76OkUawWFdpDjuTJfAe5An0OojnKhagr2ZY9/jkIFVaSoQEZmfKdXm9pK2EGEY7bSllO55Vf0bYRxkqkTqDNfZkhucGfwogQLyuFl4F1gVHniqSD0pA8F8WXrWoRBMlM+lSKVUVjTa3A6EMVRPExg4Ci0/cwzDpae5SIUAgemiflgzll51omP79h4rBC9rmba8S1ooGZbpST5+aX1oSnrPw5+T5UWM/Emh5bvDJSOeRsQ/lCsnmsoPZ11lY3f4JOFt7JHmMjJHN/D8tPKlAf3UKsn1ZuMLXIgKlzoZO3F5sEEbl8USmWx58S78HCa7Jp8xzinxsIw==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070124", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/PXbTWI8SkidcxZxzJzRs7sjaG4+WwtxNPz+gbxYeMZG8qV9FTxvHJ+uHkxWINc4YE2sAypNpfPLQAjH3tNIWbD/BnwWDNN0D1azCzAzBkhj7Vj29F6Iy9tSq+V9I2zhwxl4s4+s09KN+ay6Gd73G2pEanxH2eRLRlBV2Wu4LoqwPc4MJ49Z/Nlz7a4Li5jvnR/NtGbgFZusZzYlW416UI6zkEX+v0SQZf4+3EaFvjbGjjZ05duYujljQphtFpbWw29hNDkcNBbdJ9lpzrqzxwKMVvG3Ouq0FZh5dzUxufcLj4x2Hw6BU6dHkjJYV5tCgnnQG4aGZxmWDcXClVkZN//9wK2UQ3PV1Pn32gkjaHjGSdb9Pm+Y/4gOywrrxi4OMzIUSJJxzaV54ZdvPCPidlw+efMahgPbdoAGLrPNs3vDb/YIKc2nkM0tA2Kjf39SOLgY30K2D6sJ3rnNF1AOBCT7w857TAia6OZkjfwsGD0Q==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "25i9e5Dgi1nLt4glQR+yzO6/NCvWD2MF7muMQrNxdDHrXavOLuLsiZp+MlKdjFJ1smHPt62w5EcKirgb+oebdTFDV58vwcPJ0evlyXRFc8Rd2pR64doPbvtDyS6+NNvdYPt2yGGMLkTkbjazSDBjnDjVgjxfu8O6tTOiRN93zxNym4J75ckyNdSe1eiE7UysjgOQ1XWWCKlsEEDZts+9+EaP4JYwsI2CpCbe5rT1m+HW4s1LbQ4SrYl8aBuomOgP9CszVIi7bhR3/9jeREzrLySqJhoU9sW5llFxwI0lVGgg/RBIwopFIsEzxorrvzcjLI1lE3O3pkdIxpp1XBaaNKq90Xzs5Uc2e31rcYJsqG02oBqPLUc+jmOZDCNEgIV5vtwYjAFxbi9PmjbyjTyAwHGAPJXv6ov5xef2pvlK5uMuOgGDNEnLU4lcZ6qAM293iuyDHadSIJZoGWLnM9Fu/zb3NISV3C0E39dgIHGn4CKc0t/6Om76t4f8zsB5VLwIN9/C7Nj3uVKHdSbsMXiBZ9/hSw3MQUD28hpxpRExwS4esiL5HJ1t/DkEkXDwQFckk2fwfnOik61Pqo2IP4M00P3t0zsTmfg4iJ72wBU5VQ21ij9XuoWLD19O2EfTDY0XwQssALESVILesnqTlGSQT3MacY7hCa2JgzhA3/qxjW5xs5kKUMyZJQ3Tytsnyx/xDulxUHWtgZK5NO9VCWU56bd1iu+4996zcLOpI3MvYh+5Ta9W9dVGaRZ+A0edEi1BZPTuWY9eSONK7nv2mTVHRHQJFV/I/rscXAi58IT6YWnVI6EZChvxd7IJAI75XEKPJ/6qw3DZD7OQlFWtH1AtTy7dIKIIpQLidYj3IFO9lml2udXtN1hJBIEWLyLgNF+xoLrDChQ/PyoqOodCfgfXUlAwnDuDN+tojqITY1giR+iwHFECnhRdljDVTllLtAwbTaq+SVwpaMnNT/UEaTT7mpR385vOd6Q=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070125", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "25G9bp3yxRDl+cUoXRL+yursdW3fEW8Qt3aMXOM5MEbqWqPRLuHx3pJjLlKOzU9z9zbBsarl+VdDz4VU+prfYDAGaIpjzd6dl+DiynRSc89K2oR3958NaOcAwzvtQMHJK/t92m+OZwiwRTivB3h1mn2WpnNTu5D78SKoV8g+0AE7mYk4oIgFOduT1r/Trg2+lA+D3neUCLBlBVGLvM+kpwO4pZE9p9nNpjPP8ea5m/vH+dEFIkUSmYp+cFPxkaQG9y4rE8tQhMhNtRyhF3cyal+AQi0=", 
		"explanation": "25G9bp3yxRDl+cUoXRL+yursdW3fEW9RtHeGXONjeX/nFKLQYen72td9KFOaiBto52TAoqb1t14Om61J4I+TPGIAbI5u3NmH0KTzwWFTNtVXk49899oWcrRUxDjteNXVJO1tz36FZ3H4Yiq4RHh7mD3ZnW8WqZG+tTSzVcoyxFUwj8dv5MY4cdWT1r+dqF25lBKL33eUW/EkFkaYsdup50+F4I43osifuDzctODxn7jU4tEebAwSs4NpZleAmZQH2isqUsC1ZlJP5OrVchTsMi3jJBwY6sjm2GAk1YooTWwwtAxHjIcWZtV904ukvz09MsJkGSr6pUtVyZA8VhnWQKiq22339FQxNX4udo9/qD51lQeZMRNsnyufRC1DlYN/+8IQjwFnPW1Z3HegkSuOhXXPa5rt75f9l+yws7Vs4qZnKE+EdV2YW4IOYPPHImlmxuzbAaNZJJ51E2L1Mdo++XW5JpmG0jAD15kkOnKn4CXZh8P8PWyotpHth9t4FbNAIdjL7fe5jFLrbibyMj2adYv1GRH1Q3D3xEIlsRErzWwX+mPRBox7uW0MkHrwTEV3myv5LH+zg7Ne5oeKP5001/zh2DwEmeZh35b2wBguTgW3zVZX9ZffX05GwFXEF8EehAohAaQOB5PVsmKQ1WXZR2hAbMfsBKzH0y1azurygmRu89AKUJyBPxDPj9pmyg7xFvR3USutqYj9ffUGSm8i9aV/iuuupYqyYeDkKmA4exO7UPtAs5RfbEJuAg6dDCoPYb+8X54LTfRawHD2mTtGbnEJAV/f/rocTkjqvcXca3ieYrIIBxHsI7oWU8H+WkLBdfKhySLIBauZh06kWkBlTCPdJ7wM9g+wfID9Kxeg01tx/cXgPB0bTY0DOSngcSurpKqNDQc2c2wmKZ9Uf1SVWRE0nTqDNexpgqEGPFguU62mDVkYkVFfkCnXHF5QvAwfUaHtUFwzL6dRKVodwS71FaUMSA7fhS4DmFPc0Tf+Lv9YcUYlO3OSm0ny24ZunuupgY+PSsbnPrUawohDPL5eBJ7TDF4OjrPo7u/kAm84Fmg13Evb6R8yiqcyNxr/QCNgGQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Deflation hollows formation, Winds lowering the ground", 
		"option_b": "Most prevalent dunes in deserts of Turkestan, Barchan", 
		"option_c": "Loess description, Yellow & friable material", 
		"option_d": "Desert water action, Flash-floods", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070126", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "25G9eIP2wgrj+ItgWxCy4PrmJX+QAWcdrGjDQaZ1MH3mQqLOLqC+75Z4PkmEzX9+4mTDsLb5+F1Dz4xO54vfdi0Rc45riNSc0qTjyzFOMdVQm4N+4doTdf9FjC+id9/IYLMu7G+SJE3xaXX9IHVnkSPCynpTqZeu5yL7Q9MjyFUz1op97MY1MtDfnruE51+8wUbPnEiUQbsoUXGBocum+EqKpcI0usieonLf8eT2ifHHsNIEYQlGtolxIxb8v78I9i11ecf0ahNY+OqSZIQ+SfKuKoIMbqPmTXZalQ==", 
		"explanation": "25O5YYjm3FnO8pUyVw3hzPLxdWLDQ2NRrXCXU6F4dTHkUajFfOzuwZ5yZ1qMjE9u4HOGqquw0lQWn7wXqZ2WZDcCao5riNKM2+vghGJEMoZIn5Z36No2aLNTjDyjNNXVI/drwHrAJUTjbjf9An9mmTTSyn5P6IS++iu0U9M0wRlyhpV37s0vL9KMleiS5kn4jxKRnH2UWqltHVHZpsGh51DcqIMusI2epCLL++btn/yT+MsGYwYSrINrd1e5mq0H7Dl4V8emKAZD/vHDYFrpM2isIU4E/MrxxUhn+owLXHs3/B5IwodDbMVglpn2uXIzLch5Fja0twlTz5VsWhPWZ7y21Cjg9Vs6ZjooaodgsyM5uE+aJ0Zzn2/cRSIRkIV4+8INhkRXdWpJjjbkiyyfiWuMaJr17sDvjengpflq4eMkO0SBIVncFo8FJabOLmN72OyYGa9TPZ5rVzXvM9E9vDz3I5mB0S0IwtAuKDfo9jmNk875PHb6v5vyi5RkG7wLJZ2F+86kpVDTaC3mYXSdJsq0Shz1Smy4xAdrsw8k2iVQ+27XGIw/9CMJ3n/wREt2l2fnaXK1mrsc5oeLaI8j17X/0T0Anch2o5XE0RQ6BwCug3pQ8oWNShxLyEfTDNlHwgwvGKETEYWR/GybkHKQSnoZety2FaCCgw1a2+H4jSFqsIIKFYqBPlmcmckp2hP2QclxUHTo6Ir2M/tZSnc46LN4zeW199m6e/fkKHAkagn3X+BL/tVBaRB6HQfYCWRbb/i6XpheUfJKxHTDmw5GQD9eDFTIu6wBTwGpvs3HYCaeZLgKBxDlI6cNFsO4TwfLPOK9wT7KEraKkAe8U0UhS3eRKLsIpQbgaonzNhK9kG0k+ML3PUJIBJcfOWf3cXi8t7fDBwc0ez8mKZpCRknpRSQskX7rMPhpiuoof1gvQLuuFxAfhVFO3yzXCVFKvgwXUeWOSFopK+lOLlQGw3ezHrJfVQjZxj8SmlOS0Sv6LLpPNFksaG2Hz0Pm255pmuz6zs6AStLrI7hXkosGOqJSSJ+aX1oSnrP96u3sHnswFWU3Pf3MV+/Uvlv3ENG0r8LOwE5CyLJIAlcyNnmPjI/W4zN5b61OfDBasXIAqc6SY0apy51a3FFkEEfj+USkSGlhpRlyfprlbZ3IIp7l4lVYHyvJEKoDlP122T/nNM/UJBsxAyMmhBeAecDezjqEfa380qQKEBS2wovOBxxJBzcscefA0/aGHlk3/cA=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Depression in Egypt below sea level, Faiyum Depression", 
		"option_b": "Dune formed due to obstacle like rocks, Barchan", 
		"option_c": "Desert feature with a meaning 'sword', Seif", 
		"option_d": "Extensive loess deposit location, Hwang-Ho basin", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070127", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sUmXRL+yur2O2yKQZbz8lKouUU5KkfC3UCYa2E=", 
		"answer": "25m5ZpX13gvnt4E1V17myr3rOnnCBmwFqn6PErF1eX+jXamCaujtzIVlZxHJqk53/n/DsOXx+VdPnalN4ICaY25DXYNuxt6M2/e3wGNYc8tLiZQy65xfaPxFjCmkedGbKfAuymuTIlfkJ3T9M3FwnSKaylhTuJG+5jSyW9R3xhk9mZU46809KMKN3LvTpQ2ahwyD2HrRSbNgUUScscel7k2I7MIUtN+KtHLa5vH4ibja/p4cZxtGupRxI26PtugC9iUvX4iyZwALvKT3c1HsNGiHMh0JuenswXgrQlHXWTsnNPC5XvImBChn1w==", 
		"explanation": "25KtZJ361Aqq9oskEgzz0/TxMHiQAnAU43OCXKdyf2PuR+fLYK36zIR0NUiazUl+4WPKt6z+8BMJnadWqYeRZCcNbY4v2tGA2eL2yH0BB8lWiIV88JMecLREwyqjZNvOMu0uzW+VNECwdTitDXQ0kSPZmXVZps/78yipWdM5x1U8l5Vq4t98P9+e16aW5F74kQ+W1DuCXLhhARSKvMqt+AOoqIcrsI2LtDPP4eb8ibjD/N8SIgkSqY9rYlf8hacF/WoxX4inYBNb+OrXIVDoMy2xM04R+MXnxXdo1oc6YWcI+ihHhopFIsFh09jgritwLcR8ECG4pkBTh5tuHxSedbO21WT3oFwxNX4udo9/qD51lgeVJFE+jnKMRS9QmIxyvtELnAAvPXtImW+gizGfhXeCdYf37o7oifGwo7hx4LpnPkCUME6YUpgObL3HZ3Vzw+fbCLBZPYt0W2LrPN4n8j65NJ6R0nkOwswjJnbrtCyWgI3iOHG/odL/gtthVL4OMpHA+8SkuVPJITPzLn6WddjxSkj5QTz81h1gpQxlzS8G4XDXBoR6+zkeonCMR2ZlmCbkbW/hl7BYqpKLe4c81vv4znIRivE4m57k0Q8oBwi6g3tFvZaSXBxtzF7XGswUhAg8CfQDBpnQ9iHWhnrfW3UDeI7mDamOzT8I3Ozjg2R5/5IXFZiGKVnYhd8qzQSyBPN6UCfirsb4MfAAHG0t9vJ3y+Oy+4qsffqoKSU6ah6+VOpX54YRaRB+UQzYCzBDefinWJ4SSO5K1jXYmARDB29FBE7K9LoFTkSspdHGairfd/EIBhuiYbIWFo73SAfCOuSn3DHACP+OlEm5WlcZQAaTFbgIpSDif43mZDemgHwk287yPhFJQYUSLjSzYGT5pOOLAhUucD4sK4tLOlfQWRkrkH7KKblzhaJAIUF+EbvrWUAXhAVGnCveD0pJqQwXUeW5SFZnPaxWNF4Dw3eAIoFfbxncgygPzlKOzTfrIe4HcUosbnSfikigjJtyl7/5jYGTStjjI7lb34wNKbFeSZ/YCxsMiPLn++jjFH91RmFyKrjcUaLGuUvzEdjmp8LehU9EwLJIM000NjCEh9/Y/j4tK6BZbmNevGcQos2SZhO5zchKwV96XUagtUjpUWYiohh9adPqbc/VKY6p5EVNE2TGWb0Dm/N10DnqPMvYYQl9b3fbDEh1fEmQbsCEu1IJnQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Landform due to torrential rain in desert, Gullies and ravines", 
		"option_b": "Channels dry most of the time in desert, Wadis", 
		"option_c": "Depression floor features, Bajada and pediment", 
		"option_d": "Large areas in western USA known for, Great Dust Bowl", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070128", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0hj/5IAzEhr3w/H+IWLfDSIZrHOPXbRnMHjtFKPHfejs3YQuZVguexX2lZW/5u6yHb2v6gI=", 
		"answer": "24KxZpXgkRvm+JIpXBmyxOr+LCvFDWEerWyMXqpwcWXmUOfPb/n7255wK0/LNR7+Rnm9tgC3XDjYWhVDlQ==", 
		"explanation": "25G9bp3yxRDl+cUIXRL+yursdWLeQ0YUsHqRRrAuMFXmUqvDeuTxx9d5KFCFgkxosn/I46H15FYdm7sb6JyaMCYGbplq28OA2OrkhH5Tc8VLlINz8p9fevFB2Ci/ccebKfAu2maFZ0nxaT2uB3FkkXHQhW5brYf79z77QNIygAI7mIM16do1KtKRmbqW5UKuhwrC033RRLJrAlHV9cih5UbRp5A5vMOItXLL9ebtk/vf9c1HIhtHvI4/Ykj8hKkH/Go5X8z0extH5aTxchT5KC3jMAcT/Yv3xHVn1ZImT30ntAtOh5BTItByxIztvz41LIEqHCf6oEVOh5duWhaCcf2w32To70IsNXMlJYt/uSwm4RiVPFw+lm6PX2xSm417/9MNkAAjcn0AnXjjijCZhWHPb5zq58JMcBul7+i5Jp8bcHIUufKL", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Winds eroding solid rocks", 
		"option_b": "Water seeping from the underground", 
		"option_c": "Plant growth restricting sand movement", 
		"option_d": "Winds blowing away unconsolidated materials", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070129", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1A/v+ZFgXhv2henwdX/YBiISsXqCRqp7fjHsUufWZui+7oV0JkjJqU5o5jbkrLL8t1oBz7xT7M6IdTEXe5lhiOW69ru1R3wsZHcEAxPsnKCOmDSwKw==", 
		"answer": "24asepjjwRDk8MUvVF78xOnqJ2rcQ3QUpHqXU7d9f3+jUqjQLuv/25p4KVvJjFV/smXSsar+8BMYhqZf+swnrR08DTYPLh5cvuVgUcYe", 
		"explanation": "25KqbZDnkT3/5JFgcBHlyb3aI27eFzhRl3eGEoRmdXD3FIPXffm+65hmKxyAgxtv+nOGtKDj41Ydgehu54eLdSZDTZ9u3NWal/P21zFRIc9Jm5J76INff/VV3zipNNbCYP8uzWGNJUz+Zi20C340mzeWmXlArZG+tSOpW88wyAF+1pJ2/t0vKNaW16mR5Ej4hwGQ1XiERKlxA1WV9d666kCIqYE9poHNsDzftOftiPfd954cawZW/4NtbEi1mKZJ/D8qWMazKAZD9KSBOAe9M2iXLwtd6dns2ntnwYctHW0m+wpBipcWbsV3lozr/CY4Oo19HCeyplZJyZM8UBHWd6+3wHuk4Vs7NX8zdYV+uSl1ow6OLRRtlWKQAGxGnIlo9pxZnAojaXpSkjqglT6YwGCOb5rv8sDsjOv7pb0j57NnK1jAIVTdFp0TcrbSIXJ+iv6SA6JPf99kBSfnKdwg+3n0IYWH1i8IkN01PGOn5z6WgMDme3VKgmcB+eZtMUXsyPReDvo=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Volcanic eruptions", 
		"option_b": "Heavy rainfalls", 
		"option_c": "Introduction of invasive plant species", 
		"option_d": "Stripping of natural vegetation for farming and strong winds", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070130", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kR3v5IAyRl76xO6/N27VDSIcpnGXW6x6dXWjQKiCZuzozNd1Mk+dzU9z82KGsKDk418KnOhS586LeCdDVpxuxtfE/+u3xnBSOsgb2B0nEDgIfd9sbt2Tswr1R6g=", 
		"answer": "25K3apiz9Rz58pc0ELT+7Z+pQev914N3B54bibk=", 
		"explanation": "252vaZ/0nDHlt6chQRf8hdnqJn+KQ1YZpj+kXaF9MFXmR6LQeqG+3p94JFTJnkt6/GWGrari41sKnaYbyoaWfiNDf4VriMOGwvD/wWNPc+tLlId96JMeMLRIzS7tdtHeLr5jy2CULkr+Yj39EH80hCPZjmlVrcO/4DSvFMkjzwc/hcds5ckofMSazbyf7Q2xiEaW1H7RYKplH1PUncHoo3qZrI43oo2/uCTe5r25mPnA+dBLVgBX/6FwYVL8s60a/TgsEcGnKBlF/vPeIVLiMmiqMx1d+Nnq0jRqyYwtVH09+xFVwoJYZoB735/s/CElLM5vBSezoU1MzoBlHwOZNKqx3myk5UcwZnMka8ip1gswSU5DWzg5VmNZMFKW", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Sahara Desert", 
		"option_b": "Atacama Desert", 
		"option_c": "Mojave Desert", 
		"option_d": "Gobi Desert", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070131", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt6chQB36xPPsailNCqgCgeeun6/VkuyWgnuH", 
		"answer": "25aqbYLw1Bf+t4oyEhP9yvOyJmPRE2cV43uWXKZnMqh9C3ZCD4VWlXMV+EbknjQ=", 
		"explanation": "25e5epL70Bf5rcUCUwzxzfzxJivREWdRoG2GQaBxfmWuR6/Dfuj6iYRwKVjJiU5192WGoKr9+lwBg7Eb74GKfiZDd4UvzNWa0vbj1zF1O8Nd2ohz8p9ffbRHyTO5eNGbM/Jh3mvAKEuwczG4RGd9mjXBi25S6JCy8SL7VdQzgBRyhZN96Ng5LpeM1aeD7Q23iEaW1H7RRLhhBlWLsY674keZ4KA5p86FsDzItPL2iPWT8c1LY0hAupVqb0/8mK5J7CI9Ed26YRZC4+HTdV3iLimvZxkU98+vlmNhz4EhHWo14QxDkcNFY853lozr/DMzPNhnAD+7t0EAyJo8Sx+TNKqx3mzz4Uc7NWkiYY8tvSMx4RuULVo+iGSQQGxegoV5vsQRkERgb2pTiDb0jX+fiGDPcJbm/IHugajjqb1msBhg2AnjNzulwrfSDtXtXWI=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Long, narrow ridges of sand", 
		"option_b": "Dunes shaped like stars", 
		"option_c": "Hills of sand formed near oases", 
		"option_d": "Crescent or moon-shaped dunes", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070132", 
		"question": "24KwbYP2kRD5t5EoV17/yu7rdW7IF2cfsHaVV+NwdWHsR67WLuL4iZt+Ik+azV1053jC/OcuCYdwSyNvz5i6Jmk2eEzk", 
		"answer": "25y2KJ/8ww3iupIlQQqy5vX2O2qQCmxRt3eGEq97dWLwFLfOb/n7yIIxKFrJmVN+sl7Roqv3unsAz6pa+oeRMntvM49tRPBKEI+EaJDYeM8=", 
		"explanation": "25CgfJT9whD88sUMXRvh1r3bMHvfEGsF+T+3WqY0fX7wQOfHdvn7x4R4MVnJiV5r/WXPt+X/8RMDgK1I+sLfcWIFd4Vqhdeb1u35wXUNc9FNlIQ/5pYQa/oA3zipfdneLuoijmeTZ0P/cje5RHl61CXejzx4p5Gv/WeYXNM5wVUCmoZx44gINN6MmbqW70S3iErC33OQWrxnBVGLvNSt7wOeucI+sN+ZuD7etOf2k/TAsNoOcAFEuoI/ZUmzmugF9y8rQoT0YQEL/urVIVvrYDyrIk4Q9tj3lnVu1IsqSGUg4Q1Hjo9PItBh2ZzxvyY5KcgqFCG/olcAzpo8fB+ferz61aPoWDDK1ou6e2nzULYIuA==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Sahara Desert", 
		"option_b": "Thar Desert", 
		"option_c": "Australian Desert", 
		"option_d": "In north-west China in the loess plateau of the Hwang-Ho basin", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070133", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt5IhVhfhhfTxdX/YBiISrHGXV7tgMH7lFKPHfejs3YQuZfPIgt3J0i+JYWhyhTI2c98=", 
		"answer": "25G9bYH23xzut4EyS17xzfzxO27cECIesT+VU694dWjwFjzkNUdCKhk2Z+4PVQ95LJY=", 
		"explanation": "24K5bJjgkRDkt6ElQRvg0e6ldULeQ2YUsHqRRuN3f3/3Ub/WfaG+3pZ1Lk/Jn15992SGt6qw80EWz7pS/4uNcicHbctg2pCA2fDy1nxIJ9JBlJQy944NefVN3325fNXPYPFgwnfAIUn/cHm5EWJ9mjaWmnlEoYy/5me0Upo/xRQkj8dq7MEyOtaT1eic+g2+igeR1DuXRLJrFUfZgcat+Ebcpoc5odiftCGb9eb82vvc/dMEbEhbscZ+cVK417oM/yM3X9v0aRxPsefRbxTvJSusKgtd68rz33Bl38IgU3w68B5Sh4cWZtVh35bj/Ds+Od9vBCa/rVAAxYFoHx6YYLi2w22k8lQ2ezouc49jqD53nYi8zzokgHJ/+/zeQMOBqQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Small oasis with water", 
		"option_b": "Sand dunes shaped by wind", 
		"option_c": "Underground water reservoirs", 
		"option_d": "Deepened dry channels or valleys", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070134", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kR3v5IAyRl70wPzrIHnVQ3UQsD+NU65xdDHiUrPHfK3/iYV0IFWGgxty/Db1rLDk/xMrjqNU/Y/fdDcGPp9giNmdxKTy3GVEPdVNjIUy4YgQb/1Pwn2vbZTJIfdg3XqPNUjjOHv/CO4GuWEXUaMgAHDZqMfe", 
		"answer": "25e5bJ3y3x35tSL07/ge2wXb4QYVMumE4fA=", 
		"explanation": "25e5bJ3y3x35t6MlUwrn1/ildV/YBiIFpm2OEp82UnDnWKbMav7Ci9dmJk/Jg1p293KGoqPk8kFPm6BeqZyadysMcMtmxpC62PHjzDFlMs1LjoEy4I8aPOBPjDS5Z5TeOOprwH2JMUCwYiuyF3l7mnHUkzxEqYq15jO0RtckgDczkot548wvfNaN3OiSqFmhlgPC033RQLRjGViA9cu65EeZpM54t8yfozfVtPj4lPzA898bZ0hRt4dtYliokroA4i88EcqtKBZO9PScIUf5JS2zah0U/c7nlnN8yo4gWHp09RFCwopYdtJ61ZnwuX5wLdhtEja+41BF1YZ9VhnWQLW9ySjl8lB/enw/YIQtuiIgrwvcIVo+m3mVSGxehsB4+90Q2AVxdGsAjnPnizCFkyefiVJEktSLM6OEXtEyPkHo", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Mesas", 
		"option_b": "Badlands", 
		"option_c": "Zeugen", 
		"option_d": "Yardangs", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070135", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzwQvl9IAzQV77y737MHjVEXYC43OGU6dnMGXsFLPKa63925JwM1WGgxt09Db64ajl5FsdgKdWqZyQcykQQskwita7vQM8+jq5hUapdP+YFK4=", 
		"answer": "25S6epDg2BbkteKXet0gVfiOGrbX6K49YlE=", 
		"explanation": "25ite5nh3hbnt7cvURXh+b+/E2TCDmMFqnCNCONIMlz2R6/QYeLziYV+JFeasRk7+3iGp6Dj8kEbnOha+4vffyQXe4Uvy8KM1vDywDFVO9RLj4d6pJtfbOZPzzi+Z5TYIfJiy2rAI0z2YTyvAX5gnTDaynlEp5Cy+in7YNI+01U9lYRt/9t8K9+a1+iSqB69lErC0XSDTf12FEeQptqp5Vfco4Mop8KOunLL5vvtn/vH454fag0SrIl5d16u170H/C8qXdG9ZhUL/OXEZEbkISTjIRwS9IvmxHt6z40nHUYi8Q0GlopbZ4wzwpDh/CE/OdlvB3O3olBF1Z19U1eTZrK81Xuk4UI+bDZraY9sqiQ7pk+eLVx3lG/cTWxcgZNj7N8WmElwdW5QmXKgkDCIiyWJc4Hu6pT1iuayAs+JvYgKrNzsfkJDKyEF9w==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Exfoliation", 
		"option_b": "Attrition", 
		"option_c": "Deflation", 
		"option_d": "Abrasion", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070136", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kR3v5IAyRl70wPzrIHnVQ3AUsHqOUK9xYzHiFLPDbOH7iZZ/IxyBjEg75HPUuuXj41YKn+hI4IqaY31Bfc5NZuX7KZzcI2KTMv/T2Q==", 
		"answer": "25i9e5CxAWMT67xQVnk4Cj4gW0gHzA==", 
		"explanation": "24G5ap32kTTl4os0Uxf8hdn6Jm7CFyI3pn6XR7FxKjHCFKrHfey+wIQxJhyNiEh+4GKGpaDx40YdiuhP4Y+LMDAGbY5iytyMxKT2hGVAMcpB2qlmpJMMPPdIzS+sd8DeMvd0y2rAJVywZnm7CHFg2HHThnlAqZe+8WevW8p31xwmnsdu6NolfMSL3K2DqF6xggORnFaUW7x3UVWLsI6u5FGRpYZ4ocWfvifc/LT42vvc/dwCbAlGtolxI1S6168M9yY3VsG3aR4L4fbfYlH+My2wa04U98jvw3BgyIVpWHs75xZJjMNUe4Bk35bg/DM+O419FCe/sQaV+/fMAmkmyneufgFeLl14", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Zeugen", 
		"option_b": "Yardangs", 
		"option_c": "Inselberg", 
		"option_d": "Mesa", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070137", 
		"question": "25y2KIb72Brit4ElQRvg0b3+J26QF2oU42yTV6BgcXL2WKbQLvT/25NwKVuazU9z82KGsazj8hMbgOgJvMPKIGIFe457iMCb0uD4yXhPMshQlpky4pUKcvAfjqWUxMaxgvGjxn9J/zH5opY=", 
		"answer": "25y2fJTh2Bb4t4ElQRvg0e6/Om2QIGcft22CXuNVY3jiFrOWAyPmHnipui9OEfYcAOc=", 
		"explanation": "24y5epXy3x75t4wuEjr31vjtIXiKQ1EBpnyXU6BhfHDxFL7DfOn/x5BiaxyehVJ4+jbFoquw5VociuhP5s6XdSsEdp98iN+Pl7aiiSQRc8BBn5Q+pJsNebRQ3jipe9nSLv9g2mKZZ0P/cje5RHl61CXejzx6vZf70SKoUcgjjFUzmpR3rcMyM8CRmamAqGm5lQ6WkX7RZKhwXRSQu4675FaIqIc5ptmIozyb3eb4lLjq8cwPYwZVrMZ+cV78hLwb/Ss1XcG6bRYHseHcblrqITymI04R+MXn0Ht7y5FpXnsx9QtDhsNUe4Bk35bg/DciMN5jGj3241BZ151/Xhuabf2+333q5BU2ezoqd4Np/D8wpgaTJkc8jIu36o2RSaAuJ4yTPFCO5g==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Sahara Desert", 
		"option_b": "Atacama Desert", 
		"option_c": "Kalahari Desert", 
		"option_d": "Interior deserts of Central Asia", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070138", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7gzPD+J3KQAGMEsHrDXaU0cWPqUK7Wd633x9d1Ik+Mn09orTQb3YcAELNmuYF0KFK41BPE", 
		"answer": "25y2e4T11xDp/oAuRl7gxPTxM2rcDyIQrXvDWqpzeDHmQqbSYf//3Z5+KRybjE9+4TTC4Zbr6TyTcW8Yt8grv3pg", 
		"explanation": "24WqYZzywwCq1IQ1QRuyyvu/FHnZB2sFuj+KXONQdWLmRrPRNK3KwZIxN06AgFpp6zbForDj8hMAieha+4ebeTYaPoJhiNSMxOHl0GIBOtUEjoh3pJYef/8AwzvtedvSM+p73GvAI1D1Jy2yRHx7g3HGmHlVoZOy4SavXdU5gBk3gIJ0/ogYOcSay7yAqF+9hQOLyn7RXrh2CBSVvNq850bcsoMxu8uMvT6XtPj8m/za/tlLdgcSu5RmI1izmawA7CM3X9v0ThNI5evCchT+NSurZw8Ouczm2XN7x5IhVGp0+BBFg5dfbc4/lpnwsT0jL8VvBzq540dJ1ZdpUxaCfbK2kHjl9EE6Z3Q4Kcpssil1sw6VJhRtkmqYQzsRkYZt+9MNhkRgfGEAn3nuli2CgnCbedP35MD4gPv1sq0j87EuLUiULB7yzi8nn29aFsBeJogU4iRp", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Cold currents", 
		"option_b": "Vegetation cover", 
		"option_c": "Insufficient rainfall and high evaporation rates", 
		"option_d": "Mountainous terrain", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070139", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxRz4+sUkVw3x1/T9MHiQF2oU43CNW6x6PWHmUavLYOq+2YV+JFmanht09DbLpqb49l0GjKlXqZmacTYLe5lmxtfJ2ObkwWNXNsIEk44y4J8MeeZU32LvenvmuiSQqz9pzxrkIsm+yA==", 
		"answer": "25Cgbp7/2Bj+/oouENlHs3fBFtT5hDWfUHvnwjc=", 
		"explanation": "25q2YZ79nCnv8okpXBmy8vj+IWPVEWsfpD+KXONQdWLmRrPRNK3KwZIxM1mbgBtv+nfS46H15FAdhqpe+s6LeCdDcYVmx97Ex+HyyHhPNIZUiI9x4YkMPPtGjDCod9zaLvdtz2LAMEDxczG4Fnl6k3HZiG9TupW+8WeyWpozxQY3hJNrrcEvfOvd3LCV50GxhxKL03WtCv1BCVKWucep/0qTrsI3ts6YoyGb4/z8lLjc5coOcEhevp96cUj8mK5J6iU7Wtv4KBdY4eHTaFXhLDHjMwYS6s6jwX19zsItVHog/RFFlopAZ4B/14Hhrjs+OI1lB3O8rEhJxoB1UBnaNLqq0Wzx4VkzbDo7YI9h/CwioBbcLEF72n+TDC9ZlY5s+8NZnAojaWpNjHPygyuekmDDPIPx7pPvkPr17Pli/KdnJE6JJkjNRIhcabbWImthit2TBLUcI41oFCf1LpUn73n6L5uZ0DdN2ddgLmXu8GqcnNv8K2q0vpf3msc2A7cFJNSF/c66oFnVYDf0M3jTYMfhWhzlTmjx3AB29xk3zWED4WXWAY929iwDijwvaMkY48E5aCq7CRoyTFMl", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Abrasion", 
		"option_b": "Deflation", 
		"option_c": "Attrition", 
		"option_d": "Exfoliation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070140", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gcxL+hfn6Jm7CF3FRom2GEq97c3D3UaOCbOjq3pJ0KRzY2Is75nmG8PUgt18Om6FP/IqaTCw/cLlqycOG2b635X1MPNVQ2oF+6NobeedF3im+NNjSJb5nwC6UL0Cwcyu8AHU0gzjYjjxUrY+vtSi1FM4/xVUlk5Rs6NoyfMeey7yAqEK+xgWN0m+YRrhqBUfZosat+UbclJA5scjNhjvV8Oe5m+rWsNENZEVBt4ltZhnmbTBwO3Pbc2DP8zhhDO8u", 
		"answer": "25T4YYKz1xjm5IBgUAvmhc+/PHiQF3AEpj1H3esm/O0e/DyDhrhK09GF", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/M2rcEGdRonGHErd8dTHxUabRYeO+wIQxN12bmVdismLUtqDM+W8BoadPqY+TfGIHe5hq2sSal+XlwTFNPMVFjoV2pJgaaONFyTPtJYELYOphjj3Q9wX8Zi20EGVwkXHignlErcO65yL7UN8kxQcmhcdx44gzKN+ay+if6VmxkhOG2WjdCK5xElzZtN3o/0uZ4KMqttmEsnLa+vC5u/bH8cwIdgFR/4J6cF6ug7tFuD4wVIiVfBNI8OnRIXDoMy2xM04U94vQ2WF9zsIIUGwm/RxHwssEMhBAn9SkvTw0f9liEHOUoklJxdRYWgSTZqn42WakwVMtfHkqJcI/6f0G6DOSFFpKkm7cXilQh49lvtkK1RRib3tMhTb0kCqOwGeKf5L2+IW8iOfjtPln97AiO1WTdVjXFoEVYPPJKSdmwuzbGbRdN5onACvoOZUs+TXtYJmany0F1Zk3KmTz8TiX0t30K3Gp853/ztd5GqsJONTL/dj3hFTCITfzIHmWJtz9VwzjD33q1k5ytgoohGEU+nuYH4Bx8T5NinaxXQRmnij3LHqzmbMc/oqLP4swwOGsyT1QjPx934zyxwl8cAy+gz9XuoGGD05KzFfeXtkPwUk5CacVEYTfsm6ZlGXEWDwCeY71DqaTyiJN1PfiwiFpt5UXFY2cKVndhcwlzRPxFfI5R27+rcb2K/kHSnAk//J8xfivo8uye+DobHIiZhm/GexY5oZUe0JvGQ7QRTBAILuhWZFeQO5LknnFhAIIU3dMDEiM9qcBThC/uMGIWmLXcPEOCw33b6cWU8f2DlPHMLGvxyLEB6uVmkn+UEJlSj+OJKIZ9kf/dMzmLBbzhG137cT3PBFITYcSL2f8ciu6qq2XAgg/cTg2FIR7dG/aXBUykSyPZ+1viLUFMBk/ROimFUMZ1hVKjDvAGksFpEQfS+WsUlZnJqZGIU8UyXe6H+ALVBmKgzsZmlOOzGL/IP5OIgksfSSQgEL0kpxjkev6zs6SH9fqbbwIkpkLLfZoRZLXDVpcvvb36vP0UWU3RkxxPPHLX6KZ4homLIG0o83ehUhDzP4pJF45LDiFybvc4z9/O+VGYTBrrnoY7IKAN9aEkMht3VV7VRXo8FLhU3My9hBha9PlZcmcJpSm8URaEmTOWflXkPk4yT7lMdqRcxMxAyM3lAuEOpLI0iDDKaT+2e0IFx3i25bIRJ5o6AhwwJyz0UlBuHtih3nwDjbOauKt6RdGYnVrC7CaCV5YiBMr2z39nkTgNIyix6cFnb8ByrAA9ADjsWF/gR6IXVOOYHzk2v+KvmnIrXsv9aRQUyrjT3tojg03V/U55nBhTm01QaBg/Lf5IPHAm3KqPIirjY0f4BZYSaTLO7i//df5MbTAKqusiNVTb2buscA51LWjJMoMNGPJYX0Wt/7yY4jXaEXTPWWAkq+QF2ucICFI4XcujmqPQFhtIW28WN0dHzpe0IZzMLwDsN2kvENgPGPOWqVg3OEdiVpdCRBOQ/Ll2HNIFOwiNoDcZldov0EZGvsQeGP3eUtkc88G1GX0QCih/yCyhrR6F5fihlRpKRmOyz3IbWfJ7akxM+9ZDQFupe7eUhYMvTaj", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070141", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gdwb0yvH2NH/ZDGxRqmzDU+N3eHTuXaTDYq3pzJZlL1mbhFV8smbUrKb15EAzgZRV24ueYy0NJMtK0NaG2+320HhOPYZNlJZ96Iwab7RUxDjtZNHeLPdgyS6PIUOwaD/9Fn93n3Hai2VTupD78TK+FM44gAE3m5d9/8koKcWama6f/U6skweW1XSfW//nElM8mO0pjIcTpq2Cb53d", 
		"answer": "25T4YYKz1xjm5IBgUAvmhc+/PHiQF3AEpj1H3esm/O0e/DyDhrhK09GF", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gexDxyu/tMGjEQ0cJpXCPW6JgeX7tFK7RLuy+xJJyL12HhFh6/jbRpqTk/1YdhqZcqZ6NfyEGbZgjiN6Gw6T0zHRMOsVFlsBb8NoWcuJPwCuoZ5TPKPsu3maZNEzzZjX9F3VklSPXnnVZpsO052erUd87yRs11oZv7NF8M9Hf1r2H7V/4igeb2WmCCLJiUUaWtsXo71aZ4JY39cuMsibU5ue5lvHY9Z4fZwVCupR+d06ukugK8Cs2Vs2nJFJb4+HDckH/JWixIgIY+NjmmjRoyIZpWHs75xZJjL9YXs5B05n3szxqf+5lByG/oFAA85x5HwWTda633ijh+EUzdHMldspopCs6rQadPF1xlCudTy9EhoF/+9wA2URneHtBlXrpjDjLiGqYPIfm5pD5l+nktatmsqUrPEKUIF3MX4ISdvPMImZ2iv2UTbJUNt93EifqNNspvDb/Jtab2Xkf39orb3vm7S+LgY3dNnK/pZfrwpR/AP8DOd/R+8qzuV/TcmP1KXjTZ9jnXBrkRnP2lB0ltBQkwSxQ52SYAZ0/9ygEkHnwSARnmiLtZX+gmv5M+I2Nep0ikSmx+mbPS911vT8U4Xf5Mps=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070142", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gax/gwfzxMniQAnAU43mMR61wMHjtFKLUa//niZN0NFmbmWd1znj0pqTj+F1Vz5Fa+4qefiUQPop9zZCaw+Hy1DxSOsJBnsB+5ZQbevtSwS7td8beIepryi6CPgXnbje5RHF2hjDFg3NY6uct48EUSr92Wmvg8yCQaaM=", 
		"answer": "25T4YYKz1xjm5IBgUAvmhc+/PHiQF3AEpj1H3esm/O0e/DyDhrhK09GF", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gexDxyu/tMGjEQ1sQsXuCXKRnMHDxUefMYfm+z5hkKVjJhFU792DDsbyw81YcirpPqbqXdTtDf5lqiMOd0uHniWJIN8NA2oxz6p4Zc+ZN332re8bWJfouzHfAMEz+Y3m8BmJ1hzjZhDAWqY2/tTOzUdMlgAUgk5R948s5fNOaya2d7F74iQjCz2uUS7RiGFfZssun50ybqYE5uY2Mvzab8frvk+rc/tMObBxTs8Z8bFW4nrwA9yQrbcaIZiBO8Pffbw6tAyexNQse7YvX3nEp1IcoTmY6tA9UjZVfZsVglpnq/DMzPNh4FCe/40BF1JduVgeCfbK2kGfioEw+Z34qa41+8G0wuR+QKV1wk2WbDDhZlZQr6tgcjERib2oAn2TlgyuOhCWbdIHs/of0xf/5rr0j86E1KFKJOlKYfoILYKXFNSsyw/3bCalZIJEgA2LnOdE8+SrqYIKc2nkMw8olPWPu+yTegY32NWSzvtL4jNtjAP8UPtTM+4uivlXRZDHyIHHTdtnxSg3+THm42gAlsx02zTME+y6YBYh0/CMK3nekCU1qhCbsZXjjozm2j0lSAipcM01NSYh+EQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070143", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gdhv0yfzrPGTeQ2oer3OMRbA0eX+jUKLRa//q2tdwNVnJi1Rp/3PC46Hl8hMbgOhM4ICbY2IBcoR4wd6Ol+XgxWgBJ85B2pV855URb/tMxTmsYNHfYPNv2muSLkT8dAWzOH5GkTDFhXIM6LSz8Cn7QNIygAA8lYh2/scwNdOeza2XqEC5kgOQ1XqdW/1lA1HZp8ul5FWZpM54psCMvT6b8PHpiP3A49cEbBsSsodmI12zhaVLWg0tkYPg1MfkKU1vBuBZqw==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiIQrXvDYON9YzH3XKKCbeLs25JyMxyMlUt383jHt6z/+RMJgLobyMzhe6ddeFdnLLMGFYjfRT4E", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gcRHg1/j8ISv0BmQdomuKXa00eH7vWKjVfa3/25IxLlKNiF5/snDJsaj18xMNluhP4YvfYicOcZ1uxJCG0aT7y35SNooEj45x65QMc/hJyDy5cdCbLf96y3yJJknjJzukRGd9mjWWq28WvIu+5iL7WdsjxQc7l4trrckuOZec2LqB4Ui8xgeV3WLdCK5pEFiV9cqt+1GZs5ExusOe8T3JtPz2lvTc581LYQlc/4J6dV6wmLhJ8SR4RcCxKB5K/+DDYlX9JRStGwAv/Mrw2XozhqEmT3sx9wsGtotTItJ214vrsnIxPM5/BzKupkhZh5FkTxuXfbOrkHzs5RUvZ3UoYJl+/C8s4RiUIVd22m+ZSiBQgIlk8JARmghvcnhT3HDvkDLHwHaabIPs+ZT1i++wtLFmsqI0OkSSIVXXWM9EulyPTJ54NpKWyVMYS5Er", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070144", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gdgvh0b35J2TdQ3YZpj+wU6t1YnCjcKLRa//qiZRwKRydn1pt93qGoqbi+EAcz7xT7M6ydSYKao592tGH0uX5+H99PfRBm5N96sBfT/tNyX2pYcfPYPl8z2eONAXxdTz9AWNgnTzXnnlS6Je0tTOpVcwyzFUzhcd+7Np8PcTfi+TAuB34iw+O2WjRSrhiHkac9dqg7lrcoZA99cmIoT3I/eD8nrqPracHqh9xkSLnKW4+vaVz", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiIQrXvDYON9YzH3XKKCbeLs25JyMxyMlUt383jHt6z/+RMJgLobyMzhe6ddeFdnLLMGFYjfRT4E", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gcRHg1/j8ISv0FnEF43mRXa40ZHnmFJTDZuzsyNdVIk+Mn0878XfI46z+81YKi+hZ7M6ccTARd45riNGKxevk1zFVO8MEt4V27Y4abuZBwjisepTZOb55x2CENAmwZj+7AXNgnT/Rym5Tr4q0+zT7Vcl3xhQg1oZrrdszKcOX3LqdqGitlAmS2UefdLNWFFWKusDyq2CTspA9ttnNhTretOb8m+vc/p4bcAdEtoJ6cBu9megI+yktQ8mgbVJO4vDZbFX5JWisIU4J8c6j0n160oMnXmx04BdHlsNFbc12lpzxryZwON9rHD2p40dBydRoTRaAcbH40m3i70c6NWkucZ5htSMy7U+PPURulXmIRSJW1JRj+5AYhhdmb3tJk3inkX+IjGSGcdES7CegeW9nsMhFUcO0OcVN", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070145", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gfhH31u6/PHiQAiIIpnOPXbQ4MHfxXabAYui+xJZlIk6AjFc79HnTraGw/l1Pga1S7oadfzAKcIwvxNGH0/e3y3cBN8NXn5Jm96YRQPpyyTy+e9qBYNJhy32TZ0zjJz24FnlikTWWjG5ZpcOs/Cm/Gdg40hs31op5+c0uNdaTyuiX7V23lQ+W2X/RSakkBVyc9cus7Ebcr4R4vM6I8SHT8fHtibjX5cwCbA8Sq456I3K/kugo/y8rE8+mMs+51oM2b8LEZXK5XfU=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Fnr+YFgYF7z1/i/IXnFBiIQrXvDYON9YzH3XKKCbeLs25JyMxyMlUt383jHt6z/+RMJgLobyMzhe6ddeFdnLLMGFYjfRT4E", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gcRHg1/j8ISv8DGcCsD+KQeN1MGjmWKvNeaG+z4V4Jl6FiBt282LDsazx+xMMgKVW5oCTaWIFcZ5hzJCA2aT21nRAIIZKn4l17JgQbv1Oy32pccfeMup9jkeUZ1XibjS8Fnl4jXHVhXJFoZCv5me0UpogyRs224V04t8yfMSW1bzT6UO8xgCL0n7RW7xqFWiXicCa7kKPr4xi9e6CoyDe9+C5rvDWsMwOYxtdscZ6e0uwlqEH62osWc30ZwBC9u3eIVvrYCSsIh0Oucrg1WF7x5YsUXB4tAxSg5dfbMczwpDlqHI5K4p5VTe/sU1WwpA8WQWZef2v2WbgrVcwZ3QuJYdsqCgnqA6QOxR6n3uTXyVFkYQr/8RZgQxmPWpEm3OgjTnLiWaKPIDr7oXolqj0tatq/KRnPUmFdXXbU809YrbTZ1N6w/rbHrNMI5B1AzGmKd0rvDjqM5OGyzAC3p4zb3Tr9SOU0MRwrAvk2qBINZjoL1FVfrM=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation for A", 
		"option_b": "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A", 
		"option_c": "A is true but R is false", 
		"option_d": "A is false but R is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070146", 
		"question": "24GwbdHM7ibVyMUmQBH/hen3MCvjAmoQsX7DdqZndWP3FK7RLv7xxJJlLlGMnht5/nnRreXx9EEAnLsb/YaaMA8GeoJ7zcKb1uryxX8BJ8kEnIF+6Noeb7Q4zjGie9CbMv9nwH3HZ0z+JxCpBXxt1D7EynNY6Jez8Ge8WNs0yRAghcd364gPK96Lw62B5Ey2gkQ9o+6S38pHa2Xlhd34hIqw", 
		"answer": "27Gte4WxI88X6FhMLmDpiM6L/RVNkQ==", 
		"explanation": "24a5YJDh0Beq85AzRl7gwPv6J3iQF21RpXaNV+NkcWP3XaTOa/6yiZ5/JFCciVJ19TbVoqv0t1IBi+hW4ICaYiMPbccv3NiIw6TwwWUBP89CjoV2pJMRaPsA2DWoNNXPLfF93maFNUCwYSuyCTBgnDSWuX1eqZG6tQO+R98l1FUGnoJr6IgsPcWL0Kuf7V74hQeMnHmUCKl2EFqKpcG6/0aY4IAh9dqEvzbItPvvn+qT/NEFZUhWtpVrYlW/krtJyyU1VNy9ZRdYvaTHaVHjYDyrIh0Yudzq2HB6hoAlUn504BBRg5FScYBWw4rrrDd8f9liEHOJokxB1ZVyHxODZ6n402nqoFg2bTo8bJ5l/D80qAHcJ0Y+iWWTWypQmIwnvtcQgw1tei9JiDbhwi2OhGGGb5uj6pDsgOniobdg9+MTIUiTdUzQU4MTaLbOKGkyw/rbDqlQP5B2AivnMdk3vDL3L4GanzgekJ4iI3jo8GqLk8T7fiW+ppe5mts2HasTdsPA7c++o1SHaTbkY8gHRp6+1g9i9M0EAiRyAOo=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "du,st,st,and", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070147", 
		"question": "25e5epL70Beq85AuVw2yxO/6dWbfEHZRs22GRKJ4dX/3FK7MLvn2zNd1Ik+Mn09osnnA45Hl5VgKnLxa586efiZDQbRQ9+/LOP1XgZ4bOdSxXnEysBpM4g==", 
		"answer": "24a5YJDh0Ft5J/WXFS5+mycNds9Yy79o", 
		"explanation": "25e5epL70Beq85AuVw2yxO/6dWjCBnESpnGXH7B8cWHmUOfRb+P6iZNkKVmazU9z82KGpari+hMGgeha+4ueY2IUd59niNyA2u3jwXUBIMdKnsBh8YoPcO0AzTOpNNfULu1n3XqFKVGwcDCzADBwnSPTiWhfp437wS++TZo20hBylY95/8k/KNKN0LKW7A26n0aDnHyURqloFBSKucG47gOTrsIsvcjNpjvV8OP4iPyT49cPZ0hTsYI/Yhuvg60M6C8qEdu4ZwJOseveIUDlJWivIgsK+NnnlmdgwodpaXwm/xpVloJYLoBk3pHntHI5Mc5mADe/sARDyIFySwWfca743GHv5RUKb3guboN+qCw74Q6SLBRKj3mXQSlfnZN//95V1QVteS9lm2/wln+DgXOKPIfr7sDujO/4tPlm/LUuO06OOFnWQowQJbDPKWN73uCUA7UcNZB1VzbuOJUo8yv0IYKd0DdN399gO3/i5y/Zltj7PHb4YCjurAQ5jX7mnrlbeQ0tBw==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Sa,ha,ra,ne,il", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070148", 
		"question": "24a9YZez2Aqq9otgcwzzx/T8dXzfEWZRrnqCXKp6dzHca5j9Ua9DYQ3/nEyFPU7TByw9+Sce", 
		"answer": "26avZ4P3kz9hRE0OuPBB6YBVgCob2Uo=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avnt7liQRv7w8G9dWLDQ2Mf416RU6F9czH0W7XGLvn2yIMxM06Ig0h382LDsOXk+BMzzbtM5pybTGBDd4Uv7d6O2+3kzDFoPYZQkoUy55URaPFY2H2icpTfJe1r3HqTawXxJyq4DXY0kCTYjzxfu8O6tSu0Wt17gBszhJV3+ogvPdmbmayG5kj4kQ+W1DuQCK5sEEaJ9c267lCI7MIqsN6IvDDX/fr+2uzb9Z4YaglCusZwZRu917se9zg8E0VugzleO/oC/PlfyvkkBJk=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "swo,rd,kn,ief", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070149", 
		"question": "24GwbdH+3gr+t4A4Rhv81vTpMCvUBnIesHaXEqxyMH3sUbTRLuTtiZF+MlKNzVJ1skn5nJrPt1oBz7xT7M6TfycQbct/xNGd0uXihH5Hc9JMn8Ba85sRe7low32vdcfSLrwF4dSuvv9WOBBJd9G1IA6e", 
		"answer": "27u3eoX7nA7v5JFgcRb7y/y91FdYVe6rqV5jzamxPWkfDw==", 
		"explanation": "25m3bYLgkRD5t4RgVBf8wLD4J2rZDWcV7z+UW61wPXPvW7DMLv77zZ58IlKdzU9z82KGqraw/1oIh6RCqYiaYjYKco4vyd6Nl+vx0HRPc8dXiY9x7ZsLefAA2zS5fJTaJ+xnzXuMM1DiZjX9FGJ7kCTVnnVAoZeitROzUZo6zwYm1oJg+c0yL96J3OiX7V23lQ+WnHSXCLFrFEeK9ce7q0WTtYw89cSD8RHT/fr41rjA4NsIaw5bvIdzb0L8nqZJ7CI9EcS7bQFYsfTcYEDoIT3jKAhd7cPmllx+x4wuEEE7tFd/h49abdcz5JHyuSB5f89rBjq043BIzoc8TRKRfbK2kGH3oF4xem0lJYxirm08tRzcLFF7iifcXiVSnMBn8dUKhkRwcmZMjzTS+rJI+V5Jn2ndDjShYh8D", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "no,rt,h-w,es,t C,hi,na,ja,pan", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070150", 
		"question": "24GwbdHM7ibVyMUpQV7zhc7vNGXZEGpRtHCRVuN5dXDtXanFLpXqyJV9IiXJjFV/smTDpaDi5BMbgOhaqYiTcTZPPp9uytyMmuj+z3QBP8dKno1z94ld783gHe2Axv8GoaR/kWSNyQ==", 
		"answer": "25i9e5CxAWMT67xQVnk4Cj4gW0gHzA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avnt8INVw3zgr32JivUBnAYtXqHEqVmf3yjQK/HLt7uyJl4NFTJgVp19WPHpKCw4FsGjKAb5IuefjFDOZ9uytyMkKTe0DFIIIZRiYV2pI4QPPBF3z6/fdbeYP8uyGKBMwmwczi/CHU5mDjdjzxaqY2/+CaoR5o+zlU1k4h//8ksNN6c2KTT/EiqixXOnH6CWLhnGFWVudfo4k3cpIcrsN+Z8T7a+vDqmfnD9c1Jln7yqWlTAqwutYaUbqqzjQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Me,sa,po,dt", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070151", 
		"question": "24qHV67MkR3v5IAyRg2yxO/6dX/YDHEU43mMR61wMH7tFK/LaeXyyJl1NByamFhzsnfV47X89kcKjr1IqY+RdGIOcZ5h3NGA2aTlxX9GNtUGtJrgpIkks1BeBr+IjTymHg==", 
		"answer": "25i3fZ/n0BDktbESszt8w5bAJujk7aMwmPk=", 
		"explanation": "252xb5n/0Bfut4ElQRvg0e6/NHnVQ2MDqnvDQKZzeX7tR+fOYe7/3ZJ1Z12dzVNy9X6Gpqn14VIbhqdV+sLffyQXe4Uvx97Jx+j20HRAJtUEm452pJcQafpUzTSjNMbaLvlr3S60L0DjYnm5AWNxhiXFynlOuIap/CK1V993xAcr1oR348w1KN6Q17vT7Fi9xhKNnH2QS6lrA0fZucej7gOOoYs29d6FsDbU47T8nP7W88oYLkhFt4NtZhuxmKEa7Go5WNr0bgBE/KTEaVGtLyumJgBd8Nij1HhmxYksWSk27V9Oi4ReItR2xIrltTx8f8FvFDezrUMA05s8TRKSYb691Cj08lA8fGoicYt5tSI742QXnp8LDZrAjqFb5oe8uKc=", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Mo,un,ta,in,ri,ver", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070152", 
		"question": "24GwbdHM7ibVyMUlVBj3xum/Om2QFGsfp2zDU6R1eX/wQOfSfOL0zJRlLlKOzUl08X2GrqTj5FYcz7pe+puTZDFDd4Uv3NiMl+L41nxAJ89LlMB94toNc/dLjC2ocNHINP9i3S6PNQX9ciq1Fn97mXHEhX9du8EocF5U0AxKGhzpjbRxF56d", 
		"answer": "26a5ZpXx3Rj544wuVVw+A9hg1cAgns8I/eA3uHib", 
		"explanation": "25S6epDg2Bbkt4wzEh+y1e/wNm7DECIepT+OV6B8cX/qV6bOLvr7yIN5Ik6Ag1w75X7DsaCw5VwMhLsb6JyaMDUMbIUvzN+e2aT2ynUBIclRlIR34NodZbRUxDjtddbJIe1n2GvAJkbkbjazRH9y1CbfhHhUpIys+2eoVdQzgBog1pB5+c0uPtiN163T+0i8jwuH0m+CCIpsFFrZptq65E2b4JUxu8me8THU+uftm/bH/MdLYwpAvoJ6I1r8h7oG8i87RcG6b1JZ/ufbIVnsMzvvZwcJucji2DRs1I0tWCk14x5fwpdeZ4Bg2Z7wuSBwLcJpHnO2ol1F1YcwHxuTdaux3m+k4lA3fHQvJYstsSInpE+OLUd3iX+dQjgRl4F77N8ankRscy9Uk2agtjeCkyWMbpbi/4Xvxe7/srRi5qooJ1LAPlLXQYNcZKCANWhxwamLCKJZIItmGzGmMsdu8SzqKISb0DRNwtYjJGSlOnmeb+4K1vaOr8uPZcbCYg==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "sa,nd,bl,as,ti,ng", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070153", 
		"question": "24GwbdH63w34/oYhRhuy1fzrIW7CDXFRrHnDQKpkYH3mR+fNYK363Jl0Z0+cn1168XPV46z+81oMjrxeqZqXdWIHd5lqy8SA2Oq3y3cBJ85B2r9N26UgPhfCAY2VzJdj/cZsxUE87ls=", 
		"answer": "26KxZpXgkzviUH5ZEOd/v4HwK2/amV4=", 
		"explanation": "25GtZpSzwxD654klQV7z1/i/JmbRD25csHyCXqY4MGbiQqLOZ+b7iZF0Jkicn15osnnI47H48hMcmrpd6I2aMC0FPphuxtTJ0/H5wWIBB85BiYUy9pMPbPhF332re8bWYPp7yy6UKAXkbzz9CX9ikTzThGgWp4X75ia1UJow0hQ7mJQ479F8K96R3ein4Ej4gg+Q2XiFQbJqUVWXsY6740KMpcI3s42ZuTfI8bTrk+jD/NsYIhhAsJB2Z178gakF7Ss6Xc30YRxN/vbdYEDkLybjJgwS7N+jwnxshpI7WH81/RNPjIQWdcl90tjgtSA1PNljGj36qkoAxtR4WgSTZqn48nGk80EqcWMia40tqCUwsgrcOFVqjm6OQj8d1JJu7dUYhwdreH1T3HXhjH+MgWyBPJrt+In7jfzj4LBt5qxnPUmFdVjXW4QSZL3UZ3B7xO3bHadIJ5p1GTGmNNtu/XnpIYSA1joY3Ngyb3b18Svbbgw84K6RLiKf1KO9sWSp5Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Geography >> Arid or Desert Landforms  >> Types of Deserts to Landforms due to Water Action in Deserts", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "wi,nds,fre,eze", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	}
]